<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>auto-multiple-choice</pkgname>
  <icon width="64" height="64" type="cached">auto-multiple-choice.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">auto-multiple-choice.png</icon>
  <id>net.auto_multiple_choice.amc.desktop</id>
  <name>Auto Multiple Choice</name>
  <summary>Multiple choice papers management</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Gestion d'examens QCM papier</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>
      Auto Multiple Choice is a piece of software that can help you
      creating and managing multiple choice questionnaires (MCQ), with
      automated marking from the papers' scans (using Optical Mark
      Recognition).
    </p>
    <p>
      Questions and answers can be randomly shuffled, so that each
      answer sheet is unique. Using this feature, it is more difficult
      for students to copy on their neighbour's sheets…
    </p>
    <p>
      Answers sheets are formatted with LaTeX, allowing mathematical
      formulas and many other potential uses, but you can also write
      your questions using a simple plain text syntax.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>
      Auto Multiple Choice est une application permettant de créer,
      gérer et corriger automatiquement des questionnaires à choix
      multiples (QCM) à partir des scans des copies.
    </p>
    <p>
      L'ordre des questions et des réponses peut être aléatoire, de
      sorte que chaque sujet se présente différemment. Il est ainsi
      plus difficile pour les étudiants de copier sur leurs voisins…
    </p>
    <p>
      Les sujets de QCM sont préparés par LaTeX, ce qui permet entre
      autres d'y écrire des formules mathématiques, mais vous pouvez
      également écrire votre questionnaire en utilisant un simple
      fichier texte.
    </p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">net.auto_multiple_choice.amc.desktop</launchable>
  <provides>
    <binary>auto-multiple-choice</binary>
  </provides>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.auto-multiple-choice.net/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://project.auto-multiple-choice.net/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://download.auto-multiple-choice.net/apercu/AMC-preparation.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://download.auto-multiple-choice.net/apercu/AMC-saisie.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://download.auto-multiple-choice.net/apercu/AMC-notation.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>