<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>bookworm</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.github.babluboy.bookworm.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">com.github.babluboy.bookworm.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">com.github.babluboy.bookworm.png</icon>
  <id>com.github.babluboy.bookworm</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_group>bookworm</project_group>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">書蟲</name>
  <name lang="zh">书虫</name>
  <name lang="vi">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="uk">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="tr">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="sv">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="sc">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="ru">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="ro">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Bibliófilo</name>
  <name lang="pt">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="pl">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="nb_NO">Bokorm</name>
  <name lang="ja">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="it">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="is">Bókaormur</name>
  <name lang="ie">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="id">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="hr">Bibliofil</name>
  <name lang="he">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="fr">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="fi">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="et">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="es_MX">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="es">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="eo">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="el">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="de">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="cs">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="ca">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="be">Bookworm</name>
  <name lang="ar">دودة الكتب</name>
  <summary>A focused eBook reader</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">一個電子書閱讀器</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_HK">專業電子書閱讀器</summary>
  <summary lang="zh">专业电子书阅读器</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Програма для зосередженого читання електронних книг</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Odaklanmış eKitap okuyucu</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">En fokuserad e-bokläsare</summary>
  <summary lang="sc">Unu leghidore de libros eletrònicos</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Программа для сосредоточенного чтения электронных книг</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Un Cititor de eBook-uri</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Um leitor de livros digitais</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Um leitor de livros digitais</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Czytnik e-booków</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">電子書籍向けリーダー</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Un lettore di libri digitali senza distrazioni</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Rafbókalesari</summary>
  <summary lang="ie">Un focat letor de eLibres</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Pembaca e-Book</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Fokusirani čitač e-knjiga</summary>
  <summary lang="he">קורא ספרים אלקטרוניים במיקוד גבוה</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Une liseuse numérique sans distraction</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Keskittynyt e-kirjan lukija</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Koondav e-raamatu luger</summary>
  <summary lang="es_MX">Un lector de libros electrónicos</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Un lector centrado en los libros electrónicos</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Enfokusigita Bitlibro-Legilo</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">A focused e-book reader</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Ένας εστιασμένος αναγνώστης ηλεκτρονικών βιβλίων</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Ein fokussierter E-Buch-Lesegerät</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Pozoruhodná čtečka elektronických knih</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Un lector de llibres electrònics focalitzat</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Засяроджаны на чытанні электронных кніг</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">قارئ كتب الكتروني متقدم</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Read the books you love without having to worry about the different format complexities like EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, etc.</p>
    <p>Manage your library by tagging and updating metadata on books, to quickly find books using metadata searching and tag based filtering.</p>
    <p>This version supports EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2 and comics (CBR and CBZ) formats with support for more formats to follow soon.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>اقرأ الكتب التي تحب دون الانشغال بمختلف الصيغ المعقدة مثل epub, pdf, mobi, cbr, إلخ.</p>
    <p>يمكنك إدارة مكتبتك عن طريق وضع علامات على الكتب وتحديث البيانات الوصفية، وذلك للعثور على الكتب بسرعة باستخدام البحث عن البيانات الوصفية والفلترة باستخدام العلامات.</p>
    <p>يدعم هذا الإصدار تنسيقات EPUB و MOBI و PRC و PDF و Comics (CBR و CBZ) مع إضافة دعم لمزيد من التنسيقات قريبا.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Чытайце кнігі, якія вы любіце, не турбуючыся аб складанасцях розных фарматаў, такіх як EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR і г.д.</p>
    <p>Кіруйце вашай бібліятэкай з дапамогай тэгаў і абнаўленняў метаданых кніг, каб хутка знайсці кнігі з дапамогай пошуку метаданых і фільтрацыі на аснове тэгаў.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Llegiu els llibres que us encanten sense preocupar-vos per les complexitats dels formats com ara EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, etc.</p>
    <p>Gestioneu la vostra biblioteca amb etiquetes i metadades als llibres, amb les quals podreu trobar ràpidament el que cerqueu.</p>
    <p>Aquesta versió admet els formats de llibres EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF i FB2, i també els còmics CBR i CBZ. Aviat s’hi afegirà compatibilitat per a més formats.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Čtěte milované knihy bez starostí kvůli záludnostem odlišných formátů, jako jsou EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR a další.</p>
    <p>Spravujte knihovnu za pomoci značkování a obnovování popisných údajů ke knihám, abyste knihy našli s pomocí vyhledávání v popisech a s využitím na značkách založeného filtrování rychle.</p>
    <p>Tato verze podporuje knižní formáty EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2 a formáty kreslených příběhů (CBR a CBZ) s tím, že podpora dalších přijde brzy.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Lies deine Lieblingsbücher, ohne dir über verschiedene Formate wie EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR usw. den Kopf zu zerbrechen.</p>
    <p>Verwalte deine Bibliothek, indem du Bücher markierst und die Metadaten aktualisierst, um Bücher schnell per Metadaten zu suchen und nach ihren Markierungen zu filtern.</p>
    <p>Diese Version unterstützt EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2 und Comics (CBR und CBZ) Formate und die Unterstützung für weitere Formate folgt bald.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Διαβάστε τα αγαπημένα σας βιβλία χωρίς να ανησυχείτε για τους διαφορετικούς τύπους αρχείων όπως EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR κτλ.</p>
    <p>Διαχειριστείτε τη βιβλιοθήκη σας προσθέτοντας ετικέτες και ενημερώνοντας μετα-δεδομένα σε βιβλία, για να βρείτε γρήγορα βιβλία χρησιμοποιόντας αναζήτηση μετα-δεδομένων και φιλτράρισμα με βάση τις ετικέτες.</p>
    <p>Η έκδοση αυτή υποστηρίζει EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2 και κόμικ (CBR και CBZ) με την υποστήριξη για περισσότερους τύπους αρχείων να έπεται.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Read the books you love without having to worry about the different format complexities like EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, etc.</p>
    <p>Manage your library by tagging and updating metadata on books, to quickly find books using metadata searching and tag based filtering.</p>
    <p>This version supports EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2 and comics (CBR and CBZ) formats with support for more formats to follow soon.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p>Legu amatajn librojn, sen zorgado pri la diversaj dosierformoj kiel EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, ktp.</p>
    <p>Mastrumu vian bibliotekon per etikedoj kaj ĝisdatigo de metadatenoj en libroj, por rapide trovi librojn per metadatena serĉado kaj etikeda filtrado.</p>
    <p>Ĉi tiu versio subtenas la dosierformojn EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2, kaj bildlibrojn (CBR kaj CBZ); pliaj dosierformoj baldaŭ subteniĝos.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Lea los libros que le encantan sin tener que preocuparse de la complejidad de los distintos formatos, como EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CRB, etc.</p>
    <p>Gestione su biblioteca etiquetando y actualizando los metadatos de los libros para poder encontrar los libros rápidamente mediante búsqueda por metadatos y filtrado por etiquetas.</p>
    <p>Esta versión admite los formatos EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2 así como formatos CBR y CBZ (para cómics), y próximamente se añadirá compatibilidad para más.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es_MX">
    <p>Lea los libros que ama sin tener que preocuparse del formato, como EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, etc.</p>
    <p>Gestione su biblioteca etiquetando y actualizando los metadatos de los libros para poder encontrarlos rápidamente mediante la búsqueda por metadatos y el filtrado por etiquetas.</p>
    <p>Esta versión soporta los formatos EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF y cómics CBR y CBZ. Pronto habrá soporte para otros formatos.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Loe erinevates oma armastatud raamatuid muretsemata nende vormingute nagu EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR jt pärast.</p>
    <p>Halda oma raamatukogu raamatute metaandmete sildistamise ja värskendamisega, et metaandmete abil raamatuid kiirelt otsida ja siltide põhjal filtreerida.</p>
    <p>See versioon toetab EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF and comics (CBR and CBZ) vorminguid; täiendavate vormingute tugi lisandub peagi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Lue rakastamiasi kirjoja välittämättä eri tiedostomuodoista kuten EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, jne.</p>
    <p>Järjestä kirjastosi lisäämällä tunnisteita ja päivittämällä kirjoja metatietoja. Näin löydät etsimäsi kirjat nopeasti haun avulla ja tunnisteita suodattamalla.</p>
    <p>Tämä versio tukee EPUB-, MOBI-, PRC-, PDF-, FB2- ja sarjakuvatiedostoja (CBR ja CBZ). Pian myös muita tiedostoja tuetaan.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Lisez les livres que vous aimez sans avoir à vous soucier de la complexité des différents formats comme EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, etc.</p>
    <p>Gérez votre bibliothèque en étiquetant et en mettant à jour les métadonnées des livres, afin de trouver rapidement les livres à l'aide de la recherche de métadonnées et du filtrage basé sur les étiquettes.</p>
    <p>Cette version prend en charge les formats EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF et Comics (CBR et CBZ) et d'autres formats à venir.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>מאפשר לקרוא את הספרים שאהובים עליך מבלי לחשוש מסיבוכי תסדירי הקבצים כגון EPUB,‏ PDF,‏ MOBI,‏ CBR וכו׳.</p>
    <p>מאפשר לנהל את הספרייה שלך על ידי תיוג ועדכון נתונים על ספרים כדי למצוא ספרים בקלות באמצעות חיפוש נתוני הקשר וסינון לפי תגיות.</p>
    <p>גרסה זו תומכת בתסדירי EPUB,‏ MOBI,‏ PRC,‏ PDF,‏ FB2 וקומיקס (CBR ו־CBZ) עם עוד כמה תסדירים בקרוב.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Čitaj knjige koje voliš bez da si razbijaš glavu o raznim formatima kao što su EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR itd.</p>
    <p>Upravljaj vlastitom knjižnicom označavanjem i aktualiziranjem metapodataka knjiga, za brzo pronalaženje knjiga pomoću pretraživanja metapodataka i filtriranja na temelju oznaka.</p>
    <p>Ova verzija podržava EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2 i formate stripova (CBR i CBZ), a uskoro će podržati i daljnje formate.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Baca buku yang Anda sukai tanpa harus khawatir tentang berbagai format seperti EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, dll.</p>
    <p>Atur perpustakaan Anda dengan label dan perbarui metadata buku, untuk mencari buku dengan cepat menggunakan pencari metadata dan filtering berdasarkan label.</p>
    <p>Versi ini mendukung format EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF dan Komik (CBR dan CBZ) dengan format lainnya yang akan segera didukung.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ie">
    <p>Leer li libres que vu ama sin egard a complicaties de formates quam EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>Lestu bækur eins og þig lystir, án þess að þurfa að hugsa um mismun á flóknum skráasniðum eins og EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, o.sv.frv.</p>
    <p>Skipuleggðu safnið þitt með því að merkja og uppfæra lýsigögn bóka, sem nýtist svo til að leita að bókum hratt og vel.</p>
    <p>Þessi útgáfa styður EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF og Comic (CBR og CBZ) skráasnið auk þess sem stuðningur enn fleiri snið er væntanlegur.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Leggi i libri che ami senza doverti preoccupare per la complessità dei diversi tipi di formato come EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, ecc.</p>
    <p>Gestisci la tua libreria etichetando e aggiornando i metadati dei libri per trovarli rapidamente filtrando per etichetta e metadati.</p>
    <p>Questa versione supporta i formati EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2 e fumetti (CBR e CBZ) con supporto per formati aggiuntivi presto in arrivo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>EPUB・PDF・MOBI・CBR など異なったファイル形式の複雑さを気にせずに愛読書を読みましょう。</p>
    <p>本にタグ付けしたりメタデータを更新したりしてライブラリを管理して、メタデータ検索とタグに基づくフィルタリングを使用し本を素早く見つけましょう。</p>
    <p>このバージョンは EPUB・MOBI・PRC・PDF・FB2 とコミックス (CBR と CBZ) 形式をサポートしています。まもなく、さらなるファイル形式がサポートされます。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Czytaj książki, które kochasz nie martwiąc się o formaty w jakich są zapisane, takie jak  EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR itp.</p>
    <p>Zarządzaj swoją biblioteką poprzez znaczniki i aktualizację metadanych książek. Możesz szybko znaleźć książki za pomocą wyszukiwania metadanych i filtrowania opartego na znacznikach.</p>
    <p>Ta wersja obsługuje formaty EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2 i komiksy (CBR i CBZ). Obsługa kolejnych formatów zostanie dodana wkrótce.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Leia os livros que gosta sem ter que se preocupar com as complexidades de formatos diferentes, como EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, etc.</p>
    <p>Faça a gestão da sua biblioteca marcando e atualizando os metadados dos livros, para localizar rapidamente livros usando a pesquisa de metadados e a filtragem baseada em etiquetas.</p>
    <p>Esta versão suporta os formatos EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF e comics (CBR e CBZ) com suporte para mais formatos no futuro.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Leia seus livros favoritos sem se preocupar com diferentes formatos como EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, etc.</p>
    <p>Gerencie sua biblioteca com tags e metadados para achá-los com base nos filtros de pesquisa .</p>
    <p>Esta versão suporta os formatos EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2 e quadrinhos (CBR e CBZ), com suporte para mais formatos em breve.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Citiți cărțile pe care le iubiți fără să vă faceți griji cu privire la diferitele complexități de format, cum ar fi EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR etc.</p>
    <p>Gestionați-vă biblioteca prin etichetarea și actualizarea metadatelor din cărți, pentru a găsi rapid cărți folosind căutarea metadatelor și filtrarea bazată pe etichete.</p>
    <p>Această versiune poate citi doar formatele EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, inclusiv CBR și CBZ pentru benzi desenate urmând ca în curând lista să se extindă.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Читайте любимые книги, не беспокоясь о различиях форматов вроде EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR и им подобных.</p>
    <p>Управляйте своей библиотекой, добавляя теги и обновляя мета данные книг для того, чтобы находить их быстрее поиском по метаданным и фильтрацией по тегам.</p>
    <p>Эта версия поддерживает EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2 и форматы комиксов: CBR и CBZ. В будущем — ещё больше форматов.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sc">
    <p>Leghe sos libros chi amas chene tènnere bisòngiu de ti preocupare de sa complessidade de sos formados diferentes comente a EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, etz.</p>
    <p>Manìgia sa biblioteca tua etichetende e carrighende sos metadatos de sos libros, pro agatare in presse libros impreende sa chirca cun sos metadatos e sos filtros cun sas etichetas.</p>
    <p>Custa versione suportat sos formados EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF e cussos (CBR and CBZ) pro sos fumetos, e in su tempus imbeniente nd'at a suportare medas àteros.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Läs böckerna du älskar utan att behöva oroa dig för olika formatkomplexiteter som EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR, etc.</p>
    <p>Hantera ditt bibliotek genom att tagga och uppdatera metadata på böcker, för att snabbt hitta böcker med hjälp av metadatasökning och taggbaserad filtrering.</p>
    <p>Denna version stöder EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2 och comics (CBR och CBZ) format med stöd för fler format att följa snart.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Sevdiğiniz kitapları EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR vb. format sıkıntısı yaşamadan okuyun.</p>
    <p>Kitaplığınızdaki kitapları etiketleyerek ve meta verilerini güncelleyerek, arama sırasında daha çabuk bulabilirsiniz.</p>
    <p>Bu sürüm EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2 ve çizgi roman biçimlerini (CBR ve CBZ) desteklemektedir. Daha fazla biçim desteği planlanmaktadır.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Читайте улюблені книги, не турбуючись про різницю форматів EPUB, PDF, MOBI, CBR тощо.</p>
    <p>Керувуйте своєю бібліотекою за допомогою міток та оновлюючи метадані книг, щоб швидко знаходити книги за допомогою пошуку метаданих та фільтрування за мітками.</p>
    <p>Ця версія підтримує EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2 і формати коміксів(CBR та CBZ). Та ще більше форматів у майбутньому.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="vi">
    <p>Phiên bản này hỗ trợ các định dạng EPUB, MOBI, PRC, PDF, FB2, truyện tranh (CBR và CBZ) và sẽ sớm hỗ trợ nhiều định dạng khác.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh">
    <p>只管阅读你喜欢的图书，无需在意格式，如 epub、pdf、mobi、cbr 等。</p>
    <p>通过标记和更新书籍上的元数据来管理你的书库，使用元数据搜索和基于标签的过滤来快速找到书籍。</p>
    <p>当前版本支持 EPUB、MOBI、PRC、PDF、FB2 和漫画（CBR 和 CBZ）格式。未来将支持更多格式。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_HK">
    <p>您可以簡單咁管理基本資料同標籤，亦可以用呢類資料去搵書。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>閱讀您喜愛的書籍，而不必擔心不同的格式複雜性，如 EPUB、PDF、MOBI、CBR 等。</p>
    <p>通過標記和更新書籍上的元數據來管理您的庫，使用元數據搜尋和基於標籤的過濾快速找到書籍。</p>
    <p>此版本支援 EPUB、MOBI、PRC、PDF、FB2 和漫畫（CBR 和 CBZ）格式，支援更多格式的版本即將推出。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Bookworm Library View</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">Bookworm 書庫視圖</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_HK">書櫃模式</caption>
      <caption lang="zh">书虫书库视图</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Подання бібліотеки Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Bookworm Kütüphane Görünümü</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Bookworm biblioteksvy</caption>
      <caption lang="sc">Vista de sa biblioteca de Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Режим библиотеки Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="ro">Vizualizare bibliotecă Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Visualizar a biblioteca do Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Visualização da biblioteca Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Bookworm Widok Biblioteki</caption>
      <caption lang="nb_NO">Bokorm biblioteksvisning</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">Bookworm ライブラリビュー</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Bookworm in visualizzazione biblioteca</caption>
      <caption lang="is">Sýn á Bókaormssafn</caption>
      <caption lang="ie">Vise de biblioteca de Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Lihat Perpustakaan Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Bibliofil – prikaz knjižnica</caption>
      <caption lang="he">תצוגת ספרייה של Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Vue de la bibliothèque de Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Bookwormin kirjastonäkymä</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Bookwormi Raamatukogu Vaade</caption>
      <caption lang="es_MX">Vista de la biblioteca de Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Vista de la biblioteca de Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">Biblioteka Vido de Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">Bookworm Library View</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Εκτέλεση Bookworm σε λειτουργία βιβλιοθήκης</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Bookworm Bibliotheks-Ansicht</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Knihovnický pohled</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Visualització de biblioteca del Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="be">Прагляд бібліятэкі Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">عرض مكتبة دودة الكتب</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/babluboy/bookworm/gh-pages/images/BookwormLibraryView.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Bookworm Reading View</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">Bookworm 閱讀視圖</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_HK">閱讀模式</caption>
      <caption lang="zh">书虫阅读视图</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Подання для читання Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Bookworm Okuma Görünümü</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Bookworm läsläge</caption>
      <caption lang="sc">Vista de leghidura de Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Режим чтения</caption>
      <caption lang="ro">Rulează Bookworm în modul info</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Modo Leitura</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Modo de leitura Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Uruchom Bookworm w trybie czytelnika</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">Bookworm リーディングビュー</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Bookworm in visualizzazione lettura</caption>
      <caption lang="is">Keyra Bókaorm í lesham</caption>
      <caption lang="ie">Vise de letion de Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Tampilan Membaca Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Bibliofil – prikaz za čitanje</caption>
      <caption lang="he">תצוגת קריאה של Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Vue de lecture de Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Bookwormin lukunäkymä</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Käivita Bookworm lugemisrežiimis</caption>
      <caption lang="es_MX">Vista de lectura de Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Vista de lectura de Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">Lega Vido de Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">Bookworm Reading View</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Εκτέλεση Bookworm σε λειτουργία ανάγνωσης</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Bookworm Lese-Ansicht</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Čtenářský pohled</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Visualització de lectura del Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="be">Чытальніцкі выгляд Bookworm</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">عرض قراءة دودة الكتب</caption>
      <caption lang="ab">Abkhazian</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/babluboy/bookworm/gh-pages/images/BookwormReadingView.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>com.github.babluboy.bookworm</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.1.2" date="2019-08-10">
      <description>
        <p>This release has some new features, fixes and new translations:</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本包含一些新的特性、修復以及翻譯：</p>
        <p lang="zh">这个版本包含了新的特性、修复以及翻译：</p>
        <p lang="vi">Bản phát hành này có một số tính năng mới, bản sửa lỗi và bản dịch mới:</p>
        <p lang="uk">У цьому випуску — нові функції, виправлення помилок і нові переклади:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu güncelleme kimi yeni özellikler, düzeltmeler ve çeviriler içeriyor:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna utgåva har några nya funktioner, fixar och nya översättningar:</p>
        <p lang="sc">Custa versione tenet carchi funtzionalidade noa, curretziones de errores e incluet bortaduras noas:</p>
        <p lang="ru">В этом релизе — новые функции, исправления ошибок и переводы:</p>
        <p lang="ro">Această versiune are câteva funcții noi, remedieri și noi traduceri:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão possui novas funcionalidades, correções e novas traduções:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Este lançamento tem algumas funcionalidades novas, correções e inclui novas traduções:</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie ma kilka nowych funkcji, poprawek i nowych tłumaczeń:</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースは、いくつかの新機能と修正、新しい翻訳を含んでいます:</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa release contiene alcune nuove funzionalità, correzioni e nuove traduzioni:</p>
        <p lang="is">Þessi útgáfa er með nokkra nýja eiginleika, lagfæringar og nýjar þýðingar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Ti-ci version have quelc nov functiones, correctiones e traductiones:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini memiliki beberapa fitur baru, perbaikan dan terjemahan baru:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovo izdanje sadrži poneke nove funkcije, ispravke i nove prijevode:</p>
        <p lang="he">במהדורה זו יש מגוון יכולות חדשות, תיקונים ותרגומים חדשים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version apporte quelques nouveautés, corrections et nouvelles traductions :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tässä versiossa on joitakin uusia ominaisuuksia, korjauksia ja uusia käännöksiä:</p>
        <p lang="et">Sellel versioonil on mõned uued funktsioonid, parandused ja tõlked:</p>
        <p lang="es_MX">Esta nueva actualización tiene algunas nuevas funcionalidades, arreglaos y nuevas traducciones:</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta publicación incorpora funciones nuevas, correcciones y traducciones actualizadas:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Ĉi tiu eldono havas novajn funkciojn, korektojn kaj novajn tradukojn:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">This release has some new features, fixes and new translations:</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση έχει κάποια νέα χαρακτηριστικά, επιδιορθώσεις και νέες μεταφράσεις:</p>
        <p lang="de">Dieses Release hat ein paar neue Funktionen, Korrekturen und neue Übersetzungen:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání má některé nové vlastnosti, opravy a nové překlady:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquest llançament incorpora prestacions noves, algunes correccions i traduccions actualitzades:</p>
        <p lang="be">Гэты выпуск мае некаторыя новыя функцыі, выпраўленні і новыя пераклады:</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذا الإصدار به مزايا وإصلاح وترجمات جديدة:</p>
        <p>New Features:</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">新特性：</p>
        <p lang="zh">新特性：</p>
        <p lang="vi">Các tính năng mới:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Нові функції:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Yeni Özellikler:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Nya funktioner:</p>
        <p lang="sc">Funtzionalidades noas:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Новые возможности:</p>
        <p lang="ro">Funcții noi:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Novas funcionalidades:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Novas funcionalidades:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Nowe funkcje:</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Nye funksjoner:</p>
        <p lang="ja">新機能:</p>
        <p lang="it">Nuove funzionalità:</p>
        <p lang="is">Nýir eiginleikar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Nov functiones:</p>
        <p lang="id">Fitur Baru:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Nove funkcije:</p>
        <p lang="he">תכונות חדשות:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Nouvelles fonctionnalités :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Uudet ominaisuudet:</p>
        <p lang="et">Uued funktsioonid:</p>
        <p lang="es_MX">Nuevas funcionalidades:</p>
        <p lang="es">Prestaciones nuevas:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Novaj Trajtoj:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">New features:</p>
        <p lang="el">Νέα χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
        <p lang="de">Neue Features:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Nové vlastnosti:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Funcionalitats noves:</p>
        <p lang="be">Новыя функцыі:</p>
        <p lang="ar">مزايا جديدة:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Library is paginated to load large libraries quickly</li>
          <li lang="zh_TW">將書庫分頁，以更快載入大書庫</li>
          <li lang="zh">为快速加载大型库，应用对书库进行分页</li>
          <li lang="vi">Thư viện được phân trang để tải các thư viện lớn một cách nhanh chóng</li>
          <li lang="uk">Бібліотеку пронумеровано для швидкого завантаження великих бібліотек</li>
          <li lang="tr">Büyük kütüphaneleri hızlıca yüklemek için kütüphane sayfalandırıldı</li>
          <li lang="sv">Biblioteket sidoindelas för att snabbt ladda stora bibliotek</li>
          <li lang="sc">Sa biblioteca est impaginada pro carrigare bibliotecas mannas in presse</li>
          <li lang="ru">Библиотека разделена на страницы для быстрой загрузки</li>
          <li lang="ro">Biblioteca este paginată pentru a încărca rapid bibliotecile mari</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">A biblioteca é paginada para carregar grandes bibliotecas rapidamente</li>
          <li lang="pt">A biblioteca está paginada para carregar uma grande quantidade de bibliotecas rapidamente</li>
          <li lang="pl">Biblioteka jest podzielona na strony, aby szybko ładować duże biblioteki.</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Biblioteket er sideinndelt for å laste inn store bibliotek raskt</li>
          <li lang="ja">大きなライブラリを素早く読み込めるように、ライブラリのページ割りをしました</li>
          <li lang="it">La Libreria è visualizzata in pagine per consentire la visualizzazione rapida di grandi librerie</li>
          <li lang="is">Safninu er skipt upp í síður til að flýta fyrir innhleðslu stórra safna</li>
          <li lang="id">Perpustakaan diberi nomor halaman untuk memuat perpustakaan besar dengan cepat</li>
          <li lang="hr">Knjižnica je paginirana za brzo učitavanje velikih knjižnica</li>
          <li lang="he">הספרייה מחולקת לעמודים כדי לטעון ספריות גדולות במהירות</li>
          <li lang="fr">La bibliothèque est paginée pour charger de larges bibliothèques rapidement</li>
          <li lang="fi">Kirjasto on jaettu usealle sivulle, jotta suurien kirjastoja lataaminen on nopeaa</li>
          <li lang="et">Raamatukogu on jagatud lehtedeks, et kiirelt laadida suured raamatukogud</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">La biblioteca está paginada, así puede cargar extensas bibliotecas rápidamente</li>
          <li lang="es">La biblioteca está paginada para cargar bibliotecas grandes velozmente</li>
          <li lang="eo">Biblioteko estas paĝigita por ŝarĝi grandajn bibliotekojn rapide</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Library is paginated to load large libraries quickly</li>
          <li lang="el">Η βιβλιοθήκη είναι σελιδοποιημένη για γρήγορη φόρτωση</li>
          <li lang="de">Die Bibliothek hat eine Seitenzahlnummerierung, um große Bibliotheken schneller zu laden zü können</li>
          <li lang="cs">Knihovna je kvůli rychlému nahrávání rozsáhlých knihoven stránkována</li>
          <li lang="ca">La biblioteca és paginada perquè es carregui ràpidament quan hi ha nombrosos llibres</li>
          <li lang="ar">المكتبة مقسمة إلى صفحات لتحميل مكتبات كبيرة بسرعة</li>
          <li>Support for FB2 Format - .fb2 and .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="zh_TW">支援 FB2 格式 - .fb2 and .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="zh">支持FB2格式- .fb2和.fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="vi">Hỗ trợ định dạng FB2 - .fb2 và .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="uk">Підтримка формату FB2 - .fb2 та .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="tr">FB2 biçim desteği - .fb2 ve .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="sv">Stöd för FB2-format - .fb2 och .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="sc">Suportu pro su formadu FB2 - .fb2 e .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="ru">Поддержка формата FB2 (.fb2 и .fb2.zip)</li>
          <li lang="ro">Suport pentru formatul FB2 - .fb2 și .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Suporte para o formato FB2 - .fb2 e .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="pt">Suporte para o formato FB2 - fb2 e .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="pl">Obsługa formatu FB2 - .fb2 and .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="ja">FB2 形式 (.fb2、.fb2.zip) への対応</li>
          <li lang="it">Supporto per il formato FB2 - .fb2 e .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="is">Stuðningur við FB2-snið - .fb2 og .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="ie">Supporte de formate FB2 - .fb2 e .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="id">Mendukung Format FB2 - .fb2 dan .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="hr">Podrška za FB2 format – .fb2 i .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="he">תמיכה בתסדיר FB2‏ - ‎.fb2 ו־‎.fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="fr">Prise en charge du format FB2 - .fb2 et .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="fi">Tuki FB2-tiedostoille (.fb2 ja .fb2.zip)</li>
          <li lang="et">FB2-vormingu tugi - .fb2 ja .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Soporta el formato FB2 (.fb2, .fb2.zip)</li>
          <li lang="es">Compatibilidad con el formato FB2 - .fb2 y .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="eo">Subteno de la dosierformo FB2 - .fb2 kaj .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Support for FB2 Format – .fb2 and .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="el">Υποστήριξη για τύπο αρχείου FB2 - .fb2 και .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="de">Unterstützung für das FB2-Format - .fb2 und .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="cs">Podpora pro formát FB2 - .fb2 a .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="ca">Compatibilitat amb el format FB2: .fb2 i .fb2.zip</li>
          <li lang="ar">دعم تنسيق FB2 - .fb2 و. fb2.zip</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Fixes:</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">修復：</p>
        <p lang="zh">修复：</p>
        <p lang="vi">Sửa lỗi:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Виправлення помилок:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Düzeltmeler:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Fixar:</p>
        <p lang="sc">Acontzos:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Исправления ошибок:</p>
        <p lang="ro">Remedii:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Correções:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Correções:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Poprawki:</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Fikser:</p>
        <p lang="ja">修正:</p>
        <p lang="it">Correzioni:</p>
        <p lang="is">Lagfæringar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Correctiones:</p>
        <p lang="id">Perbaikan:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ispravci:</p>
        <p lang="he">תיקונים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Corrections :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Korjaukset:</p>
        <p lang="et">Parandused:</p>
        <p lang="es_MX">Mejoramientos:</p>
        <p lang="es">Correcciones:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Korektoj:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Fixes:</p>
        <p lang="el">Διορθώσεις:</p>
        <p lang="de">Fehlerbehebungen:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Opravy:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Correccions:</p>
        <p lang="be">Выпраўленні:</p>
        <p lang="ar">إصلاحات:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Intuitive representation of book removal button on library</li>
          <li lang="zh">书库中直观展现书籍移除按钮</li>
          <li lang="uk">Очевидніший вигляд кнопки вилучення книг з бібліотеки</li>
          <li lang="tr">Kitap kaldırma düğmesi kütüphane üzerinde artık sezgisel olarak temsil ediliyor</li>
          <li lang="sv">Intuitiv representation av bokborttagningsknappen på biblioteket</li>
          <li lang="sc">Rapresentatzione intuitiva de su butone pro bogare sos libros in sa biblioteca</li>
          <li lang="ru">Видимая кнопка удаления книг на экране библиотеки</li>
          <li lang="ro">Reprezentare intuitivă a butonului de eliminare a cărții din bibliotecă</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Representação intuitiva do botão de remoção de livros na biblioteca</li>
          <li lang="pt">Representação intuitiva do botão que remove os livros na biblioteca</li>
          <li lang="pl">Intuicyjna prezentacja przycisku usuwania książek w bibliotece</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Intuitiv representasjon av bokfjerningsknapp ved tillegg i bibliotek</li>
          <li lang="ja">ライブラリの本の削除ボタンを直感的な表示に変更</li>
          <li lang="it">Rappresentazione intuitiva del pulsante di rimozione libri nella libreria</li>
          <li lang="is">Augljósari framsetning hnapps til að fjarlægja bækur úr safni</li>
          <li lang="id">Representasi intuitif tombol penghapusan buku di perpustakaan</li>
          <li lang="hr">Intuitivni prikaz gumba za uklanjanje knjiga u knjižnici</li>
          <li lang="he">ייצוג נוח יותר של כפתור הסרת ספרים בספרייה</li>
          <li lang="fr">Représentation intuitive du bouton de retrait de livre dans la bibliothèque</li>
          <li lang="fi">Kirjan poistamiseen käytetyn painikkeen intuitiivinen esitys kirjastossa</li>
          <li lang="et">Raamatu raamatukogust eemaldamise nupu intuitiivne esitus</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Representación del botón para eliminar libros de la biblioteca</li>
          <li lang="es">Botón de representación intuitiva para la eliminación de libros en la biblioteca</li>
          <li lang="eo">Intuicia prezento de butono por forigi libron el biblioteko</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Intuitive representation of book removal button on library</li>
          <li lang="el">Αναπαράσταση του κουμπιού αφαίρεσης βιβλίων</li>
          <li lang="de">Intuitive Darstellung der Schaltfläche zum Entfernen von Büchern in der Bibliothek</li>
          <li lang="cs">Znázornění tlačítka pro odstranění knihy v knihovně</li>
          <li lang="ca">Representació intuïtiva del botó de supressió de llibres a la biblioteca</li>
          <li lang="ar">تمثيل بديهي لزر إزالة الكتاب في المكتبة</li>
          <li>Fix for keeping the preference dialog open until all adjustments are completed</li>
          <li lang="zh">修复了首选项对话框在所有调整完成前就关闭的错误</li>
          <li lang="uk">Тепер діалогове вікно налаштувань буде відкритим доки всі налаштування не буде виконано</li>
          <li lang="tr">Düzeltme: Tüm ayarlamalar tamamlanıncaya kadar tercihler iletişim kutusunu artık açık tut</li>
          <li lang="sv">Åtgärd för att hålla inställningsdialogrutan öppen tills alla justeringar är slutförda</li>
          <li lang="sc">Acontzu pro mantènnere abertu su diàlogu de sas preferèntzias finas a cando totu sas regulatziones sunt acabadas</li>
          <li lang="ru">Диалог настроек остается открытым до их полного применения</li>
          <li lang="ro">Remediere pentru menținerea dialogului de preferințe deschis până la finalizarea tuturor ajustărilor</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Correção para manter a caixa de diálogo de preferências aberta até que todos os ajustes sejam concluídos</li>
          <li lang="pt">Correção para manter o dialogo de preferências aberto até que todos os ajustamentos estejam completos</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zatrzymaj okno dialogowe preferencji otwarte do momentu zakończenia wszystkich korekt</li>
          <li lang="ja">すべての調整が完了するまで設定ダイアログを閉じないように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Correzione per mantenere aperta la finestra di dialogo delle preferenze fino al completamento di tutte le regolazioni</li>
          <li lang="is">Lagfæring til að halda kjörstillingaglugga opnum þar til öllum breytingum er lokið</li>
          <li lang="id">Memperbaiki untuk menjaga dialog preferensi tetap terbuka sampai semua penyesuaian selesai</li>
          <li lang="hr">Ispravak: ostavljanje dijaloga postavki otvorenim, dok se prilagođavanja ne dovrše</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון להשארת תיבת דו־שיח ההעדפות פתוח עד להשלמת השינויים</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction pour garder le dialogue de préférences ouvert jusqu'à ce que tous les ajustements soient faits</li>
          <li lang="fi">Älä sulje asetusikkunaa ennen kuin kaikki muutokset on tehty</li>
          <li lang="et">Parandus hoidmaks eelistuste dialoog avatuna kuni kõik muudatused on lõpetatud</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Mantener abierto el diálogo de preferencias hasta que todas las tareas sean completadas</li>
          <li lang="es">Correción para mantener el diálogo de preferencias abierto hasta que todos los cambios se hayan finalizado</li>
          <li lang="eo">Korekto por teni la dialogon pri preferoj malfermita ĝis la agordado finiĝas</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix for keeping the preference dialogue open until all adjustments are completed</li>
          <li lang="el">Επιδιόρθωση για διατήρηση του διαλόγου προτιμήσεων ανοιχτό μέχρι να ολοκληρωθούν όλες οι ρυθμίσεις</li>
          <li lang="de">Korrektur, dass der Einstellungsdialog geöffnet bleibt, bis alle Einstellungen abgeschlossen sind</li>
          <li lang="cs">Oprava kvůli zachování dialogu nastavení otevřeného, dokud nejsou dokončeny všechny úpravy</li>
          <li lang="ca">Correcció per a mantenir obert el diàleg de preferències fins que es completin tots els ajustaments</li>
          <li lang="ar">إصلاح للإبقاء على مربع حوار التفضيلات مفتوحًا حتى تكتمل جميع التعديلات</li>
          <li>Fix for header title changing during open</li>
          <li lang="zh">修复标题在书籍打开期间改变的错误</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено зміну назви заголовка під час відкриття</li>
          <li lang="tr">Açılış sırasında değişen üst başlık için düzeltme</li>
          <li lang="sv">Fix för att rubrik ändras under öppen</li>
          <li lang="sc">Acontzu pro sa muda de su tìtulu durante s'abertura</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправление заголовка окна в ходе открытия книг</li>
          <li lang="ro">Remediere pentru schimbarea titlului antetului în timpul deschiderii</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Correção para a alteração do título do cabeçalho durante a abertura</li>
          <li lang="pt">Correção para a mudança do título do cabeçalho enquanto este está aberto</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawiono zmianę tytułu nagłówka podczas otwierania</li>
          <li lang="ja">本を開く際にヘッダーのタイトルを変更するように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Correzione del titolo di intestazione che varia durante l'apertura</li>
          <li lang="is">Lagfæring til að breyta titli við opnun</li>
          <li lang="id">Perbaikan untuk perubahan judul header saat terbuka</li>
          <li lang="hr">Ispravak: promjena naslova zaglavlja za vrijeme otvaranja</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון לכך שהכותרת משתנה במהלך הפתיחה</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction pour le changement du titre de l'en-tête pendant l'ouverture</li>
          <li lang="fi">Korjaa yläpalkin otsikko vaihtuminen avauksen aikana</li>
          <li lang="et">Parandus päise tiitli muutmiseks avamisel</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Cambiar el encabezado al abrir</li>
          <li lang="es">Corrección para cambiar el texto del título mientras este abierto</li>
          <li lang="eo">Korekto pri ŝanĝado de titolo dum malfermado</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix for header title changing during open</li>
          <li lang="el">Επιδιόρθωση για αλλαγή τίτλου επικεφαλίδας κατά το άνοιγμα</li>
          <li lang="de">Korrektur für die Änderung der Titelüberschrift während des Öffnens</li>
          <li lang="cs">Oprava pro změnu názvu záhlaví během otevírání</li>
          <li lang="ca">Reparació del problema pel qual el títol a la capçalera canviava durant l’obertura</li>
          <li lang="ar">إصلاح لتغيير عنوان الرأس أثناء الفتح</li>
          <li>Fix for handling cancelation of dialog to open an ebook</li>
          <li lang="zh">修复了处理取消打开电子书对话框方面的问题</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено скасування відкривання діалогового вікна для відкриття книги</li>
          <li lang="tr">Ekitap açmak için iletişim kutusunun iptal edilmesiyle ilgili düzeltme</li>
          <li lang="sv">Fix för att hantera annullering av dialog för att öppna en e-bok</li>
          <li lang="sc">Acontzu pro contipigiare s'annulladura de su diàlogu pro abèrrere unu libru</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлена обработка отмены диалога открытия книги</li>
          <li lang="ro">Remediere pentru schimbarea titlului antetului în timpul deschiderii</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Correção para lidar com o cancelamento da caixa de diálogo para abrir um livro</li>
          <li lang="pt">Correção do comportamento do dialogo de cancelamento para a abertura um livro digital</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawiono obsługę anulowania okna dialogowego, aby otworzyć ebooka</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Fiks for håndtering av dialogsendring for åpning av e-bok</li>
          <li lang="ja">電子書籍を開く際のダイアログのキャンセル処理に関する修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Correzione per gestire la cancellazione nel pannello di apertura di libro</li>
          <li lang="is">Lagfæring við að hætta við í samskiptaglugga til að opna rafbók</li>
          <li lang="id">Perbaikan untuk menangani pembatalan dialog untuk membuka ebook</li>
          <li lang="hr">Ispravak: rukovanje prekidanjem dijaloga za otvaranje e-knjige</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון לטיפול בביטול תיבות דו־שיח לפתיחת ספר אלקטרוני</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction pour le traitement de l'annulation du dialogue pour ouvrir un livre numérique</li>
          <li lang="fi">Korjaa e-kirjan avaus -ikkunan peruminen</li>
          <li lang="et">Parandus e-raamatu avamise dialoogist loobumiseks</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Corrección del manejo de la cancelación del diálogo para abrir un libro electrónico</li>
          <li lang="es">Corrección para manejar la cancelación del diálogo de apartura de un libro electrónico</li>
          <li lang="eo">Korekto pri nuligo de dialogo por malfermi bitlibron</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix for handling cancelation of dialogue to open an e-book</li>
          <li lang="el">Επιδιόρθωση χειρισμού ακύρωσης του παραθύρου διαλόγου κατά το άνοιγμα ebook</li>
          <li lang="de">Korrektur für die Handhabung des Abbruchdialogs zum Öffnen eines E-Buchs</li>
          <li lang="cs">Oprava pro zacházení se zrušením dialogu pro otevření elektronické knihy</li>
          <li lang="ca">S’ha arreglat la cancel·lació del diàleg per a obrir un llibre electrònic</li>
          <li lang="ar">إصلاح للتعامل مع إلغاء مربع الحوار لفتح كتاب إلكتروني</li>
          <li>Fix for toggling between full screen mode with F11</li>
          <li lang="zh">修复了用F11 键进入/退出全屏模式方面的问题</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено перемикання між повноекранним режимом за допомогою F11</li>
          <li lang="tr">F11 ile tam ekran kipi arasında geçiş yapmak ile ilgili düzeltme</li>
          <li lang="sv">Fix för att växla mellan helskärmsläge med F11</li>
          <li lang="sc">Acontzu pro allughere o istudare sa modalidade a ischermu intreu incarchende F11</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправление переключения полноэкранного режима по клавише F11</li>
          <li lang="ro">Remediere pentru comutarea între modul ecran complet cu F11</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Correção para alternar entre o modo de tela cheia com F11</li>
          <li lang="pt">Correção ao alternar entre o modo de ecrã inteiro com o F11</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawiono przełączanie pomiędzy trybem pełnoekranowym z użyciem F11</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Fiks for veksling av fullskjermsmodus med F11</li>
          <li lang="ja">F11 キーで全画面表示モードを切り替えできるように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Correzione per il salto da modalità a tutto schermo con F11</li>
          <li lang="is">Lagfæring við að víxla á milli skjáfyllihams með F11</li>
          <li lang="id">Perbaikan saat beralih antara mode layar penuh dengan F11</li>
          <li lang="hr">Ispravak: prebacivanje na modus cjeloekranskog prikaza pomoću F11</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון למעבר מילוי המסך וביטולו עם F11</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction pour basculer entre le mode plein écran avec F11</li>
          <li lang="et">Parandus lülitumiseks klahviga F11 täisekraami vaatesse</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Alternar el modo pantalla completa con F11</li>
          <li lang="es">Corrección para poder intercambiar el modo de pantalla completa con la tecla F11</li>
          <li lang="eo">Korekto por baskuligi plenekranan reĝimon per F11</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix for toggling between full screen mode with F11</li>
          <li lang="el">Επιδιόρθωση εναλλαγής λειτουργίας πλήρους οθόνης με το F11</li>
          <li lang="de">Korrektur für das Umschalten zwischen Vollbildmodus mit F11</li>
          <li lang="cs">Oprava pro přepínání mezi režimem na celou obrazovku pomocí F11</li>
          <li lang="ar">إصلاح للتبديل بين وضع ملء الشاشة باستخدام F11</li>
          <li>Fix for annotation dialog for books with empty titles</li>
          <li lang="zh">修复了和标题为空的书籍的注释对话框有关的问题</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлення діалогового вікна приміток для книг без назви</li>
          <li lang="tr">Boş başlıkları olan kitaplar için açıklama iletişim kutusunu düzelt</li>
          <li lang="sv">Fix för anteckningsdialogrutan för böcker med tomma titlar</li>
          <li lang="sc">Acontzu pro su diàlogu de annotatzione pro sos libros cun tìtulos bòidos</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправление диалога примечаний для книг без названия</li>
          <li lang="ro">Remedierea dialogului de adnotare pentru cărțile cu titluri goale</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Correção na caixa de diálogo de anotação para livros com títulos vazios</li>
          <li lang="pt">Correção do dialogo de anotações para livros com o título vazio</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawiono okno dialogowe adnotacji dla książek z pustymi tytułami</li>
          <li lang="ja">タイトルのない本における注釈ダイアログの修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Correzione per pannello annotazioni nei libri senza titolo</li>
          <li lang="is">Lagfæring á glósuglugga fyrir bækur með auða titla</li>
          <li lang="id">Perbaikan untuk dialog anotasi untuk buku dengan judul kosong</li>
          <li lang="hr">Ispravak: dijalog za napomene knjiga s praznim naslovima</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון תיבת דו־שיח של הערות לספרים עם כותרות ריקות</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correvtion pour le dialogue d'annotation avec des titres vides</li>
          <li lang="fi">Korjaa huomautusikkuna nimettömissä kirjoissa</li>
          <li lang="et">Parandus e-raamatute annotatsiooni dialoogis, kui raamatu tiitel puudub</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Corrección para el diálogo de anotación para libros sin título</li>
          <li lang="es">Corrección para el diálogo de anotación para libros sin título</li>
          <li lang="eo">Korekto pri prinota dialogo por libroj sen titoloj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix for annotation dialogue for books with empty titles</li>
          <li lang="el">Επιδιόρθωση διαλόγου σχολιασμού για βιβλία χωρίς τίτλους</li>
          <li lang="de">Korrektur des Anmerkungsdialogs für Bücher mit leeren Titeln</li>
          <li lang="cs">Oprava pro dialog vysvětlivky pro knihy s prázdnými názvy</li>
          <li lang="ar">إصلاح لمربع حوار التعليقات التوضيحية للكتب ذات العناوين الفارغة</li>
          <li>Fix for returning to the page position from the info view</li>
          <li lang="zh">修复了和从信息视图返回到页面位置有关的问题</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено повернення до положення сторінки з подання відомостей</li>
          <li lang="tr">Bilgi görünümünden sayfa konumuna geri dönmek ile ilgili düzeltme</li>
          <li lang="sv">Fixa för att återgå till sidpositionen från infovyn</li>
          <li lang="sc">Acontzu pro torrare a sa positzione in sa pàgina dae sa vista de sas informatziones</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправление положения на странице после закрытия экрана сведений</li>
          <li lang="ro">Remediere pentru revenirea la poziția paginii din vizualizarea cu informații</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Correção para retornar à posição da página na visualização de informações</li>
          <li lang="pt">Correção para quando voltar à posição da página da vista de informações</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawiono powrót do pozycji strony z widoku informacji</li>
          <li lang="ja">情報ビューからページの位置に戻るように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Correzione per tornare alla posizione nella pagina dalla vista info</li>
          <li lang="is">Lagfæring til að fara á staðsetningu á síðu úr upplýsingasýn</li>
          <li lang="id">Perbaikan untuk kembali ke posisi halaman dari tampilan info</li>
          <li lang="hr">Ispravak: vraćanje na položaj stranice iz prikaza informacija</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון לחזרה למיקום העמוד מתצוגת המידע</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction pour retourner sur la position de la page depuis la vue d'infos</li>
          <li lang="et">Parandus, et infovaatest naasmisel jõuda samale leheküljele</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Corrección para regresar a la página previa desde la vista de información</li>
          <li lang="es">Corrección para regresar a la página previa desde la vista de información</li>
          <li lang="eo">Korekto por reveni de la informa vido al la paĝa pozicio</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix for returning to the page position from the info view</li>
          <li lang="el">Επιδιόρθωση για επιστροφή στη θέση της σελίδας από την προβολή πληροφοριών</li>
          <li lang="de">Korrektur für die Rückkehr zur Seitenposition aus der Info-Ansicht</li>
          <li lang="cs">Oprava pro návrat na polohu na stránce ze zobrazení informací</li>
          <li lang="ar">إصلاح للعودة إلى موضع الصفحة من عرض المعلومات</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-09-30" version="1.1.0">
      <description>
        <p>This release has some new features, fixes and new translations:</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本包含一些新的特性、修復以及翻譯：</p>
        <p lang="zh">这个版本包含了新的特性、修复以及翻译：</p>
        <p lang="vi">Bản phát hành này có một số tính năng mới, bản sửa lỗi và bản dịch mới:</p>
        <p lang="uk">У цьому випуску — нові функції, виправлення помилок і нові переклади:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu güncelleme kimi yeni özellikler, düzeltmeler ve çeviriler içeriyor:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna utgåva har några nya funktioner, fixar och nya översättningar:</p>
        <p lang="sc">Custa versione tenet carchi funtzionalidade noa, curretziones de errores e incluet bortaduras noas:</p>
        <p lang="ru">В этом релизе — новые функции, исправления ошибок и переводы:</p>
        <p lang="ro">Această versiune are câteva funcții noi, remedieri și noi traduceri:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão possui novas funcionalidades, correções e novas traduções:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Este lançamento tem algumas funcionalidades novas, correções e inclui novas traduções:</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie ma kilka nowych funkcji, poprawek i nowych tłumaczeń:</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースは、いくつかの新機能と修正、新しい翻訳を含んでいます:</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa release contiene alcune nuove funzionalità, correzioni e nuove traduzioni:</p>
        <p lang="is">Þessi útgáfa er með nokkra nýja eiginleika, lagfæringar og nýjar þýðingar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Ti-ci version have quelc nov functiones, correctiones e traductiones:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini memiliki beberapa fitur baru, perbaikan dan terjemahan baru:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovo izdanje sadrži poneke nove funkcije, ispravke i nove prijevode:</p>
        <p lang="he">במהדורה זו יש מגוון יכולות חדשות, תיקונים ותרגומים חדשים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version apporte quelques nouveautés, corrections et nouvelles traductions :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tässä versiossa on joitakin uusia ominaisuuksia, korjauksia ja uusia käännöksiä:</p>
        <p lang="et">Sellel versioonil on mõned uued funktsioonid, parandused ja tõlked:</p>
        <p lang="es_MX">Esta nueva actualización tiene algunas nuevas funcionalidades, arreglaos y nuevas traducciones:</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta publicación incorpora funciones nuevas, correcciones y traducciones actualizadas:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Ĉi tiu eldono havas novajn funkciojn, korektojn kaj novajn tradukojn:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">This release has some new features, fixes and new translations:</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση έχει κάποια νέα χαρακτηριστικά, επιδιορθώσεις και νέες μεταφράσεις:</p>
        <p lang="de">Dieses Release hat ein paar neue Funktionen, Korrekturen und neue Übersetzungen:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání má některé nové vlastnosti, opravy a nové překlady:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquest llançament incorpora prestacions noves, algunes correccions i traduccions actualitzades:</p>
        <p lang="be">Гэты выпуск мае некаторыя новыя функцыі, выпраўленні і новыя пераклады:</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذا الإصدار به مزايا وإصلاح وترجمات جديدة:</p>
        <p>New Features:</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">新特性：</p>
        <p lang="zh">新特性：</p>
        <p lang="vi">Các tính năng mới:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Нові функції:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Yeni Özellikler:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Nya funktioner:</p>
        <p lang="sc">Funtzionalidades noas:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Новые возможности:</p>
        <p lang="ro">Funcții noi:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Novas funcionalidades:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Novas funcionalidades:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Nowe funkcje:</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Nye funksjoner:</p>
        <p lang="ja">新機能:</p>
        <p lang="it">Nuove funzionalità:</p>
        <p lang="is">Nýir eiginleikar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Nov functiones:</p>
        <p lang="id">Fitur Baru:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Nove funkcije:</p>
        <p lang="he">תכונות חדשות:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Nouvelles fonctionnalités :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Uudet ominaisuudet:</p>
        <p lang="et">Uued funktsioonid:</p>
        <p lang="es_MX">Nuevas funcionalidades:</p>
        <p lang="es">Prestaciones nuevas:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Novaj Trajtoj:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">New features:</p>
        <p lang="el">Νέα χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
        <p lang="de">Neue Features:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Nové vlastnosti:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Funcionalitats noves:</p>
        <p lang="be">Новыя функцыі:</p>
        <p lang="ar">مزايا جديدة:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Right click a selected word and look up its meaning in an online dictionary</li>
          <li lang="zh_TW">在選取的文字上按右鍵，在線上字典查詢它的意思</li>
          <li lang="zh">右击选中的词，可以通过在线词典查看其含义</li>
          <li lang="vi">Nhấp chuột phải vào một từ đã chọn và tra nghĩa của nó bằng từ điển trực tuyến</li>
          <li lang="uk">Натисніть правою кнопкою миші на виділеному слові, щоб дізнатися його значення в онлайн-словнику</li>
          <li lang="tr">Vurgulanmış bir kelimeye sağ tıklayarak çevrimiçi sözlükte anlamına bakabilirsiniz</li>
          <li lang="sv">Högerklicka på ett valt ord och slå upp dess betydelse i en online-ordlista</li>
          <li lang="sc">Incarca cun sa tecla destra una paràula ischertada e abbàida su significadu suo in unu ditzionàriu in lìnia</li>
          <li lang="ru">Нажмите правой кнопкой мыши на выделенном слове, чтобы узнать его значение в онлайн-словаре</li>
          <li lang="ro">Faceți clic dreapta pe un cuvânt selectat și căutați semnificația acestuia într-un dicționar online</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Clicar com botão direito sobre uma palavra selecionada busca a sua definição online</li>
          <li lang="pt">Clique com o botão direito do rato numa palavra selecionada e veja o seu significado utilizando um dicionário na Internet</li>
          <li lang="pl">Kliknij wybrane słowo prawym przyciskiem myszy i sprawdź jego znaczenie w słowniku online</li>
          <li lang="ja">選択した単語を右クリックして、意味をオンライン辞書で調べる</li>
          <li lang="it">Clicca con il tasto destro su una parola selezionata e ricercane il significato in un dizionario online</li>
          <li lang="is">Hægri-smelltu á valið orð og flettu merkingu þess upp í orðasafni á netinu</li>
          <li lang="id">Klik kanan kata yang dipilih dan cari maknanya dalam kamus online</li>
          <li lang="hr">Desni klik na odabranu riječ za pretraživanje značenja u internetskom rječniku</li>
          <li lang="he">ניתן ללחוץ על מילה עם כפתור ימני כדי לחפש את משמעותה במילון מקוון</li>
          <li lang="fr">Clic droit sur un mot sélectionné cherche sa définition dans un dictionnaire en ligne</li>
          <li lang="fi">Napsauttamalla hiiren oikeaa painiketta valitun sanan päällä pystyt etsimään sen määritelmän verkkosanakirjasta</li>
          <li lang="et">Vaatamaks sõna tähendust onlain sõnastikust tee valitud sõnal paremklõps</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Clic derecho en alguna palabra seleccionada para buscar su significado en línea</li>
          <li lang="es">Pulse con el botón secundario del ratón en una palabra seleccionada y consulte su significado en un diccionario en línea</li>
          <li lang="eo">Dekstre alklaku elektitan vorton por kontroli ĝian signifon en interreta vortaro</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Right click a selected word and look up its meaning in an online dictionary</li>
          <li lang="el">Κάντε δεξί κλικ σε μια επιλεγμένη λέξη και αναζητήστε τη σημασία της σε ένα διαδικτυακό λεξικό</li>
          <li lang="de">Markieren Sie ein Wort und klicken Sie mit der rechten Maustaste, um dessen Bedeutung in einem Online-Wörterbuch nachzuschlagen</li>
          <li lang="cs">Klepnutí pravým tlačítkem myši na vybrané slovo a vyhledání jeho významu v internetovém slovníku</li>
          <li lang="ca">Feu clic dret a un mot seleccionat i trobeu-ne el significat a un diccionari en línia</li>
          <li lang="be">Пстрыкніце правай кнопкай па абраных слове і знайдзіце яго значэнне ў анлайн слоўніку</li>
          <li lang="ar">انقر باليمنى على الكلمة المختارة وابحث عن معناها في معجم على النت</li>
          <li>Added option to customize highlight colour</li>
          <li lang="zh_TW">加入自訂高亮度標示顏色的選項</li>
          <li lang="zh">增加了自定义高亮颜色的选项</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано можливість вибору кольору виділення</li>
          <li lang="tr">Vurgu rengini kişiselleştirme seçeneği eklendi</li>
          <li lang="sv">Tillagt alternativ för att anpassa markeringens färg</li>
          <li lang="sc">Annanta un'optzione pro personalizare su colore de evidentziatzione</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлена возможность выбрать цвет выделения</li>
          <li lang="ro">Opțiune adăugată pentru a personaliza culoarea evidențiată</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Opção para customizar a cor do marca-texto adicionada</li>
          <li lang="pt">Adicionada uma opção nas preferências para personalizar a cor de destaque</li>
          <li lang="pl">Dodano opcję dostosowania koloru podświetlenia</li>
          <li lang="ja">ハイライトされた色をカスタマイズするオプションを追加</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta opzione per personalizzare il colore dell'evidenziatore</li>
          <li lang="is">Bætt við kjörstillingu til að sérsníða áherslulitun</li>
          <li lang="id">Menambahkan opsi untuk menyesuaikan warna sorotan</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana opcija za prilagođavanje boje za isticanje</li>
          <li lang="he">נוספה אפשרות לשנות את צבע ההדגשה</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout d'une option pour personnaliser la couleur de surlignage</li>
          <li lang="fi">Korostuksen väriä on nyt mahdollista muuttaa</li>
          <li lang="et">Lisati võimalus esiletõstu värvi kohandamiseks</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Añadida la opción para cambiar el color del subrayado</li>
          <li lang="es">Se añadió una opción para personalizar el color del resalte</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldonis opcion por personecigi reliefigan koloron</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Added option to customise highlight colour</li>
          <li lang="el">Προστέθηκε επιλογή για την προσαρμογή του χρώματος επισήμανσης</li>
          <li lang="de">Option zur Anpassung der Hervorhebungsfarbe hinzugefügt</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána volby pro přizpůsobení barvy zvýraznění</li>
          <li lang="ca">S’ha afegit una opció per a personalitzar el color de ressaltament</li>
          <li lang="be">Дададзеная магчымасць налады колеру падсвятлення</li>
          <li lang="ar">ميزة مضافة لتخصيص لون الإبراز</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Fixes:</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">修復：</p>
        <p lang="zh">修复：</p>
        <p lang="vi">Sửa lỗi:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Виправлення помилок:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Düzeltmeler:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Fixar:</p>
        <p lang="sc">Acontzos:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Исправления ошибок:</p>
        <p lang="ro">Remedii:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Correções:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Correções:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Poprawki:</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Fikser:</p>
        <p lang="ja">修正:</p>
        <p lang="it">Correzioni:</p>
        <p lang="is">Lagfæringar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Correctiones:</p>
        <p lang="id">Perbaikan:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ispravci:</p>
        <p lang="he">תיקונים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Corrections :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Korjaukset:</p>
        <p lang="et">Parandused:</p>
        <p lang="es_MX">Mejoramientos:</p>
        <p lang="es">Correcciones:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Korektoj:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Fixes:</p>
        <p lang="el">Διορθώσεις:</p>
        <p lang="de">Fehlerbehebungen:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Opravy:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Correccions:</p>
        <p lang="be">Выпраўленні:</p>
        <p lang="ar">إصلاحات:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Prevent Bookworm from opening links like HTTP, FTP etc. and use the default browser to open them</li>
          <li lang="zh_TW">避免 Bookworm 開啟連結，例如 HTTP、FTP 等，並使用預設瀏覽器開啟它們</li>
          <li lang="zh">阻止书虫打开HTTP、FTP等超链接，改用默认浏览器打开</li>
          <li lang="vi">Ngăn Bookworm mở các liên kết như HTTP, FTP, v.v. và sử dụng trình duyệt mặc định để mở chúng</li>
          <li lang="uk">Посилання на зразок HTTP, FTP та подібні тепер відкриваються не в Bookworm, а в переглядачі</li>
          <li lang="tr">HTTP, FTP gibi linkleri Bookworm'un açmasını engelleyerek, onlar için varsayılan tarayıcıyı kullan</li>
          <li lang="sv">Förhindra att Bookworm öppnar länkar som HTTP, FTP etc. och använd standardwebbläsaren för att öppna dem</li>
          <li lang="sc">Non permìtere a Bookworm de abèrrere ligàmenes comente a HTTP, FTP etz. e imprea s'esploradore (browser) predefinidu pro los abèrrere</li>
          <li lang="ru">Ссылки вроде HTTP, FTP и так далее теперь открываются не в Bookworm, а в браузере по умолчанию</li>
          <li lang="ro">Împiedicați Bookworm să deschidă linkuri precum HTTP, FTP etc. și utilizați browserul implicit pentru a le deschide</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Impede Bookworm de abrir ligações como HTTP, FTP, etc., abrindo-os no navegador padrão</li>
          <li lang="pt">Impedir que o Bookworm abra hiperligações como HTTP, FTP, etc. e utilize o navegador padrão para o abrir</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zapobiegaj otwieraniu przez Bookworma linków takich jak HTTP, FTP itp. I otwieraj je za pomocą domyślnej przeglądarki</li>
          <li lang="ja">HTTP や FTS などのリンクを、Bookworm ではなくデフォルトのブラウザで開くように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Impedire a Bookworm di aprire collegamenti come HTTP, FTP ecc. ed utilizzare il browser predefinito per questi</li>
          <li lang="is">Komið í veg fyrir að Bookworm opni tengla á borð við HTTP, FTP, o.s.frv. og nota freka sjálfgefinn vafra til þess</li>
          <li lang="id">Cegah Bookworm membuka tautan seperti HTTP, FTP dll. gunakan browser bawaan untuk membukanya</li>
          <li lang="hr">Spriječi otvaranje poveznica kao što su HTTP, FTP itd. u Bibliofilu. Za otvaranje tih poveznica koristi standardi preglednik</li>
          <li lang="he">למנוע מ־Bookworm לפתוח קישורים כגון HTTP,‏ FTP וכו׳ ולהשתמש בדפדפן כדי לפתוח אותם</li>
          <li lang="fr">Empêche Bookworm d'ouvrir des liens HTTP, FTP, etc. et utilise le navigateur par défaut pour les ouvrir</li>
          <li lang="fi">Avaa HTTP, FTP, yms. -linkit WWW-selaimessa Bookwormin sijasta</li>
          <li lang="et">Takista Bookwormil HTTP, FTP jt. linkide avamist ning kasuta nende avamiseks vaikesirvijat</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Usar el navegador por defecto para abrir enlaces</li>
          <li lang="es">Evitar que Bookworm abra enlaces como HTTP y FTP y utilizar el navegador predeterminado para hacerlo</li>
          <li lang="eo">Igi, ke Bookworm ne malfermos ligilojn de HTTP, FTP ktp kaj ke la implicita TTT-legilo malfermos tiajn ligilojn</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Prevent Bookworm from opening links like HTTP, FTP etc. and use the default browser to open them</li>
          <li lang="el">Αποτρέψτε το Bookworm από το να ανοίγει συνδέσμους όπως HTTP, FTP κτλ και χρησιμοποιείστε το προεπιλεγμένο πρόγραμμα αναζήτησης για να τους ανοίξετε</li>
          <li lang="de">Verhindern Sie, dass Bookworm Links wie HTTP, FTP usw. öffnet und verwenden Sie den Standardbrowser, um sie zu öffnen</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zabránění Bookwormu v otevírání odkazů, jako jsou HTTP, FTP a další, a použití výchozího prohlížeče k jejich otevření</li>
          <li lang="ca">El Bookworm evita obrir enllaços HTTP i FTP, entre d’altres; en comptes d’això, s’utilitza el navegador per defecte</li>
          <li lang="be">Прадухіляе Bookworm ад адкрыцця спасылак, такіх як HTTP, FTP і іншых, і выкарыстоўвае агаданы аглядальнік, каб адкрыць іх</li>
          <li lang="ar">منع دودة الكتب من فتح روابط مثل HTTP وFTP وغيرها، واستعمل المتصفح التلقائية لفتحها</li>
          <li>Fixed an issue where the lines overlapped for the first couple of pages in the book</li>
          <li lang="zh_TW">修復了書籍中前幾頁列重疊的問題</li>
          <li lang="zh">修复了书籍前几页的行重叠问题</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено проблему перекривання ліній на парі перших сторінок книги</li>
          <li lang="tr">Kitabın ilk bir kaç sayfasında satırların üst üste gelme sorunu düzeltildi</li>
          <li lang="sv">Fixade ett problem där raderna överlappade varandra de första par sidorna i boken</li>
          <li lang="sc">Curretu un'errore in ue sas lìnias andabant una in subra de s'àtera in sa prima pàia de pàginas de su libru</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлена проблема, когда перекрывались линии на паре первых страниц книги</li>
          <li lang="ro">S-a rezolvat o problemă în care liniile se suprapuneau pentru primele două pagini din carte</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Corrigido um problema onde as linhas das primeiras páginas de um livro se sobrepunham</li>
          <li lang="pt">Corrigido um problema em que as linhas se sobrepunham nas primeiras páginas dos livros</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawiono problem, w którym linie nakładały się na pierwsze kilka stron książki</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Fikset et problem der linjene overlappet de første sidene av en bok</li>
          <li lang="ja">本の最初の数ページの行が重なってしまう問題を修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Risolto un problema in cui le linee si sovrapponevano nelle prime pagine di un libro</li>
          <li lang="is">Lagfært vandamál þegar línur sköruðust á fyrstu tveimur síðum bókar</li>
          <li lang="id">Memperbaiki masalah di mana garis tumpang tindih untuk beberapa halaman pertama dalam buku</li>
          <li lang="hr">Popravljen problem preklapanja redaka u prvim stranicama knjige</li>
          <li lang="he">תוקנה בעיה שהשורות חופפות בעמודים הראשונים של הספר</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction d'un problème où les lignes se chevauchaient pour les deux premières pages du livre</li>
          <li lang="et">Parandati viga, kus raamatu esimestel lehekülgedel tekkis ridade ülekattumine</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Solución al problema de las lineas se encimaban en las primeras paginas del libro</li>
          <li lang="es">Corregido un problema en el que las líneas se superponían en el primer par de páginas de un libro</li>
          <li lang="eo">Korektis problemon pri interkovrado de linioj en la unuaj du paĝoj en libro</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fixed an issue where the lines overlapped for the first couple of pages in the book</li>
          <li lang="el">Διορθώθηκε ένα πρόβλημα όπου οι γραμμές επικαλύπτονται για τις πρώτες σελίδες στο βιβλίο</li>
          <li lang="de">Es wurde ein Problem behoben, bei dem sich die Zeilen bei den ersten paar Seiten des Buches überlappen</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opraven problém s překrýváním řádků na několika prvních stranách v knize</li>
          <li lang="be">Выпраўлена праблема перакрыцця радкоў на першай пары старонак у кнізе</li>
          <li lang="ar">إصلاح مشكلة تداخل السطر في الصفحتين الأوليين في الكتاب</li>
          <li>Use of GResource to speed up loading of icons, scripts, etc.</li>
          <li lang="zh_TW">使用 GResource 來加速載入圖示、腳本等等。</li>
          <li lang="zh">使用GResource加速图标、脚本等的加载。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Використання GResource для прискорення завантаження піктограм, сценаріїв тощо.</li>
          <li lang="tr">GResource kullanılarak simge, betik vb. yükleme hızı arttırıldı.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Användning av GResource för att snabba upp laddning av ikoner, skript, etc.</li>
          <li lang="sc">Impreu de GResource pro illestrare su carrigamentu de iconas, testos de còdighes (scripts), etz.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Использование GResource для ускорения загрузки иконок, текстов и остального.</li>
          <li lang="ro">Utilizarea GResource pentru a accelera încărcarea pictogramelor, scripturilor etc.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Utiliza GResource para acelerar o carregamento de ícones, scripts, etc.</li>
          <li lang="pt">Utilização do GResource para acelerar o carregamento de ícones, scripts, etc.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Wykorzystanie GResource do przyspieszenia ładowania ikon, skryptów itp.</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Bruk av GResource for å framskynde innlasting av ikoner, skript, osv.</li>
          <li lang="ja">GResource を使用することで、アイコンやスクリプトなどの読み込みを高速化</li>
          <li lang="it">Utilizzo di GResource per velocizzare il caricamento di icone, scripts, ecc.</li>
          <li lang="is">Notkun GResource til að hraða hleðslu táknmynda, keyrslu á skriftum, o.s.frv.</li>
          <li lang="ie">Usa de GResource por accelerar carga de icones, scriptes etc.</li>
          <li lang="id">Penggunaan GResource untuk mempercepat pemuatan ikon, skrip, dll.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Koristi se GResource za brže učitavanje ikona, skripta itd.</li>
          <li lang="he">שימוש ב־GResource כדי להאיץ טעינת סמלים, סקריפטים וכו׳</li>
          <li lang="fr">Utilisation de GResource pour accélérer le chargement des icônes, des scripts, etc.</li>
          <li lang="et">GResource'i kasutamine ikoonide, skriptide jms. laadimise kiirendamiseks.</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Uso de GResource para acelerar el cargado de iconos, scripts, etc.</li>
          <li lang="es">Uso de «GResource» para acelerar la carga de iconos, guiones («scripts»), etc.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Uzo de GResource por rapidigi ŝargon de ikonoj, programetoj ktp.</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Use of GResource to speed up loading of icons, scripts, etc.</li>
          <li lang="el">Χρήση του GResource για την επιτάχυνση της φόρτωσης εικονιδίων, δεσμών ενεργειών κλπ.</li>
          <li lang="de">Verwendung von GResource zur Beschleunigung des Ladens von Symbolen, Skripten usw.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Použití GResource ke zrychlení nahrávání ikon, skriptů atd.</li>
          <li lang="ca">En fer servir el GResource s’accelera la càrrega d’icones, scripts i altres recursos</li>
          <li lang="be">Выкарыстоўваць GResource для паскарэння загрузкі іконак, сцэнароў і іншага.</li>
          <li lang="ar">استعمل GResource لتسريع تحميل الأيقونات والسكريبتات وغيرها.</li>
          <li>Some minor CSS compatibility with Juno</li>
          <li lang="zh_TW">一些 CSS 與 Juno 相容性的小問題</li>
          <li lang="zh">一些CSS和Juno兼容性的小问题</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено незначні проблеми сумісності CSS з Juno</li>
          <li lang="tr">Juno'ya uygunluk için kimi CSS düzeltmeleri</li>
          <li lang="sv">Vissa mindre CSS-kompatibilitet med Juno</li>
          <li lang="sc">Carchi cumpatibilidade minore de CSS cun Juno</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлены некоторые небольшие проблемы совместимости CSS с Juno</li>
          <li lang="ro">Unele compatibilități CSS minore cu Juno</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Pequenos ajustes no CSS para compatibilidade com Juno</li>
          <li lang="pt">Alguma compatibilidade CSS com o Juno</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nieznaczna kompatybilność CSS z Juno</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Små CSS-tilpasninger for kompatibilitet med Juno</li>
          <li lang="ja">Juno との CSS の互換性</li>
          <li lang="it">Minima compatibilità CSS con Juno</li>
          <li lang="is">Ýmis minniháttar CSS-samhæfni við Juno</li>
          <li lang="id">Beberapa kompatibilitas CSS kecil dengan Juno</li>
          <li lang="hr">Poneke manje CSS kompatibilnosti s Juno</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון מזערי לתאימות CSS מול Juno</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajustements mineurs de la compatibilité du CSS avec Juno</li>
          <li lang="et">Mõningane CSSi ühilduvus Junoga</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Algunos cambios menores en la compatibilidad del CSS con Juno</li>
          <li lang="es">Alguna compatibilidad menor de CSS con Juno</li>
          <li lang="eo">Kelkaj etaj kongruigoj de CSS kun Juno</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Some minor CSS compatibility with Juno</li>
          <li lang="el">Κάποια μικρή συμβατότητα CSS με το Juno</li>
          <li lang="de">Einige kleinere CSS-Kompatibilität mit Juno</li>
          <li lang="cs">Menší slučitelnost CSS s Juno</li>
          <li lang="ca">Canvis petits al CSS per a compatibilitat amb Juno</li>
          <li lang="be">Некаторая нязначная CSS-сумяшчальнасць з Juno</li>
          <li lang="ar">بعض أنماط العرض CSS تتوافق مع Juno</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2018-02-11">
      <description>
        <p>Right to Left Reading</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">從右到左閱讀</p>
        <p lang="zh">从右往左阅读</p>
        <p lang="vi">Đọc từ phải sang trái</p>
        <p lang="uk">Читання справа наліво</p>
        <p lang="tr">Sağdan sola okuma</p>
        <p lang="sv">Höger till vänster läsning</p>
        <p lang="sc">Leghidura dae destra a manca</p>
        <p lang="ru">Чтение справа налево</p>
        <p lang="ro">Lectură de la dreapta la stânga</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Leitura da direita para esquerda</p>
        <p lang="pt">Leitura da direita para a esquerda</p>
        <p lang="pl">Czytanie od prawej do lewej</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Lesning høyre til venstre</p>
        <p lang="mr">उजवीकडून डावीकडे वाचन</p>
        <p lang="ja">右から左に文字が書かれた本に対応</p>
        <p lang="it">Lettura da destra a sinistra</p>
        <p lang="is">Lestur frá hægri-til-vinstri</p>
        <p lang="ie">Letion dextri-al-levul</p>
        <p lang="id">Membaca dari Kanan ke Kiri</p>
        <p lang="hr">Čitanje s desna nalijevo</p>
        <p lang="he">קריאה מימין לשמאל</p>
        <p lang="fr">Lecture de droite à gauche</p>
        <p lang="et">Paremalt vasakule lugemine</p>
        <p lang="es_MX">Lectura de Derecha a Izquierda</p>
        <p lang="es">Lectura de derecha a izquierda</p>
        <p lang="eo">Dedekstre-Maldekstren-Legreĝimo</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Right to Left Reading</p>
        <p lang="el">Δεξιά προς αριστερά ανάγνωση</p>
        <p lang="de">Rechts nach linkes Darstellung</p>
        <p lang="cs">Čtení zprava doleva</p>
        <p lang="ca">Lectura de dreta a esquerra</p>
        <p lang="be">Чытанне справа на лева</p>
        <p lang="ar">قراءة من اليمين إلى اليسار</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Support for right-to-left script</li>
          <li lang="zh_TW">支援從右到左的書寫</li>
          <li lang="zh">支持从右往左的脚本</li>
          <li lang="uk">Підтримка текстів справа наліво</li>
          <li lang="tr">Sağdan sola dizgi için destek</li>
          <li lang="sv">Stöd för höger till vänster skript</li>
          <li lang="sc">Suportu pro sa leghidura dae destra a manca</li>
          <li lang="ru">Поддержка текстов справа налево</li>
          <li lang="ro">Suport pentru scriptul de la dreapta la stânga</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Suporte para scripts de leitura direita-esquerda</li>
          <li lang="pt">Suporte à leitura de direita para a esquerda</li>
          <li lang="pl">Obsługa skryptu od prawej do lewej</li>
          <li lang="ja">RTL のスクリプトへの対応</li>
          <li lang="it">Supporto per lettura da destra a sinistra</li>
          <li lang="is">Bætir við stuðningi fyrir lestur frá hægri-til-vinstri</li>
          <li lang="id">Dukungan untuk skrip kanan-ke-kiri</li>
          <li lang="hr">Podrška za pisma koja se pišu s desna nalijevo</li>
          <li lang="he">תמיכה בסוגי כתב מימין לשמאל (כמו עברית)</li>
          <li lang="fr">Prise en charge du script de lecture de doite à gauche</li>
          <li lang="fi">Tuki oikealta vasemmalle skriptille</li>
          <li lang="et">Paremalt vasakule skripti tugi</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Soporte para el script rigth-to-left</li>
          <li lang="es">Compatibilidad con escrituras de derecha a izquierda</li>
          <li lang="eo">Subteno de dedekstre-maldekstren-skribsistemoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Support for right-to-left script</li>
          <li lang="el">Υποστήριξη για δεξιά προς τα αριστερά γραφή</li>
          <li lang="de">Unterstützung für Rechts-nach-Links-Texte</li>
          <li lang="cs">Podpora pro skript zprava doleva</li>
          <li lang="ca">Compatibilitat amb escritures de direcció de dreta a esquerra</li>
          <li lang="be">Падтрымка пісьма справа на лева</li>
          <li lang="ar">دعم الكتابة من اليمين إلى اليسار</li>
          <li>A shiny new icon and new cover images</li>
          <li lang="zh_TW">嶄新的圖示和新的封面圖片</li>
          <li lang="zh">崭新的图标和封面图</li>
          <li lang="uk">Нова яскрава піктограма і нові зображення обкладинок</li>
          <li lang="tr">Gözalıcı yeni simge ve kapak resimleri</li>
          <li lang="sv">En skinande ny ikon och nya omslagsbilder</li>
          <li lang="sc">Una icona noa e immàgines de cobertedda noas</li>
          <li lang="ru">Новая яркая иконка и новые изображения обложек</li>
          <li lang="ro">O nouă pictogramă strălucitoare și noi imagini de copertă</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Um novo ícone e novas imagens de capa</li>
          <li lang="pt">Um novo ícone e novas imagens de capas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nowiutka ikona oraz nowe okładki</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Skinnende nytt ikon og nye omslagsbilder</li>
          <li lang="ja">一新されたアイコンとカバー画像</li>
          <li lang="it">Una scintillante nuova icona e nuove immagini di copertina</li>
          <li lang="is">Glansandi ný táknmynd og nyjar forsíðumyndir</li>
          <li lang="id">Ikon baru yang mengkilap dan gambar sampul baru</li>
          <li lang="hr">Potpuno nova ikona i nova slika naslovnice</li>
          <li lang="he">סמל ותמונות כותרת חדישים</li>
          <li lang="fr">Une nouvelle icône resplendissante et de nouvelles images de couverture</li>
          <li lang="fi">Kiiltävä uusi kuvake ja uusia kansikuvia</li>
          <li lang="et">Uus särav ikoon ja uus kaanepilt</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Nuevo icono y nueva portada</li>
          <li lang="es">Un nuevo icono resplandeciente y nuevas imágenes de portada</li>
          <li lang="eo">Nova bela ikono kaj novaj kovrilaj bildoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">A shiny new icon and new cover images</li>
          <li lang="el">Ένα λαμπερό νέο εικονίδιο και νέες εικόνες καλύμματος</li>
          <li lang="de">Ein glänzend neues Icon und neue Coverbilder</li>
          <li lang="cs">Blýskající se nová ikona a nové obrázky obalů</li>
          <li lang="ca">Una icona nova i imatges de coberta renovades</li>
          <li lang="be">Бліскучы новы значок і новыя выявы вокладкі</li>
          <li lang="ar">أيقونة لامعة وصورة غلاف جديدتين</li>
          <li>Better support for EPUB table of contents</li>
          <li lang="zh_TW">對 EPUB 目錄較好的支援</li>
          <li lang="zh">对EPUB目录支持得更好了</li>
          <li lang="vi">Hỗ trợ tốt hơn cho mục lục của EPUB</li>
          <li lang="uk">Краща підтримка змісту книг в EPUB</li>
          <li lang="tr">EPUB, içindekiler için daha iyi destek</li>
          <li lang="sv">Bättre stöd för EPUB innehållsförteckning</li>
          <li lang="sc">Unu suportu megioradu pro sas tabellas de cuntenutos de sos EPUBs</li>
          <li lang="ru">Улучшена поддержка содержания книг в EPUB</li>
          <li lang="ro">Suport mai bun pentru cuprinsul EPUB</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Melhor suporte para indexes EPUB</li>
          <li lang="pt">Melhor suporte a Índices EPUB</li>
          <li lang="pl">Lepsze obsługa spisu treści dla formatów EPUB</li>
          <li lang="ja">EPUB の表の内容への対応を強化</li>
          <li lang="it">Miglior supporto per tavole dei contenuti EPUB</li>
          <li lang="is">Betri stuðningur við efnisyfirlit í EPUB</li>
          <li lang="id">Dukungan yang lebih baik untuk daftar isi EPUB</li>
          <li lang="hr">Bolja podrška za EPUB kazalo</li>
          <li lang="he">תמיכה טובה בתוכן עניינים של EPUB</li>
          <li lang="fr">Meilleure prise en charge pour la table des matières du format EPUB</li>
          <li lang="fi">Perempi tuki EPUB-tiedostojen sisällysluetteloille</li>
          <li lang="et">Parem tugi EPUB vormingu sisukorrale</li>
          <li lang="es_MX">Soporte para tablas de contenido EPUB mejorado</li>
          <li lang="es">Mejor compatibilidad con sumarios de libros EPUB</li>
          <li lang="eo">Pli bona subteno de EPUB-enhavtabeloj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Better support for EPUB table of contents</li>
          <li lang="el">Καλύτερη υποστήριξη για τον πίνακα περιεχομένων EPUB</li>
          <li lang="de">Bessere Unterstützung des EPUB-Inhaltsverzeichnisses</li>
          <li lang="cs">Lepší podpora pro obsah EPUB</li>
          <li lang="ca">Es processen de millor manera les taules de contingut dels EPUB</li>
          <li lang="be">Палепшаная падтрымка зместу EPUB</li>
          <li lang="ar">دعم أفضل لجدول محتويات EPUB</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.5" date="2017-12-10">
      <description>
        <p>Annotations and two page views</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">註釋和雙頁視圖</p>
        <p lang="zh">注释和双页视图</p>
        <p lang="uk">Примітки та двосторінкове подання</p>
        <p lang="tr">Açıklama ve çift sayfa görünümü</p>
        <p lang="sv">Anteckningar och två sidvyer</p>
        <p lang="sc">Notas e vistas a duas pàginas</p>
        <p lang="ru">Аннотации и просмотр двух страниц</p>
        <p lang="ro">Etichetele Adnotării</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Anotações e visualização em duas páginas</p>
        <p lang="pt">Visualizações de anotações e página dupla</p>
        <p lang="pl">Przypisy i widok dwóch stron</p>
        <p lang="ja">注釈と 2 ページごとのビュー</p>
        <p lang="it">Annotazioni e visualizzazione su due pagine</p>
        <p lang="is">Glósur og tveggja-síðna sýnir</p>
        <p lang="id">Anotasi dan dua tampilan halaman</p>
        <p lang="hr">Napomene i prikazi dviju stranica</p>
        <p lang="he">הערות ותצוגות שני עמודים</p>
        <p lang="fr">Annotations et vue double page</p>
        <p lang="fi">Huomautukset ja kahden sivun näkymät</p>
        <p lang="et">Annotatsioonid ja kahe lehe vaated</p>
        <p lang="es_MX">Vistas de anotaciones y de página doble</p>
        <p lang="es">Vistas de anotaciones y de página doble</p>
        <p lang="eo">Notoj kaj dupaĝa legreĝimo</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Annotations and two page views</p>
        <p lang="el">Σχολιασμοί και προβολές δύο σελιδών</p>
        <p lang="de">Anmerkungen und Doppelseitenansicht</p>
        <p lang="cs">Vysvětlivky a zobrazení na dvě strany</p>
        <p lang="ca">Anotacions y visualitzacions de dues pàgines</p>
        <p lang="be">Від анатацый і дзвюх старонак</p>
        <p lang="ar">عرض التعليقات التوضيحية و صفحتين</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9" date="2017-07-23">
      <description>
        <p>Support for MOBI format and UX improvements</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">支援 MOBI 格式和改進使用者體驗</p>
        <p lang="zh">支持MOBI格式，改进用户体验</p>
        <p lang="vi">Hỗ trợ định dạng MOBI và cải tiến UX</p>
        <p lang="uk">Підтримка формату MOBI та поліпшення зручності</p>
        <p lang="tr">MOBI için destek ve kullanıcı deneyimi geliştirmeleri</p>
        <p lang="sv">Stöd för MOBI-format och UX-förbättringar</p>
        <p lang="sc">Suportu de su formadu MOBI e megiorias de s'esperièntzia de s'impreadore (UX)</p>
        <p lang="ru">Поддержка формата MOBI и улучшения UX</p>
        <p lang="ro">Suport pentru îmbunătățirea formatului MOBI și UX</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Suporte para o formato MOBI e melhorias da interface</p>
        <p lang="pt">Suporte ao formato MOBI e melhorias na experiência do utilizador</p>
        <p lang="pl">Obsługa formatu MOBI oraz ulepszenia UX</p>
        <p lang="ja">MOBI 形式への対応と、UX の改善</p>
        <p lang="it">Supporto per formato MOBI e migliorie UX</p>
        <p lang="is">Stuðningur við MOBI-snið og endurbætur á viðmóti</p>
        <p lang="id">Dukungan untuk format MOBI dan peningkatan UX</p>
        <p lang="hr">Podrška za MOBI format i poboljšanja korisničkog doživljaja</p>
        <p lang="he">תמיכה בתסדיר MOBI ושיפורי חווית משתמש</p>
        <p lang="fr">Prise en charge du format MOBI et améliorations de l'interface</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tuki MOBI formaatille ja UX parannuksia</p>
        <p lang="et">MOBI vormingu tugi ja kasutajakogemuse täiustused</p>
        <p lang="es_MX">Compatibilidad con el formato MOBI y mejoras de experiencia de usuario</p>
        <p lang="es">Compatibilidad con el formato MOBI y mejoras de experiencia de usuario</p>
        <p lang="eo">Subteno de dosierformo MOBI; plibonigoj de fasado</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Support for MOBI format and UX improvements</p>
        <p lang="el">Υποστήριξη για τη MOBI format και βελτιώσεις ΕΧ</p>
        <p lang="de">Unterstützung für das MOBI-Format und UX-Verbesserungen</p>
        <p lang="cs">Podpora pro formát MOBI a vylepšení UX</p>
        <p lang="ca">Compatibilitat amb el format MOBI i millores d’experiència d’usuari</p>
        <p lang="be">Падтрымка фармату MOBI і паляпшэнні UX</p>
        <p lang="ar">دعم صيغة MOBI و تحسين UX</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-06-18" version="0.8">
      <description>
        <p>UX improvements for list view and other preference customizations</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">改進清單視圖和其他偏好設定的使用者體驗</p>
        <p lang="zh">改进列表视图和其他自定义选项的用户体验</p>
        <p lang="uk">Поліпшено зручність подання списку книг та інші налаштування</p>
        <p lang="tr">Liste görünümü için deneyim geliştirmesi ve kişiselleştirme seçenekleri</p>
        <p lang="sv">UX-förbättringar för listvy och andra preferensanpassningar</p>
        <p lang="sc">Megiorias de s'esperièntzia de s'impreadore (UX) pro sa vista de sa lista e àteras personalizaziones de sas preferèntzias</p>
        <p lang="ru">Улучшения UX при просмотре списка книг и другие пользовательские настройки</p>
        <p lang="ro">Îmbunătățiri UX pentru vizualizarea listei și alte personalizări ale preferințelor</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Melhorias na interface para visualização em lista e outras preferencias customizáveis</p>
        <p lang="pt">Melhoramento na experiência do utilizador na Visualização em lista e outras personalizações de preferências</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ulepszenia UX dla widoku listy i innych dostosowań preferencji</p>
        <p lang="ja">リストビューの UX の改善と、その他パフォーマンスのカスタマイズ</p>
        <p lang="it">Migliorie UX per la vista ad elenco ed altre personalizzazioni delle preferenze</p>
        <p lang="is">Endurbætur á viðmóti í listasýn og öðrum sérsniðnum kjörstillingum</p>
        <p lang="id">Penyempurnaan UX untuk tampilan daftar dan kustomisasi preferensi lainnya</p>
        <p lang="hr">Poboljšanja korisničkog doživljaja za prikaz popisa i druga prilagođavanja postavki</p>
        <p lang="he">שיפורי חווית משתמש לתצוגת רשימת ומגוון התאמות אחרות להעדפות</p>
        <p lang="fr">Améliorations de l'interface pour la vue en liste et autres préférences de personnalisation</p>
        <p lang="et">Loendi vaate ja teiste eelistuste kohandamise kasutuskogemuse täiendused</p>
        <p lang="es_MX">Mejoras de la experiencia de usuario para la vista de lista y otras preferencias de personalización</p>
        <p lang="es">Mejoras de la experiencia de usuario para la vista de lista y otras preferencias de personalización</p>
        <p lang="eo">Plibonigoj de fasado pri lista vido kaj aliaj agordeblaĵoj</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">UX improvements for list view and other preference customisations</p>
        <p lang="el">Βελτιώσεις ΕΧ για την προβολή λίστας και άλλες προσαρμογές προτιμήσεων</p>
        <p lang="de">UX-Verbesserungen für die Listenansicht und andere Einstellungsanpassungen</p>
        <p lang="cs">Vylepšení UX pro seznamové zobrazení a jiné úpravy nastavení</p>
        <p lang="ca">Millores d’experiència d’usuari en la visualització de llista i altres personalitzacions de preferències</p>
        <p lang="be">Паляпшэнні UX для выгляду спіса і іншых налад пераваг</p>
        <p lang="ar">تحسين تجربة المستخدم لعرض ا لقائمة وتخصيص الإعدادات الأخرى</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7" date="2017-05-20">
      <description>
        <p>Comics support and UX improvements</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">漫畫支援和改進使用者體驗</p>
        <p lang="zh">支持漫画，改进用户体验</p>
        <p lang="vi">Hỗ trợ truyện tranh và cải tiến UX</p>
        <p lang="uk">Підтримка коміксів та поліпшено зручність</p>
        <p lang="tr">Çizgi roman desteği ve kullanıcı deneyimi geliştirmeleri</p>
        <p lang="sv">Seriestöd och UX förbättringar</p>
        <p lang="sc">Megiorias pro su suportu pro sos fumetos e pro s'esperièntzia de s'impreadore (UX)</p>
        <p lang="ru">Поддержка комиксов и улучшения UX</p>
        <p lang="ro">Suport pentru benzi desenate și îmbunătățiri UX</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Suporte para Quadrinhos e melhorias de interface</p>
        <p lang="pt">Suporte a banda desenhada e melhorias na experiência do utilizador</p>
        <p lang="pl">Obsługa komiksów oraz ulepszenia UX</p>
        <p lang="ja">コミックスへの対応と、UX の改善</p>
        <p lang="it">Supporto per fumetti e migliorie UX</p>
        <p lang="is">Stuðningur við Comics og endurbætur á viðmóti</p>
        <p lang="id">Dukungan komik dan peningkatan UX</p>
        <p lang="hr">Podrška za stripove i poboljšanja korisničkog doživljaja</p>
        <p lang="he">תמיכה בקומיקס ושיפורי חווית משתמש</p>
        <p lang="fr">Prise en charge du format Comics et améliorations de l'interface</p>
        <p lang="et">Koomiksite tugi ja kasutuskogemuse täiustused</p>
        <p lang="es_MX">Compatibilidad con cómics y mejoras de la experiencia de usuario</p>
        <p lang="es">Compatibilidad con cómics y mejoras de la experiencia de usuario</p>
        <p lang="eo">Subteno de bildlibroj; plibonigoj de fasado</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Comics support and UX improvements</p>
        <p lang="el">Υποστήριξη κόμικς και βελτιώσεις ΕΧ</p>
        <p lang="de">Comic-Unterstützung und UX-Verbesserungen</p>
        <p lang="cs">Podpora pro kreslené příběhy a vylepšení UX</p>
        <p lang="ca">Compatibilitat amb còmics i millores d’experiència d’usuari</p>
        <p lang="be">Падтрымка Comics і паляпшэнні UX</p>
        <p lang="ar">دعم القصص المصورة وتجربة المستخدم</p>
        <p lang="ab">Abkhazian</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-05-15" version="0.6">
      <description>
        <p>PDF support and UX improvements</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">PDF 支援和改進使用者體驗</p>
        <p lang="zh">支持PDF，改进用户体验</p>
        <p lang="vi">Hỗ trợ PDF và cải tiến UX</p>
        <p lang="uk">Підтримка формату PDF та поліпшено зручність</p>
        <p lang="tr">PDF desteği ve kullanıcı deneyimi geliştirmeleri</p>
        <p lang="sv">PDF-stöd och UX-förbättringar</p>
        <p lang="sc">Megiorias pro su suportu pro sos PDF e pro s'esperièntzia de s'impreadore (UX)</p>
        <p lang="ru">Поддержка формата PDF и улучшения UX</p>
        <p lang="ro">Suport PDF și îmbunătățiri UX</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Suporte para PDF e outras melhorias</p>
        <p lang="pt">Suporte a PDF e melhorias na experiência do utilizador</p>
        <p lang="pl">Obsługa plików PDF i ulepszenia UX</p>
        <p lang="ja">PDF への対応と、UX の改善</p>
        <p lang="it">Supporto PDF e migliorie UX</p>
        <p lang="is">Stuðningur við PDF og endurbætur á viðmóti</p>
        <p lang="id">Dukungan PDF dan peningkatan UX</p>
        <p lang="hr">Podrška za PDF i poboljšanja korisničkog doživljaja</p>
        <p lang="he">תמיכה ב־PDF ושיפורי חווית משתמש</p>
        <p lang="fr">Prise en charge du format PDF et améliorations de l'interface</p>
        <p lang="et">PDFi tugi ja kasutuskogemuse täiustused</p>
        <p lang="es_MX">Compatibilidad con PDF y mejoras de la experiencia de usuario</p>
        <p lang="es">Compatibilidad con PDF y mejoras de la experiencia de usuario</p>
        <p lang="eo">Subteno de PDF; plibonigoj de fasado</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">PDF support and UX improvements</p>
        <p lang="el">Υποστήριξη PDF και βελτιώσεις ΕΧ</p>
        <p lang="de">PDF-Unterstützung und UX-Verbesserungen</p>
        <p lang="cs">Podpora pro PDF a vylepšení UX</p>
        <p lang="ca">Compatibilitat amb PDF i millores d’experiència d’usuari</p>
        <p lang="be">Падтрымка PDF і паляпшэнні UX</p>
        <p lang="ar">دعم PDF وتحسين تجربة المستخدم</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-04-25" version="0.5">
      <description>
        <p>Initial release with support for EPUB format</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">最初版本，支援 EPUB 格式</p>
        <p lang="zh">最初版本，支持EPUB格式</p>
        <p lang="vi">Bản phát hành đầu tiên có hỗ trợ định dạng EPUB</p>
        <p lang="uk">Початковий випуск із підтримкою формату EPUB</p>
        <p lang="tr">EPUB desteği ile ilk yayın</p>
        <p lang="sv">Första utgåvan med stöd för EPUB-format</p>
        <p lang="sc">Versione de incumintzu cun suportu pro su formadu EPUB</p>
        <p lang="ru">Первый релиз с поддержкой формата EPUB</p>
        <p lang="ro">Lansare inițială cu suport pentru formatul EPUB</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Versão inicial com suporte para EPUB</p>
        <p lang="pt">Lançamento incial com suporte ao formato EPUB</p>
        <p lang="pl">Pierwsze wydanie z obsługą formatu EPUB</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Første utgave, med støtte for EPUB-format</p>
        <p lang="ja">EPUB 形式に対応した、初めてのリリース</p>
        <p lang="it">Rilascio iniziale con supporto per formato EPUB</p>
        <p lang="is">Upphafleg útgáfa með stuðningi við EPUB-snið</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis awal dengan dukungan untuk format EPUB</p>
        <p lang="hr">Prvo izdanje s podrškom za EPUB format</p>
        <p lang="he">מהדורה ראשונית עם תמיכה בתסדיר EPUB</p>
        <p lang="fr">Version initiale avec prise en charge du format EPUB</p>
        <p lang="et">Algne väljalase EPUB vormingu toega</p>
        <p lang="es_MX">Versión inicial con compatibilidad con el formato EPUB</p>
        <p lang="es">Versión inicial con compatibilidad con el formato EPUB</p>
        <p lang="eo">Unua eldono, subtenante la dosierformon EPUB</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Initial release with support for EPUB format</p>
        <p lang="el">Αρχική έκδοση με υποστήριξη για EPUB format</p>
        <p lang="de">Erstveröffentlichung mit Unterstützung für das EPUB-Format</p>
        <p lang="cs">Počáteční vydání s podporou pro formát EPUB</p>
        <p lang="ca">Llançament inicial amb compatibilitat amb el format EPUB</p>
        <p lang="be">Першы выпуск з падтрымкай фармату EPUB</p>
        <p lang="ar">الإصدار الأولي مع دعم تنسيق EPUB</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <developer_name>Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="vi">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sc">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Сиддхартха Дас</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb_NO">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="is">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ie">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">סידהרת׳ה דאס</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="et">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es_MX">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Σιντάρτα Ντας</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="be">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ar">Siddhartha Das</developer_name>
  <url type="homepage">https://babluboy.github.io/bookworm</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/babluboy/bookworm/issues</url>
  <url type="help">https://github.com/babluboy/bookworm/wiki</url>
  <update_contact>bablu.boy_AT_gmail.com</update_contact>
  <custom>
    <value key="x-appcenter-color-primary">#e29ffc</value>
    <value key="x-appcenter-color-primary-text">#260063</value>
    <value key="x-appcenter-suggested-price">2</value>
  </custom>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-desecration">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-slavery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-worship">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-homosexuality">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-prostitution">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-adultery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-appearance">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>