<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>bustle</pkgname>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">org.freedesktop.Bustle.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" height="128" type="cached">org.freedesktop.Bustle.png</icon>
  <id>org.freedesktop.Bustle</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.freedesktop.Bustle.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA-3.0</metadata_license>
  <name>Bustle</name>
  <summary>Draw sequence diagrams of D-Bus activity</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Bustle draws sequence diagrams of D-Bus activity.
        It shows signal emissions, method calls and their
        corresponding returns, with time stamps for each individual
        event and the duration of each method call. This can help
        you check for unwanted D-Bus traffic, and pinpoint why your
        D-Bus-based application is not performing as well as you
        like. It also provides statistics like signal frequencies
        and average method call times.</p>
  </description>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.1+</project_license>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot height="848" width="1548" type="default">
      <image>https://gitlab.freedesktop.org/bustle/bustle/raw/master/data/appdata/bustle-diagram.png</image>
      <caption>Explore sequence diagrams of D-Bus activity</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot height="848" width="1548">
      <image>https://gitlab.freedesktop.org/bustle/bustle/raw/master/data/appdata/bustle-statistics.png</image>
      <caption>See statistics summarizing the log</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot width="1548" height="848">
      <image>https://gitlab.freedesktop.org/bustle/bustle/raw/master/data/appdata/bustle-welcome.png</image>
      <caption>Relax with this soothing greyscale welcome page</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://gitlab.freedesktop.org/bustle/bustle#readme</url>
  <update_contact>will_at_willthompson.co.uk</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">bustle</translation>
  <provides>
    <id>bustle.desktop</id>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release date="2020-07-31" version="0.8.0">
      <description>
        <p>Bustle has a new icon, kindly provided by Tobias Bernard.</p>
        <p>Closing a window without saving a recorded log no longer prompts for confirmation. Anecdotally, most users just want to record and read logs, not save them.</p>
        <p>Bustle now uses GLib's implementation of the D-Bus wire protocol throughout. The only user-facing consequence is that message bodies are now pretty-printed in the GVariant text format.</p>
        <p>Since Bustle no longer depends on any GPL libraries, the project license has been simplified to plain LGPL 2.1 or later.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-03-08" version="0.7.5">
      <description>
        <p>As well as being able to filter out messages involving certain services, you can now also filter messages to only show certain services.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-12-07" version="0.7.4">
      <description>
        <p>In the details for an error reply, the error name is now shown, and the error message is formatted more legibly.</p>
        <p>The default file extension for log files is now ‘.pcap’, reflecting what they actually are.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.3" date="2018-11-15">
      <description>
        <p>Bustle now handles the application/vnd.tcpdump.pcap MIME type, which in practice means that your file manager will offer to open pcap files with Bustle.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-07-24" version="0.7.2">
      <description>
        <p>You can now explore messages while they're being recorded. Filtering, statistics and exporting are still only available once you stop recording.</p>
        <p>The raw sender and destination for each message is now shown in the details pane.</p>
        <p>Bytestrings with embedded NULs which are otherwise ASCII are now shown as ASCII strings.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-06-15" version="0.7.1">
      <description>
        <p>It's now possible to monitor the system bus (from the user interface and with the bustle-pcap command-line tool), with no need to reconfigure the system bus. It's also possible to monitor an arbitrary bus by address.</p>
        <p>Bustle now requires that dbus-monitor (≥ 1.9.10) and pkexec are installed on your system.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>