<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>calibre</pkgname>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">calibre-ebook-edit.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" height="128" width="128">calibre-ebook-edit.png</icon>
  <id>calibre-ebook-edit.desktop</id>
  <name>calibre - E-book Editor</name>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <summary>Edit the text and styles inside e-books</summary>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="social-info">mild</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">mild</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <description>
    <p>The calibre E-book editor allows you to edit the text and styles inside the book with a live preview of your changes.</p>
    <p>It can edit books in both the EPUB and AZW3 (Kindle) formats. It includes various useful tools for checking the book for errors, editing the Table of Contents, performing automated cleanups, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>calibre E-book editor вѝ позволява да редактирате текста и стиловете вътре в книгата със жив преглед на вашите промени.</p>
    <p>Може да редактира книги както във форматите EPUB, така и в AZW3 (Kindle). Включва различни полезни инструменти за проверка на книгата за грешки, редактиране Таблицата на Съдържание, извършване на автоматизирани почиствания и др.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Editor e-knih Calibre vám umožňuje upravit text a styly uvnitř knihy s živým náhledem vašich změn.</p>
    <p>Může upravit knihy ve formátech EPUB a AZW3 (Kindle). Zahrnuje různé užitečné nástroje pro kontrolu chyb v knize, úpravu obsahu, provedení automatizovaných čištění atd.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>El editor de libros electrónicos de calibre le permite modificar el texto y estilo del libro con previsualización en tiempo real de los cambios.</p>
    <p>Puede editar libros en formatos EPUB y AZW3 (Kindle). Incluye varias herramientas útiles para detectar errores en el libro, modificar el índice, realizar limpiezas automáticas, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>L'éditeur de livre numérique de calibre vous permet d'éditer le texte et les styles dans le livre avec une prévisualisation directe de vos changements.</p>
    <p>Il peut éditer des livres tant aux formats EPUB qu'AZW3 (Kindle). Il inclut divers outils utiles pour examiner le livre : décelant les erreurs, éditant la Table des Matières, exécutant des nettoyages automatisés, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Calibre e-könyv szerkesztő lehetővé teszi a könyvben lévő szöveg és stílusok szerkesztését a módosítások élő előnézetével.</p>
    <p>Képes szerkeszteni mind az EPUB, mind az AZW3 (Kindle) formátumú könyveket. Különféle hasznos eszközöket tartalmaz a könyv hibáinak ellenőrzéséhez, a tartalomjegyzék szerkesztéséhez, automatizált tisztítások elvégzéséhez stb.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>L'Editor di e-book di calibre ti permette di modificare il testo e gli stili del libro con un'anteprima in tempo reale delle tue modifiche.</p>
    <p>Può modificare libri sia nel formato EPUB sia in AZW3 (Kindle). Include vari strumenti utili per controllare la presenza di errori, modificare l'indice, effettuare pulizie automatiche, ecc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>Calibre電子書籍エディターは、本の文章や書式をライブプレビューで確認しながら編集することができます。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>De calibre e-boek editor laat u de tekst en stijlen in het boek aanpassen met een direct voorbeeld van uw wijzigingen.</p>
    <p>Het kan boeken zowel in EPUB als in AZW3 (Kindle) formaat bewerken. Het bevat verscheidene handige gereedschappen voor foutcontrole, bewerken van de Inhoudsopgave, automatische clean-ups, enz.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Edytor e-booków Calibre umożliwia edycję tekstu i stylów w książce z podglądem na żywo zmian.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O editor do Calibre permite-lhe editar o texto e os estilos dentro de um livro com pré-visualização das alterações em tempo real.</p>
    <p>Permite editar livros em formatos EPUB e AZW3 (Kindle). Inclui várias ferramentas úteis para verificar erros no livro, editar o índice, efetuar limpezas automáticas, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>O editor de E-books do calibre permite que você edite o texto e os estilos dentro do livro com uma visualização em tempo real de suas alterações.</p>
    <p>Pode editar livros nos formatos EPUB e AZW3 (Kindle). Ele inclui várias ferramentas úteis para a verificação de erros do livro, edição do Índice, realização de limpezas automáticas, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Редактор электронных книг calibre позволяет редактировать текст и стили в книге с предпросмотром изменений в реальном времени.</p>
    <p>В нём можно редактировать книги в форматах EPUB и AZW3 (Kindle). В него включены различные полезные функции для проверки книги на ошибки, редактирования оглавления, автоматической очистки и т. д.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Med calibre e-bokredigeraren kan du redigera text och format inne i boken med realtidsförhandsvisning av dina ändringar.</p>
    <p>Det kan redigera böcker i både formaten EPUB och AZW3 (Kindle). Det innehåller olika användbara verktyg för att kontrollera boken för fel, redigera innehållsförteckningen, utföra automatiserade rengöringar o.s.v.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>За допомогою редактора книг calibre ви зможете редагувати текст та стилі у книзі і бачити наслідки внесених змін у інтерактивному режимі.</p>
    <p>Передбачено можливості з редагування книг у форматах EPUB та AZW3 (Kindle). Також можна скористатися різноманітними корисними інструментами для пошуку помилок у книзі, редагування змісту, виконання автоматичного чищення коду книги тощо.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>calibre 电子书编辑器允许您编辑本书中的文本和样式, 并对所做的更改进行实时预览。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://calibre-ebook.com/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="1408" height="792">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-M2MAVc3A8e4/UvHMWqGRa8I/AAAAAAAAATA/cecQeWUYBVs/w1408-h792-no/edit-default.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image width="1408" height="792">https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-WhoMxuRb34c/UvHMWqN8aGI/AAAAAAAAATI/8SDBYWXb7-8/w1408-h792-no/edit-check.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image width="887" height="575">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-KwaOwHabnBs/UvHMWidjyXI/AAAAAAAAAS8/H6xmCeLnSpk/w887-h575-no/edit-toc.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">calibre-ebook-edit.desktop</launchable>
  <summary lang="nl">Bewerk de tekst en stijlen in de e-boeken</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Редагування тексту і стилів у електронних книгах</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Sunting teks dan gaya di dalam e-buku</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Labot tekstu un stilu e-grāmatas iekšpusē</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Text und Styles innerhalb von eBooks bearbeiten</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Редактируйте текст и стили внутри электронной книги</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Edycja tekstu i stylów wewnątrz książki</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">编辑电子书中的文本和样式</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Редактиране на текста и стиловете вътре в е-книги</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Muuda e-raamatutes olevaid teksti ja laade</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Redigera texten och format inuti böcker</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Az e-könyvekben található szövegek és stílusok szerkesztése</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Edita textos e modelos em e-books</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Editar o texto e o estilo dentro de livros</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Muokkaa tekstiä ja tyylejä kirjojen sisällä</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Upravit text a styly uvnitř e-knih</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Editer le texte et les styles à l'intérieur des livres numériques</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Modifica testo e stili interni agli e-book</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">電子書籍内のテキストとスタイルを編集</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Editatu liburu elektronikoko testua eta estiloak</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Modificar texto y estilos dentro de los libros</summary>
</component>