<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>calibre</pkgname>
  <icon width="64" type="cached" height="64">calibre-viewer.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" type="cached" width="128">calibre-viewer.png</icon>
  <id>calibre-ebook-viewer.desktop</id>
  <name>calibre - E-book Viewer</name>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <summary>Read e-books in over a dozen different formats</summary>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="social-info">mild</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">mild</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <description>
    <p>The calibre E-book viewer allows you to read e-books in over a dozen different formats.</p>
    <p>It has a full screen mode for distraction free reading and can display the text with multiple columns per screen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>calibre E-book viewer, позволява да четете е-книги в над дузина различни формати.</p>
    <p>Той има режим на цял екран за свободно четене и може да покаже текста с няколко колони на екран.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El visor de llibres electrònics del calibre us permet llegir llibres electrònics en una dotzena de formats diferents.</p>
    <p>Té mode de pantalla completa per a una lectura lliure de distraccions i pot mostrar el text en diverses columnes per pantalla.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Prohlížeč e-knih Calibre vám umožňuje číst e-knihy ve více než tuctu různých formátů.</p>
    <p>Má režim na celou obrazovku pro čtení bez rozptylování a může zobrazit text s více sloupci na obrazovku.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Calibres eBook-Betrachter ermöglicht Ihnen das Lesen von eBooks in den unterschiedlichsten Formaten.</p>
    <p>Er besitzt einen Vollbildmodus für ablenkungsfreies Lesen und kann Text in mehreren Spalten pro Bildschirm anzeigen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Έχει επιλογή πλήρους οθόνης για διάβασμα ελέυθερο από περισπασμούς και μπορεί να εμφανίσει το κείμενο σε πολλαπλές στήλες ανά οθόνη.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>El visor de libros de calibre le permite leer libros en más de una docena de formatos diferentes.</p>
    <p>Tiene un modo de pantalla completa para lectura sin distracciones y puede mostrar el texto a varias columnas por pantalla.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>calibre E-raamatute vaatur võimaldab sul lugeda paljudes eri formaatides e-raamatuid.</p>
    <p>Sellel on täisekraanirežiim, et lugemisel tähelepanu ei hajuks, ja suudab teksti näidata mitmes tulbas ekraanil.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>La Visionneuse de livres numériques vous permet de lire des livres numériques dans plus d'une douzaine de formats différents.</p>
    <p>Il a un mode pleine page pour la lecture exempte de distraction et peut montrer le texte avec des colonnes multiples par écran.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Calibre e-könyvnézegető több mint tucat különböző formátumú e-könyvek olvasását teszi lehetővé.</p>
    <p>Egész oldalas móddal rendelkezik a zavartalan olvasás érdekében, és képes a szöveget képernyőnként több oszlopban megjeleníteni.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Il lettore di e-book di calibre ti permette di leggere gli e-book in più di una dozzina di formati differenti.</p>
    <p>È presente una modalità a schermo intero per la lettura senza distrazioni che può mostrare il testo in colonne multiple per display.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>Calibre電子書籍リーダーを使えば、様々な種類の電子書籍を読むことができます。</p>
    <p>読書に集中するための全画面モード機能を持ち、また画面毎に複数の段組で表示をすることもできます。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>Calibre e-grāmatu skatītājs ļauj lasīt e-grāmatas vairāk nekā duci dažādos formātos.</p>
    <p>Tai ir pilnekrāna režīms netraucētai lasīšanai un tā spēj attēlot uz ekrāna vairākas teksta slejas.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Ia menyediakan mod berskirn penuh untuk pembacaan bebas gangguan dan dapat paparkan teks dengan lajur berbilang dalam satu skrin.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>De calibre e-boek viewer geeft u de mogelijkheid e-boeken te lezen in meer dan een dozijn formaten.</p>
    <p>Het heeft een full screen modus voor afleidingsloos lezen en het kan tekst in verschillende kolommen tonen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Czytnik książek calibre umożliwia czytanie e-booków w wielu różnych formatach.</p>
    <p>Ma tryb pełnoekranowy dla wygody czytania i może wyświetlać tekst w wielu kolumnach.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O visualizador de livros do Calibre permite-lhe ler livros digitais em dezenas de formatos diferentes.</p>
    <p>Possui um modo de visualização em ecrã inteiro para permitir a leitura sem distrações e pode ainda mostrar o texto em múltiplas colunas por ecrã.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>O Visualizador de e-books do calibre permite a leitura de e-books em mais de uma dezena de formatos diferentes.</p>
    <p>Tem um modo de tela cheia para distração de leitura livre e pode exibir o texto com várias colunas por tela.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Читалка calibre поддерживает более дюжины форматов электронных книг.</p>
    <p>В ней есть полноэкранный режим для чтения без отвлекающих факторов, а текст можно отображать в несколько колонок.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>calibre e-bokvisaren tillåter att du läser e-böcker i över ett dussin olika format.</p>
    <p>Den har ett helskärmsläge för distraktionsfri läsning och kan visa texten med flera spalter per skärm.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Dikkatinizin dağılmasına engel olacak tam ekran kipi olduğu gibi sayfa başına birden fazla sütun da görüntüleyebilir.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>За допомогою програми для перегляду електронних книг calibre ви зможете читати книги у будь-якому з понад десятка форматів.</p>
    <p>Щоб вам було зручніше читати, передбачено режим розгортання вікна програми на весь екран та показу тексту на екрані у декілька стовпців.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>calibre 电子书阅读器可以阅读的电子书格式多达十余种</p>
    <p>它有一个全屏模式来进行无干扰阅读，并且可以显示每个屏幕有多个栏的文本。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://calibre-ebook.com/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="1408" height="792">https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-dzSO82BPpaE/UvHMYY5SpNI/AAAAAAAAATk/I_kF9fYWrZM/w1408-h792-no/viewer-default.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image width="1920" height="1080">https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-n32Ae5RytAk/UvHMY0QD94I/AAAAAAAAATs/Zw8Yz08HIKk/w1920-h1080-no/viewer-fs.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">calibre-ebook-viewer.desktop</launchable>
  <summary lang="ca">Llegiu llibres electrònics en una dotzena de formats diferents</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Lees E-boeken in meer dan een dozijn formaten</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Читання електронних книг понад десяти форматах</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Baca e-buku melangkaui sedozen format yang berlainan</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Lasīt e-grāmatas vairāk nekā duci dažādos formātos</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Lesen Sie eBooks in über einem Dutzend verschiedener Formate</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Читайте электронные форматы более чем в дюжине форматов</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Umożliwia czytanie e-booków w wielu różnych formatach</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">可以阅读的电子书格式多达十余种</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Прочетете е-книги в над дузина различни формати</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Loe paljudes eri formaatides e-raamatuid</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Läs e-böcker i över ett dussin olika format</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">E-könyvek olvasása több mint tucat különböző formátumban</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Leia e-books em mais de uma dúzia de diferentes formatos</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Ler ebooks numa dezena de formatos diferentes.</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Číst e-knihy ve více než tuctu různých formátů</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Lire des livres numériques dans plus d'une douzaine de formats différents</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Lestu rafbækur á mörgum mismunandi sniðum</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Leggi e-book in oltre dieci formati diversi</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Irakurri liburu elektronikoak dozena bat baino gehiago formatutan</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Leer libros en más de una docena de formatos distintos</summary>
</component>