<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <description>
    <p>
      Calligra Stage is an easy to use yet still flexible presentation application.
      You can easily create presentations containing a rich variety of elements, from graphics to text, from charts to images. Calligra Stage is extensible through a plugin system,
      so it is easy to add new effects, new content elements or even new ways of managing your presentation. Because of the integration with Calligra, all the power and flexibility
      of the Calligra content elements are available to Stage.
    </p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Multiple master slides</li>
      <li>Easily switch between slides during a presentation</li>
      <li>Add notes for your slide</li>
      <li>Supports most ODF file transitions</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Calligra Stage je lagana ali fleksibilna prezentacijska aplikacija. Možete lako kreirati prezentacije s dosta elemenata, iz grafike i teksta, dijagrama i slika. Calligra Stage se može proširivati kroz sistem dodataka, tako da je lako dodati nove efekte, nove sadržajne elemente ili čak nove načine upravljanja prezentacijom. Zbog integracije sa Calligra, sva moć i fleksibilnost od Calligra sadržaja elemenata su dostupni u Stage.</p>
    <p>Svojstva:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Više master slajdova</li>
      <li>Lako prebacujte između slajdova tokom prezentacije</li>
      <li>Dodajte zabilješke za vaš slajd</li>
      <li>Podržava većinu tranzicija ODF datoteka</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>L'Stage del Calligra és una aplicació de presentació flexible i fàcil d'utilitzar. Podeu crear presentacions fàcilment que continguin una gran varietat d'elements, des de gràfics a text, des de diagrames a imatges. L'Stage del Calligra és ampliable mitjançant un sistema de connectors, de manera que és senzill afegir efectes nous, elements de contingut nous o inclús noves maneres de gestionar les presentacions. Gràcies a la integració amb el Calligra, tota la potència i la flexibilitat dels elements de contingut del Calligra són disponibles per l'Stage.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Múltiples diapositives mestres</li>
      <li>Canvi senzill entre dispositives durant una presentació</li>
      <li>Permet afegir notes a les dispositives</li>
      <li>Accepta la majoria de les transicions de fitxer ODF</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>L'Stage del Calligra és una aplicació de presentació flexible i fàcil d'utilitzar. Podeu crear presentacions fàcilment que continguen una gran varietat d'elements, des de gràfics a text, des de diagrames a imatges. L'Stage del Calligra és ampliable mitjançant un sistema de connectors, de manera que és senzill afegir efectes nous, elements de contingut nous o inclús noves maneres de gestionar les presentacions. Gràcies a la integració amb el Calligra, tota la potència i la flexibilitat dels elements de contingut del Calligra són disponibles per l'Stage.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Múltiples diapositives mestres</li>
      <li>Canvi senzill entre dispositives durant una presentació</li>
      <li>Permet afegir notes a les dispositives</li>
      <li>Accepta la majoria de les transicions de fitxer ODF</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Vlastnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Přidejte poznámky ke snímku</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Funktionen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Mehrere Folienmaster</li>
      <li>Einfacher Wechsel zwischen Folien während einer Präsentation</li>
      <li>Hinzufügen von Notizen zu Folien</li>
      <li>Unterstützt die meisten ODF-Dateiübergänge</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το Calligra Stage είναι μια ευκολόχρηστη αλλά και ευέλικτη εφαρμογή παρουσιάσεων. Μπορείτε εύκολα να δημιουργήσετε παρουσιάσεις που να περιέχουν μια πλούσια ποικιλία αντικειμένων, από γραφικά σε κείμενο,, από διαγράμματα σε εικόνες. Το Calligra Stage είναι επεκτάσιμο μέσα από ένα σύστημα προσθέτων, έτσι είναι εύκολο να προστεθούν νέα εφέ, νέα αντικείμενα περιεχομένου ή ακόμη και νέοι τρόποι διαχείρισης παρουσιάσεων. Λόγω της ενσωμάτωσης στο Calligra, όλη η ισχύς και η ευελιξία των αντικειμένων περιεχομένου του Calligra είναι διαθέσιμη στο Stage.</p>
    <p>Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Πολλαπλές κύριες διαφάνειες</li>
      <li>Εύκολη εναλλαγή ανάμεσα σε διαφάνειες κατά τη διάρκεια μιας παραουσίασης</li>
      <li>Προσθήκη σημειώσεων για τη διαφάνειά σας</li>
      <li>Υποστηρίζει τις περισσότερες μεταβάσεις αρχείων ODF</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>Calligra Stage is an easy to use yet still flexible presentation application. You can easily create presentations containing a rich variety of elements, from graphics to text, from charts to images. Calligra Stage is extensible through a plugin system, so it is easy to add new effects, new content elements or even new ways of managing your presentation. Because of the integration with Calligra, all the power and flexibility of the Calligra content elements are available to Stage.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Multiple master slides</li>
      <li>Easily switch between slides during a presentation</li>
      <li>Add notes for your slide</li>
      <li>Supports most ODF file transitions</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Calligra Stage es un aplicación para presentaciones, fácil de utilizar y flexible. Permite crear fácilmente presentaciones que contengan una amplia variedad de elementos, desde gráficos a texto, desde diagramas a imágenes. Calligra Stage es extensible a través de un sistema de complementos, por lo que es fácil añadir nuevos efectos, nuevos elementos de contenido e incluso nuevas maneras de gestionar las presentaciones. Debido a su integración con Calligra, toda la potencia y flexibilidad de los elementos de contenido de Calligra están disponibles para Stage.</p>
    <p>Características:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Múltiples diapositivas maestras</li>
      <li>Permite cambiar fácilmente entre diapositivas durante una presentación</li>
      <li>Permite añadir notas a una diapositiva</li>
      <li>Implementa la mayoría de las transiciones de archivo de ODF</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Calligra Stage on hõlpsasti kasutatav, aga väga paindlik esitluste rakendus. Selle abil saab vähese vaevaga luua rikkalikult elemente sisaldavaid esitlusi, milles leidub kõike alates graafikast tekstini ja diagrammidest piltideni. Calligra Stage'i saab laiendada pluginate abil, mis võimaldab lihtsalt lisada uusi efekte, uusi sisuelemente või isegi päris uusi viise esitlusi hallata. Calligraga lõimimise tõttu saab Stage paindlikult ära kasutada kõiki Calligra sisuelementide võimalusi.</p>
    <p>Omadused:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Mitme juhtslaidi kasutamise võimalus</li>
      <li>Hõlpus lülitumine slaidide vahel esitluse ajal</li>
      <li>Märkmete lisamine slaididele</li>
      <li>Enamiku ODF-vormingu failiüleminekute toetamine</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Calligra Stage on helppokäyttöinen mutta silti joustava esityssovellus. Voit luoda esityksiä, jotka sisältävät monenlaisia elementtejä grafiikasta tekstiin ja kaavioista valokuviin. Calligra Stagea voi laajentaa liitännäisin, joten uusia tehosteita, uusia sisältöelementtejä tai jopa uusia esityksesi hallinnan tapoja on helppo lisätä. Calligra-integroinnin ansiosta Calligran sisältöelementtien teho ja joustavuus ovat Stagenkin käytössä.</p>
    <p>Ominaisuuksia:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Useammat pohjadiat</li>
      <li>Helppo siirtyminen diasta toiseen esityksen aikana</li>
      <li>Muistiinpanojen lisäys dioihisi</li>
      <li>Useimpien ODF-siirtymien tuki</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Calligra Stage est une application de présentation à la fois flexible et facile à utiliser. Vous pouvez facilement créer des présentations comprenant une grande variété d'éléments, allant des graphiques au texte, en passant par les diagrammes et les images. Calligra Stage propose un système d'extensions ; il est facile d'ajouter de nouveaux effets, des nouveaux éléments de contenu ou même de nouvelles façons de gérer votre présentation. Du fait de l'intégration avec Calligra, toute la puissance et la flexibilité des contenu de Calligra sont disponibles dans Stage.</p>
    <p>Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Planches-maîtresses multiples</li>
      <li>Passage facile d'une planche à une autre pendant une présentation</li>
      <li>Ajoutez des notes à vos planches</li>
      <li>Prend en charge la plupart des transitions ODF</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Calligra Stage é unha aplicación de presentacións fácil de usar pero flexíbel. Permítelle crear presentacións cunha ampla variedade de elementos, incluíndo texto, gráficos e imaxes. As funcionalidades de Calligra Stage poden ampliarse mediante un sistema de complementos, así que resulta doado engadir efectos e elementos novos, así como novos xeitos de xestionar as presentacións. Grazas á súa integración con Calligra, Stage pode facer uso da potencia e flexibilidade dos elementos de contido dispoñíbeis en Calligra.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Varias diapositivas mestre.</li>
      <li>Permite cambiar facilmente entre diapositivas durante as presentacións.</li>
      <li>Permite engadir notas ás presentacións.</li>
      <li>Compatíbel coa meirande parte das transicións dos ficheiros ODF.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ia">
    <p>Characteristicas:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Facilemente commuta inter diapositivas durante un presentation</li>
      <li>Adde notas per tu diapositiva</li>
      <li>Supporta le majoritate del transitiones de file ODF</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Calligra Stage adalah aplikasi presentasi yang mudah digunakan namun tetap fleksibel. Anda dapat dengan mudah membuat presentasi yang mengandung beragam elemen, dari grafik ke teks, dari bagan ke gambar. Calligra Stage dapat diekstensi melalui sistem plugin, sehingga mudah untuk menambahkan efek baru, elemen konten baru atau bahkan cara baru mengelola presentasi Anda. Karena integrasi dengan Calligra, semua kekuatan dan fleksibilitas elemen konten Calligra tersedia untuk tahap (Stage).</p>
    <p>Fitur:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Multipel slide master</li>
      <li>Secara mudah beralih antara slide selagi presentasi</li>
      <li>Penambahan catatan Anda untuk slide Anda</li>
      <li>Dukungan beberapa transisi file ODF</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Calligra Stage è un'applicazione per presentazioni tanto facile da utilizzare quanto è flessibile. Puoi creare facilmente presentazioni che contengono un'ampia varietà di elementi, dalla grafica al testo, dai grafici alle immagini. Calligra Stage è espandibile tramite un sistema di estensioni, per cui è semplice aggiungere nuovi effetti o anche nuovi modi di gestire le tue presentazioni. Grazie all'integrazione con Calligra, tutta la potenza e la flessibilità degli elementi di Calligra sono disponibili in Stage.</p>
    <p>Funzionalità:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Diapositive master multiple</li>
      <li>Cambia facilmente le diapositive durante una presentazione</li>
      <li>Aggiungi note alle tue diapositive</li>
      <li>Supporta la maggior parte delle transizioni dei file ODF</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>Caligra 스테이지는 사용하기 쉽지만 여전히 탄력적인 프레젠테이션 프로그램입니다. 그래픽에서 텍스트, 차트에서 이미지에 이르기까지 다양한 요소가 들어 있는 프레젠테이션을 쉽게 만들 수 있습니다. Caligra 스테이지는 플러그인 시스템을 통해 확장 가능하므로 새로운 효과, 새로운 컨텐츠 요소 또는 프레젠테이션을 관리하는 새로운 방법을 쉽게 추가할 수 있습니다. Caligra와의 통합으로 인해 Caligra 콘텐츠 요소의 모든 기능과 유연성을 스테이지에서 사용할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p>기능:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>다중 마스터 슬라이드</li>
      <li>프레젠테이션 중에 간편하게 슬라이드 전환</li>
      <li>슬라이드에 메모 추가</li>
      <li>대부분의 ODF 파일 전환 지원</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Calligra Stage is een gemakkelijk te gebruiken maar toch flexibele toepassing voor presentaties. U kunt gemakkelijk presentaties maken met een rijke variatie van elementen, van grafische tot tekst, van grafieken tot afbeeldingen. Calligra Stage is uit te breiden met een systeem van plug-ins, zodat het gemakkelijk is om nieuwe effecten toe te voegen, nieuwe soorten inhoud of zelfs nieuwe manieren van het beheren van uw presentatie. Vanwege de integratie met Calligra, is alle kracht en flexibiliteit van de inhoudselementen van Calligra beschikbaar in Stage.</p>
    <p>Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Meerdere voorbeelddia's</li>
      <li>Schakel gemakkelijk tussen dia's tijdens een presentatie</li>
      <li>Voeg notities toe aan uw dia</li>
      <li>Ondersteunt de meeste ODF-bestandstransities</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Scena Calligra jest łatwym w użyciu, a zarazem elastycznym programem do prezentowania. Można łatwo tworzyć prezentację zawierające bogatą różnorodność elementów, od grafiki do tekstu, od wykresów do obrazów. Scena Calligra jest rozszerzalna przez system wtyczek, tak że można łatwo dodać nowe efekty, nowe elementy lub nawet nowe sposoby na zarządzanie prezentacją. Ze względów na powiązanie z Calligrą, cała moc i elastyczność elementów Calligry jest dostępna również dla Sceny.</p>
    <p>Cechy:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Wiele głównych plansz</li>
      <li>Łatwe przełączanie pomiędzy planszami przy prezentowaniu</li>
      <li>Dodawanie notatek do plansz</li>
      <li>Obsługa większości przejść plików ODF</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Calligra Stage é uma aplicação de apresentações simples de usar, mas também bastante flexível. Poderá criar facilmente apresentações que contêm uma grande variedade de elementos, desde gráficos a texto, assim como de gráficos a imagens. O Calligra Stage é modular através de um sistema de 'plugins', pelo que é fácil adicionar novos efeitos, elementos de conteúdo ou até novas formas de gerir a sua apresentação. Devido à integração com o Calligra, todo o poder e flexibilidade dos elementos de conteúdo do Calligra estão disponíveis no Stage.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Diversos 'slides'-mestres</li>
      <li>Mudar facilmente de 'slides' durante uma apresentação</li>
      <li>Adicionar notas ao seu 'slide'</li>
      <li>Suporta a maioria das transições nos ficheiros ODF</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>Calligra Stage é um aplicativo de apresentações fácil de usar, mas também bastante flexível. Você pode criar facilmente apresentações que contenham uma grande variedade de elementos, desde gráficos a texto, assim como de gráficos a imagens. O Calligra Stage é expansível através de um sistema de plugins, permitindo adicionar facilmente novos efeitos, elementos de conteúdo ou até novas formas de gerenciar sua apresentação. Devido à integração com o Calligra, todo o poder e flexibilidade dos elementos de conteúdo do Calligra também estão disponíveis no Stage.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Vários slides-mestres</li>
      <li>Troca facilmente de slides durante uma apresentação</li>
      <li>Adiciona notas ao seu slide</li>
      <li>Suporte à maioria das transições em arquivos ODF</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Возможности:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Calligra Stage je jednoducho použiteľná a flexibilná aplikácia na prezentácie. Môžete jednoducho vytvárať prezentácie obsahujúce bohatý výber prvkov, od grafických po textové, od grafov po obrázky. Calligra Stage je rozšíriteľná cez systém pluginov, takže je jednoduché pridať nové efekty, nové obsahové prvky alebo dokonca nové spôsoby správy vašej prezentácie. Vďaka integrácii so systémom Calligra je k dispozícii celá sila a flexibilita obsahových prvkov Calligra.</p>
    <p>Funkcie:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Viacero hlavných snímok</li>
      <li>Jednoducho prepnúť medzi snímkami počas prezentácie</li>
      <li>Pridať poznámky pre vašu snímku</li>
      <li>Podporuje väčšinu ODF súborových prechodov</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Calligra Stage är ett lättanvänt men ändå flexibelt presentationsprogram. Du kan enkelt skapa presentationer som innehåller en rik variation av element, från grafik till text, från diagram till bilder. Calligra Stage är utökningsbar via ett insticksprogramsystem, så det är lätt att lägga till nya effekter, nya innehållselement eller till och med nya sätt att hantera presentationer. På grund av integration med Calligra är de kraftfulla och flexibla innehållselementen i Calligra tillgängliga för Stage.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Flera förlagssidor</li>
      <li>Enkelt byte mellan bilder under presentationer</li>
      <li>Lägg till anteckningar för bilder</li>
      <li>Stöder de flesta ODF-filövergångar</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Calligra Stage — проста, але потужна програма для роботи з презентаціями. За її допомогою ви без проблем зможете створити презентацію з багатим набором елементів, від графіки до тексту, від діаграм до зображень. Можливості Calligra Stage можна розширити за допомогою системи додатків: ви можете додати нові ефекти, нові елементи вмісту і навіть нові способи керування презентацією. Через тісну інтеграцію з рештою програм Calligra ви можете скористатися усіма потужними та гнучкими елементами решти програм Calligra безпосередньо у Stage.</p>
    <p>Можливості:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Використання декількох основних слайдів.</li>
      <li>Просте перемикання між слайдами під час презентації.</li>
      <li>Додавання нотаток до слайдів.</li>
      <li>Підтримка більшості переходів у файлах ODF.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxCalligra Stage is an easy to use yet still flexible presentation application. You can easily create presentations containing a rich variety of elements, from graphics to text, from charts to images. Calligra Stage is extensible through a plugin system, so it is easy to add new effects, new content elements or even new ways of managing your presentation. Because of the integration with Calligra, all the power and flexibility of the Calligra content elements are available to Stage.xx</p>
    <p>xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>xxMultiple master slidesxx</li>
      <li>xxEasily switch between slides during a presentationxx</li>
      <li>xxAdd notes for your slidexx</li>
      <li>xxSupports most ODF file transitionsxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>功能：</p>
  </description>
  <pkgname>calligra</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.calligrastage.desktop</launchable>
  <icon height="64" width="64" type="cached">calligrastage.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">calligrastage.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.calligrastage.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="ca">Stage del Calligra</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">Stage del Calligra</name>
  <name lang="cs">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="de">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="el">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="es">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="et">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="fi">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="fr">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="gl">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="ia">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="id">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="it">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="ko">Calligra 스테이지</name>
  <name lang="nl">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="pl">Scena Calligra</name>
  <name lang="pt">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="ru">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="sk">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="sv">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="uk">Calligra Stage</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxCalligra Stagexx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">Calligra Stage</name>
  <summary>Presentation</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Prezentacija</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Presentació</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Presentació</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Prezentace</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Präsentation</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Παρουσίαση</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Presentation</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Presentación</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Esitlus</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Esitysgrafiikka</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Présentation</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Presentación</summary>
  <summary lang="ia">Presentation</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Presentasi</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Presentazioni</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">프레젠테이션</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Presentatie</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Prezentacja</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Apresentação</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Apresentação</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Prezentácia</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Presentation</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Презентації</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxPresentationxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">演示</summary>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.calligra.org/stage/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=calligrastage</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=stage</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/calligra/calligrastage.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>calligrastage</binary>
  </provides>
</component>