<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <description>
    <p>
    Celluloid is a simple media player that can play virtually all video and
    audio formats. It supports playlists and MPRIS2 media player controls. The
    design of Celluloid follows the GNOME Human Interface Guidelines, but can
    also be adapted for other systems that don't use client-side decorations
    (CSD). It is based on the mpv library and GTK.
  </p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Drag and drop playlist</li>
      <li>Loading external mpv configuration files</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus interface</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>السيلولويد هو مشغل وسائط بسيط يمكنه تشغيل جميع تنسيقات الفيديو والصوت تقريبًا. وهو يدعم قوائم التشغيل وعناصر تحكم مشغل الوسائط MPRIS2. يتبع تصميم السيلولويد إرشادات واجهة جنوم البشرية ، ولكن يمكن أيضًا تكييفه مع الأنظمة الأخرى التي لا تستخدم الزخارف من جانب العميل (CSD). يعتمد على مكتبة mpv و GTK.</p>
    <p>ملامح:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>سحب وإسقاط قائمة التشغيل</li>
      <li>تحميل ملفات تكوين mpv الخارجية</li>
      <li>واجهة MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Celluloid е прост медиен плеър, който може да възпроизвежда практически всички видео и аудио формати. Той поддържа плейлисти и MPRIS2 контроли на медийния плеър. Дизайнът на Celluloid следва GNOME Human интерфейса, но може да бъде адаптиран и за други системи, които не използват декорации от страна на клиента (CSD). Той е базиран на MPV и GTK библиотеките.</p>
    <p>Опции:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Поддръжка на Drag'n'Drop</li>
      <li>Зареждане на външни MPV конфигурационни файлове</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus интерфейс</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Cel·luloide és un reproductor multimèdia senzill que pot reproduir pràcticament qualsevol format de vídeo i àudio. Admet llistes de reproducció i controls de reproducció MPRIS2. El disseny del Celluloid segueix les guies d'interfície d'usuari del GNOME, però també pot adaptar-se a altres entorns que no fan servir les decoracions del client (CSD). Es basa en les biblioteques mpv i GTK.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Es poden arrossegar i deixar anar les entrades de la llista de reproducció</li>
      <li>Carrega fitxers de configuració externs de l'mpv</li>
      <li>Interfície D-Bus de MPRIS2</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Celluloid je jednoduchý přehrávač médií, který dokáže přehrávat prakticky všechny formáty videa a zvuku. Podporuje seznamy přehrávání a ovládací prvky MPRIS2. Design aplikace Celluloid odpovídá GNOME Human Interface Guidelines, ale lze jej také přizpůsobit pro jiné systémy, které nepoužívají dekorace na straně klienta (CSD). Je založen na knihovně mpv a GTK.</p>
    <p>Nabízí:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Seznam přehrávání („playlist“) s možností přetáhnout soubory myší</li>
      <li>Načítání externího konfiguračního souboru pro mpv</li>
      <li>Rozhraní MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Celluloid er en simpel medieafspiller som kan afspille næsten alle video- og lydformater. Den understøtter afspilningslister og MPRIS2-medieafspillerstyring. Celluloids design følger GNOME Human Interface Guidelines men kan også tilpasses andre systemer der ikke bruger klientside-dekorationer (CSD). Den er baseret på mpv-biblioteket og GTK.</p>
    <p>Funktionaliteter:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Træk og slip afspilningsliste</li>
      <li>Indlæser eksterne mpv-konfigurationsfiler</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus-grænseflade</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Celluloid ist ein einfach zu bedienender Medienspieler, der so gut wie alle Video- und Audioformate abspielen kann. Es werden Wiedergabelisten und Fernsteuerung über die MPRIS2-Schnittstelle unterstützt. Celluloid ist gemäß der "GNOME Human Interface Guidelines", der Designrichtlinien des GNOME-Projekts gestaltet, kann aber für Systeme angepasst werden, welche keine clientseitigen Fensterdekorationen (CDSs) unterstützen. Die technische Basis stellen mpv und GTK.</p>
    <p>Funktionen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Wiedergabeliste mit Drag and Drop-Unterstützung</li>
      <li>Laden externer mpv-Konfigurationsdateien</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus Schnittstelle</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Ο Celluloid είναι ένας απλός αναπαραγωγέας πολυμέσων ο οποίος μπορεί να αναπαράξει όλες σχεδόν τις μορφές βίντεο και ήχου. Υποστηρίζει λίστες αναπαραγωγής και εργαλεία ελέγχου αναπαραγωγέα πολυμέσων MPRIS2. Η σχεδίαση του Celluloid ακολουθεί τις οδηγίες ανθρώπινης διασύνδεσης (Human Interface Guidelines) του GNOME, αλλά μπορεί να προσαρμοστεί και για άλλα συστήματα που δε χρησιμοποιούν client-side διακοσμήσεις (CSD). Βασίζεται στη βιβλιοθήκη mpv και στο GTK.</p>
    <p>Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Σύρε και απόθεσε λίστα αναπαραγωγής</li>
      <li>Φόρτωση εξωτερικών αρχείων διαμόρφωσης του mpv</li>
      <li>Διεπαφή MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p>Celuloido estas simpla aŭdvida spektilo, kiu povas ludi preskaŭ ĉiujn aŭdvidajn dosierformojn. Ĝi subtenas spektolistojn kaj estas regebla per MPRIS2. La fasono de Celuloido konformas al la fasadaj gvidnormoj de GNOME, sed ankaŭ povas adapti sin por aliaj sistemoj, kiuj ne uzas klient-flankajn ornamaĵojn (CSD). Ĝi uzas la bibliotekojn MPV kaj GTK.</p>
    <p>Funkcioj:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ŝovmeti spektoliston</li>
      <li>Ŝargante eksterajn agordajn dosierojn de MPV</li>
      <li>Interfaco de « MPRIS2 D-Bus »</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Celluloid es un reproductor multimedia sencillo que puede reproducir prácticamente cualquier formato de vídeo y audio. Admite listas de reproducción y controles de reproducción MPRIS2. El diseño de Celluloid sigue las guías de interfaz de usuario de GNOME, pero también puede adaptarse a otros entornos que no usan decoraciones del lado del cliente (CSD). Se basa en las bibliotecas mpv y GTK.</p>
    <p>Características:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Permite arrastrar y soltar entradas en la lista de reproducción</li>
      <li>Carga archivos de configuración de mpv externos</li>
      <li>Interfaz D-Bus de MPRIS2</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Celluloid multimedia erreproduzigailu sinple bat da, eta bideo eta audio formatu ia guztiak erreproduzitu ditzake. Erreprodukzio-zerrenda eta MPRIS2 multimedia erreproduzigailu kontrolen euskarria du. Celluloiden diseinuak GNOMEren Gizakientzako interfaze gidalerroak jarraitzen ditu, baina bezeroaren aldeko apaingarriak (CSD) erabiltzen ez dituzten beste sistemetara egokitu daiteke. mpv liburutegian eta GTK-n oinarritua dago.</p>
    <p>Ezaugarriak:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Erreprodukzio-zerrendak arrastatu eta jaregitea</li>
      <li>Kanpoko mpv konfigurazio-fitxategiak kargatzea</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus interfazea</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fa">
    <p>سلولوید یک پخش‌کنندهٔ ساده است که می‌تواند تقریباً تمام قالب‌های صوتی و تصویری را پخش کند. این برنامه از فهرست‌های پخش و واپایگشرهای پخش‌کنندهٔ رسانهٔ MPIRS2 پشتیبانی می‌کند. طرّاحی سلولوید پیرو رهنمودهای رابط انسانی گنوم بوده، ولی برای دیگر سامانه‌ها که از تزیینات سمت کارخواه (CSD) استفاده نمی‌کنند نیز قابل تطبیق است. این برنامه بر مبنای کتابخانهٔ mpv و GTK است.</p>
    <p>ویژگی‌ها:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>فهرست پخش با کشش و رهایی</li>
      <li>بار کردن پرونده‌های پیکربندی mpv</li>
      <li>رابط دی‌باس MPIRS2</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Celluloid on yksinkertainen mediasoitin, joka voi toistaa käytännössä kaikki video- ja äänimuodot. Se tukee soittolistoja ja MPRIS2-mediasoittimen ohjaimia. Celluloidin suunnittelu noudattaa GNOME Human Interface -ohjeita, mutta sitä voidaan mukauttaa myös muihin järjestelmiin, jotka eivät käytä ikkunatehosteita (CSD). Se perustuu MPV-kirjastoon ja GTK:hon.</p>
    <p>Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Vedä ja pudota soittolista</li>
      <li>Ladataan ulkoisia MPV-asetustiedostoja</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 -D-Bus-liitäntä</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Celluloid est un lecteur multimédia simple capable de lire pratiquement tous les formats vidéo et audio. Il supporte les listes de lecture et le contrôle à distance MPRIS2. Sa conception est basée sur les recommandation GNOME en matière d’interfaces graphiques mais il peut aussi s’adapter aux autres environnements de bureaux qui n’utilisent pas de décorations de fenêtres côté client (CSD).</p>
    <p>Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Glisser-déposer des listes de lecture</li>
      <li>Chargement des fichiers de configuration externes pour mpv</li>
      <li>Interface D-Bus MPRIS2</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Celuloid je jednostavan medijski reproduktor koji može reproducirati virtualno sve video i zvučne formate. Podržava popise izvođenja i MPRIS2 medijsko upravljanje reprodukcijom. Dizajn Celuloida slijedi smjernice GNOME Human sučelja , ali isto tako može biti prilagođen za druge sustave koji ne koriste ukrase od strane klijenta (CSD). Temelji se na mpv biblioteci i GTK-u.</p>
    <p>Značajke:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Povuci i ispusti popis izvođenja</li>
      <li>Učitavanje vanjske mpv datoteke podešavanja</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus sučelje</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Celluloid egy egyszerű médialejátszó, ami gyakorlatilag minden videó- és hangformátumot le tud játszani. Támogatja a lejátszási listákat és az MPRIS2 médialejátszó-vezérlőket. A Celluloid dizájnja követi a GNOME Human Interface irányelveket, de más, kliensoldali dekorációkat nem támogató rendszereken is használható. Az mpv könyvtáron és a GTK-n alapul.</p>
    <p>Funkciók:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Fogd és vidd lejátszási lista</li>
      <li>Külső mpv konfigurációs fájlok betöltése</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus interfész</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Celluloid adalah pemutar media sederhana yang dapat memutar hampir semua format video dan audio. Ini mendukung daftar putar dan kontrol pemutar media MPRIS2. Desain Celluloid mengikuti Pedoman Antarmuka Manusia GNOME, tetapi juga dapat diadaptasi untuk sistem lain yang tidak menggunakan dekorasi sisi klien (CSD). Hal ini didasarkan pada perpustakaan MPV dan GTK.</p>
    <p>Fitur-fitur:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Seret dan lepas daftar putar</li>
      <li>Memuat berkas konfigurasi mpv eksternal</li>
      <li>Antarmuka MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ie">
    <p>Celluloid es un simplic reproductor de media quel posse reproducter practicmen omni formates de video e audio. It supporta playlistes e control de reproduction med MPRIS2. Li dessin de Celluloid conforma al recomandationes por interfacie de usator GNOME, ma it posse esser adaptat por altri sistemas quel ne usa decorationes del látere de cliente (CSD). It usa li bibliotecas mpv e GTK.</p>
    <p>Caracteristicas:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Tirar-e-cader in li playlist</li>
      <li>Interfacie D-Bus de MPRIS</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>Eiginleikar:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Draga og sleppa á spilunarlista</li>
      <li>Hleð inn utanaðkomandi mpv-stillingaskrám</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus viðmót</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Celluloid è un semplice lettore multimediale in grado di riprodurre praticamente tutti i formati audio e video. Supporta playlist e controlli MPRIS2 multimediali. Il design di Celluloid segue le linee guida GNOME Human Interface, ma può anche essere adattato per altri sistemi che non usano decorazioni lato client (CSD). Si basa sulle librerie libmpv e GTK.</p>
    <p>Caratteristiche:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Trascinamento della playlist</li>
      <li>Caricamento di file di configurazione esterni di mpv</li>
      <li>Interfaccia MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>셀룰로이드는 거의 모든 비디오 및 오디오 형식을 재생할 수있는 간단한 미디어 플레이어입니다. 재생 목록 및 MPRIS2 미디어 플레이어 컨트롤을 지원합니다. 셀룰로이드의 디자인은 그놈 휴먼 인터페이스 지침을 따르지만 클라이언트 측 장식 (CSD)을 사용하지 않는 다른 시스템에도 적용 할 수 있습니다. mpv 라이브러리와 GTK를 기반으로합니다.</p>
    <p>기능:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>재생 목록 드래그 앤 드롭</li>
      <li>외부 mpv 구성 파일로드</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus 인터페이스</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb_NO">
    <p>Celluloid er en enkel mediaspiller som kan spille nesten alle video- og lydformater. Den støtter MPRIS2-mediaspillerkontroller. Designet følger GNOME sine menneskelige grensesnittsveiledninger, men kan også tilpasses systemer som ikke bruker klientside-dekorasjoner (CSD). Basert på mpv-biblioteket og GTK.</p>
    <p>Funksjoner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>MPRIS2-D-Bus-grensesnitt</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Celluloid is een eenvoudige mediaspeler die nagenoeg alle video en audioformaten kan afspelen. Het ondersteunt afspeellijsten en MPRIS2 mediaspeler bediening. Het ontwerp van Celluloid volgt de GNOME Human Interface richtlijnen, maar kan ook worden aangepast voor andere systemen die geen client-side-decortions gebruiken. Het is gebaseerd op de mpv bibliotheek en op GTK. </p>
    <p>Functies:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Sleep en plaats afspeellijst</li>
      <li>Externe mpv configuratiebestanden laden</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus interface</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Celluloid to prosty odtwarzacz multimedialny obsługujący praktycznie wszystkie formaty dźwięku i wideo. Umożliwia korzystanie z list odtwarzania i sterowanie za pomocą MPRIS2. Interfejs programu Celluloid jest zgodny z Wytycznymi projektowania interfejsów GNOME, ale może być używany także w innych środowiskach, które nie obsługują wyświetlania obramowań okna po stronie klienta (CSD). Celluloid korzysta z bibliotek mpv i GTK.</p>
    <p>Cechy:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>lista odtwarzania obsługująca przeciąganie plików,</li>
      <li>wczytywanie zewnętrznych plików konfiguracji programu mpv,</li>
      <li>obsługa interfejsu D-Bus MPRIS2</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>O Celluloid é um media player simples que pode reproduzir praticamente todos os formatos de vídeo e áudio. Ele suporta listas de reprodução e controles MPRIS2 media player. O design do Celluloid segue as Diretrizes da interface humana do GNOME, mas também pode ser adaptado para outros sistemas que não usam decorações do lado do cliente (CSD). É baseado na biblioteca mpv e GTK.</p>
    <p>Recursos:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Arrastar e soltar lista de reprodução</li>
      <li>Carregando arquivos externos de configuração do mpv</li>
      <li>Interface MPRIS2 D-BUS</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_PT">
    <p>O Celluloid é um reprodutor multimédia simples que pode reproduzir praticamente todos os formatos de vídeo e áudio. Tem suporte a listas de reprodução e controlos MPRIS2. O projeto Celluloid segue as diretrizes GNOME Human Interface, mas também pode ser adaptado para outros sistemas que não utilizem decorações 'client-side' (CSD). É baseado na biblioteca mpv e no GTK.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Arrastar e largar listas de reprodução</li>
      <li>Carregar ficheiros de configuração mpv externos</li>
      <li>Interface MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Celluloid - это простой медиа плеер, который способен воспроизводить практически все видео и аудио форматы. Он поддерживает списки воспроизведения и управление плеером через MPRIS2. Дизайн Celluloid соответствует GNOME HIG, но также может быть адаптирован для других систем, которые не используют декорирование на стороне клиента (CSD). Он основан на библиотеке mpv и GTK.</p>
    <p>Возможности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Поддержка drag-and-drop</li>
      <li>Загрузка внешних конфигурационных файлов MPV</li>
      <li>Интерфейс MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Celluloid je jednoduchý prehrávač médií, ktorý dokáže prehrávať prakticky všetky formáty videa a zvuku. Podporuje zoznamy skladieb a ovládacie prvky prehrávača médií MPRIS2. Dizajn Celluloidu sa riadi usmerneniami GNOME Human Interface Guidelines, ale možno ho prispôsobiť aj pre iné systémy, ktoré nepoužívajú dekorácie na strane klienta (CSD). Je založený na knižnici mpv a GTK.</p>
    <p>Funkcie:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Potiahni a pusť playlist</li>
      <li>Načítavanie externých konfiguračných súborov mpv</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Celluloid is a simple media player that can play virtually all video and audio formats. It supports playlists and MPRIS2 media player controls. The design of Celluloid follows the GNOME Human Interface Guidelines, but can also be adapted for other systems that don't use client-side decorations (CSD). It is based on the mpv library and GTK.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Drag and drop playlist</li>
      <li>Loading external mpv configuration files</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus interface</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Целулоид је једноставан програм за пуштање мултимедијалног садржаја који може да пушта виртуелно све видео и аудио формате. Подржава спискове пуштања и „MPRIS2“ контроле мултимедијалног пуштача. Дизајн Целулоида прати смернице Гномовог сучеља, али такође може бити прилагођен за друге системе који не користе украсе од стране клијента (CSD). Заснован је на „mpv“ библиотеци у Гтк-у.</p>
    <p>Могућности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Превлачење и убацивање списка пуштања</li>
      <li>Учитавање спољне датотеке подешавања „mpv“-а</li>
      <li>„MPRIS2“ сучеље Д-сабирнице</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Mogućnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Prevuci i otpusti listu puštanja</li>
      <li>Učitavam spoljne mpv konfiguracione datoteke</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus sučelje</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Celluloid är en enkel mediaspelare som kan spela upp i stort sett alla film- och ljudformat. Den stödjer spelningslistor och MPRIS2 mediaspelarkontroller. Designen av Celluloid följer GNOME Human Interface Guidelines, men kan också anpassas för andra system som inte använder klientsidans dekorationer (CSD). Den är baserad på biblioteket mpv och GTK.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Dra och släpp spelningslista</li>
      <li>Läser in externa mpv konfigurationsfiler</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus gränssnitt</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Celluloid, neredeyse tüm video ve ses biçimlerini oynatabilen basit bir medya oynatıcıdır. Oynatma listelerini ve MPRIS2 medya oynatıcı kontrollerini destekler. Celluloid tasarımı GNOME Arayüz Kılavuzlarına uygundur, ancak istemci tarafı süslemeleri (CSD) kullanmayan diğer sistemler için de uyarlanabilir. Mpv kütüphanesine ve GTK'ya dayanmaktadır.</p>
    <p>Özellikler:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Oynatma listesini sürükleyip bırak</li>
      <li>Harici mpv yapılandırma dosyalarını yükle</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus arayüzü</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Celluloid — це простий медіапрогравач, який може відтворювати майже всі відео та звукові формати. Він підтримує добірки та елементи керування програвачем MPRIS2. Дизайн Celluloid відповідає GNOME Human Interface Guidelines, але також може бути пристосований для інших систем, які не використовують клієнтські декорації (CSD). Його засновано на бібліотеці mpv і GTK.</p>
    <p>Можливості:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Перетягування добірок</li>
      <li>Завантаження зовнішніх файлів конфігурації mpv</li>
      <li>Інтерфейс MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>Celluloid 是一个简单的媒体播放器，几乎可以播放所有视频和音频格式。它支持播放列表和 MPRIS2 媒体播放器控件。 Celluloid 的设计遵循 GNOME 人机界面指南，但也适用于其他不使用客户端装饰 (CSD) 的系统。它基于 mpv 库和 GTK。</p>
    <p>特性：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>拖放播放列表</li>
      <li>正在载入外部 MPV 配置文件</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus 接口</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>Celluloid 是一個簡單的媒體播放器，可以播放幾乎所有影片和音訊格式。支援播放清單和 MPRIS2 媒體播放器控制介面。Celluloid 的設計遵循 GNOME Human Interface Guidelines，但也可以適用於不使用客戶端裝飾 (CSD) 的其他系統。Celluloid 基於 mpv 函式庫和 GTK。</p>
    <p>特性：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>拖放播放清單</li>
      <li>載入外部 mpv 設定檔</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus 介面</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>celluloid</pkgname>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">io.github.celluloid_player.Celluloid.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" type="cached" width="128">io.github.celluloid_player.Celluloid.png</icon>
  <id>io.github.celluloid_player.Celluloid</id>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA-4.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">赛璐珞</name>
  <name lang="uk">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="tr">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="sv">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="sr">Целулоид</name>
  <name lang="sl">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="sk">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="ru">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="ro">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="pt_PT">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="pl">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="nl">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="nb_NO">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="ko">미디어 플레이어</name>
  <name lang="ja">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="it">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="is">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="ie">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="id">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="hu">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="hr">Celuloid</name>
  <name lang="fr">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="fi">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="fa">سلولوید</name>
  <name lang="eu">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="es">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="eo">Celuloido</name>
  <name lang="el">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="de">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="da">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="cs">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="ca">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="bg">Celluloid</name>
  <name lang="ar">سليوليد</name>
  <summary>GTK+ frontend for mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">MPV 的 GTK+ 前端程式</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">MPV 的 GTK+ 前端程序</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">GTK+ клієнтська частина для mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Mpv için GTK + arayüz</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">GTK+ gränssnitt för mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">GTK+ pročelje za mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Гтк+ челник за „mpv“</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">GTK+ frontend for mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">GTK+ frontend pre mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">GTK+ интерфейс для MPV</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_PT">Interface GTK+ para mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Interface em GTK+ para o mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Interfejs GTK dla biblioteki mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">GTK+ frontend voor mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">mpv 용 GTK + 프런트 엔드</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">MPVのGTKフロントエンド</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Un frontend in GTK+ per mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="is">GTK+ viðmót fyrir mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="ie">Un interfacie GTK+ por MPV</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Tampilan depan GTK+ untuk mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">GTK+ felület az mpv-hez</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">GTK+ sučelje za mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Interface GTK+ pour mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">GTK+-käyttöliittymä MPV:lle</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">پیشانهٔ ‪GTK+‬ برای mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">mpv-ren GTK+ interfazea</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Interfaz GTK para el reproductor mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Fasado per GTK por MPV</summary>
  <summary lang="el">GTK+ διεπαφή για τον mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Eine GTK-Oberfläche für den Medienspieler mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="da">GTK+-frontend til mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">GTK+ rozhraní nad mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Interfície GTK per al reproductor mpv</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">GTK+ интерфейс за MPV</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">واجهة GTK+ ل mpv</summary>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.celluloid_player.Celluloid.desktop</launchable>
  <translation type="gettext">celluloid</translation>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <provides>
    <id>io.github.GnomeMpv.desktop</id>
  </provides>
  <developer_name>The Celluloid Developers</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">Celluloid 開發者</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">Celluloid 开发者</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Розробники Celluloid</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">Celluloid Geliştiricileri</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">Celluloids utvecklare</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Програмери Целулоида</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">The Celluloid Developers</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Vývojári Celluloidu</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Разработчики Celluloid</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_PT">Os programadores do Celluloid</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">Os Desenvolvedores do Celluloid</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Deweloperzy programu Celluloid</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">De Celluloid ontwikkelaars</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb_NO">Celluloid-utviklerne</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">프로그램 개발자</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Gli sviluppatori di Celluloid</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="is">Celluloid þróunarteymið</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ie">Li developatores de Celluloid</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Pengembang Celluloid</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A Celluloid fejlesztői</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">Celuloid razvijatelji</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Développeurs de Celluloid</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Celluloid-kehittäjät</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fa">توسعه‌دهندگان سلولوید</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">Celluloiden garatzaileak</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Los desarrolladores de Celluloid</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">La programistoj de Celuloido</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Οι Developers του Celluloid</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Die Celluloid-Entwickler</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">Celluloids udviklere</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Vývojáři aplikace Celluloid</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">Els desenvolupadors del Celluloid</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="bg">Разработчиците на Celluloid</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ar">مطورو السيليلويد</developer_name>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.23" date="2022-03-07">
      <description>
        <p>
     This is mostly a bugfix release. It contains the following changes:
    </p>
        <ul>
          <li>
      Fix autofit triggering regardless of settings.
     </li>
          <li>
      Fix window size shrinking across sessions.
     </li>
          <li>
      Fix crash when playing files with names containing invalid encoding.
     </li>
          <li>
      Fix drag-and-drop not working with some file managers.
     </li>
          <li>
      Fix playback starting when the last playlist item is removed.
     </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
     This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個清單不是完整的。請到 git log 中檢視完整的變更記錄。</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个列表不完整。请到 git log 中查看完整的 changelog。</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей перелік не повний. Вичерпний перелік змін перегляньте у журналі git.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu liste eksik. Değişikliklerin tamamı için git günlüğüne bakın.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här listan är ofullständig. Se git-loggen för fullständig ändringslogg.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Овај списак је непотпун. Видите гитов дневник за потпуни дневник измена.</p>
        <p lang="sl">This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Это не полный список. Полный список изменений см. в журнале git.</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta lista está incompleta. Consulte o registo git para ver todas as alterações.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta listagem está incompleta. Veja log git para changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta lista jest niepełna. Polecenie „git log” wyświetli pełną listę zmian.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze lijst is onvolledig. Zie git log voor volledige changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 목록은 불완전합니다. 전체 변경 로그는 git 로그를 참조하십시오.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa lista è incompleta. Consultare git log per il changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="id">Daftar ini tidak lengkap. Lihat catatan git untuk daftar perubahan yang lengkap.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovaj popis je nepotpun. Pogledajte git zapis za potpuni pregled promjena.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette liste n’est pas complète. Pour voir tous les changements utilisez git log.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä luettelo on puutteellinen. Katso täydellinen git-muutosloki.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Zerrenda hau osatugabea da. Ikusi git log aldaketen zerrenda osorako.</p>
        <p lang="es">Este listado está incompleto. Consulte el registro de Git para obtener un registro de cambios completo.</p>
        <p lang="eo">La listo estas nekompleta. Uzu la komandon 'git log' por plena ŝanĝaro.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η καταχώρηση είναι ατελής. Δες την καταγραφή (log) του git για την πλήρη καταγραφή των αλλαγών (changelog).</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Liste ist unvollständig. Eine detaillierte Übersicht bietet das Changelog.</p>
        <p lang="da">Listen er ikke komplet. Se git-loggen for en komplet ændringslog.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tento seznam je neúplný. Úplný přehled změn najdete v git logu.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquest llistat és incomplet. Consulteu el registre del Git per obtenir un registre de canvis complet.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Списъкът не е завършен. Вижте Git лога за пълния списък с промени.</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذه القائمة غير مكتملة. انظر سجل بوابة التغيير الكامل.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.22" date="2021-11-05">
      <description>
        <p>
     This release contains the following changes:
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此發行版本包含了以下變更：</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">该发布版本包含了以下变更：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск містить такі зміни:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm aşağıdaki değişiklikleri içerir:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här versionen innehåller följande ändringar:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање садржи следеће измене:</p>
        <p lang="sl">This release contains the following changes:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje nasledujúce zmeny:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск содержит следующие изменения:</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera następujące zmiany:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze uitgave bevat de volgende aanpassingen:</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Denne utgaven inneholder følgende endringer:</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리스에는 다음 변경 사항이 포함됩니다:</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione contiene le seguenti modifiche:</p>
        <p lang="is">Þessi útgáfa inniheldur eftirfarandi breytingar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Ti version contene li sequent modificationes:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini berisi perubahan berikut:</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás a következő változtatásokat tartalmazza:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovo izdanje sadrži sljedeće promjene:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version apporte les changement suivants :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä julkaisu sisältää seuraavat muutokset:</p>
        <p lang="fa">این نسخه شامل تغییرات زیر است:</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek ondorengo aldaketak ditu:</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión contiene los cambios siguientes:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Ĉi tiu eldono enhavas la jenajn ŝanĝojn:</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση περιλαμβάνει τις παρακάτω αλλαγές:</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Veröffentlichungen umfasst die folgenden Änderungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Udgivelsen indeholder følgende ændringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tato verze obsahuje následující změny:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió conté els canvis següents:</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание съдържа следните промени:</p>
        <p lang="ar">يحتوي هذا الإصدار على التغييرات التالية:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>
      Migrate to GTK4.
     </li>
          <li>
      Add Greek translation by @lepa22.
     </li>
          <li>
      Add Korean translation by @jullee96.
     </li>
          <li>
      Add Norwegian Bokmål translation by Allan Nordhøy.
     </li>
          <li>
      Add Occidental translation by OIS.
     </li>
          <li>
      Add Arabic translation by Mohamed Benkouider.
     </li>
          <li>
      Add Urdu translation by Ahmed Iqbal.
     </li>
          <li>
      Add option to show title buttons in fullscreen mode.
     </li>
          <li>
      Add option to present the window when opening files.
     </li>
          <li>
      Change default screenshot filename template to FILENAME-TIMESTAMP (%f-%P).
     </li>
          <li>
      Fix inaccurate timestamp preview.
     </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
     This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個清單不是完整的。請到 git log 中檢視完整的變更記錄。</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个列表不完整。请到 git log 中查看完整的 changelog。</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей перелік не повний. Вичерпний перелік змін перегляньте у журналі git.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu liste eksik. Değişikliklerin tamamı için git günlüğüne bakın.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här listan är ofullständig. Se git-loggen för fullständig ändringslogg.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Овај списак је непотпун. Видите гитов дневник за потпуни дневник измена.</p>
        <p lang="sl">This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Это не полный список. Полный список изменений см. в журнале git.</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta lista está incompleta. Consulte o registo git para ver todas as alterações.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta listagem está incompleta. Veja log git para changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta lista jest niepełna. Polecenie „git log” wyświetli pełną listę zmian.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze lijst is onvolledig. Zie git log voor volledige changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 목록은 불완전합니다. 전체 변경 로그는 git 로그를 참조하십시오.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa lista è incompleta. Consultare git log per il changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="id">Daftar ini tidak lengkap. Lihat catatan git untuk daftar perubahan yang lengkap.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovaj popis je nepotpun. Pogledajte git zapis za potpuni pregled promjena.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette liste n’est pas complète. Pour voir tous les changements utilisez git log.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä luettelo on puutteellinen. Katso täydellinen git-muutosloki.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Zerrenda hau osatugabea da. Ikusi git log aldaketen zerrenda osorako.</p>
        <p lang="es">Este listado está incompleto. Consulte el registro de Git para obtener un registro de cambios completo.</p>
        <p lang="eo">La listo estas nekompleta. Uzu la komandon 'git log' por plena ŝanĝaro.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η καταχώρηση είναι ατελής. Δες την καταγραφή (log) του git για την πλήρη καταγραφή των αλλαγών (changelog).</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Liste ist unvollständig. Eine detaillierte Übersicht bietet das Changelog.</p>
        <p lang="da">Listen er ikke komplet. Se git-loggen for en komplet ændringslog.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tento seznam je neúplný. Úplný přehled změn najdete v git logu.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquest llistat és incomplet. Consulteu el registre del Git per obtenir un registre de canvis complet.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Списъкът не е завършен. Вижте Git лога за пълния списък с промени.</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذه القائمة غير مكتملة. انظر سجل بوابة التغيير الكامل.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-03-22" version="0.21">
      <description>
        <p>
     This release contains the following changes:
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此發行版本包含了以下變更：</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">该发布版本包含了以下变更：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск містить такі зміни:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm aşağıdaki değişiklikleri içerir:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här versionen innehåller följande ändringar:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање садржи следеће измене:</p>
        <p lang="sl">This release contains the following changes:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje nasledujúce zmeny:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск содержит следующие изменения:</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera następujące zmiany:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze uitgave bevat de volgende aanpassingen:</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Denne utgaven inneholder følgende endringer:</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리스에는 다음 변경 사항이 포함됩니다:</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione contiene le seguenti modifiche:</p>
        <p lang="is">Þessi útgáfa inniheldur eftirfarandi breytingar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Ti version contene li sequent modificationes:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini berisi perubahan berikut:</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás a következő változtatásokat tartalmazza:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovo izdanje sadrži sljedeće promjene:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version apporte les changement suivants :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä julkaisu sisältää seuraavat muutokset:</p>
        <p lang="fa">این نسخه شامل تغییرات زیر است:</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek ondorengo aldaketak ditu:</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión contiene los cambios siguientes:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Ĉi tiu eldono enhavas la jenajn ŝanĝojn:</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση περιλαμβάνει τις παρακάτω αλλαγές:</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Veröffentlichungen umfasst die folgenden Änderungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Udgivelsen indeholder følgende ændringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tato verze obsahuje následující změny:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió conté els canvis següents:</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание съдържа следните промени:</p>
        <p lang="ar">يحتوي هذا الإصدار على التغييرات التالية:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>
      Add Basque translation by @aldatsa.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加 @aldatsa 贡献的巴斯克语翻译。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано переклад баскською від @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Baskça çeviriyi hazırlayan @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Lägg till Baskiska-översättning av @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додат је превод на баскијски који је урадио „@aldatsa“.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add Basque translation by @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="sk">Pridaný baskický preklad (@aldatsa).</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлен перевод на баскский от @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Tradução Basca adicionada por @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Acrescentar tradução basca por @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nowe tłumaczenie na język baskijski od @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Baskisk oversettelse ved @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="ko">@aldatsa로 바스크어 번역을 추가하십시오.</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahan translasi Bahasa Basque oleh @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Baskijski prijevod je dodao @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout de la traduction en basque par @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisätty baski käännös käyttäjältä @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="fa">افزودن ترجمهٔ باسکی به دست @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="eu">@aldatsa-ren euskarazko itzulpena gehitu.</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade la traducción al euskera de @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni eŭsklingvigon de @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη Βασκικής μετάφρασης από @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="de">Baskische Übersetzung hinzufügen von @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidán baskický překlad od @aldatsa.</li>
          <li lang="ar">أضف الترجمة الباسكية بواسطة @aldatsa.</li>
          <li>
      Make the shuffle and loop command line options work properly.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">使随机播放和循环播放命令行选项正常工作。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Впорядковано роботу параметрів перемішування та повторення у командному рядку.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Karıştır ve yinele komut satırı seçeneklerinin düzgün çalışmasını sağla.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Опције терминала за мешање и понављање раде исправно.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Make the shuffle and loop command line options work properly.</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zabezpečí správne fungovanie možností shuffle a loop príkazového riadka.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Сделать так, чтобы параметры командной строки shuffle и loop работали правильно.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Fazer com que as opções de linha de comandos shuffle e loop funcionem corretamente.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Fazer as opções misturar e repetir de linha de comando funcionarem corretamente.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Umożliwienie poprawnego działania opcjom wiersza poleceń: losowe odtwarzanie i powtarzanie.</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Korrekt håndtering av tilfeldig avspilling og gjentakelse med kommandolinjevalg.</li>
          <li lang="ko">셔플 및 루프 명령 줄 옵션이 제대로 작동하도록합니다.</li>
          <li lang="id">Opsi baris perintah acak dan ulang berfungsi dengan baik.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Mogućnosti naredbenog retka za naizmjeničnu reprodukciju i ponavljanje sada rade ispravno.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Faire fonctionner correctement les options de ligne de commande shuffle et loop.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Tee sekoitus- ja silmukka-asetukset toimimaan komentorivillä oikein.</li>
          <li lang="fa">درست کردن کارکرد گزینه‌های خط فرمان حلقه و بر زدن.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Komando lerroko ausaz nahasi eta begizta aukerek ondo funtzionatzea.</li>
          <li lang="es">Hacer que las opciones de línea de comandos shuffle y loop funcionen correctamente.</li>
          <li lang="el">Κάνε τις επιλογές γραμμής εντολών shuffle και loop να λειτουργούν σωστά.</li>
          <li lang="de">Sicherstellen, dass die Befehlszeilenoptionen shuffle und loop richtig funktionieren.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Možnosti příkazového řádku shuffle a loop fungují správně.</li>
          <li lang="ar">اجعل خيارات سطر الأوامر العشوائي والحلقة تعمل بشكل صحيح.</li>
          <li>
      Make the main menu button toggleable by pressing F10.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">可按 F10 切换主菜单按钮。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Кнопка головного меню тепер перемикається клавішею F10.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Ana menü düğmesini F10 tuşuna basarak değiştirilebilir hale getir.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Gör den huvudsakliga meny-knappen växlingsbar genom att trycka på F10.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Главно дугме изборника се може окинути притиском на тастер Ф10.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Make the main menu button toggleable by pressing F10.</li>
          <li lang="sk">Tlačidlo hlavnej ponuky bude prepínateľné stlačením klávesy F10.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Сделать кнопку главного меню нажимаемой по F10.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Tornar o botão do menu principal comutável premindo F10.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Faça com que o botão do menu principal seja alternável pressionando F10.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Umożliwienie przełączania przycisku menu głównego poprzez wciśnięcie klawisza F10.</li>
          <li lang="ko">F10을 눌러 기본 메뉴 버튼을 토글 가능하게 만드십시오.</li>
          <li lang="id">Jadikan tombol menu utama dapat dialihkan dengan menekan F10.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Tipka glavnog izbornika sada se može uključiti/isključiti pritiskom na F10.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Rendre le bouton du menu principal basculable en appuyant sur F10.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Tee päävalikon painikkeesta vaihdettava painamalla F10.</li>
          <li lang="fa">قابلیت تغییر وضعیت دکمهٔ فهرست اصلی با فشردن F10.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Menu nagusiko botoia F10 sakatuz txandakatu ahal izatea.</li>
          <li lang="es">Haz que el botón del menú principal sea conmutable pulsando F10.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Igi la ĉefmenuan butonon baskuligebla per la klavo F10.</li>
          <li lang="el">Κάνε το κουμπί του κύριου μενού εναλλάξιμο (toggleable) πιέζοντας το F10.</li>
          <li lang="de">Die Hauptmenütaste kann durch Drücken von F10 umgeschaltet werden.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Tlačítko hlavní nabídky je přepínatelné stisknutím klávesy F10.</li>
          <li lang="ar">اجعل زر القائمة الرئيسية قابلاً للتبديل بالضغط على F10.</li>
          <li>
      Add a setting for always appending opened files to the playlist.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">新增一个设置以总是将打开的文件追加到播放列表。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано параметр завжди додавати відкриті файли на початок списку відтворення.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Açılan dosyaları her zaman oynatma listesine eklemek için bir ayar ekle.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Lägg till en inställning för att alltid lägga till öppna filer till spellistan.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додата је поставка да увек додаје отворене датотеке на списак пуштања.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add a setting for always appending opened files to the playlist.</li>
          <li lang="sk">Pridá nastavenie pre pridanie otvorených súborov do playlistu.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавить параметр, чтобы открытые файлы всегда добавлялись в список воспроизведения.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionar uma configuração para anexar sempre os ficheiros abertos à lista de reprodução.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionar uma configuração para sempre anexar os arquivos abertos à lista de reprodução.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Dodanie ustawienia, aby zawsze dołączać otwarte pliki do listy odtwarzania.</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Legg til innstilling for alltid å legge til åpnede filer i spillelisten.</li>
          <li lang="ko">열린 파일을 항상 재생 목록에 추가하는 설정을 추가합니다.</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan pengaturan untuk selalu menambahkan file yang dibuka ke daftar putar.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana je postavka za dodavanje otvorenih datoteka u popis izvođenja.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout d’un paramètre permettant de toujours ajouter les fichiers ouverts à la liste de lecture.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää asetus avattujen tiedostojen lisäämiseksi aina soittolistaan.</li>
          <li lang="fa">افزودن تنظیمی برای افزودن همیشگی پرونده‌های گشوده به سیاههٔ پخش.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Irekitako fitxategiak beti erreprodukzio-zerrendara gehitzeko aukera ematen duen ezarpena sortu.</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade un ajuste para añadir siempre los archivos abiertos a la lista de reproducción.</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη ρύθμισης για την προσάρτηση των ανοιχτών αρχείων στη λίστα αναπαραγωγής.</li>
          <li lang="de">Hinzufügen einer Einstellung, um geöffnete Dateien immer an die Wiedergabeliste anzuhängen.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidáno nastavení pro připojování otevřených souborů do seznamu k přehrávání.</li>
          <li lang="ar">أضف إعدادًا لإلحاق الملفات المفتوحة دائمًا بقائمة التشغيل.</li>
          <li>
      Allow appending files to playlist by holding shift while dropping files
      onto the video area.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">允许在将文件拖拽到适配区域时，通过按下 shift 键来将文件追加到播放列表。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Дозволено додавати файли на початок списку відтворення, утримуючи Shift, перетягуючи файли на зону відтворення.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Dosyaları video alanına bırakırken shift tuşuna basılı tutarak oynatma listesine dosya eklemeye izin ver.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Tillåt att lägga till filer i spellistan genom att hålla ner shift medans du släpper filer på video-området.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додавање датотека на списак пуштања се може урадити држањем тастера „шифт“ приликом убацивања датотека у област за видео.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Allow appending files to playlist by holding shift while dropping files onto the video area.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Позволить добавлять файлы в список воспроизведения, перетаскивая их на область видео при зажатой Shift.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Permitir a anexação de ficheiros à lista de reprodução, pressionando o shift enquanto se largam ficheiros na área de vídeo.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Permitir anexar arquivos à lista de reprodução, segurando o shift enquanto solta os arquivos na área de vídeo.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Umożliwienie dołączania plików do listy odtwarzania poprzez przytrzymanie klawisza Shift podczas upuszczania plików na obszar wideo.</li>
          <li lang="ko">파일을 비디오 영역에 놓는 동안 Shift 키를 눌러 재생 목록에 파일을 추가 할 수 있습니다.</li>
          <li lang="id">Izinkan penambahan file ke daftar putar dengan menahan tombol shift sambil menjatuhkan file ke area video.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Omogućeno je dodavanje datoteka u popis izvođenja držanjem tipke shift tijekom ispuštanja datoteka u područje videa.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Permettre l’ajout de fichiers à la liste de lecture en maintenant la touche Maj tout en déposant les fichiers sur la zone vidéo.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Salli tiedostojen lisääminen soittolistaan pitämällä shift-näppäintä painettuna, kun pudotat tiedostoja videoalueelle.</li>
          <li lang="fa">اجازهٔ افزودن پرونده‌ها به سیاههٔ پخش با نگه داشتن تبدیل هنگام رها کردن پرونده‌ها در ناحیهٔ ویدیو.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Fitxategiak bideo-areara jaregitean Maius sakatuz erreprodukzio-zerrenda gehitzeko aukera eman.</li>
          <li lang="es">Permite añadir archivos a la lista de reproducción manteniendo pulsada la tecla shift mientras se sueltan los archivos en el área de vídeo.</li>
          <li lang="el">Να επιτρέπεται η προσάρτηση αρχείων στη λίστα αναπαραγωγής κρατώντας πατημένο το πλήκτρο shift κατά την απόθεση αρχείων στην περιοχή του βίντεο.</li>
          <li lang="de">Bei gedrückter Shift-Taste können Dateien durch Ziehen auf den Videobereich der Wiedergabeliste angehängt werden.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Umožněno přidávání souborů do seznamu přehrávání podržením klávesy Shift a přesunutím souborů do oblasti videa.</li>
          <li lang="ar">اسمح بإلحاق الملفات بقائمة التشغيل بالضغط على مفتاح shift أثناء إسقاط الملفات في منطقة الفيديو.</li>
          <li>
      Make CSD header bar toggleable via the mpv property "border".
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">通过 mpv 属性“border”使 CSD 标题栏可切换。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Панель заголовків CSD тепер перемикається за допомогою властивості mpv «межа».</li>
          <li lang="tr">CSD başlık çubuğunu "border" mpv özelliği aracılığıyla değiştirilebilir yap.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Gör CSD-huvudfältet växlingsbart via mpv-egenskapen "kant".</li>
          <li lang="sr">Трака „CSD“ заглавља се може окинути путем „mpv“ својства „ивица“.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Make CSD header bar toggleable via the mpv property "border".</li>
          <li lang="ru">Сделать полосу заголовка CSD переключаемой через свойство mpv "border".</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Tornar a barra de cabeçalho do CSD comutável através da "margem" da propriedade mpv.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Fazer a barra de cabeçalho CSD acionável por meio da propriedade "border" do mpv.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Sprawienie, aby pasek nagłówka CSD był przełączalny za pomocą właściwości mpv "border".</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Avslagsbar overleggsmeny via mpv-egenskaper «border».</li>
          <li lang="ko">mpv 속성 "border"를 통해 CSD 헤더 표시 줄을 전환 할 수 있도록합니다.</li>
          <li lang="id">Jadikan header bar CSD dapat diubah lewat properti mpv "batas".</li>
          <li lang="hr">Traka CSD zaglavlja sada se može uključiti/isključiti putem mpv svojstva "border".</li>
          <li lang="fr">Rendre la barre d’en-tête de la CSD basculable via la propriété « border » de mpv.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Tee CSD-otsikkopalkista vaihdettava mpv:n "border" avulla.</li>
          <li lang="fa">قابلیت تغییر وضعیت نوار سرایند CSD با ویژگی border در MPV.</li>
          <li lang="eu">CSD goiburu-barra txandakagarri egin mpv-ren "border" propietatea erabiliz.</li>
          <li lang="es">Hacer que la barra de cabecera del CSD sea conmutable a través de la propiedad mpv "border".</li>
          <li lang="el">Κάνε την κεφαλίδα CSD εναλλάξιμη (toggleable) μέσω της ιδιότητας "border" του mpv.</li>
          <li lang="de">CSD-Kopfleiste ist mittels des mpv-Attributs "border" an-/ausschaltbar.</li>
          <li lang="cs">CSD (dekorace na straně klienta) header bar (lišta záhlaví) je přepínatelná pomocí mpv vlastnosti „border“.</li>
          <li lang="ar">جعل شريط رأس CSD قابلاً للتبديل عبر خاصية mpv "الحدود".</li>
          <li>
      Include Flatpak manifest in the repo. This allows Celluloid to be built in
      one click in apps like GNOME Builder.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">在 repo 中包含 Flatpak manifest。 这允许在 GNOME Builder 等应用程序中一键构建 Celluloid。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Включено маніфест Flatpak до репозиторію. Це дозволяє будувати Celluloid в один натиск у таких програмах як GNOME Builder.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Depoya Flatpak bildirimini dahil et. Bu, Celluloid'in GNOME Builder gibi uygulamalarda tek bir tıklamayla derlenmesini sağlar.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Inkludera Flatpak-manifestet i filförrådet. Det här tillåter Celluloid att byggas på ett klick i appar såsom GNOME Builder.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Проглас Флатпака је укључен у ризницу. Ово омогућава да се Целулоид може изградити једним кликом у програмима као што је Гномов Градитељ.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Include Flatpak manifest in the repo. This allows Celluloid to be built in one click in apps like GNOME Builder.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Включать манифест Flatpak в репозиторий. Это позволит собирать Celluloid одним щелчком в программах, подобных GNOME Builder.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Incluir o manifesto Flatpak no repositório. Isto permite que o Celluloid seja compilado com um clique em aplicações como o GNOME Builder.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Incluir o manifesto do Flatpak no repositório. Isto permite que o Celluloid seja construído com um clique em aplicativos como o GNOME Builder.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Dołączenie manifestu Flatpak do repozytorium. Pozwala to na kompilowanie programu Celluloid jednym kliknięciem w aplikacjach takich jak GNOME Builder.</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Inkluder Flatpak-manifest i pakkebrønnen. Dette tillater bygging av Celluloid med ett klikk i programmer som GNOME Builder.</li>
          <li lang="ko">저장소에 Flatpak 매니페스트를 포함합니다. 이를 통해 GNOME Builder와 같은 앱에서 한 번의 클릭으로 Celluloid를 만들 수 있습니다.</li>
          <li lang="id">Sertakan manifes Flatpak di repo. Ini memungkinkan Celluloid untuk dibangun dengan satu klik di aplikasi seperti GNOME Builder.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Flatpak manifest je uključen u repozitorij. To omogućuje Celluloidu izgradnju jednim pritiskom u aplikacijama kao što je GNOME Builder.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Inclure le manifeste Flatpak dans le dépôt. Cela permet de construire Celluloid en un clic dans des applications comme GNOME Builder.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Sisällytä Flatpak-manifesti repoon. Näin Celluloid voidaan rakentaa yhdellä napsautuksella GNOME Builderin kaltaisissa sovelluksissa.</li>
          <li lang="fa">شامل شدن بیانیهٔ فلت‌پک در مخزن. این مار می‌گذارد سلولوید در کاره‌هایی چون سازندهٔ گنوم، با یک کلیک ساخته شود.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Flatpak manifestua gehitu biltegian. Horri esker Celluloid GNOME Builder bezalako aplikazioetan klik bakarrean eraiki daiteke.</li>
          <li lang="es">Incluir el manifiesto Flatpak en el repositorio. Esto permite construir Celluloid con un solo clic en aplicaciones como GNOME Builder.</li>
          <li lang="el">Συμπερίλαβε το manifest του Flatpak στο αποθετήριο. Αυτό επιτρέπει στον Celluloid να δομηθεί (build) σε εφαρμογές ενός κλικ όπως ο GNOME Builder.</li>
          <li lang="de">Flatpak-Manifest ist im Quellcode-Repositorium enthalten. So kann Celluloid mit nur einem Klick in Anwendungen wie GNOME Builder erstellt werden.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Flatpak manifest byl zahrnut do repo. To umožňuje, aby byl Celluloid vytvořen jedním kliknutím v aplikacích jako je GNOME Builder.</li>
          <li lang="ar">قم بتضمين بيان Flatpak في الريبو. يتيح ذلك إنشاء السيلولويد بنقرة واحدة في تطبيقات مثل GNOME Builder.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
     This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個清單不是完整的。請到 git log 中檢視完整的變更記錄。</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个列表不完整。请到 git log 中查看完整的 changelog。</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей перелік не повний. Вичерпний перелік змін перегляньте у журналі git.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu liste eksik. Değişikliklerin tamamı için git günlüğüne bakın.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här listan är ofullständig. Se git-loggen för fullständig ändringslogg.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Овај списак је непотпун. Видите гитов дневник за потпуни дневник измена.</p>
        <p lang="sl">This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Это не полный список. Полный список изменений см. в журнале git.</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta lista está incompleta. Consulte o registo git para ver todas as alterações.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta listagem está incompleta. Veja log git para changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta lista jest niepełna. Polecenie „git log” wyświetli pełną listę zmian.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze lijst is onvolledig. Zie git log voor volledige changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 목록은 불완전합니다. 전체 변경 로그는 git 로그를 참조하십시오.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa lista è incompleta. Consultare git log per il changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="id">Daftar ini tidak lengkap. Lihat catatan git untuk daftar perubahan yang lengkap.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovaj popis je nepotpun. Pogledajte git zapis za potpuni pregled promjena.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette liste n’est pas complète. Pour voir tous les changements utilisez git log.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä luettelo on puutteellinen. Katso täydellinen git-muutosloki.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Zerrenda hau osatugabea da. Ikusi git log aldaketen zerrenda osorako.</p>
        <p lang="es">Este listado está incompleto. Consulte el registro de Git para obtener un registro de cambios completo.</p>
        <p lang="eo">La listo estas nekompleta. Uzu la komandon 'git log' por plena ŝanĝaro.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η καταχώρηση είναι ατελής. Δες την καταγραφή (log) του git για την πλήρη καταγραφή των αλλαγών (changelog).</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Liste ist unvollständig. Eine detaillierte Übersicht bietet das Changelog.</p>
        <p lang="da">Listen er ikke komplet. Se git-loggen for en komplet ændringslog.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tento seznam je neúplný. Úplný přehled změn najdete v git logu.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquest llistat és incomplet. Consulteu el registre del Git per obtenir un registre de canvis complet.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Списъкът не е завършен. Вижте Git лога за пълния списък с промени.</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذه القائمة غير مكتملة. انظر سجل بوابة التغيير الكامل.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.20" date="2020-09-19">
      <description>
        <p>
     This release contains the following changes:
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此發行版本包含了以下變更：</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">该发布版本包含了以下变更：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск містить такі зміни:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm aşağıdaki değişiklikleri içerir:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här versionen innehåller följande ändringar:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање садржи следеће измене:</p>
        <p lang="sl">This release contains the following changes:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje nasledujúce zmeny:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск содержит следующие изменения:</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera następujące zmiany:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze uitgave bevat de volgende aanpassingen:</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Denne utgaven inneholder følgende endringer:</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리스에는 다음 변경 사항이 포함됩니다:</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione contiene le seguenti modifiche:</p>
        <p lang="is">Þessi útgáfa inniheldur eftirfarandi breytingar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Ti version contene li sequent modificationes:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini berisi perubahan berikut:</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás a következő változtatásokat tartalmazza:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovo izdanje sadrži sljedeće promjene:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version apporte les changement suivants :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä julkaisu sisältää seuraavat muutokset:</p>
        <p lang="fa">این نسخه شامل تغییرات زیر است:</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek ondorengo aldaketak ditu:</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión contiene los cambios siguientes:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Ĉi tiu eldono enhavas la jenajn ŝanĝojn:</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση περιλαμβάνει τις παρακάτω αλλαγές:</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Veröffentlichungen umfasst die folgenden Änderungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Udgivelsen indeholder følgende ændringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tato verze obsahuje následující změny:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió conté els canvis següents:</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание съдържа следните промени:</p>
        <p lang="ar">يحتوي هذا الإصدار على التغييرات التالية:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>
      Make it possible to activate context menu when the playlist is empty.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">可以在播放列表为空时激活上下文菜单。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Відтепер можна увімкнути контекстне меню, коли добірка порожня.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Oynatma listesi boşken içerik menüsünü etkinleştirmeye izin ver.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Gör det möjligt att aktivera kontextmenyn när spellistan är tom.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Могуће је активирати приручни изборник када је списак пуштања празан.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Make it possible to activate context menu when the playlist is empty.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Появилась возможность открытия контекстного меню при пустом списке воспроизведения.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Tornar possível ativar o menu de contexto quando a lista de reprodução estiver vazia.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Possibilita ativar o menu de contexto quando a lista de reprodução estiver vazia.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Można teraz aktywować menu kontekstowe, kiedy lista odtwarzania jest pusta.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Maak het mogelijk om contextmenu te activeren als afspeellijst leeg is.</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Gjør det mulig å aktivere bindeleddsmeny når spillelisten er tom.</li>
          <li lang="ko">재생 목록이 비어있을 때 상황에 맞는 메뉴를 활성화 할 수 있습니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Rende possibile l'attivazione del menu contestuale quando la playlist è vuota.</li>
          <li lang="id">Memungkinkan untuk mengaktifkan menu konteks ketika daftar putar kosong.</li>
          <li lang="hu">Lehetővé teszi a helyi menü aktiválását, amikor a lejátszási lista üres.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Omogući aktiviranje sadržajnog izbornika kada je popis izvođenja prazan.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Permettre l’activation du menu contextuel lorsque la liste de lecture est vide.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Voit aktivoida pikavalikon, kun soittolista on tyhjä.</li>
          <li lang="fa">می‌گذارد هنگام خالی بودن سیاههٔ پخش، فهرست بافتاری فعّال شود.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Erreprodukzio-zerrenda hutsik dagoenean laster-menua aktibatzeko aukera eman.</li>
          <li lang="es">Permite activar el menú contextual cuando la lista de reproducción está vacía.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ebligi kuntekstan menuon eĉ se la spektolisto estas malplena.</li>
          <li lang="el">Κάνε εφικτή την ενεργοποίηση του context menu όταν η λίστα αναπαραγωγής είναι κενή.</li>
          <li lang="de">Anzeige des Kontextmenüs bei leerer Wiedergabeliste ermöglichen.</li>
          <li lang="da">Gør det muligt at aktivere genvejsmenuen når afspilningslisten er tom.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Kontextovou nabídku je možné vyvolat i při prázdném seznamu přehrávání.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Permet activar el menú de context quan la llista de reproducció és buida.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Да бъде възможно активирането на контекстното меню, когато списъкът е празен.</li>
          <li lang="ar">اجعل من الممكن تنشيط قائمة السياق عندما تكون قائمة التشغيل فارغة.</li>
          <li>
      Prevent constant resizing of the seek bar due to timestamp label resizing
      as its value changes.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">防止搜索栏因时间戳大小随值变化而频繁调整大小。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено ваду безперервної зміни розміру панелі прокручування викликану зміною значення мітки часу.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Zaman damgası etiketinin değeri değiştikçe yeniden boyutlandırılması nedeniyle arama çubuğunun sürekli yeniden boyutlandırılmasını önle.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Förhindra konstant ändring av storlek på tidslinjen då tidräknarens värde ändras.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Спречава се непрестана промена величине траке премотавања због промене величине натписа временског жига при променама његових вредности.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Prevent constant resizing of the seek bar due to timestamp label resizing as its value changes.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Убрано постоянное изменение размера полосы прокрутки из-за изменения размера метки времени.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Impedir o redimensionamento constante da barra de procura devido ao redimensionamento da etiqueta do selo temporal à medida que o seu valor muda.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Evita o redimensionamento constante da barra de busca devido ao redimensionamento do rótulo do carimbo de data / hora conforme seu valor muda.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Pasek przewijania nie zmienia już bez przerwy rozmiaru z powodu zmieniania się rozmiaru etykiety z czasem podczas odtwarzania.</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Forhindre konstant størrelsesendring i blafringsfeltet som følge av at tidsstempeletiketten endrer størrelse ettersom verdien endrer seg.</li>
          <li lang="ko">값이 변경 될 때 타임 스탬프 레이블 크기가 조정되어 탐색 막대의 지속적인 크기 조정을 방지합니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Prevenzione del ridimensionamento costante della barra di ricerca a causa del ridimensionamento dell'etichetta timestamp quando il suo valore cambia.</li>
          <li lang="id">Cegah pengubahan ukuran seek bar secara konstan karena perubahan ukuran label timestamp saat nilainya berubah.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Veličina trake premotavanja ostaje ista, neovisno o promjenama vrijednosti vremenske oznake.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Empêcher le redimensionnement constant de la barre de recherche lié au redimensionnement de l’étiquette d’horodatage lorsque sa valeur change.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Estä palkin jatkuva koon muuttaminen aikaleiman otsikon koon muuttuessa tai sen arvon muuttuessa.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Denbora-zigiluaren balioa aldatzean bere etiketaren tamaina aldatzearen ondorioz bilaketa-barraren tamaina etengabe tamainaz aldatzea eragotzi.</li>
          <li lang="es">Evita el cambio constante del tamaño de la barra de posición debido al cambio de tamaño de la etiqueta del cronomarcador a medida que cambia su valor.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ne konstante regrandigi la serĉobreton pro la ŝanĝado de la tempo-etikedo dum ludado.</li>
          <li lang="el">Αποφυγή της συνεχούς αναπροσαρμογής του μεγέθους της μπάρας αναζήτησης λόγω της αναπροσαρμογής του μεγέθους της ετικέτας χρονικής σήμανσης καθώς αλλάζει η τιμή της.</li>
          <li lang="de">Größe der Wiedergabe-Fortschrittsleiste wird unabhängig verschieden lang angezeigter Zahlenwerte konstant gehalten.</li>
          <li lang="da">Forhindr at størrelsen på søgelinjen konstant tilpasses pga. at størrelsen på tidsstempeletiketten tilpasses efterhånden som dens værdi ændres.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Oprava neustálých změn velikosti přehrávacího pruhu kvůli změnám velikosti ukazatele času.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Evita el canvi constant de la mida de la barra de cerca a causa del canvi de mida de l'etiqueta de la marca de temps a mesura que canvia el seu valor.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Предотвратяване на постоянното преоразмеряване на лентата за търсене поради преоразмеряването на етикета с времева щампа при промяна на стойността му.</li>
          <li lang="ar">منع التغيير المستمر لحجم شريط البحث بسبب تغيير حجم ملصق الطابع الزمني مع تغير قيمته.</li>
          <li>
      Only show a single error dialog when a large number of errors occurs in
      rapid succession.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">当大量的错误快速连续发生时，只显示一个错误对话框。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Показувати одне діалогове вікно помилок лише якщо виникає велика кількість помилок в одному сеансі.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Art arda çok sayıda hata oluştuğunda yalnızca tek bir hata iletişim kutusu göster.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Visa endast ett felmeddelande när ett stort antal fel uppstår i snabb följd</li>
          <li lang="sr">Приказује се само један прозорчић грешке када дође до великог броја грешака једне за другом.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Only show a single error dialog when a large number of errors occurs in rapid succession.</li>
          <li lang="ru">При большом количестве появляющихся подряд ошибок отображается только одно окно с ошибкой.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Apenas mostrar um único diálogo de erro quando ocorre um grande número de erros em sucessão rápida.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Mostra apenas uma única caixa de diálogo de erro quando um grande número de erros ocorre em rápida sucessão.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Wyświetlane jest tylko jedno okno z błędem, kiedy wystąpi duża liczba błędów w krótkim czasie.</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Kun vis én feildialog når et stort antall feil skjer i rask takt.</li>
          <li lang="ko">많은 수의 오류가 연속적으로 빠르게 발생할 때 하나의 오류 대화 상자 만 표시합니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Mostra solo una finestra di dialogo di errore quando si verifica un numero elevato di errori in rapida successione.</li>
          <li lang="id">Hanya tampilkan satu dialog kesalahan ketika sejumlah besar kesalahan terjadi secara berurutan dengan cepat.</li>
          <li lang="hu">Csak egy hibaüzenet-dialógus megjelenítése, amikor sok hiba történik gyorsan egymás után.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Prikaži samo jedan prozor greške kada se dogode brojne greške u brzom slijedu.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Montrer une seule boîte de dialogue d’erreur quand un large nombre d’erreurs se succèdent rapidement.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Näytä vain yksi virheikkuna, kun suuri määrä virheitä tapahtuu nopeasti peräkkäin.</li>
          <li lang="fa">هنگامی که تعداد زیادی خطا به سرعت رخ دهند، فقط یک گفت‌وگوی خطا نشان می‌دهد.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Errore kopuru handi bat azkar batean ematen direnean elkarrizketa-koadro bakarra erakutsi.</li>
          <li lang="es">Solo muestra un diálogo de error único cuando se produce un gran número de errores en una sucesión rápida.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Montri nur unu erardialogon, kiam multaj eraroj okazas rapide.</li>
          <li lang="el">Εμφάνιση μόνο ενός παραθύρου διαλόγου σφάλματος όταν μεγάλος αριθμός σφαλμάτων λαμβάνει χώρα σε γρήγορη διαδοχή.</li>
          <li lang="de">Im Falle mehrerer schnell aufeinander folgender Fehler wird nur eine Meldung angezeigt.</li>
          <li lang="da">Vis kun én fejldialog når der opstår et stort antal fejl hurtigt efter hinanden.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Při velkém počtu chyb, které nastanou v rychlém sledu, bude zobrazen pouze jeden chybový dialog.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Només mostra un diàleg d'error únic quan es produeix un gran nombre d'errors en una successió ràpida.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Да се показва само един диалогов прозорец за грешка при поява на голям брой грешки за кратко време.</li>
          <li lang="ar">أظهر مربع حوار خطأ واحد فقط عند حدوث عدد كبير من الأخطاء في تتابع سريع.</li>
          <li>
      Add menu item for opening folders.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加用于打开文件夹的菜单项。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано пункт меню для відкриття тек.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Klasörleri açmak için menü ögesi ekle.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Lägg till menyobjekt för att öppna mappar.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додата је ставка изборника за отварање фасцикли.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add menu item for opening folders.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлен пункт меню для открытия папок.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionar item de menu para abrir pastas.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adiciona item de menu para abrir pastas.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Menu otwierania katalogów.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Voeg menu-item toe om mappen te openen.</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Legg til menyelement for åpning av mapper.</li>
          <li lang="ko">폴더를 열기위한 메뉴 항목을 추가합니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta una voce al menu per aprire le cartelle.</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan item menu untuk membuka folder.</li>
          <li lang="hu">Menüelem hozzáadása mappák megnyitásához.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodaj stavku izbornika za otvaranje mapa.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout d’une entrée de menu pour ouvrir les répertoires.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää valikkoon kohde kansioiden avaamista varten.</li>
          <li lang="fa">افزودن مورد فهرست برای گشودن شاخه‌ها.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Karpetak irekitzeko menuko elementua gehitu.</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade un elemento al menú para abrir carpetas.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni menueron por malfermi dosierujojn.</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη αντικειμένου μενού για το άνοιγμα φακέλων.</li>
          <li lang="de">Menüeintrag zum Öffnen von Ordnern hinzufügen.</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj menupunkt til at åbne mapper.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Do nabídky přidána položka pro otevírání složek.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix un element al menú per obrir carpetes.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавяне на меню на елементите за отворените папки.</li>
          <li lang="ar">أضف عنصر قائمة لفتح المجلدات.</li>
          <li>
      Adjust position of UI elements of modal dialogs in non-CSD mode to be more
      consistent with CSD mode.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">调整非 CSD 模式下模态对话框 UI 元素的位置，使其与 CSD 模式更加一致。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Налаштовано розташування елементів інтерфейсу модальних вікон у режимі вимкненого CSD, щоб більше відповідати режиму CSD.</li>
          <li lang="tr">CSD olmayan modda kalıcı iletişim kutularının kullanıcı arayüzü ögelerinin konumunu CSD moduyla daha tutarlı olacak şekilde ayarla.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Justera positionen för UI-element i modala dialoger i icke CSD-läge för att bli mer konsekvent med CSD-läge.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Прилагођава се положај елемената корисничког сучеља модалних прозорчића у не-CSD режиму како би био доследнији са „CSD“ режимом.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Adjust position of UI elements of modal dialogs in non-CSD mode to be more consistent with CSD mode.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Настроена позиция элементов модальных окон в режиме отключенного CSD для большего соответствия с CSD режимом.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Ajustar a posição dos elementos de UI dos diálogos modais em modo não-CSD para ser mais consistente com o modo CSD.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Ajusta a posição dos elementos da IU de diálogos modais no modo não-CSD para ser mais consistente com o modo CSD.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Położenie elementów interfejsu w oknach dialogowych w trybie bez CSD jest spójniejsze z trybem CSD.</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Justering av posisjon for grensesnittelementer tilhørende bryterdialoger i ikke-skjermmenymodus for bedret samsvar med skjermmeny-modus.</li>
          <li lang="ko">비 CSD 모드에서 모달 대화 상자의 UI 요소 위치를 조정하여 CSD 모드와 더 일관성을 유지합니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Regola la posizione degli elementi della UI delle finestre di dialogo in modalità non CSD per essere più coerente con la modalità CSD.</li>
          <li lang="id">Sesuaikan posisi elemen UI dari dialog modal dalam mode non-CSD agar lebih konsisten dengan mode CSD.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Prilagodi položaj elemenata korisničkog sučelja modalnih dijaloga u ne-CSD načinu rada kako bi bili što dosljedniji s CSD načinom rada.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajuste la position des éléments d’interface utilisateur des boîtes de dialogue modales en mode non-CSD pour plus de consistance avec le mode CSD.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Säädä valintaikkunoiden sijaintia muussa kuin CSD-tilassa, joka olisi johdonmukaisempi CSD-tilan kanssa.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Elkarrizketa-koadro modalen interfazeko elementuen kokapena doitu ez-CSD moduetan, CSD moduarekin koherenteago izateko.</li>
          <li lang="es">Ajusta la posición de los elementos de la interfaz de usuario de los diálogos modales en el modo no CSD para ser más coherente con el modo CSD.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Kongruigi poziciojn de fasaderoj en dialogoj en la reĝimo sen klientflankaj ornamaĵoj kun tiuj en la reĝimo de klientflankaj ornamaĵoj.</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσαρμογή της θέσης στοιχείων UI των λειτουργικών παραθύρων διαλόγου στη λειτουργία non-CSD ώστε να είναι πιο συνεπή με τη λειτουργία CSD.</li>
          <li lang="de">Für den Nicht-CSD-Modus wurde die Anordnung der Elemente in modalen Dialogfenstern an die des CSD-Modus angepasst.</li>
          <li lang="da">Juster placeringen af brugerfladeelementer i modale dialoger i ikke-CSD-tilstand for at være mere konsistent med CSD-tilstand.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Upraveno umístění prvků uživatelského rozhraní v modálních dialozích, aby bylo konzistentní s CSD módem.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Ajusta la posició dels elements de la interfície d'usuari dels diàlegs modals en el mode no CSD per ser més coherent amb mode CSD.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Настройване на позицията на елементите на потребителския интерфейс на модалните диалогови прозорци в режим, който не е CSD, за да бъде по-съгласуван с режима CSD.</li>
          <li lang="ar">اضبط موضع عناصر واجهة المستخدم لمربعات الحوار المشروطة في الوضع غير CSD لتكون أكثر اتساقًا مع وضع CSD.</li>
          <li>
      Add support for loading external video tracks.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加对加载外部视频轨道的支持。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано підтримку завантаження зовнішніх відеодоріжок.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Harici video parçalarını yükleme desteği ekle.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Lägg till stöd för externa videospår</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додата је подршка за учитавање спољних видео нумера.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add support for loading external video tracks.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлена возможность подгрузки внешних видео дорожек.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionar apoio ao carregamento de faixas de vídeo externas.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adiciona suporte para carregar trilhas de vídeo externas.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Obsługa wczytywania zewnętrznych ścieżek wideo.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Voeg ondersteuning to voor het laden van externe videofragmenten.</li>
          <li lang="ko">외부 비디오 트랙로드 지원을 추가합니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunto il supporto per il caricamento di tracce video esterne.</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahan dukungan untuk memuat trek video eksternal.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana je podrška za učitavanje vanjskih videa.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout du support pour charger des pistes vidéo externes.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää tuki ulkoisten videoiden lataamiseen.</li>
          <li lang="fa">افزودن پشتیبانی از بار کردن قطعه‌های ویدیویی خارجی.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Kanpoko bideo-pistak kargatzeko euskarria gehitu.</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade la posibilidad de cargar pistas de vídeo externas.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Subteni ŝargadon de eksteraj filmaj trakoj.</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη υποστήριξης για τη φόρτωση εξωτερικών κομματιών βίντεο.</li>
          <li lang="de">Unerstützung für das Laden externer Videospuren.</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj understøttelse af indlæsning af eksterne videospor.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána podpora pro nahrávání externích stop videa.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix la possibilitat de carregar pistes de vídeo externes.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавяне на поддръжка за зареждане на външни видеозаписи.</li>
          <li lang="ar">أضف دعمًا لتحميل مسارات الفيديو الخارجية.</li>
          <li>
      Make playlist shuffle toggleable.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">使播放列表随机播放可切换。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано можливість перемикати перемішування добірки.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Oynatma listesini karıştırmayı değiştirilebilir hale getir.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Gör det möjligt att växla mellan spellistor.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Мешање списка пуштања се може окидати.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Make playlist shuffle toggleable.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Воспроизведение в случайном порядке сделано переключаемым.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Tornar a lista de reprodução baralhável.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Torna a reprodução aleatória da lista de reprodução alternável.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Można teraz przełączać losowe odtwarzanie listy odtwarzania.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Maak willekeurig afspelen van afspeellijst schakelbaar.</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Mulighet for å skru av og på tilfeldig avspilling i spilleliste.</li>
          <li lang="ko">재생 목록 셔플을 전환 가능하게 만듭니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Resa attivabile la riproduzione in ordine casuale delle playlist.</li>
          <li lang="id">Buat daftar putar dapat diacak.</li>
          <li lang="hu">Lejátszási lista keverésének kapcsolhatóvá tétele.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Omogući uključivanje/isključivanje naizmjenične reprodukcije popisa izvođenja.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Permettre le basculement de la liste de lecture en mode aléatoire.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Tee soittolistasta satunnainen.</li>
          <li lang="fa">بر زدن سیاههٔ پخش را قابل تغییر وضعیت می‌کند.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Erreprodukzio-zerrendak nahastea txandakatzeko aukera eman.</li>
          <li lang="es">Permite alternar la mezcla de las listas de reproducción.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Baskuligebligi miksadon de spektolisto.</li>
          <li lang="el">Κάνε το ανακάτεμα της λίστας αναπαραγωγής εναλλάξιμο.</li>
          <li lang="de">Zufällige Wiedergabe schnellschaltbar.</li>
          <li lang="da">Gør så bland afspilningsliste kan slås til/fra.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Míchání skladeb v seznamu přehrávání je možné přepínat.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Permet alternar la barreja de les llistes de reproducció.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Възможност за превключване на разбъркването на списъка.</li>
          <li lang="ar">جعل قائمة التشغيل قابلة للتبديل.</li>
          <li>
      Make arrow key bindings work with arrow keys on numpad.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">使箭头键绑定与小键盘上的箭头键一起使用。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Пов'язування клавіш зі стрілками з клавішами зі стрілками на числовій клавіатурі.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Ok tuşu atamalarının sayısal tuş takımındaki ok tuşlarıyla çalışmasını sağla.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Få piltangentens bindningar att fungera med piltangenterna på numerisk tangentbord.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Свезе тастера стрелица раде са тастерима стрелица на бројевном делу тастатуре.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Make arrow key bindings work with arrow keys on numpad.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Использовать клавиши со стрелками на цифровой панели.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Fazer com que as teclas de seta funcionem com as teclas de seta no teclado numérico.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Faz com que as setas do teclado funcionem com as teclas de seta no teclado numérico.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Skróty z klawiszami strzałek działają teraz ze strzałkami na klawiaturze numerycznej.</li>
          <li lang="ko">숫자 키패드의 화살표 키로 화살표 키 바인딩이 작동하도록합니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Fa in modo che le associazioni dei tasti freccia funzionino con i tasti freccia sul tastierino numerico.</li>
          <li lang="id">Jadikan keybinding tombol panah berfungsi dengan tombol panah di numpad.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Tipke sa strelicama funkcioniraju s tipkama sa strelicama na brojčanoj tastaturi.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Permettre aux raccourcis clavier des flèches de fonctionner avec les flèches du pavé numérique.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Nuolinäppäinten käyttäminen numeronäppäimistön nuolinäppäimillä.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Zenbakizko teklatuko geziak gezien laster-tekletan erabil daitezke.</li>
          <li lang="es">Hace que las combinaciones de teclas funcionen con las teclas de flecha del teclado numérico.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Funkciigi sagoklavojn en la nombra klavaro por klavkombinoj.</li>
          <li lang="el">Κάνε τις συνδέσεις πλήκτρων (key bindings) από τα βελάκια να λειτουργούν με τα βελάκια στο αριθμητικό πληκτρολόγιο.</li>
          <li lang="de">Tastenkombinationen funktionieren auch mit Tasten des Nummernfeldes.</li>
          <li lang="da">Gør så piletastbindinger virker med piletaster på det numeriske tastatur.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Klávesové zkratky fungují s šipkami na numerické klávesnici.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Fa que les combinacions de tecles funcionin amb les tecles de fletxa del teclat numèric.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Клавишите за посоки да могат да работят обвързано с клавишите на цифровата клавиатура.</li>
          <li lang="ar">جعل روابط مفاتيح الأسهم تعمل مع مفاتيح الأسهم على اللوحة الرقمية.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
     This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個清單不是完整的。請到 git log 中檢視完整的變更記錄。</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个列表不完整。请到 git log 中查看完整的 changelog。</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей перелік не повний. Вичерпний перелік змін перегляньте у журналі git.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu liste eksik. Değişikliklerin tamamı için git günlüğüne bakın.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här listan är ofullständig. Se git-loggen för fullständig ändringslogg.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Овај списак је непотпун. Видите гитов дневник за потпуни дневник измена.</p>
        <p lang="sl">This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Это не полный список. Полный список изменений см. в журнале git.</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta lista está incompleta. Consulte o registo git para ver todas as alterações.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta listagem está incompleta. Veja log git para changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta lista jest niepełna. Polecenie „git log” wyświetli pełną listę zmian.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze lijst is onvolledig. Zie git log voor volledige changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 목록은 불완전합니다. 전체 변경 로그는 git 로그를 참조하십시오.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa lista è incompleta. Consultare git log per il changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="id">Daftar ini tidak lengkap. Lihat catatan git untuk daftar perubahan yang lengkap.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovaj popis je nepotpun. Pogledajte git zapis za potpuni pregled promjena.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette liste n’est pas complète. Pour voir tous les changements utilisez git log.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä luettelo on puutteellinen. Katso täydellinen git-muutosloki.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Zerrenda hau osatugabea da. Ikusi git log aldaketen zerrenda osorako.</p>
        <p lang="es">Este listado está incompleto. Consulte el registro de Git para obtener un registro de cambios completo.</p>
        <p lang="eo">La listo estas nekompleta. Uzu la komandon 'git log' por plena ŝanĝaro.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η καταχώρηση είναι ατελής. Δες την καταγραφή (log) του git για την πλήρη καταγραφή των αλλαγών (changelog).</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Liste ist unvollständig. Eine detaillierte Übersicht bietet das Changelog.</p>
        <p lang="da">Listen er ikke komplet. Se git-loggen for en komplet ændringslog.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tento seznam je neúplný. Úplný přehled změn najdete v git logu.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquest llistat és incomplet. Consulteu el registre del Git per obtenir un registre de canvis complet.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Списъкът не е завършен. Вижте Git лога за пълния списък с промени.</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذه القائمة غير مكتملة. انظر سجل بوابة التغيير الكامل.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.19" date="2020-04-08">
      <description>
        <p>
     This release contains the following changes:
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此發行版本包含了以下變更：</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">该发布版本包含了以下变更：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск містить такі зміни:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm aşağıdaki değişiklikleri içerir:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här versionen innehåller följande ändringar:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање садржи следеће измене:</p>
        <p lang="sl">This release contains the following changes:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje nasledujúce zmeny:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск содержит следующие изменения:</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera następujące zmiany:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze uitgave bevat de volgende aanpassingen:</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Denne utgaven inneholder følgende endringer:</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리스에는 다음 변경 사항이 포함됩니다:</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione contiene le seguenti modifiche:</p>
        <p lang="is">Þessi útgáfa inniheldur eftirfarandi breytingar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Ti version contene li sequent modificationes:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini berisi perubahan berikut:</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás a következő változtatásokat tartalmazza:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovo izdanje sadrži sljedeće promjene:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version apporte les changement suivants :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä julkaisu sisältää seuraavat muutokset:</p>
        <p lang="fa">این نسخه شامل تغییرات زیر است:</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek ondorengo aldaketak ditu:</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión contiene los cambios siguientes:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Ĉi tiu eldono enhavas la jenajn ŝanĝojn:</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση περιλαμβάνει τις παρακάτω αλλαγές:</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Veröffentlichungen umfasst die folgenden Änderungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Udgivelsen indeholder følgende ændringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tato verze obsahuje následující změny:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió conté els canvis següents:</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание съдържа следните промени:</p>
        <p lang="ar">يحتوي هذا الإصدار على التغييرات التالية:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>
      Adjust the range of volume button based on the value of the volume-max
      property.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">根据 volume-max 属性的值调整音量按钮的范围。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Налаштування меж гучності на основі значення властивості volume-max.</li>
          <li lang="tr">volume-max özelliğinin değerine göre ses düğmesi aralığını ayarla.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Justera intervallet för volymknappen baserat på värdet på egenskapen volym-max.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Прилагођава се опсег дугмета гласности на основу вредности својства нејвеће гласности.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Adjust the range of volume button based on the value of the volume-max property.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Установка диапазона кнопки громкости в зависимости от свойства volume-max.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Ajuste o intervalo do botão de volume com base no valor da propriedade volume-max.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Ajuste o botão do intervalo de volume, com base no valor da propriedade volume-máximo.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Dostosowanie zakresu przycisku głośności na podstawie wartości własności „volume-max”.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Stel het bereik van de volumeknop in op basis van de volume-max eigenschappen</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Juster lydstyrkespenn for lydstyrkeknapp basert på verdien av «volume-max».</li>
          <li lang="ko">volume-max 속성의 값에 따라 볼륨 버튼의 범위를 조정합니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Regolazione dell'intervallo del pulsante del volume basata sul valore della proprietà volume-max.</li>
          <li lang="id">Sesuaikan rentang tombol volume berdasarkan nilai properti volume-max.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Prilagodba raspona tipke glasnoće zvuka temeljene na vrijednosti svojstva najveće glasnoće zvuka.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajuste la portée du bouton de volume en se basant sur la valeur de la propriété volume-max.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Säädä painikkeen aluetta äänenvoimakkuuden enimmäisarvon mukaan.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Bolumenaren botoiaren tartea gehienezko bolumena propietatearen balioaren arabera doitu.</li>
          <li lang="es">Ajusta el rango del botón de volumen basándose en el valor de la propiedad «volumen máximo».</li>
          <li lang="eo">Agordi la gamon de la laŭto laŭ la atributo 'volume-max'.</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσαρμογή της έκτασης του πλήκτρου έντασης ήχου βασισμένη στην τιμή της ιδιότητας volume-max.</li>
          <li lang="de">Die Spanne des Lautstärkereglers kann über den Wert volume-max beeinflusst werden.</li>
          <li lang="da">Juster lydstyrkeknappens område baseret på værdien af egenskaben volume-max.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Rozsah klávesy hlasitosti přizpůsobit na základě hodnoty volume-max.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Ajusta el rang del botó de volum basant-se en el valor de la propietat «volum màxim».</li>
          <li lang="bg">Регулиране диапазона на бутона за усилване въз основа на зададените от вас стойности за максимално ниво.</li>
          <li lang="ar">اضبط نطاق زر الصوت بناءً على قيمة خاصية Volume-max.</li>
          <li>
      Retain window maximization state across sessions.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">跨会话保留窗口最大化状态。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Зберігати стан розгорнутих вікон у всіх сеансах.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Oturumlar arasında pencere büyütme durumunu koru.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Behåll fönstrets maximeringstillstånd över sessioner.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Задржава се стање увећаности прозора кроз сесије.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Retain window maximization state across sessions.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Сохранение режима развернутого окна между сессиями.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Manter o estado de maximização da janela ao longo das sessões.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Manter o estado de maximização da janela entre as sessões.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zachowywanie stanu maksymalizacji okna między sesjami.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Behoud maximale venstergrootte tussen verschillende sessies</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Vedvarende vindusmaksimeringstilstand mellom økter.</li>
          <li lang="ko">세션 전체에서 창 최대화 상태를 유지합니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Ricorda lo stato dalla massimizzazione della finestra da una sessione all'altra.</li>
          <li lang="id">Pertahankan status maksimalisasi jendela di seluruh sesi.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Zadržavanje stanja uvećanog prozora po sesijama.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Retenir l’état de maximisation de la fenêtre entre les sessions.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Säilytä ikkunan maksimitila istuntojen välillä.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Leihoaren maximizazio egoera mantendu saioen artean.</li>
          <li lang="es">Recuerda el estado de maximización de la ventana.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Konservi maksimumecon de fenestroj inter seancoj.</li>
          <li lang="el">Διατήρηση της κατάστασης μεγιστοποίησης του παραθύρου σε όλες τις συνεδρίες.</li>
          <li lang="de">Fenstermaximierungsstatus wird über Sitzungen hinweg beibehalten.</li>
          <li lang="da">Bibehold vinduets maksimeret tilstand på tværs af sessioner.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zachovat stav maximalizace okna napříč relacemi.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Recorda l'estat de maximització de la finestra.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Запазване състоянието на максимизиран прозорец през сесиите.</li>
          <li lang="ar">الاحتفاظ بحالة تكبير النافذة عبر الجلسات.</li>
          <li>
      Retain loop state across sessions.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">跨会话保持循环状态。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Зберігати режим повторення у всіх сеансах.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Oturumlar arasında döngü durumunu koru.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Behåll fönstrets maximeringstillstånd över sessioner.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Задржава се стање понављања кроз сесије.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Retain loop state across sessions.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Сохранение режима повтора между сессиями.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Manter o estado do ciclo ao longo das sessões.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Manter o estado do loop entre as sessões.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zachowywanie stanu powtarzania między sesjami.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Behoud herhaalinstelling tussen verschillende sessies</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Vedvarende gjentagelsestilstand mellom økter.</li>
          <li lang="ko">세션 전체에서 루프 상태를 유지합니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Ricorda lo stato della ripetizione da una sessione all'altra.</li>
          <li lang="id">Pertahankan status putar ulang di seluruh sesi.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Zadržavanje stanja ponavljanja po sesijama.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Retenir l’état des boucles entre les sessions.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Säilytä toisto tauotta koko istunnon ajan.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Begiztaren egoera saioen artean mantendu.</li>
          <li lang="es">Recuerda el estado de la reproducción en bucle.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Konservi ripetontecon inter seancoj.</li>
          <li lang="el">Διατήρηση της κατάστασης loop σε όλες τις συνεδρίες.</li>
          <li lang="de">Wiederholungspräferenzen wird über Sitzungen hinweg beibehalten.</li>
          <li lang="da">Bibehold løkketilstand på tværs af sessioner.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zachovat stav smyčky napříč relacemi.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Recorda l'estat de la reproducció en bucle.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Запазване на състоянието на превъртане през сесиите.</li>
          <li lang="ar">احتفظ بحالة الحلقة عبر الجلسات.</li>
          <li>
      Implement playlist search.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">实现播放列表搜索。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Впроваджено пошук у добірці.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Oynatma listesi aramasını uygula.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Implementera sökning i spellista.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Примењена је претрага списка пуштања.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Implement playlist search.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Реализован поиск по списку воспроизведения.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Implementar a pesquisa na lista de reprodução.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Implementar pesquisa na lista de reprodução.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Implementacja wyszukiwania na liście odtwarzania.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Implementeer zoeken in afspeellijst</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Implementering av spillelistesøk.</li>
          <li lang="ko">재생 목록 검색을 구현합니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Implementata la ricerca nella playlist.</li>
          <li lang="id">Mengimplementasikan pencarian daftar putar.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Implemetirana je pretraga popisa izvođenja.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Implémentation de la recherche dans les listes de lecture.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Ota soittolistan haku käyttöön.</li>
          <li lang="fa">جست‌وجوی سیاههٔ پخش پیاده‌شد.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Erreprodukzio-zerrenden bilaketa inplementatu.</li>
          <li lang="es">Implementa la búsqueda en la lista de reproducción.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ebligi serĉadon de spektolisto.</li>
          <li lang="el">Υλοποίηση αναζήτησης της λίστας αναπαραγωγής.</li>
          <li lang="de">Suche in Wiedergabelisten implementiert.</li>
          <li lang="da">Implementer søgning i afspilningsliste.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Implementovat vyhledávání v seznamu přehrávání.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Implementa la cerca a la llista de reproducció</li>
          <li lang="bg">Внедряване на търсене в списъка.</li>
          <li lang="ar">تنفيذ البحث في قائمة التشغيل.</li>
          <li>
      Update the list of shortcuts in Keyboard Shortcuts dialog.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">更新快捷键对话框中的快捷方式列表。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Оновлено список комбінацій клавіш у діалоговому вікні комбінацій клавіш.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Klavye Kısayolları iletişim kutusundaki kısayolların listesini güncelle.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Освежава се списак пречица у прозорчету пречица тастатуре.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Update the list of shortcuts in Keyboard Shortcuts dialog.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обновлен список комбинаций клавиш.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Atualize a lista de atalhos na janela de teclas de atalho.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Atualizar a lista de atalhos na caixa de diálogo, Atalhos do teclado.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Aktualizacja listy skrótów w oknie skrótów klawiszowych.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Werk de lijst met sneltoetsen bij in het dialoogvenster Sneltoetsen</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Oppdater listen over snarveier i tastatursnarveisdialogen.</li>
          <li lang="ko">키보드 단축키 대화 상자에서 단축키 목록을 업데이트합니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiornata la lista della scorciatoie nell'apposita finestra di dialogo.</li>
          <li lang="id">Memperbarui daftar pintasan di dialog Pintasan Papan Ketik.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Nadopunjen je popis prečaca u dijalogu prečaca tipkovnice.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Mise à jour de la liste des raccourcis dans la boîte dialogue des raccourcis clavier.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Päivitä pikanäppäinten luettelo pikanäppäimet-valintaikkunassa.</li>
          <li lang="fa">به‌روز رسانی سیاههٔ میان‌برها در گفت‌وگوی میان‌برهای صفحه‌کلید.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Laster-teklak elkarrizketa-koadroko zerrenda eguneratu.</li>
          <li lang="es">Actualiza la lista de atajos en el diálogo de los atajos del teclado.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝisdatigi la liston de klavkombinoj en la dialogo Klavkombinoj.</li>
          <li lang="el">Ενημέρωση της λίστας συντομεύσεων στο παράθυρο διαλόγου Συντομεύσεις Πληκτρολογίου.</li>
          <li lang="de">Liste der Tastenkombinationen aktualisiert.</li>
          <li lang="da">Opdater listen over genveje i dialogen Tastaturgenveje.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Aktualizovat seznam klávesových zkratek.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Actualitza la llista de dreceres en el diàleg de les dreceres de teclat.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Обновяване на списъка с бързи клавиши в диалога Бързи клавиши.</li>
          <li lang="ar">قم بتحديث قائمة الاختصارات في مربع حوار اختصارات لوحة المفاتيح.</li>
          <li>
      Correctly handle quotes and escape sequences in extra mpv options.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">正确处理额外 MPV 选项中的引号和转义序列。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Правильна обробка лапок та екранувальних послідовностей у додаткових параметрах mpv.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Ek mpv seçeneklerinde tırnak işaretlerini ve kaçış dizilerini doğru şekilde işle.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Исправно ради са наводницима и знацима краја реда у додатним „mpv“ опцијама.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Correctly handle quotes and escape sequences in extra mpv options.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлена обработка кавычек и экранирующих последовательностей в дополнительных параметрах mpv.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Manusear correctamente as citações e as sequências de escape em opções de extra mpv.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Manuseie corretamente as citações e sequências de escape em opções extras do mpv.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Właściwa obsługa cudzysłowów i sekwencji sterujących w dodatkowych opcjach mpv.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Behandel citaten en escape-reeksen correct in extra mpv-opties</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Korrekt håndtering av sitat og skiftesekvenser i ekstra mpv-innstillinger.</li>
          <li lang="ko">추가 mpv 옵션에서 따옴표와 이스케이프 시퀀스를 올바르게 처리합니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Gestione corretta delle virgolette e delle esclusioni nelle opzioni di mpv.</li>
          <li lang="id">Tangani kutipan dan urutan keluar dengan benar dalam opsi mpv tambahan.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Ispravljeno je rukovanje s navodnicima i escape nizovima u dodatnim mpv mogućnostima.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Gère correctement les guillemets et les séquences d’échappement dans les options supplémentaires de mpv.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Käsitelle oikein lainaumerkkejä ja erikoismerkkejä MPV valinnoissa.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Komatxoak eta ihes sekuentziak zuzen maneiatu mpv-ren aukera gehigarrietan.</li>
          <li lang="es">Maneja correctamente las comillas y las secuencias de escape en las opciones extra de mpv.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝuste trakti citilojn kaj specialajn signojn en ekstraj opcioj de MPV.</li>
          <li lang="el">Σωστός χειρισμός εισαγωγικών και αλληλουχιών διαφυγής στις επιπλέον επιλογές του mpv.</li>
          <li lang="de">Korrektes Interpretieren von Escape-Sequenzen und Anführungszeichen in Extra-MPV-Optionen.</li>
          <li lang="da">Korrekt håndtering af citationstegn og undvigesekvenser i ekstra mpv-tilvalg.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zacházet správně s uvozovkami a escape sekvencemi v rozšířených možnostech mpv.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Gestiona correctament les cometes i les seqüències d'escapada en les opcions extra de MPV.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Коректна работа с цитати и избягване на последователности в допълнителни опции за mpv.</li>
          <li lang="ar">تعامل بشكل صحيح مع علامات الاقتباس وإلغاء التسلسلات في خيارات mpv الإضافية.</li>
          <li>
      Display time at cursor position when hovering the seek bar.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">当鼠标悬停在进度条时，在光标位置显示时间。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Показ часу біля положення курсора під час наведення вказівника миші на панель прокручування.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Arama çubuğunun üzerine gelindiğinde imleç konumunda süreyi görüntüle.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Приказује се време на положају курзора када се наднесе над траком премотавања.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Display time at cursor position when hovering the seek bar.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Отображение времени возле курсора при наведении на панель прокрутки.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Mostrar o tempo na posição do cursor ao passar o rato na barra de pesquisa.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Mostra o tempo na posição do cursor ao passar o mouse na barra de busca.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Wyświetlanie czasu w pozycji kursora po najechaniu na pasek przewijania.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Geef de tijd weer op de cursorpositie wanneer u de zoekbalk beweegt</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Vis tid i pekerposisjon når pekeren holdes over blafrefeltet.</li>
          <li lang="ko">탐색 막대를 가리키면 커서 위치에 시간이 표시됩니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Mostra il tempo quando il cursore si sovrappone alla barra di selezione.</li>
          <li lang="id">Tampilkan waktu di posisi kursor saat posisi kursor di seek bar.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Prikaz vremena na položaju pokazivača pri prelasku preko trake pretrage.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Affiche le temps à la position du pointeur lors du survol de la barre de recherche.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Näytä aika kohdistimessa kun siirrät hakupalkkia.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Denbora kurtsoaren posizioan bistaratu bilaketa-barraren gainean jartzean.</li>
          <li lang="es">Muestra el tiempo junto al puntero al situarlo sobre la barra de posición.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Montri tempon ĉe la musmontrilo dum ĝi estas super la serĉobreto.</li>
          <li lang="el">Προβολή του χρόνου στη θέση του δρομέα κατά την αιώρηση πάνω από τη μπάρα αναζήτησης.</li>
          <li lang="de">Anzeige der Zeit, wenn der Mauszeiger über die Suchbar geführt wird.</li>
          <li lang="da">Vis tidspunktet ved markørens placering når der holdes over søgelinjen.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zobrazit čas na pozici kurzoru při najetí na přehrávací pruh.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Mostra el temps en la posició del punter en situar-lo en la barra de cerca.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Показване на време в позицията на курсора, когато се намира в лентата за търсене.</li>
          <li lang="ar">عرض الوقت في موضع المؤشر عند تحريك شريط البحث.</li>
          <li>
      Deprecate '--mpv-options'. Options starting with '--mpv-' can be
      used to set mpv options instead. For example, passing
      '--mpv-vf=vflip' to Celluloid is equivalent to passing
      '--vf=vflip' to mpv.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">弃用“--mpv-options”。以 '--mpv-' 开头的选项可用于设置 mpv 选项。例如，将 '--mpv-vf=vflip' 传递给 Celluloid 相当于将 '--vf=vflip' 传递给 mpv。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Припинено підтримку '--mpv-options'. Натомість можна застосовувати параметри, що починаються на '--mpv-' для встановлення параметрів mpv. Наприклад, передавання '--mpv-vf=vflip' до Celluloid еквівалентне передаванню '--vf=vflip' to mpv.</li>
          <li lang="tr">'--mpv-options' seçeneğini kullanımdan kaldır. Bunun yerine, '--mpv-' ile başlayan seçenekler mpv seçeneklerini ayarlamak için kullanılabilir. Örneğin, Celluloid ile '--mpv-vf=vflip' seçeneğini kullanmak, mpv ile '--vf=vflip' seçeneğini kullanmakla aynıdır.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Застарела је опција „--mpv-options“. Опције које почињу са „--mpv-“ се могу користити за постављање „mpv“ опција уместо тога. На пример, давање опције „--mpv-vf=vflip“ Целулоиду је исто што и давање опције „--vf=vflip“ „mpv“-у.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Deprecate '--mpv-options'. Options starting with '--mpv-' can be used to set mpv options instead. For example, passing '--mpv-vf=vflip' to Celluloid is equivalent to passing '--vf=vflip' to mpv.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Параметр '--mpv-options' устарел. Для указания параметров mpv используется префикс '--mpv-'. Например, параметр Celluloid '--mpv-vf=vflip' соответствует параметру mpv '--vf=vflip'.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Depreciar "--mpv-opções". Opções que começam com '--mpv-' podem ser usadas para definir opções de mpv. Por exemplo, passar '--mpv-vf=vflip' para Celluloid é equivalente a passar '--vf=vflip' para mpv.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Preterir '--mpv-options'. Opções começando com '--mpv-' podem ser usadas para definir as opções do mpv. Por exemplo, passar '--mpv-vf = vflip' para o Celluloid é equivalente a passar '--vf = vflip' para o mpv.</li>
          <li lang="pl">„--mpv-options” jest przestarzałe. Zamiast tego do ustawiania opcji mpv można używać opcji zaczynających się od „--mpv-”. Na przykład przekazanie „--mpv-vf=vflip” do programu Celluloid jest odpowiednikiem przekazania „--vf=vflip” do mpv.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Beëindig '--mpv-opties'. Opties die beginnen met '--mpv-' kunnen in plaats daarvan worden gebruikt om mpv-opties in te stellen. Het doorgeven van '--mpv-vf = vflip' aan Celluloid is bijvoorbeeld gelijk aan het doorgeven van '--vf = vflip' aan mpv</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Foreldelse av '--mpv-options'-valg som starter med '--mpv-' kan brukes for å sette mpv-valg istedenfor. For eksempel er det å sende '--mpv-vf=vflip' til Celluloid det samme som å sende '--vf=vflip' til mpv.</li>
          <li lang="ko">'--mpv-options'를 사용하지 않습니다. 대신 '--mpv-'로 시작하는 옵션을 사용하여 mpv 옵션을 설정할 수 있습니다. 예를 들어 '--mpv-vf = vflip'을 Celluloid에 전달하는 것은 '--vf = vflip'을 mpv에 전달하는 것과 같습니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">'--mpv-options' obsoleto. Le opzioni che iniziano con '--mpv-' possono essere usate come opzioni di mpv. Per esempio, '--mpv-vf=vflip' in Celluloid è l'equivalente di '--vf=vflip' in mpv.</li>
          <li lang="id">Hilangkan '--mpv-options'. Opsi yang dimulai dengan '--mpv-' dapat digunakan untuk menyetel opsi mpv. Misalnya, meneruskan '--mpv-vf=vflip' ke Celluloid sama dengan meneruskan '--vf=vflip' ke mpv.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Zastarjelo '--mpv-options'. Mogućnosti koje započinju s '--mpv-' umjesto se mogu koristiti za postavljanje mpv mogućnosti. Na primjer, prosljeđivanje '--mpv-vf=vflip' u Celluloid je ekvivalent prosljeđivanju '--vf=vflip' u mpv.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Rendre obsolète « --mpv-options ». Les options commençant avec « --mpv- » peuvent être utilisées pour régler des options de mpv à la place. Par example, activer « --mpv-vf=vflip » dans Celluloid revient à activer « --vf=vflip » dans mpv.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Jätä väliin '--mpv-options'. Asetukset, jotka alkavat '--mpv-' voidaan asettaa mpv-asetusten sen sijaan. Esimerkiksi, '--mpv-vf=vflip' on Celluloidin vastaava ohitus '--vf=vflip' mpv:n tilalle.</li>
          <li lang="eu">'--mpv-options' zaharkitutzat jo. Horren ordez '--mpv-' aurrizkiarekin hasten diren aukerak erabil daitezke mpv-ren aukerak ezartzeko. Adibidez, Celluloidi '--mpv-vf=vflip' pasatzea mpv-ri '--vf=vflip' pasatzearen baliokidea da.</li>
          <li lang="es">Desaprueba «--mpv-options». En su lugar, para configurar opciones de mpv, se pueden usar opciones que empiecen por «--mpv-». Por ejemplo, pasar «--mpv-vf=vflip» a Celulloid equivale a pasar «--vf=vflip» a mpv.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Evitindigi '--mpv-options'. Opcioj komencantaj per '--mpv-' estas uzindaj por agordi opciojn de MPV anstataŭe. Ekzemple, pasi la opcion '--mpv-vf=vflip' al Celuloido ekvivalentas pasi '--vf=vflip' al MPV.</li>
          <li lang="el">Κατάργηση '--mpv-options'. Οι επιλογές που ξεκινούν με '--mpv' μπορούν να χρησιμοποιηθούν για τον ορισμό επιλογών του mpv αντί αυτού. Για παράδειγμα, περνώντας '--mpv-vf=vflip' στον Celluloid είναι ισοδύναμο με το να περνάς '--vf=vflip' στον mpv.</li>
          <li lang="de">Die Option der Kommandozeilenschnittstelle '--mpv-options' ist als veraltet markiert. Optionen beginnend mit 'mpv-' können stattdessen verwendet werden, um mpv-Optionen zu verwenden. So entspricht die Celluloid-Option '--mpv-vf=vflip' der mpv-Option '--vf=vflip'.</li>
          <li lang="da">Gør '--mpv-tilvalg' udgået. Tilvalg som begynder med '--mpv-' kan i stedet bruges til at indstille mpv-tilvalg. Hvis man f.eks. angiver '--mpv-vf=vflip' til Celluloid, så svarer det til at angive '--vf=vflip' til mpv.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zastaralá volba „--mpv-options“. K nastavení možností mpv lze místo toho použít volby začínající na „--mpv-“. Například předání „--mpv-vf=vflip“ Celluloidu je ekvivalentní předání „--vf=vflip“ mpv.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Desaprova «--mpv-options». En el seu lloc, per configurar opcions de mpv, es poden fer servir opcions que comencin per «--mpv-». Per exemple, passar «--mpv-vf=vflip» al Celluloid equival a passar «--vf=vflip» a mpv.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Изтегляне на '--mpv-опции'. Опциите, започващи с '--mpv-', могат да се използват вместо задаване на mpv опции. Например, поставянето на  на '--mpv-vf=vflip' в Celluloid е еквивалентно на поставянето '--vf=vflip' в mpv.</li>
          <li lang="ar">اهمال "--mpv-options". يمكن استخدام الخيارات التي تبدأ ب "--mpv-" لتعيين خيارات mpv بدلاً من ذلك. على سبيل المثال ، تمرير "--mpv-vf = vflip" إلى Celluloid يعادل تمرير "--vf = vflip" إلى mpv.</li>
          <li>
      Add support for configuring dead zone, an area in which mouse movement
      will not cause controls to be shown.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加对配置死区的支持，死区是鼠标移动不会导致控件显示的区域。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано підтримку налаштування мертвої зони , ділянки, в якій пересування миші не призведе до показу елементів керування.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Fare hareketinin kontrollerin gösterilmesine neden olmayacağı bir alan olan ölü bölgeyi yapılandırma desteği ekle.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додата је подршка за подешавање мртве зоне, области у којој покрет миша неће довести до приказивања контрола.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add support for configuring dead zone, an area in which mouse movement will not cause controls to be shown.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлена возможность настройки мертвой зоны в которой движение курсора не будет приводить к показу панели управления.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionar suporte para a configuração da zona morta, uma área em que o movimento do rato não fará com que os controlos sejam mostrados.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionado suporte para configurar a zona morta, uma área na qual o movimento do mouse não fará com que os controles sejam mostrados.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Obsługa konfigurowania martwej strefy, w której ruch kursora nie spowoduje wyświetlenia przycisków sterujących.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Voeg ondersteuning toe voor het configureren van de dode zone, een gebied waarin muisbewegingen geen bediening zullen veroorzaken</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Støtte for oppsett av dødsone. Et område der musebevegelse ikke forårsaker visning av kontroller.</li>
          <li lang="ko">마우스 움직임으로 인해 컨트롤이 표시되지 않는 영역 인 데드 존 구성 지원을 추가합니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunto supporto alla dead zone, un'area nella quale i movimenti del cursore non invocheranno i controlli a schermo.</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan dukungan untuk mengkonfigurasi zona mati, area di mana gerakan mouse tidak akan menyebabkan kontrol ditampilkan.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana je mogućnost podešavanja mrtve zone, područje u kojemu pomicanje miša neće prouzročiti prikazivanje upravljačkih tipki.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout du support pour configurer une zone morte, une zone dans laquelle le mouvement du pointeur n’entraînera pas l’apparition des contrôles.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää tuki kuolleiden alueiden määrittämiselle. Alue, jolla hiiren liikkuminen ei aiheuta ohjauksen kuvakkeita näkyviin.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Zonalde hila konfiguratzeko euskarria gehitu, saguaren mugimenduek kontrolak bistaraziko ez dituzten eremua.</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade apoyo para configurar una zona muerta, un área en la que el movimiento del ratón no causará que se muestren los controles.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Subteni zonon, en kiu movo de la musmontrilo ne montros la butonojn.</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη υποστήριξης για τη διαμόρφωση νεκρής ζώνης, μιας περιοχής στην οποία η κίνηση του ποντικιού δε θα προκαλεί την εμφάνιση των εργαλείων ελέγχου.</li>
          <li lang="de">Es kann eine tote Zone angegeben werden, innerhalb derer Mauszeigerbewegung nicht zur Anzeige der Kontrollflächen führt.</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj understøttelse af konfiguration af død zone, et område hvor musebevægelser ikke får styringen til at blive vist.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidat podporu pro nastavení mrtvé zóny, tj. oblasti, ve které pohyb myši nezpůsobí zobrazení ovládacích prvků.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix suport per configurar una zona morta, una àrea en la qual el moviment del ratolí no farà que es mostrin controls.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавена е поддръжка за конфигуриране на "мъртва зона" - зона, в която движението на мишката няма да доведе до показване на контролите.</li>
          <li lang="ar">أضف دعمًا لتكوين المنطقة الميتة ، وهي منطقة لا تؤدي فيها حركة الماوس إلى إظهار عناصر التحكم.</li>
          <li>
      Make window sizing work correctly with HiDPI displays.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">让调整窗口大小可以在 HiDPI 显示下正常工作。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено розміри вікна для дисплеїв з HiDPI.</li>
          <li lang="tr">HiDPI ekranlarla pencere boyutlandırmasının doğru çalışmasını sağla.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Få fönsterstorleken att fungera korrekt med HiDPI-skärmar.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Сразмеравање прозора ради исправно са „HiDPI“ екранима.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Make window sizing work correctly with HiDPI displays.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлены размеры окна на HiDPI-дисплеях.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Faça o dimensionamento correto das janelas com os monitores HiDPI.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Faz o dimensionamento da janela funcionar corretamente em monitores HiDPI.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Rozmiar okna działa teraz poprawnie na ekranach o wysokiej rozdzielczości.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Zorg ervoor dat venstergrootte correct werkt met HiDPI-schermen</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Korrekt endring av vindusstørrelse for HiDPI-skjermer.</li>
          <li lang="ko">HiDPI 디스플레이에서 창 크기 조정이 올바르게 작동하도록합니다.</li>
          <li lang="it">Corretta la grandezza della finestra sugli schermi HiDPI.</li>
          <li lang="id">Buat pengaturan jendela berfungsi dengan benar dengan display HiDPI.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Promjena veličine prozora na zaslonima visoke razlučivosti (HiDPI) sada radi ispravno.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Permettre le redimensionnement correct des fenêtres avec les affichages HiDPI.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Tee ikkunoiden mitoitus oikein HiDPI-näytöillä.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Leiho tamainak HiDPI pantailetan behar bezala funtzionatzea.</li>
          <li lang="es">Ajusta el tamaño de la ventana correctamente en pantallas de alta densidad (HiDPI).</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝuste agordi dimensiojn de fenestroj sur densbilderaj ekranoj.</li>
          <li lang="el">Κάνε την αλλαγή του μεγέθους του παραθύρου να λειτουργεί σωστά με HiDPI οθόνες.</li>
          <li lang="de">Korrigierte Fenstergröße für HiDPI-Bildschirme.</li>
          <li lang="da">Få vinduesstørrelser til at virke korrekt med HiDPI-skærme.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zajistit, aby nastavení velikosti okna fungovalo správně na displejích s vysokým rozlišením.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Ajusta la mida de la finestra correctament en pantalles d'alta densitat (HiDPI).</li>
          <li lang="bg">Задаване на оразмеряването на прозореца да работи правилно с HiDPI дисплеи.</li>
          <li lang="ar">اجعل حجم النافذة يعمل بشكل صحيح مع شاشات HiDPI.</li>
          <li>
      Add Finnish translation by Kimmo Kujansuu.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加 Kimmo Kujansuu 贡献的芬兰语翻译。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано переклад фінською від Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Fince çeviriyi hazırlayan Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Lägg till Finsk översättning av Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додат је превод на фински који је урадио Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add Finnish translation by Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлен финский перевод от Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Tradução do Finlandês por Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionada a tradução finlandesa por Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nowe tłumaczenie na język fiński od Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Finse vertaling toegevoegd door Kimmo Kujansuu</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Finsk oversettelse ved Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="ko">Kimmo Kujansuu의 핀란드어 번역을 추가.</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta traduzione finlandese di Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="is">Bætt við finnskri þýðingu eftir Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="id">Menambahkan terjemahan Bahasa Finlandia oleh Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Finski prijevod je dodao Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout de la traduction finnoise par Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää suomenkielinen käännös, tekiä Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="fa">افزودن ترجمهٔ فنلاندی‌به دست کیمو کوجانسو.</li>
          <li lang="eu">Kimmo Kujansuu-ren suomierazko itzulpena gehitu.</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade la traducción al finlandés hecha por Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni finnlingvigon de Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη Φινλανδικής μετάφρασης από Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="de">Finnische Übersetzung beigesteuert von Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj finsk oversættelse af Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidán překlad do finštiny od Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix la traducció al finlandès feta per Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавен е фински превод от Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li lang="ar">أضف الترجمة الفنلندية بواسطة Kimmo Kujansuu.</li>
          <li>
      Add Slovenian translation by @bertronika.
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加 @bertronika 贡献的斯洛文尼亚语翻译。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано переклад словенською від @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="tr">Slovence çeviriyi hazırlayan @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="sv">Lägg till Slovensk översättning av @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додат је превод на словеначки који је урадио „@bertronika“.</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add Slovenian translation by @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлен словенский перевод от @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Tradução do Esloveno por @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionada tradução eslovena por @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nowe tłumaczenie na język słoweński od @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="nl">Sloveense vertaling toevoegd door @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Slovensk oversettelse ved @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="ko">@bertronika의 슬로베니아어 번역을 추가.</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta traduzione slovena di @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="is">Bætt við slóvenskri þýðingu eftir @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="id">Menambahkan terjemahan Bahasa Slovenia oleh @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="hr">Slovenski prijevod je dodao @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout de la traduction slovène par @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisätty Slovenian kielipaketti lähettäjä @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="eu">@bertronika-ren eslovenierazko itzulpena gehitu.</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade la traducción al esloveno hecha por @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni slovenlingvigon de @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη Σλοβενικής μετάφρασης από @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="de">Slowenische Übersetzung beigesteuert von @bertonika.</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj slovensk oversættelse af @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidán překlad do slovinštiny od @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix la traducció a l'eslovè feta per @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавен е словенски превод от @bertronika.</li>
          <li lang="ar">أضف الترجمة السلوفينية بواسطة @bertronika.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
     This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個清單不是完整的。請到 git log 中檢視完整的變更記錄。</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个列表不完整。请到 git log 中查看完整的 changelog。</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей перелік не повний. Вичерпний перелік змін перегляньте у журналі git.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu liste eksik. Değişikliklerin tamamı için git günlüğüne bakın.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här listan är ofullständig. Se git-loggen för fullständig ändringslogg.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Овај списак је непотпун. Видите гитов дневник за потпуни дневник измена.</p>
        <p lang="sl">This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Это не полный список. Полный список изменений см. в журнале git.</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta lista está incompleta. Consulte o registo git para ver todas as alterações.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta listagem está incompleta. Veja log git para changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta lista jest niepełna. Polecenie „git log” wyświetli pełną listę zmian.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze lijst is onvolledig. Zie git log voor volledige changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 목록은 불완전합니다. 전체 변경 로그는 git 로그를 참조하십시오.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa lista è incompleta. Consultare git log per il changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="id">Daftar ini tidak lengkap. Lihat catatan git untuk daftar perubahan yang lengkap.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovaj popis je nepotpun. Pogledajte git zapis za potpuni pregled promjena.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette liste n’est pas complète. Pour voir tous les changements utilisez git log.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä luettelo on puutteellinen. Katso täydellinen git-muutosloki.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Zerrenda hau osatugabea da. Ikusi git log aldaketen zerrenda osorako.</p>
        <p lang="es">Este listado está incompleto. Consulte el registro de Git para obtener un registro de cambios completo.</p>
        <p lang="eo">La listo estas nekompleta. Uzu la komandon 'git log' por plena ŝanĝaro.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η καταχώρηση είναι ατελής. Δες την καταγραφή (log) του git για την πλήρη καταγραφή των αλλαγών (changelog).</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Liste ist unvollständig. Eine detaillierte Übersicht bietet das Changelog.</p>
        <p lang="da">Listen er ikke komplet. Se git-loggen for en komplet ændringslog.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tento seznam je neúplný. Úplný přehled změn najdete v git logu.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquest llistat és incomplet. Consulteu el registre del Git per obtenir un registre de canvis complet.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Списъкът не е завършен. Вижте Git лога за пълния списък с промени.</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذه القائمة غير مكتملة. انظر سجل بوابة التغيير الكامل.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-11-05" version="0.18">
      <description>
        <p>
     This release contains the following changes:
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此發行版本包含了以下變更：</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">该发布版本包含了以下变更：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск містить такі зміни:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm aşağıdaki değişiklikleri içerir:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här versionen innehåller följande ändringar:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање садржи следеће измене:</p>
        <p lang="sl">This release contains the following changes:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje nasledujúce zmeny:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск содержит следующие изменения:</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera następujące zmiany:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze uitgave bevat de volgende aanpassingen:</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Denne utgaven inneholder følgende endringer:</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리스에는 다음 변경 사항이 포함됩니다:</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione contiene le seguenti modifiche:</p>
        <p lang="is">Þessi útgáfa inniheldur eftirfarandi breytingar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Ti version contene li sequent modificationes:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini berisi perubahan berikut:</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás a következő változtatásokat tartalmazza:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovo izdanje sadrži sljedeće promjene:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version apporte les changement suivants :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä julkaisu sisältää seuraavat muutokset:</p>
        <p lang="fa">این نسخه شامل تغییرات زیر است:</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek ondorengo aldaketak ditu:</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión contiene los cambios siguientes:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Ĉi tiu eldono enhavas la jenajn ŝanĝojn:</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση περιλαμβάνει τις παρακάτω αλλαγές:</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Veröffentlichungen umfasst die folgenden Änderungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Udgivelsen indeholder følgende ændringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tato verze obsahuje následující změny:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió conté els canvis següents:</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание съдържа следните промени:</p>
        <p lang="ar">يحتوي هذا الإصدار على التغييرات التالية:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>
      Add Persian translation by @danialbehzadi
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加 @danialbehzadi 贡献的波斯语翻译</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано переклад перською від @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="tr">Farsça çeviriyi hazırlayan @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="sv">Lägg till Persisk översättning av @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додат је превод на персијски који је урадио „@danialbehzadi“</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add Persian translation by @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлен персидский перевод от @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Tradução persa por @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adic. tradução Persa por @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nowe tłumaczenie na język perski od @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="nl">Perzische vertaling toegevoegd door @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Persisk oversettelse ved @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="ko">@danialbehzadi의 페르시아어 번역 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta traduzione persiana di @danialbehzadi.</li>
          <li lang="is">Bætt við persneskri þýðingu eftir @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="id">Menambahkan terjemahan Bahasa Persia oleh @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="hr">Perzijski prijevod je dodao @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout des traductions perses par @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisätty Persian kielipaketti lähettäjä @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="eu">@danialbehzadi-ren persierazko itzulpena gehitu</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade la traducción al persa hecha por danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni perslingvigon de @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη Περσικής μετάφρασης από @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="de">Persische Übersetzung von @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj persisk oversættelse af @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidán překlad do perštiny od @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix la traducció al persa feta per danialbehzad</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавен е превод на ирански от @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li lang="ar">إضافة الترجمة الفارسية بواسطة @danialbehzadi</li>
          <li>
      Add Ukranian translation by @vl-nix
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加 @vl-nix 贡献的乌克兰语翻译</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано переклад українською від @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="tr">Ukraynaca çeviriyi hazırlayan @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="sv">Lägg till Ukrainsk översättning av @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додат је превод на украјински који је урадио „@vl-nix“</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add Ukranian translation by @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлен украинский перевод от @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Tradução ucraniana por @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adic. tradução ucraniana por @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nowe tłumaczenie na język ukraiński od @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="nl">Oekraïense vertaling toegevoegd door @ vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Legg til Ukrainsk oversettelse ved @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="ko">@vl-nix의 우크라이나어 번역 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta traduzione ucraina di @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="is">Bætt við úkraínskri þýðingu eftir @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="id">Menambahkan terjemahan Bahasa Ukraina oleh @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="hr">Ukrajinski prijevod je dodao @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout des traductions ukrainiennes par @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisätty Ukrainan kielipaketti lähettäjä @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="eu">@vl-nix-ren ukrainerazko itzulpena gehitu</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade la traducción al ucraniano hecha por vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni ukrainlingvigon tradukon de @vl-nx</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη Ουκρανικής μετάφρασης από @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="de">Ukrainische Übersetzung von@vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj ukrainsk oversættelse af @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidán překlad do ukrajinštiny od @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix la traducció a l'ucraïnès feta per vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавен е превод на украински от @vl-nix</li>
          <li lang="ar">أضف الترجمة الأوكرانية بواسطة @vl-nix</li>
          <li>
      Add support for showing/hiding window decorations using the mpv option --border
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">使用 MPV 选项 --border 添加显示/隐藏窗口装饰的支持</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано підтримку показу/приховування обрамлення вікон за допомогою параметра mpv --border</li>
          <li lang="tr">Mpv --border seçeneğini kullanarak pencere dekorasyonlarını göstermek / gizlemek için destek</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додата је подршка за приказивање/скривање украса прозора коришћењем „mpv“ опције „--border“</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add support for showing/hiding window decorations using the mpv option --border</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлена поддержка декорирования окна при использовании параметра mpv --border</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionado suporte para mostrar/ocultar decorações de janelas com a opção mpv --border</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionado suporte para mostrar/ocultar as decorações de janela usando a opção "--border" do mpv</li>
          <li lang="pl">Obsługa wyświetlania/ukrywania obramowania okna za pomocą opcji --border programu mpv</li>
          <li lang="nl">Ondersteuning toevoegen voor het weergeven / verbergen van vensterdecoraties met behulp van de mpv-optie --border</li>
          <li lang="ko">mpv 옵션 --border를 사용하여 창 장식 표시 / 숨기기 지원 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunto supporto per l'abilitazione delle decorazioni delle finestre tramite l'opzione di mpv --border</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan dukungan untuk menampilkan/menyembunyikan dekorasi jendela menggunakan opsi mpv --border</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana je podrška za prikaz/sakrivanje ukrasa prozora pomoću mogućnosti --border</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout du support pour l’affichage/masquage des décorations de fenêtres grâce à l’option mpv --border</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisätty tuki ikkunatehosteiden näyttämistä/piilottamista varten MPV-asetuksella --border</li>
          <li lang="eu">mpv-ren --border aukera erabiliz leihoen apaingarriak erakutsi/ezkutatzeko euskarria gehitu</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade compatibilidad para mostrar/ocultar las decoraciones de la ventana usando la opción de mpv --border</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni regadon por kaŝadon/malkaŝadon de fenestraj ornamaĵoj per la MPV-opcio --border</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη υποστήριξης για την εμφάνιση/απόκρυψη των διακοσμήσεων παραθύρου χρησιμοποιώντας την επιλογή --border του mpv</li>
          <li lang="de">Möglichkeit Fensterdekorationen über die mpv-Option --border ein- und auszublenden</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj understøttelse til at vise/skjule vinduesdekorationer med mpv tilvalget --border</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána podpora pro zobrazení/skrytí dekorací okna pomocí mpv předvolby --border</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix compatibilitat per mostrar/amagar les decoracions de la finestra utilitzant l'opció --border de l'mpv</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавена е поддръжка за показване/скриване декорацията на прозореца с използване на MPV опцията --border</li>
          <li lang="ar">أضف دعمًا لعرض / إخفاء زخارف النوافذ باستخدام خيار mpv - الحدود</li>
          <li>
      Add menu item for opening discs
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加打开光盘的菜单项</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано пункт меню для відкриття дисків</li>
          <li lang="tr">Diskleri açmak için menü ögesi ekle</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додата је ставка изборника за отварање дискова</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add menu item for opening discs</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлен пункт меню для открытия дисков</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionado item de menu para abrir discos</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionado item de menu para abrir discos</li>
          <li lang="pl">Menu otwierania płyt</li>
          <li lang="nl">Menu-item toevoegen voor het openen van schijven</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Tillegg av menyelement for åpning av disker</li>
          <li lang="ko">디스크를 열기위한 메뉴 항목 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta voce del menù per l'apertura di dischi</li>
          <li lang="is">Bætt við valmyndarfærslu til að opna diska</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan item menu untuk membuka kaset</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana je stavka izbornika za otvaranje diskova</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout d’une entrée de menu pour ouvrir les disques</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisätty valikkoon kohta levyjen avaamista varten</li>
          <li lang="eu">Diskoak irekitzeko menuko elementua gehitu</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade un elemento al menú para abrir discos</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni menueron por malfermi lumdiskojn</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη αντικειμένου μενού για το άνοιγμα δίσκων</li>
          <li lang="de">Menüeintrag zum Öffnen von Datenträgern</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj menupunkt til at åbne diske</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána položka nabídky pro otevírání disků</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix un element al menú per obrir discs</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавен е елемент в менюто за отваряне на дискове</li>
          <li lang="ar">أضف عنصر قائمة لفتح الأ_قراص</li>
          <li>
      Block cursor autohide when volume popup is open in windowed mode
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">在窗口模式下打开音量弹出窗口时阻止光标自动隐藏</li>
          <li lang="uk">Блокувати автоматичне приховування курсора, коли спливне меню гучності відкрито у віконному режимі</li>
          <li lang="tr">Ses açılır penceresi pencereli kipte açıkken imlecin gizlenmesini engelle</li>
          <li lang="sr">Блок курзор се сам скрива када је облачић гласности отворен у режиму прозора</li>
          <li lang="sl">Block cursor autohide when volume popup is open in windowed mode</li>
          <li lang="ru">Блокировать автоматическое скрытие курсора, когда всплывающее окно громкости открыто в оконном режиме</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Bloqueio à ocultação automática do cursor se o alerta de volume for aberto no modo de janela</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Ocultar automaticamente o bloco do cursor quando o pop-up de volume estiver aberto no modo de janela</li>
          <li lang="pl">Blokowanie automatycznego ukrywania kursora, kiedy menu głośności jest otwarte w trybie okna</li>
          <li lang="nl">Blokkeer cursor autohide wanneer volume pop-up is geopend in venstermodus</li>
          <li lang="ko">창 모드에서 볼륨 팝업 열릴 때 커서 자동 숨기기 차단</li>
          <li lang="it">Blocco della disabilitazione del cursore quando il popup del volume è aperto in modalità finestra</li>
          <li lang="id">Blokir kursor sembunyi secara otomatis saat popup volume terbuka dalam mode jendela</li>
          <li lang="hr">Blokirano je automatsko sakrivanje pokazivača miša kada je skočni prozor glasnoće zvuka otvoren u prozorskom načinu prikaza</li>
          <li lang="fr">Bloquer le masquage du curseur lorsque la fenêtre de volume est ouverte en mode fenêtré</li>
          <li lang="fi">Estetty kohdistimen automaattinen piilottaminen, kun äänenvoimakkuuden ponnahdusikkuna on avattu</li>
          <li lang="eu">Kurtsorea automatikoki ezkutatzea blokeatu bolumenaren laster-leihoa leiho moduan irekita dagoenean</li>
          <li lang="es">Bloquea la ocultación automática del cursor cuando se abre la ventana emergente del volumen en el modo ventana</li>
          <li lang="eo">Embarasi aŭtomatan kaŝiĝon de kursuro dum ŝanĝo de laŭteco en fenestra reĝimo</li>
          <li lang="el">Εμπόδιση της αυτόματης απόκρυψης του δρομέα όταν το αναδυόμενο παράθυρο έντασης ήχου είναι ανοιχτό σε λειτουργία παραθύρου</li>
          <li lang="de">Ausblenden des Mauszeigers bei offenem Lautstärke-Popup im Fenstermodus blockieren</li>
          <li lang="da">Bloker automatisk skjulning af markør når lysstyrke-pop op er åben i vinduestilstand</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zablokovat automatické skrytí kurzoru, když je v režimu okna otevřeno ovládání hlasitosti</li>
          <li lang="ca">Bloqueja l'ocultació automàtica del cursor quan s'obre la finestra emergent del volum en el mode finestra</li>
          <li lang="bg">Блокиране на автоматичното скриване на курсора, когато уведомлението за силата на звука е отворено в прозоречен режим</li>
          <li lang="ar">قم بإخفاء المؤشر تلقائيًا عند فتح نافذة منبثقة لمستوى الصوت في وضع الإطارات</li>
          <li>
      Fix crash with mpv 0.30
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">修复 mpv 0.30 的崩溃</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено збої роботи з mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="tr">Mpv 0.30 kilitlenmesi düzeltildi</li>
          <li lang="sv">Fixa krasch med mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="sr">Исправљена су урушавања са „mpv 0.30“</li>
          <li lang="sl">Fix crash with mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлен сбой при работе с mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Correção a um erro com mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Corrigido erro com o mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="pl">Poprawka awarii podczas używania mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="nl">Fix crash met mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Krasj med mpv 0.30 fekset</li>
          <li lang="ko">mpv 0.30으로 충돌 수정</li>
          <li lang="it">Risolto il crash con mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="id">Perbaiki kerusakan dengan mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="hr">Popravljeno je rušenje s mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="fr">Règle le problème de crash avec mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="fi">Kaatuminen korjattu versiossa MPV 0.30</li>
          <li lang="eu">mpv 0.30 bertsioarekin hutsegitea zuzendu</li>
          <li lang="es">Corrige el bloqueo con la versión 0.30 de mpv</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ripari misfinon pri versio 0.30 de MPV</li>
          <li lang="el">Επιδιόρθωση κρασαρίσματος με τον mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="de">Absturz mit mpv 0.30 behoben</li>
          <li lang="da">Ret nedbryd med mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opravit pád s mpv 0.30</li>
          <li lang="ca">Corregeix el bloqueig amb la versió 0.30 de l'mpv</li>
          <li lang="bg">Фиксиране на срив в MPV 0.30</li>
          <li lang="ar">إصلاح التعطل مع MPV 0.30</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
     This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個清單不是完整的。請到 git log 中檢視完整的變更記錄。</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个列表不完整。请到 git log 中查看完整的 changelog。</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей перелік не повний. Вичерпний перелік змін перегляньте у журналі git.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu liste eksik. Değişikliklerin tamamı için git günlüğüne bakın.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här listan är ofullständig. Se git-loggen för fullständig ändringslogg.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Овај списак је непотпун. Видите гитов дневник за потпуни дневник измена.</p>
        <p lang="sl">This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Это не полный список. Полный список изменений см. в журнале git.</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta lista está incompleta. Consulte o registo git para ver todas as alterações.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta listagem está incompleta. Veja log git para changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta lista jest niepełna. Polecenie „git log” wyświetli pełną listę zmian.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze lijst is onvolledig. Zie git log voor volledige changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 목록은 불완전합니다. 전체 변경 로그는 git 로그를 참조하십시오.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa lista è incompleta. Consultare git log per il changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="id">Daftar ini tidak lengkap. Lihat catatan git untuk daftar perubahan yang lengkap.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovaj popis je nepotpun. Pogledajte git zapis za potpuni pregled promjena.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette liste n’est pas complète. Pour voir tous les changements utilisez git log.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä luettelo on puutteellinen. Katso täydellinen git-muutosloki.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Zerrenda hau osatugabea da. Ikusi git log aldaketen zerrenda osorako.</p>
        <p lang="es">Este listado está incompleto. Consulte el registro de Git para obtener un registro de cambios completo.</p>
        <p lang="eo">La listo estas nekompleta. Uzu la komandon 'git log' por plena ŝanĝaro.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η καταχώρηση είναι ατελής. Δες την καταγραφή (log) του git για την πλήρη καταγραφή των αλλαγών (changelog).</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Liste ist unvollständig. Eine detaillierte Übersicht bietet das Changelog.</p>
        <p lang="da">Listen er ikke komplet. Se git-loggen for en komplet ændringslog.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tento seznam je neúplný. Úplný přehled změn najdete v git logu.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquest llistat és incomplet. Consulteu el registre del Git per obtenir un registre de canvis complet.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Списъкът не е завършен. Вижте Git лога за пълния списък с промени.</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذه القائمة غير مكتملة. انظر سجل بوابة التغيير الكامل.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-08-08" version="0.17">
      <description>
        <p>
     This release contains the following changes:
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此發行版本包含了以下變更：</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">该发布版本包含了以下变更：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск містить такі зміни:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm aşağıdaki değişiklikleri içerir:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här versionen innehåller följande ändringar:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање садржи следеће измене:</p>
        <p lang="sl">This release contains the following changes:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje nasledujúce zmeny:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск содержит следующие изменения:</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera następujące zmiany:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze uitgave bevat de volgende aanpassingen:</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Denne utgaven inneholder følgende endringer:</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리스에는 다음 변경 사항이 포함됩니다:</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione contiene le seguenti modifiche:</p>
        <p lang="is">Þessi útgáfa inniheldur eftirfarandi breytingar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Ti version contene li sequent modificationes:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini berisi perubahan berikut:</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás a következő változtatásokat tartalmazza:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovo izdanje sadrži sljedeće promjene:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version apporte les changement suivants :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä julkaisu sisältää seuraavat muutokset:</p>
        <p lang="fa">این نسخه شامل تغییرات زیر است:</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek ondorengo aldaketak ditu:</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión contiene los cambios siguientes:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Ĉi tiu eldono enhavas la jenajn ŝanĝojn:</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση περιλαμβάνει τις παρακάτω αλλαγές:</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Veröffentlichungen umfasst die folgenden Änderungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Udgivelsen indeholder følgende ændringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tato verze obsahuje následující změny:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió conté els canvis següents:</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание съдържа следните промени:</p>
        <p lang="ar">يحتوي هذا الإصدار على التغييرات التالية:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>
      Rename project to Celluloid
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">将项目更名为 Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="uk">Проєкт перейменовано на Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="tr">Proje Celluloid olarak yeniden adlandırıldı</li>
          <li lang="sv">Döp om projekt till Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="sr">Пројекат је преименован у Целулоид</li>
          <li lang="sl">Rename project to Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="ru">Проект переименован в Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Alteração do nome da aplicação para Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Projeto renomeado para Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zmiana nazwy projektu na Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="nl">Hernoem project naar Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Endring av prosjektnavn til Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="ko">프로젝트 이름을 Celluloid로 변경</li>
          <li lang="it">Progetto rinominato in Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="ie">Renominar li projecte a Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="id">Mengubah nama proyek menjadi Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="hr">Preimenovanje projekta u Celuloid</li>
          <li lang="fr">Changement de nom de projet en Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="fi">Projekti nimetty Celluloid:ksi</li>
          <li lang="fa">تغییر نام پروژه به سلولوید</li>
          <li lang="eu">Proiektua Celluloid moduan berrizendatu</li>
          <li lang="es">Cambia el nombre del proyecto a Celulloid</li>
          <li lang="eo">Alinomi la projektojn Celuloido</li>
          <li lang="el">Μετονομασία του project σε Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="de">Projekt umbenannt in Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="da">Omdøb projektet til Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přejmenovat projekt na Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="ca">Canvia el nom del projecte a Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="bg">Проектът е преименуван на Celluloid</li>
          <li lang="ar">إعادة تسمية المشروع إلى Celluloid</li>
          <li>
      Add Turkish translation by @TeknoMobil
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加 @TeknoMobil 贡献的土耳其语翻译</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано переклад турецькою від @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="tr">Türkçe çeviriyi hazırlayan @Serdar Sağlam</li>
          <li lang="sv">Lägg till Turkisk översättning av @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додат је превод на турски који је урадио „@TeknoMobil“</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add Turkish translation by @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлен турецкий перевод от @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Tradução para turco por @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adic. tradução Turca por @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nowe tłumaczenie na język turecki od @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="nl">Turkse vertaling toegevoegddoor @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Tyrkisk oversettelse ved @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="ko">@TeknoMobil의 터키어 번역 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta traduzione turca di @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="is">Bætt við tyrkneskri þýðingu eftir @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="id">Menambahkan terjemahan Bahasa Turki oleh @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="hr">Turski prijevod je dodao @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout des traductions turques par @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisätty Turkkilainen kielipaketti lähettäjä @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="fa">افزودن ترجمهٔ ترکی به دست @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="eu">@TeknoMobil-en turkierazko itzulpena gehitu</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade la traducción al turco hecha por TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni turklingvigon de @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη Τουρκικής μετάφρασης από @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="de">Türkische Übersetzung von @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj tyrkisk oversættelse af @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidán překlad do turečtiny od @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix la traducció al turc feta per TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавен е превод на турски от @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li lang="ar">إضافة الترجمة التركية من قبل @TeknoMobil</li>
          <li>
      Add Esperanto translation by @F3nd0
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加 @F3nd0 贡献的世界语翻译</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано переклад есперанто від @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="tr">Esperanto çeviriyi hazırlayan @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="sv">Lägg till Esperanto-översättning av @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додат је превод на есперанто који је урадио „@F3nd0“</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add Esperanto translation by @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлен перевод на эсперанто от @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Tradução para esperanto por @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adic. tradução Esperanto por @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nowe tłumaczenie na język esperanto od @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="nl">Esperanto-vertaling toegevoegd door @ F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Esperanto-oversettelse ved @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="ko">@F3nd0 에스페란토 번역 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta traduzione esperanto di @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="is">Bætt við esperantó-þýðingu eftir @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan terjemahan Esperanto oleh @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="hr">Esperanto prijevod je dodao @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout des traductions Esperanto par @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisätty Esperanto kielipaketti lähettäjä @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="fa">افزودن ترجمهٔ اسپرانتو به دست @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="eu">@F3nd0-ren esperantozko itzulpena gehitu</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade la traducción al esperanto hecha por F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni esperantlingvigon de @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη Εσπεράντο μετάφρασης από @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="de">Esperanto-Übersetzung von @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj esperanto oversættelse af @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidán překlad do esperanta od @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix la traducció a l'esperanto feta per F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавен е превод на есперанто от @F3nd0</li>
          <li lang="ar">إضافة ترجمة الاسبرانتو بواسطة @F3nd0</li>
          <li>
      Migrate from opengl-cb to the new render API
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">从 opengl-cb 迁移到新的渲染 API</li>
          <li lang="uk">Перехід з opengl-cb до нового API візуалізації</li>
          <li lang="tr">Opengl-cb'den yeni render API'sına taşı</li>
          <li lang="sr">Прешло се са „opengl-cb“ на нови АПИ исцртавања</li>
          <li lang="sl">Migrate from opengl-cb to the new render API</li>
          <li lang="ru">Переход с opengl-cb на новый API рендеринга</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Migração de opengl-cb para a nova API de renderização</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Migrado do opengl-cb para o novo renderizador API</li>
          <li lang="pl">Migracja z opengl-cb na nowe API wyświetlania</li>
          <li lang="nl">Migreer van opengl-cb naar de nieuwe render-API</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Flytting fra opengl-cb til nytt opptegnings-API</li>
          <li lang="ko">opengl-cb에서 새로운 렌더링 API로 마이그레이션</li>
          <li lang="it">Migrazione da opengl-cb alla nuova API di rendering</li>
          <li lang="id">Migrasi dari opengl-cb ke render API baru</li>
          <li lang="hr">Prijelaz sa opengl-cb u novi API prikaza</li>
          <li lang="fr">Migration de opengl-cb à la nouvelle API de rendu</li>
          <li lang="fi">Siirrytty OpenGL-CB -muodosta uuteen renderöinti API-liittymään</li>
          <li lang="fa">مهاجرت از opengl-cb به API پرداخت جدید</li>
          <li lang="eu">opengl-cb-tik errendatze API berrira migratu</li>
          <li lang="es">Cambia de opengl-cb a la nueva API de representación</li>
          <li lang="eo">Migri de opengl-cb al la nova API</li>
          <li lang="el">Μετανάστευση από opengl-cb στο νέο render API</li>
          <li lang="de">Migration von opengl-cb zur neuen Render-API</li>
          <li lang="da">Migrer fra opengl-cb til den nye gengivelses API</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přejít z opengl-cb na nové vykreslovací rozhraní</li>
          <li lang="ca">Canvia de opengl-cb a la nova API de representació</li>
          <li lang="bg">Миграция от opengl-cb към нов API за рендиране</li>
          <li lang="ar">الانتقال من opengl-cb إلى واجهة برمجة تطبيقات التقديم الجديدة</li>
          <li>
      Handle numpad keybindings
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">处理小键盘按键绑定</li>
          <li lang="uk">Обробка пов'язування клавіш цифрової клавіатури</li>
          <li lang="tr">Sayısal tuş takımı atamalarını işle</li>
          <li lang="sr">Ради се са свезама тастера на бројевном делу тастатуре</li>
          <li lang="sl">Handle numpad keybindings</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обработка комбинаций клавиш цифровой клавиатуры</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Gestão de teclas de atalho em teclados numéricos</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Manipular atalhos do teclado numérico</li>
          <li lang="pl">Obsługa skrótów na klawiaturze numerycznej</li>
          <li lang="nl">Verwerk numpad sneltoetsen</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Håndter tastekombinasjoner fra numerisk tastatur</li>
          <li lang="ko">숫자 키패드 키 바인딩 처리</li>
          <li lang="it">Gestione comandi da tastierino numerico</li>
          <li lang="id">Menangani pengaturan tombol numpad</li>
          <li lang="hr">Rukovanje brojčanim prečacima</li>
          <li lang="fr">Support des touches de raccourcis numériques</li>
          <li lang="fi">Osaa numeronäppäimistön painikkeet</li>
          <li lang="fa">مدیریت ترکیب‌کلیدهای صفحه‌عدد</li>
          <li lang="eu">Zenbakizko teklatuko laster-teklak maneiatu</li>
          <li lang="es">Maneja las combinaciones de teclas del teclado numérico</li>
          <li lang="eo">Trakti ciferplatajn klavkombinojn</li>
          <li lang="el">Χειρισμός συντομεύσεων αριθμητικού πληκτρολογίου</li>
          <li lang="de">Unterstützung von Tastenkombinationen unter Einbeziehung des Ziffernblocks</li>
          <li lang="da">Håndter tastebindinger for det numeriske tastatur</li>
          <li lang="cs">Ovládat klávesové zkratky na numerické klávesnici</li>
          <li lang="ca">Controla les combinacions de tecles de teclat numèric</li>
          <li lang="bg">Присвояване на клавиши за цифрова клавиатура</li>
          <li lang="ar">التعامل مع روابط المفاتيح الرقمية</li>
          <li>
      Handle unicode keybindings
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">处理 unicode 按键绑定</li>
          <li lang="uk">Обробка пов'язування клавіш Unicode</li>
          <li lang="tr">Unicode tuş atamalarını işle</li>
          <li lang="sr">Ради се са свезама тастера јуникода</li>
          <li lang="sl">Handle unicode keybindings</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обработка сочетаний клавиш в кодировке Unicode</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Gestão de teclas de atalho unicode</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Manipulável com combinações de teclas unicode</li>
          <li lang="pl">Obsługa skrótów używających unikodu</li>
          <li lang="nl">Verwerk unicode sneltoetsen</li>
          <li lang="ko">유니 코드 키 바인딩 처리</li>
          <li lang="it">Gestione comandi unicode</li>
          <li lang="id">Menangani pengaturan tombol unicode</li>
          <li lang="hr">Rukovanje unikôdnim prečacima</li>
          <li lang="fr">Support des touches de raccourcis unicode</li>
          <li lang="fi">Osaa unicode -painikkeet</li>
          <li lang="fa">مدیریت ترکیب‌کلیدهای یونی‌کد</li>
          <li lang="eu">Unicode laster-teklak maneiatu</li>
          <li lang="es">Maneja las combinaciones de teclas de Unicode</li>
          <li lang="eo">Trakti unikodajn klavkombinojn</li>
          <li lang="el">Χειρισμός συντομεύσεων πληκτρολογίου unicode</li>
          <li lang="de">Unterstützung von UnicodeTastenkombinationen</li>
          <li lang="da">Håndter tastebindinger for unicode</li>
          <li lang="cs">Ovládat klávesové zkratky unicode</li>
          <li lang="ca">Controla les assignacions de tecles de l'Unicode</li>
          <li lang="bg">Присвояване на клавиши за Unicode</li>
          <li lang="ar">التعامل مع روابط مفاتيح يونيكود</li>
          <li>
      Forward media key events to mpv
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">将多媒体按键事件转发到 mpv</li>
          <li lang="uk">Перенаправлення подій натискання медіаклавіш до mpv</li>
          <li lang="tr">Medya anahtarı olaylarını mpv'ye ilet</li>
          <li lang="sr">Догађаји мултимедијалних тастера се прослеђују „mpv“-у</li>
          <li lang="sl">Forward media key events to mpv</li>
          <li lang="ru">Передача событий от медиа клавиш в mpv</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Encaminhamento de eventos das teclas multimédia para mpv</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Encaminha eventos-chave da mídia para o mpv</li>
          <li lang="pl">Przekierowywanie zdarzeń klawiszy multimedialnych do programu mpv</li>
          <li lang="nl">Stuur mediasleutelgebeurtenissen door naar mpv</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Send mediatasthendelser til mpv</li>
          <li lang="ko">미디어 키 이벤트를 mpv로 전달</li>
          <li lang="it">Inoltro delle chiavi di eventi multimediali a mpv</li>
          <li lang="id">Teruskan peristiwa kunci media ke mpv</li>
          <li lang="hr">Prosljeđivanje događaja medijske tipke u mpv</li>
          <li lang="fr">Envoi des évènements de touches multimédia vers mpv</li>
          <li lang="fi">Välittää medianäppäinten avaintoiminnot MPV:hen</li>
          <li lang="fa">هدایت رویدادهای کلید رسانه به mpv</li>
          <li lang="eu">Multimedia tekla gertaerak mpv-ri igorri</li>
          <li lang="es">Reenvía los eventos de las teclas multimedia a mpv</li>
          <li lang="eo">Plusendi eventojn de aŭdvidaj klavoj al MPV</li>
          <li lang="el">Προώθηση γεγονότων πλήκτρων πολυμέσων στον mpv</li>
          <li lang="de">Medientasten-Eingaben an mpv übergeben</li>
          <li lang="da">Viderestil medietast-hændelser til mpv</li>
          <li lang="cs">Předávat události mediálních kláves mpv</li>
          <li lang="ca">Reenvia els esdeveniments de les tecles multimèdia a l'mpv</li>
          <li lang="bg">Препращане на медийни ключови събития към mpv</li>
          <li lang="ar">إعادة توجيه الأحداث الرئيسية لوسائل الإعلام إلى MPV</li>
          <li>
      Add dconf key for controlling cursor speed at which controls are unhidden
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加用于当控件未隐藏时控制光标速度的 dconf 键</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано клавішу dconf для керування швидкістю курсора, за якої з'являтимуться елементи керування</li>
          <li lang="tr">Kontrollerin gizlendiği imleç hızını denetlemek için dconf anahtarı ekle</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додат је кључ д-подешавања за управљање брзином курзора при којој се конторле откривају</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add dconf key for controlling cursor speed at which controls are unhidden</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлен ключ dconf для управления скоростью курсора, при которой элементы управления не скрываются</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionada uma chave dconf para controlar a velocidade do cursor necessária para mostrar os controlos</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionado chave dconf para controlar a velocidade do cursor na qual os controles estão ocultos</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nowy klucz dconf do sterowania prędkością kursora, przy której przyciski sterowania są wyświetlane</li>
          <li lang="nl">Voeg een dconf-sleutel toe voor het instellen van de cursorsnelheid waarbij bedieningselementen zichtbaar zullen worden</li>
          <li lang="ko">컨트롤이 숨김 해제되는 커서 속도를 제어하기위한 dconf 키 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta chiave dconf per il controllo della velocità del cursore in cui i controlli sono mostrati a schermo</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan kunci dconf untuk mengontrol kecepatan kursor di mana kontrol tidak disembunyikan</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodan je dconf izraz za upravljanje brzinom pokazivača miša kada se upravljanja prikažu</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout d’une clef dconf pour contrôler la vitesse de pointeur à laquelle les commandes flottantes sont affichées</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää dconf -avaimen kohdistimen nopeuden hallintaan, kun säätimet ovat piilossa</li>
          <li lang="fa">افزودن کلید dconf برای واپایش سرعت نشانگر برای آشکارسازی واپایشگرها</li>
          <li lang="eu">Kontrolak kurtsorearen ze abiaduratan bistaratuko diren kontrolatzeko dconf gakoa gehitu</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade una clave de dconf para controlar la velocidad del cursor a la que se ocultan los controles</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldonado de dconf-ŝlosilo por regi musmontrilan rapidon de regila kaŝado</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη κλειδιού dconf για τον έλεγχο της ταχύτητας του δρομέα για την οποία τα εργαλεία ελέγχου επανεμφανίζονται</li>
          <li lang="de">dconf key für Regelung der minimalen Mauszeigergeschwindigkeit unterhalb derer die Kontrollflächen ausgeblendet werden</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj dconf-nøgle til styring af markørens hastighed hvor styring skjules</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidán dconf klíč pro nastavení rychlosti kurzoru, při které se zobrazí ovládací prvky</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix una clau del dconf per controlar la velocitat del cursor a la qual s'amaguen els controls</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавяне на dconf ключ за контролиране скоростта на курсора, когато контролерите са видими.</li>
          <li lang="ar">أضف مفتاح dconf للتحكم في سرعة المؤشر حيث يتم إخفاء عناصر التحكم</li>
          <li>
      Add option for suppressing playback errors
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加选项以隐藏播放错误</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано параметр приховування помилок під час відтворення</li>
          <li lang="tr">Oynatma hatalarını bastırmak için seçenek ekle</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додата је опција за потискивање грешака пуштања</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add option for suppressing playback errors</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлена возможность игнорирования ошибок при воспроизведении</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionada uma opção para suprimir os erros de reprodução</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionada opção para suprimir erros de reprodução</li>
          <li lang="pl">Opcja ukrywania błędów odtwarzania</li>
          <li lang="nl">Optie toevoegen om afspeelfouten te onderdrukken</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Legg til innstilling for undertrykking av avspillingsfeil</li>
          <li lang="ko">재생 오류 억제 옵션 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta opzione per sopprimere gli errori di riproduzione</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan opsi untuk menekan kesalahan pemutaran</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana je mogućnost za potiskivanje grešaka repordukcije</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout d’une option pour ignorer les erreurs de lecture</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää vaihtoehdon toistovirheiden estämiseksi</li>
          <li lang="eu">Erreprodukzio-erroreak isiltzeko aukera gehitu</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade una opción para suprimir los errores de reproducción</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni opcion por silentigi lego-erarojn</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη επιλογής για καταστολή των σφαλμάτων αναπαραγωγής</li>
          <li lang="de">Option zum Unterdrücken von Wiedergabefehlern</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj tilvalg til undertrykkelse af afspilningsfejl</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána možnost pro potlačení chyb přehrávání</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix una opció per suprimir els errors de reproducció</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавяне на опция за игнориране на грешки при възпроизвеждане</li>
          <li lang="ar">إضافة خيار لقمع أخطاء التشغيل</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
     This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個清單不是完整的。請到 git log 中檢視完整的變更記錄。</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个列表不完整。请到 git log 中查看完整的 changelog。</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей перелік не повний. Вичерпний перелік змін перегляньте у журналі git.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu liste eksik. Değişikliklerin tamamı için git günlüğüne bakın.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här listan är ofullständig. Se git-loggen för fullständig ändringslogg.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Овај списак је непотпун. Видите гитов дневник за потпуни дневник измена.</p>
        <p lang="sl">This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Это не полный список. Полный список изменений см. в журнале git.</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta lista está incompleta. Consulte o registo git para ver todas as alterações.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta listagem está incompleta. Veja log git para changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta lista jest niepełna. Polecenie „git log” wyświetli pełną listę zmian.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze lijst is onvolledig. Zie git log voor volledige changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 목록은 불완전합니다. 전체 변경 로그는 git 로그를 참조하십시오.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa lista è incompleta. Consultare git log per il changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="id">Daftar ini tidak lengkap. Lihat catatan git untuk daftar perubahan yang lengkap.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovaj popis je nepotpun. Pogledajte git zapis za potpuni pregled promjena.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette liste n’est pas complète. Pour voir tous les changements utilisez git log.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä luettelo on puutteellinen. Katso täydellinen git-muutosloki.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Zerrenda hau osatugabea da. Ikusi git log aldaketen zerrenda osorako.</p>
        <p lang="es">Este listado está incompleto. Consulte el registro de Git para obtener un registro de cambios completo.</p>
        <p lang="eo">La listo estas nekompleta. Uzu la komandon 'git log' por plena ŝanĝaro.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η καταχώρηση είναι ατελής. Δες την καταγραφή (log) του git για την πλήρη καταγραφή των αλλαγών (changelog).</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Liste ist unvollständig. Eine detaillierte Übersicht bietet das Changelog.</p>
        <p lang="da">Listen er ikke komplet. Se git-loggen for en komplet ændringslog.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tento seznam je neúplný. Úplný přehled změn najdete v git logu.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquest llistat és incomplet. Consulteu el registre del Git per obtenir un registre de canvis complet.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Списъкът не е завършен. Вижте Git лога за пълния списък с промени.</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذه القائمة غير مكتملة. انظر سجل بوابة التغيير الكامل.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-01-21" version="0.16">
      <description>
        <p>
     This release contains the following changes:
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此發行版本包含了以下變更：</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">该发布版本包含了以下变更：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск містить такі зміни:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm aşağıdaki değişiklikleri içerir:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här versionen innehåller följande ändringar:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање садржи следеће измене:</p>
        <p lang="sl">This release contains the following changes:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje nasledujúce zmeny:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск содержит следующие изменения:</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera następujące zmiany:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze uitgave bevat de volgende aanpassingen:</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Denne utgaven inneholder følgende endringer:</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리스에는 다음 변경 사항이 포함됩니다:</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione contiene le seguenti modifiche:</p>
        <p lang="is">Þessi útgáfa inniheldur eftirfarandi breytingar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Ti version contene li sequent modificationes:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini berisi perubahan berikut:</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás a következő változtatásokat tartalmazza:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovo izdanje sadrži sljedeće promjene:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version apporte les changement suivants :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä julkaisu sisältää seuraavat muutokset:</p>
        <p lang="fa">این نسخه شامل تغییرات زیر است:</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek ondorengo aldaketak ditu:</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión contiene los cambios siguientes:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Ĉi tiu eldono enhavas la jenajn ŝanĝojn:</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση περιλαμβάνει τις παρακάτω αλλαγές:</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Veröffentlichungen umfasst die folgenden Änderungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Udgivelsen indeholder følgende ændringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tato verze obsahuje následující změny:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió conté els canvis següents:</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание съдържа следните промени:</p>
        <p lang="ar">يحتوي هذا الإصدار على التغييرات التالية:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>
       Split up the General tab in the preferences dialog
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">在首选项对话框中分离“通用”标签页</li>
          <li lang="uk">Розділено вкладку Загальні у вікні налаштувань</li>
          <li lang="tr">Tercihler iletişim kutusunda Genel sekmeyi böl</li>
          <li lang="sr">Подељен је језичак „Опште“ у прозорчету поставки</li>
          <li lang="sl">Split up the General tab in the preferences dialog</li>
          <li lang="ru">Разделите вкладку Общие в диалоге настроек</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Separação do separador Geral no diálogo de preferências</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Dividir o separador Geral na aba de diálogo de preferências</li>
          <li lang="pl">Podział karty „Ogólne” w oknie preferencji</li>
          <li lang="nl">Verdeel het tabblad Algemeen in het voorkeurenvenster</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Oppdeling av «Generelt»-fane i innstillingsdialogen</li>
          <li lang="ko">환경 설정 대화 상자에서 일반 탭 분할</li>
          <li lang="it">Divisione della scheda Generale nella finestra delle preferenze</li>
          <li lang="id">Pisahkan tab Umum di dialog preferensi</li>
          <li lang="hr">Podjela kartice Općenito u dijalogu osobitosti</li>
          <li lang="fr">Onglet général scindé dans les préférences</li>
          <li lang="fi">Jakaa välilehden Yleinen asetukset-valintaikkunassa</li>
          <li lang="eu">Hobespenak elkarrizketa-koadroko Orokorra fitxa banatu</li>
          <li lang="es">Divide la pestaña General en el diálogo de preferencias</li>
          <li lang="eo">Dividi la Ĝeneralan langeton en la agorda interagujo</li>
          <li lang="el">Διαχωρισμός της καρτέλας Γενικά στο παράθυρο διαλόγου προτιμήσεων</li>
          <li lang="de">Die Allgemein-Registerkarte in den Einstellungen wurde aufgeteilt</li>
          <li lang="da">Opdeling af Generelt-fanebladet i præferencer-dialogen.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Rozdělit Hlavní záložku v dialogu předvoleb</li>
          <li lang="ca">Divideix la pestanya General al diàleg de preferències</li>
          <li lang="bg">Разделен е разделът Общи в диалога с настройките</li>
          <li lang="ar">قسّم علامة التبويب "عام" في مربع حوار التفضيلات</li>
          <li>
       Improve behavior when toggling playlist under tiling window managers
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">改善平铺式窗口管理器下的切换显示播放列表功能</li>
          <li lang="uk">Вдосконалено поведінку під час перемикання добірок у розділеному менеджері вікон</li>
          <li lang="tr">Döşeme pencere yöneticileri altında oynatma listesini değiştirirken davranışı iyileştirin</li>
          <li lang="sr">Побољшано је понашање приликом окидања списка пуштања под поплочавањем управника прозора</li>
          <li lang="sl">Improve behavior when toggling playlist under tiling window managers</li>
          <li lang="ru">Улучшено поведение при переключении плейлиста под тайловыми оконными менеджерами</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Melhorias no comportamento ao alternar a lista de reprodução em gestores de janelas 'tiling'</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Melhorar o comportamento alternando a lista de reprodução gerenciadas em janelas lado a lado</li>
          <li lang="pl">Ulepszone zachowanie podczas przełączania listy odtwarzania w kafelkowych menedżerach okien</li>
          <li lang="nl">Verbeter het gedrag bij het wisselen van afspeellijst onder tegelende vensterbeheerders</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Forbedret oppførsel ved visning/skjuling av spilleliste med flisbaserte vindusbehandlere</li>
          <li lang="ko">타일링 창 관리자에서 재생 목록을 전환 할 때 동작 개선</li>
          <li lang="it">Migliorato il comportamento della playlist con i tiling window manager</li>
          <li lang="id">Tingkatkan perilaku saat beralih daftar putar di bawah pengelola jendela tiling</li>
          <li lang="hr">Poboljšanje ponašanja uklj/isklj popisa izvođenja pri popločenom prikazu u upraviteljima prozora</li>
          <li lang="fr">Meilleur comportement lors de la bascule de la liste de lecture sous les gestionnaires de fenêtres de carrelage</li>
          <li lang="fi">Parantaa käyttäytymistä, kun soittolistat voidaan kytkeä vierekkäin ikkunanhallinan alla</li>
          <li lang="eu">Erreprodukzio-zerrenda txandakatzeko portaera hobetu mosaiko moduko leiho kudeatzaileetan</li>
          <li lang="es">Mejora el comportamiento al mostrar u ocultar la lista de reproducción en los gestores de ventana de mosaico</li>
          <li lang="eo">Plibonigi konduton dum baskuligo de spektolisto en kahelaj fenestraj aranĝiloj</li>
          <li lang="el">Βελτίωση συμπεριφοράς κατά την εναλλαγή της λίστας αναπαραγωγής όταν χρησιμοποιούνται tiling window managers</li>
          <li lang="de">Das Verhalten des Ein-/Aus-Schalters für Wiedergabelisten wurde im Zusammenhang mit Tiling-Fenstermanagern verbessert</li>
          <li lang="da">Forbedret opførsel når afspilningslisten vises/skjules under fliselæggende vindueshåndteringer</li>
          <li lang="cs">Vylepšit chování při přepínání seznamu přehrávání pod dlaždicovými správci oken</li>
          <li lang="ca">Millora el comportament en mostrar o ocultar la llista de reproducció en els gestors de finestra de mosaic</li>
          <li lang="bg">Подобряване на поведението при превключване на списъка за изпълнение при тилинг мениджъри на прозорци </li>
          <li lang="ar">تحسين السلوك عند تبديل قائمة التشغيل أسفل مديري نوافذ التجانب</li>
          <li>
       Move app menu items to primary menu
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">将应用程序菜单项移至主菜单</li>
          <li lang="uk">Переміщено елементи меню застосунку до основного меню</li>
          <li lang="tr">Uygulama menüsü ögelerini birincil menüye taşı</li>
          <li lang="sr">Ставке изборника програма су премештене на главни изборник</li>
          <li lang="sl">Move app menu items to primary menu</li>
          <li lang="ru">Элементы меню приложения перенесены в основное меню</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Colocação dos itens de menu da aplicação no menu principal</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Mover itens do menu de aplicativos para o menu principal</li>
          <li lang="pl">Przeniesienie menu programu do głównego menu</li>
          <li lang="nl">Verplaats app-menu-items naar het primaire menu</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Flytt programmenyelementer til hovedmeny</li>
          <li lang="ko">앱 메뉴 항목을 기본 메뉴로 이동</li>
          <li lang="it">Trasferite le voci dell'app menù nel menù primario</li>
          <li lang="id">Pindahkan item menu aplikasi ke menu utama</li>
          <li lang="hr">Premještanje izbornika aplikacije u glavni izbornik</li>
          <li lang="fr">Éléments du menu d’application déplacés vers le menu principal</li>
          <li lang="fi">Siirrä sovelluksen valikkokohteet päävalikkoon</li>
          <li lang="eu">Aplikazioaren menuko elementuak menu nagusira eraman</li>
          <li lang="es">Traslada los elementos del menú de aplicación al menú principal</li>
          <li lang="eo">Movi erojn de aplikaĵa menuo al ĉefmenuo</li>
          <li lang="el">Μετακίνηση αντικειμένων του μενού εφαρμογών στο κυρίως μενού</li>
          <li lang="de">Im Zuge der Abschaffung des GNOME-Anwendungsmenüs wurde dieses in das Hauptmenü integriert</li>
          <li lang="da">Flyt punkterne fra programmenuen til den primære menu</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přesunout položky menu aplikace do primátního menu</li>
          <li lang="ca">Desplaça els elements del menú d'aplicació al menú principal</li>
          <li lang="bg">Преместени са елементите от менюто на програмите в основното меню</li>
          <li lang="ar">نقل عناصر قائمة التطبيق إلى القائمة الأساسية</li>
          <li>
       Use separate MPRIS DBus connection for each window
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">为每个窗口使用分离的 MPRIS DBus 连接</li>
          <li lang="uk">Застосовано окреме з'єднання MPRIS DBus для кожного вікна</li>
          <li lang="tr">Her pencere için ayrı MPRIS DBus bağlantısı kullan</li>
          <li lang="sr">Користи се одвојена веза „MPRIS“ Д-сабирнице за сваки прозор</li>
          <li lang="sl">Use separate MPRIS DBus connection for each window</li>
          <li lang="ru">Использовать отдельное MPRIS DBus соединение для каждого окна</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Utilização de uma ligação distinta MPRIS DBus para cada janela</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Usar janelas separadas para conexões MPRIS D-BUS</li>
          <li lang="pl">Używanie oddzielnego połączenia MPRIS z magistralą D-Bus dla każdego okna</li>
          <li lang="nl">Gebruik voor elk venster een afzonderlijke MPRIS DBus-verbinding</li>
          <li lang="ko">각 창에 별도의 MPRIS DBus 연결 사용</li>
          <li lang="it">Utilizzo di connessioni DBus MPRIS separate per ogni finestra</li>
          <li lang="id">Gunakan koneksi MPRIS DBus terpisah untuk setiap jendela</li>
          <li lang="hr">Korištenje zasebnog MPRIS DBus povezivanja za svaki prozor</li>
          <li lang="fr">Utilisation d’une connexion DBUS MPRIS unique pour chaque fenêtre</li>
          <li lang="fi">Käytä erillistä MPRIS DBus -yhteyttä jokaiseen ikkunaan</li>
          <li lang="eu">MPRIS DBUS konexio bereizi bat erabili leiho bakoitzean</li>
          <li lang="es">Usa una conexión DBus de MPRIS separada para cada ventana</li>
          <li lang="eo">Uzi apartan konekton de « MPRIS DBus » por ĉiu fenestro</li>
          <li lang="el">Χρήση ξεχωριστής σύνδεσης MPRIS DBus για κάθε παράθυρο</li>
          <li lang="de">Separate MPRIS DBus-Verbindung für jedes Fenster</li>
          <li lang="da">Brug separat MPRIS DBus-forbindelse til hvert vindue</li>
          <li lang="cs">Použít pro každé okno oddělené spojení MPRIS DBus</li>
          <li lang="ca">Utilitza una connexió DBUS de la interfície MPRIS separada per a cada finestra</li>
          <li lang="bg">Използвана е отделна MPRIS DBus връзка за всеки прозорец</li>
          <li lang="ar">استخدم اتصال MPRIS DBus منفصل لكل نافذة</li>
          <li>
       Add support for MPRIS property LoopStatus
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加 MPRIS 属性 LoopStatus 的支持</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано підтримку властивості LoopStatus для MPRIS</li>
          <li lang="tr">MPRIS özelliği LoopStatus için destek ekle</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додата је подршка за „MPRIS“ својство „LoopStatus“</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add support for MPRIS property LoopStatus</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлена поддержка MPRIS cвойства LoopStatus</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionado suporte à propriedade LoopStatus MPRIS</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionar suporte para a propriedade MPRIS LoopStatus</li>
          <li lang="pl">Obsługa własności „LoopStatus” interfejsu MPRIS</li>
          <li lang="nl">Ondersteuning toevoegen voor MPRIS-eigenschap LoopStatus</li>
          <li lang="ko">MPRIS 속성 LoopStatus에 대한 지원 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunto supporto per la proprietà LoopStatus di MPRIS</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan dukungan untuk properti LoopStatus MPRIS</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana je podrška za MPRIS LoopStatus svojstvo</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout du support pour la propriété MPRIS LoopStatus</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää tuki MPRIS -ominaisuus Loop -silmukan tilaksi</li>
          <li lang="eu">MPRIS-en LoopStatus propietatearen euskarria gehitu</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade compatibilidad con la propiedad LoopStatus de MPRIS</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni subtenon por eco « LoopStatus » de MPRIS</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη υποστήριξης για την MPRIS ιδιότητα LoopStatus</li>
          <li lang="de">Unterstützung für MPRIS property LoopStatus</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj understøttelse af MPRIS-egenskaben LoopStatus</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána podpora pro MPRIS vlastnost LoopStatus</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix compatibilitat amb la propietat LoopStatus de la interfície MPRIS</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавена е поддръжка за свойствата на MPRIS LoopStatus</li>
          <li lang="ar">إضافة دعم لخاصية MPRIS LoopStatus</li>
          <li>
       Add option --mpv-options for setting arbitrary mpv options from the
       command-line
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">通过 --mpv-options 选项从命令行中设置任意 MPV 参数</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано параметр --mpv-options для налаштування довільних параметрів mpv з командного рядка</li>
          <li lang="tr">Seçenek ekle, komut satırından mpv seçeneklerini ayarlamak için --mpv-options</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додата је опција „--mpv-options“ за постављање изборних „mpv“ опција из терминала</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add option --mpv-options for setting arbitrary mpv options from the command-line</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавьте параметр --mpv-options для установки произвольных параметров mpv из командной строки</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionada a opção --mpv-options para definir opções arbitrárias mpv a partir da linha de comando</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionar a opção --mpv-options para definir opções arbitrárias do mpv em linha de comando</li>
          <li lang="pl">Opcja --mpv-options do ustawiania dowolnych opcji programu mpv z wiersza poleceń</li>
          <li lang="nl">Optie --mpv-opties toevoegen voor het instellen van willekeurige mpv-opties vanaf de opdrachtregel</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Tillegg av valget --mpv-options for å sette vilkårlige mpv-innstillinger fra kommandolinjen</li>
          <li lang="ko">명령 줄에서 임의의 mpv 옵션을 설정하기위한 --mpv-options 옵션 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta l'opzione --mpv-options per impostare opzioni di mpv dalla riga di comando</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan opsi --mpv-options untuk menyetel opsi mpv sembarang dari command-line</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana je mogućnost --mpv-options za postavljanje proizvoljne mpv mogućnosti iz naredbenog redka</li>
          <li lang="fr">Nouvelle option --mpv-options pour passer des options à mpv via la ligne de commande</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää optio --mpv -optio asettaa satunnaiset mpv-asetukset komentoriviltä</li>
          <li lang="eu">--mpv-options aukera gehitu, komando lerrotik hautazko mpv aukerak ezartzeko</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade la opción --mpv-options para configurar opciones arbitrarias de mpv desde la línea de órdenes</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni opcion « --mpv-options » por agordado de ajnaj opcioj de MPV per la komandlinio</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη επιλογής --mpv-options για τον ορισμό αυθαίρετων επιλογών του mpv από τη γραμμή εντολων</li>
          <li lang="de">Neue Kommondozeilenoption zum Setzen beliebiger MPV-Optionen: --mpv-options</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj tilvalget --mpv-options til indstilling af vilkårlige tilvalg fra kommandolinjen</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána předvolba --mpv-options pro nastavení libovolných možností mpv z příkazové řádky</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix l'opció --mpv-options per configurar opcions arbitràries de l'mpv des de la línia d'ordres</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавете опция --mpv-options за задаване на произволни mpv опции от команден ред</li>
          <li lang="ar">إضافة خيار - خيارات mpv لتعيين خيارات mpv التعسفية من سطر الأوامر</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
     This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個清單不是完整的。請到 git log 中檢視完整的變更記錄。</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个列表不完整。请到 git log 中查看完整的 changelog。</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей перелік не повний. Вичерпний перелік змін перегляньте у журналі git.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu liste eksik. Değişikliklerin tamamı için git günlüğüne bakın.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här listan är ofullständig. Se git-loggen för fullständig ändringslogg.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Овај списак је непотпун. Видите гитов дневник за потпуни дневник измена.</p>
        <p lang="sl">This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Это не полный список. Полный список изменений см. в журнале git.</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta lista está incompleta. Consulte o registo git para ver todas as alterações.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta listagem está incompleta. Veja log git para changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta lista jest niepełna. Polecenie „git log” wyświetli pełną listę zmian.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze lijst is onvolledig. Zie git log voor volledige changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 목록은 불완전합니다. 전체 변경 로그는 git 로그를 참조하십시오.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa lista è incompleta. Consultare git log per il changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="id">Daftar ini tidak lengkap. Lihat catatan git untuk daftar perubahan yang lengkap.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovaj popis je nepotpun. Pogledajte git zapis za potpuni pregled promjena.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette liste n’est pas complète. Pour voir tous les changements utilisez git log.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä luettelo on puutteellinen. Katso täydellinen git-muutosloki.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Zerrenda hau osatugabea da. Ikusi git log aldaketen zerrenda osorako.</p>
        <p lang="es">Este listado está incompleto. Consulte el registro de Git para obtener un registro de cambios completo.</p>
        <p lang="eo">La listo estas nekompleta. Uzu la komandon 'git log' por plena ŝanĝaro.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η καταχώρηση είναι ατελής. Δες την καταγραφή (log) του git για την πλήρη καταγραφή των αλλαγών (changelog).</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Liste ist unvollständig. Eine detaillierte Übersicht bietet das Changelog.</p>
        <p lang="da">Listen er ikke komplet. Se git-loggen for en komplet ændringslog.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tento seznam je neúplný. Úplný přehled změn najdete v git logu.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquest llistat és incomplet. Consulteu el registre del Git per obtenir un registre de canvis complet.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Списъкът не е завършен. Вижте Git лога за пълния списък с промени.</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذه القائمة غير مكتملة. انظر سجل بوابة التغيير الكامل.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-09-08" version="0.15">
      <description>
        <p>
     This release contains the following changes:
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此發行版本包含了以下變更：</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">该发布版本包含了以下变更：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск містить такі зміни:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm aşağıdaki değişiklikleri içerir:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här versionen innehåller följande ändringar:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање садржи следеће измене:</p>
        <p lang="sl">This release contains the following changes:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje nasledujúce zmeny:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск содержит следующие изменения:</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera następujące zmiany:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze uitgave bevat de volgende aanpassingen:</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Denne utgaven inneholder følgende endringer:</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리스에는 다음 변경 사항이 포함됩니다:</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione contiene le seguenti modifiche:</p>
        <p lang="is">Þessi útgáfa inniheldur eftirfarandi breytingar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Ti version contene li sequent modificationes:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini berisi perubahan berikut:</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás a következő változtatásokat tartalmazza:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovo izdanje sadrži sljedeće promjene:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version apporte les changement suivants :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä julkaisu sisältää seuraavat muutokset:</p>
        <p lang="fa">این نسخه شامل تغییرات زیر است:</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek ondorengo aldaketak ditu:</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión contiene los cambios siguientes:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Ĉi tiu eldono enhavas la jenajn ŝanĝojn:</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση περιλαμβάνει τις παρακάτω αλλαγές:</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Veröffentlichungen umfasst die folgenden Änderungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Udgivelsen indeholder følgende ændringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tato verze obsahuje následující změny:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió conté els canvis següents:</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание съдържа следните промени:</p>
        <p lang="ar">يحتوي هذا الإصدار على التغييرات التالية:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>
      Set default screenshot directory to XDG_PICTURES_DIR
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">设置默认的截图目录为 XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="uk">Типовим каталогом знімків екрана призначено XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="tr">Öntanımlı ekran görüntüsü dizinini XDG_PICTURES_DIR olarak ayarla</li>
          <li lang="sv">Ange standard skärmklippsmapp till XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="sr">Основни директоријум снимка екрана је постављен на „XDG_PICTURES_DIR“</li>
          <li lang="sl">Set default screenshot directory to XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="ru">Установить каталог по умолчанию для скриншотов в XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Definição do diretório de capturas de ecrã para XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Definir o local padrão para a tela de captura XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="pl">Ustawienie domyślnego katalogu zrzutów ekranu na XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="nl">Stel de standaard schermafdruk-map in op XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Forvalgt skjermavbildningsmappe satt til XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="ko">기본 스크린 샷 디렉토리를 XDG_PICTURES_DIR로 설정합니다</li>
          <li lang="it">Cartella predefinita degli screenshot impostata a XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="id">Mengubah direktori tangkapan layar bawaan menjadi XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="hr">Zadani direktorij snimki zaslona je postavljen u XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="fr">Répertoire de capture d’écran par défaut réglé à XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="fi">Aseta oletus kuvakaappauksen hakemistoon XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="eu">XDG_PICTURES_DIR pantaila-argazkien direktorio lehenetsi bezala ezarri</li>
          <li lang="es">Configura como carpeta de capturas de pantalla predeterminada la carpeta XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="eo">Agordi la implicitan ekrankopian dosierujon al XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="el">Ορισμός προεπιλεγμένου φακέλου στιγμιοτύπων οθόνης στο XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="de">XDG_PICTURES_DIR ist nun standardmäßiger Screenshot-Speicherort</li>
          <li lang="da">Indstil standardmappen for skærmbilleder til XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="cs">Nastavit výchozí adresář pro snímky obrazovky na XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="ca">Estableix com a carpeta de captures de pantalla predeterminada la carpeta XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="bg">Задаване на директорията за снимки на екрана по подразбиране в XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li lang="ar">قم بتعيين دليل لقطة الشاشة الافتراضي على XDG_PICTURES_DIR</li>
          <li>
      Improve handling of --window-scale, --autofit,
      --autofit-larger, and --autofit-smaller
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">改善对 --window-scale、 --autofit、 --autofit-larger 和 --autofit-smaller 的处理</li>
          <li lang="uk">Вдосконалено роботу з --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger, and --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="tr">İyileştirme ekle - -pencere-ölçeği, -otoölçek - otoölçek-büyük ve otoölçek-küçük</li>
          <li lang="sr">Побољшан је рад опција „--window-scale“, „--autofit“, „--autofit-larger“ и „--autofit-smaller“</li>
          <li lang="sl">Improve handling of --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger, and --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="ru">Улучшена обработка --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger и --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Melhorias na gestão das opções --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger e --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Melhorar como se lida com --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger, e --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="pl">Ulepszona obsługa opcji --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger i --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="nl">Verbeter de afhandeling van --window-schaal, --autofit, --autofit-groter en --autofit-kleiner</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Forbedret håndtering av--window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger, og --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="ko">--window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger 및 --autofit-smaller 처리 개선</li>
          <li lang="it">Migliorata la gestione di --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger, e --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="id">Meningkatkan penanganan --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger, dan --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="hr">Poboljšano je rukovanje sa --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger i --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="fr">Meilleur support de --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger et --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="fi">Paranna käsittelyä --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger, ja --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="eu">--window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger eta --autofit-smaller aukeren maneiatzea hobetu</li>
          <li lang="es">Mejora el manejo de las opciones --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger y --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="eo">Plibonigi traktadon de « --window-scale », « --autofit », « --autofit-larger », kaj « --autofit-smaller »</li>
          <li lang="el">Βελτίωση χειρισμού των --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger, and --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="de">Verbesserte Handhabung der Optionen --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger, and --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="da">Forbedret håndtering af --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger og --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="cs">Vylepšit zacházení s předvolbami --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger a --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="ca">Millora el maneig de les opcions --window-scale, --autofit, --autofit-larger i --autofit-smaller</li>
          <li lang="bg">Подобряване на обработката на мащаба на - Window, --autofit, --autofit-large и --autofit-small</li>
          <li lang="ar">تحسين التعامل مع - مقياس النافذة ، - احتواء تلقائي ، - احتواء تلقائي - الأكبر ، و - احتواء تلقائي - الأصغر</li>
          <li>
      Add command line option for setting WM_ROLE
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">增加一个命令行参数来设置 WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано параметр командного рядка для встановлення WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="tr">WM_ROLE ayarı için komut satırı seçeneği ekle</li>
          <li lang="sv">Lägg till kommandoalternativ för inställning av WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додата је опција линије наредби за постављање „WM_ROLE“</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add command line option for setting WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлен параметр командной строки для настройки WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionada uma opção de linha de comando para definir WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionar linha de comando para opção de definir WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="pl">Opcja wiersza poleceń do ustawiania WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Legg til kommandolinjevalg for innstillingen WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="ko">WM_ROLE 설정을위한 명령 줄 옵션 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta opzione da riga di comando per l'impostazione di WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan opsi command line untuk mengatur WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana je WM_ROLE mogućnost naredbenog redka</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout d’une option de ligne de commande pour renseigner WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää komentorivivalinta WM_ROLE -asetukseksi</li>
          <li lang="eu">WM_ROLE ezartzeko komando-lerroko aukera gehitu</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade una opción a la línea de órdenes para configurar WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni komandlinian opcion por agordi econ « WM_ROLE »</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη επιλογής γραμμής εντολών για τον ορισμό WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="de">Neue Kommandozeilenoption zum Setzen der WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj kommandolinjetilvalg for indstilling af WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána předvolba příkazové řádky pro nastavení WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix una opció a la línia d'ordres per configurar WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавяне опцията за команден ред за настройка на WM_ROLE</li>
          <li lang="ar">إضافة خيار سطر الأوامر لإعداد WM_ROLE</li>
          <li>
      Add context menu item for removing playlist items
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">增加上下文菜单项来移除播放列表里的项目</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано пункт контекстного меню для вилучення елементів з добірки</li>
          <li lang="tr">Oynatma listesi ögelerini kaldırmak için içerik menüsü ögesi ekle</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додата је ставка приручног изборника за уклањање ставки списка пуштања</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add context menu item for removing playlist items</li>
          <li lang="ru">В контекстное меню добавлен пункт для удаления элементов списка воспроизведения</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionado um item ao menu de contexto para remover itens da lista de reprodução</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionar menu de contexto para remover itens da lista de reprodução</li>
          <li lang="pl">Menu kontekstowe do usuwania pozycji z listy odtwarzania</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Legg til bindeleddsmenyelementer for fjerning av spillelisteelementer</li>
          <li lang="ko">재생 목록 항목 제거를위한 컨텍스트 메뉴 항목 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta voce menù per la rimozione degli elementi della playlist</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan item menu konteks untuk menghapus item daftar putar</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana je stavka sadržajnog izbornika za uklanjanje stavki popisa izvođenja</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout d’une option pour retirer les éléments de la liste de lecture dans le menu contextuel</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää pikavalikko soittolistan kohteiden poistamista varten</li>
          <li lang="eu">Erreprodukzio-zerrendako elementuak kentzeko laster-menuko elementua gehitu</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade un elemento al menú contextual para eliminar elementos de la lista de reproducción</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni kuntekstan menuon por forigado de spektolisteroj</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη αντικειμένου context menu για την αφαίρεση αντικειμένων λίστας αναπαραγωγής</li>
          <li lang="de">Neuer Kontextmenüeintrag zum Entfernen von Wiedergabelisten-Elementen</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj punkt i genvejsmenuen til fjernelse af afspilningslistepunkter</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána položka kontextové nabídky pro odstranění položek seznamu přehrávání</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix un element al menú contextual per suprimir elements de la llista de reproducció</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавена е опция в контекстното меню за премахване на елементи от списъка за изпълнение</li>
          <li lang="ar">أضف عنصر قائمة السياق لإزالة عناصر قائمة التشغيل</li>
          <li>
      Add context menu item for copying location of playlist items
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">增加上下文菜单项来复制播放列表项目的路径</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано пункт контекстного меню для копіювання розташування елементів добірки</li>
          <li lang="tr">Oynatma listesi ögelerinin konumunu kopyalamak için içerik menüsü ögesi ekle</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додата је ставка приручног изборника за умножавање места ставки списка пуштања</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add context menu item for copying location of playlist items</li>
          <li lang="ru">В контекстное меню добавлен пункт для копирования пути расположения элемента списка воспроизведения</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionado um item ao menu de contexto para copiar a localização dos itens da lista de reprodução</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionar item de menu de contexto para copiar a localização de itens da lista de reprodução</li>
          <li lang="pl">Menu kontekstowe do kopiowania ścieżki do pozycji listy odtwarzania</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Legg til bindeleddsmenyelementer for kopiering av plassering for spillelisteelementer</li>
          <li lang="ko">재생 목록 항목의 위치를 복사하기위한 컨텍스트 메뉴 항목 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta voce menù per copiare la posizione degli elementi della playlist</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan item menu konteks untuk menyalin lokasi item daftar putar</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana je stavka sadržajnog izbornika za kopiranje lokacije stavki popisa izvođenja</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout d’une option pour copier l'emplacement d'éléments de la liste de lecture dans le menu contextuel</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää pikavalikko kopioidaksesi soittolistan kohteiden sijainnin</li>
          <li lang="eu">Erreprodukzio-zerrendako elementuen kokalekua kopiatzeko laster-menuko elementua gehitu</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade un elemento al menú contextual para copiar la ubicación de los elementos de la lista de reproducción</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni kuntekstan menueron por kopiado de spektolistaj indikoj</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη αντικειμένου context menu για την αντιγραφή της τοποθεσίας αντικειμένων της λίστας αναπαραγωγής</li>
          <li lang="de">Neuer Kontextmenüeintrag zum Kopieren von Wiedergabelisten-Elementen</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj punkt i genvejsmenuen til kopiering af placering for afspilningslistepunkter</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána položka kontextové nabídky pro zkopírování umístění položek seznamu přehrávání</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix un element al menú contextual per copiar la ubicació dels elements de la llista de reproducció</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавяне на елемент от контекстното меню за копиране на местоположението на елементите от списъка за изпълнение</li>
          <li lang="ar">أضف عنصر قائمة السياق لنسخ موقع عناصر قائمة التشغيل</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
     This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個清單不是完整的。請到 git log 中檢視完整的變更記錄。</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个列表不完整。请到 git log 中查看完整的 changelog。</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей перелік не повний. Вичерпний перелік змін перегляньте у журналі git.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu liste eksik. Değişikliklerin tamamı için git günlüğüne bakın.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här listan är ofullständig. Se git-loggen för fullständig ändringslogg.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Овај списак је непотпун. Видите гитов дневник за потпуни дневник измена.</p>
        <p lang="sl">This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Это не полный список. Полный список изменений см. в журнале git.</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta lista está incompleta. Consulte o registo git para ver todas as alterações.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta listagem está incompleta. Veja log git para changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta lista jest niepełna. Polecenie „git log” wyświetli pełną listę zmian.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze lijst is onvolledig. Zie git log voor volledige changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 목록은 불완전합니다. 전체 변경 로그는 git 로그를 참조하십시오.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa lista è incompleta. Consultare git log per il changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="id">Daftar ini tidak lengkap. Lihat catatan git untuk daftar perubahan yang lengkap.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovaj popis je nepotpun. Pogledajte git zapis za potpuni pregled promjena.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette liste n’est pas complète. Pour voir tous les changements utilisez git log.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä luettelo on puutteellinen. Katso täydellinen git-muutosloki.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Zerrenda hau osatugabea da. Ikusi git log aldaketen zerrenda osorako.</p>
        <p lang="es">Este listado está incompleto. Consulte el registro de Git para obtener un registro de cambios completo.</p>
        <p lang="eo">La listo estas nekompleta. Uzu la komandon 'git log' por plena ŝanĝaro.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η καταχώρηση είναι ατελής. Δες την καταγραφή (log) του git για την πλήρη καταγραφή των αλλαγών (changelog).</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Liste ist unvollständig. Eine detaillierte Übersicht bietet das Changelog.</p>
        <p lang="da">Listen er ikke komplet. Se git-loggen for en komplet ændringslog.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tento seznam je neúplný. Úplný přehled změn najdete v git logu.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquest llistat és incomplet. Consulteu el registre del Git per obtenir un registre de canvis complet.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Списъкът не е завършен. Вижте Git лога за пълния списък с промени.</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذه القائمة غير مكتملة. انظر سجل بوابة التغيير الكامل.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-02-17" version="0.14">
      <description>
        <p>
     This release contains the following changes:
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此發行版本包含了以下變更：</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">该发布版本包含了以下变更：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск містить такі зміни:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm aşağıdaki değişiklikleri içerir:</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här versionen innehåller följande ändringar:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање садржи следеће измене:</p>
        <p lang="sl">This release contains the following changes:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje nasledujúce zmeny:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск содержит следующие изменения:</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão contém as seguintes alterações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera następujące zmiany:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze uitgave bevat de volgende aanpassingen:</p>
        <p lang="nb_NO">Denne utgaven inneholder følgende endringer:</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리스에는 다음 변경 사항이 포함됩니다:</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione contiene le seguenti modifiche:</p>
        <p lang="is">Þessi útgáfa inniheldur eftirfarandi breytingar:</p>
        <p lang="ie">Ti version contene li sequent modificationes:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini berisi perubahan berikut:</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás a következő változtatásokat tartalmazza:</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovo izdanje sadrži sljedeće promjene:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version apporte les changement suivants :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä julkaisu sisältää seuraavat muutokset:</p>
        <p lang="fa">این نسخه شامل تغییرات زیر است:</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek ondorengo aldaketak ditu:</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión contiene los cambios siguientes:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Ĉi tiu eldono enhavas la jenajn ŝanĝojn:</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση περιλαμβάνει τις παρακάτω αλλαγές:</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Veröffentlichungen umfasst die folgenden Änderungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Udgivelsen indeholder følgende ændringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tato verze obsahuje následující změny:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió conté els canvis següents:</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание съдържа следните промени:</p>
        <p lang="ar">يحتوي هذا الإصدار على التغييرات التالية:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>
      Add option to make skip buttons change playlist entries rather than
      chapters
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">增加选项来让跳转按钮可以切换播放列表项，而不是切换章节</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано можливість змінювати переходу між добірками замість розділів кнопкою пропуску</li>
          <li lang="tr">Atla düğmelerinin bölümler yerine oynatma listesi girişlerini değiştirmesini sağlamak için seçenek ekle</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додата је опција да би дугмад прескакања мењала уносе списка пуштања уместо поглавља</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add option to make skip buttons change playlist entries rather than chapters</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлена настройка использования кнопок пропуска для перехода по списку воспроизведения вместо перехода по главам</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionada uma opção para que os botões Ignorar alterem entre entradas da lista de reprodução e não entre capítulos</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionar a opção para fazer os botões de pular carregarem de lista de reprodução, ao invés de pular capítulos</li>
          <li lang="pl">Opcja zmieniająca działanie przycisków przechodzenia z rozdziałów na pozycje listy odtwarzania</li>
          <li lang="ko">건너 뛰기 버튼으로 챕터 대신 재생 목록 항목을 변경하는 옵션 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta opzione per fare in modo che i pulsanti di salto cambino gli elementi della playlist piuttosto che i capitoli</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan opsi untuk membuat tombol lewati mengubah entri daftar putar daripada bab</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana je mogućnost za stvaranje tipki preskakanja stavki popisa izvođenja radije nego poglavlja</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout d’une option pour faire agir les boutons de saut sur les éléments de la liste de lecture plutôt que sur les chapitres</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää vaihtoehto, jotta ohituspainikkeet muuttavat soittolistan merkintöjä lukujen sijasta</li>
          <li lang="eu">Saltatzeko botoiak erabiliz kapituluen ordez erreprodukzio-zerrendako sarrerak aldatzeko aukera gehitu</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade una opción para que los botones de salto seleccionen las entradas de la lista de reproducción en lugar de los capítulos</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni opcion por ŝanĝi spektolisterojn anstataŭ ĉapitrojn per preterpasaj butonoj</li>
          <li lang="el">Προσθήκη επιλογής ώστε τα κουμπιά υπερπήδησης (skip) να αλλάζουν καταχωρήσεις της λίστας αναπαραγωγής αντί για κεφάλαια</li>
          <li lang="de">Neue Option, die es erlaubt, das Verhalten der Überspringen-Schaltfläche zu verändern. Zur Wahl stehen Kapitelwechsel und Wechsel zwischen Wiedergabelisten-Elementen</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføjet valgmulighed for at få spring over-knappen til at ændre afspilningslistepunkter frem for kapitler.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána možnost, aby tlačítka pro přeskočení měnila položky seznamu přehrávání místo kapitol</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix una opció per fer que els botons de salt seleccionin les entrades de la llista de reproducció en lloc dels capítols</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавена е опция, бутона за пропускане да променя елементите от списъка, а не не заглавията</li>
          <li lang="ar">إضافة خيار لجعل أزرار التخطي تغير إدخالات قائمة التشغيل بدلاً من الفصول</li>
          <li>
      Make the file chooser accept non-local locations
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">让文件选择器可以接受非本地路径</li>
          <li lang="uk">Можливість приймати у вікні вибору файлів не локальні розташування</li>
          <li lang="tr">Dosya seçicinin yerel olmayan kaynakları kabul etmesini sağla</li>
          <li lang="sr">Бирач датотека прихвата не-месна места</li>
          <li lang="sl">Make the file chooser accept non-local locations</li>
          <li lang="ru">Поддержка сетевых расположений в диалоге выбора файла</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Permitir que o seletor de ficheiros aceite localizações não locais</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Fazer o seletor de arquivos aceitar locais não-locais</li>
          <li lang="pl">Okno wyboru pliku przyjmuje nielokalne ścieżki</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Filutvelger godtar ikke-lokale plasseringer</li>
          <li lang="ko">파일 선택 시 로컬이 아닌 위치를 허용하도록 설정</li>
          <li lang="it">Il selettore dei file ora accetta anche posizioni non-locali</li>
          <li lang="id">Buat pemilih berkas menerima lokasi berkas yang tidak ada di penyimpanan lokal</li>
          <li lang="hr">Odabiratelj datoteka sada prihvaća nelokalne lokacije</li>
          <li lang="fr">Le sélecteur de fichiers accepte les emplacements distants</li>
          <li lang="fi">Varmista, että tiedoston valitsin hyväksyy muut kuin paikalliset sijainnit</li>
          <li lang="eu">Fitxategi-hautatzaileak kokaleku ez-lokalak onartzen ditu orain</li>
          <li lang="es">Hace que el selector de archivos acepte ubicaciones no locales</li>
          <li lang="eo">Akceptigi forajn lokojn al la dosiera elektilo</li>
          <li lang="el">Κάνε τον επιλογέα αρχείων να δέχεται μη-τοπικές (non-local) τοποθεσίες</li>
          <li lang="de">Der Dateiwähler akzeptiert nun auch nicht-lokale Orte</li>
          <li lang="da">Fået filvælgeren til at accepterer placeringer som ikke er lokale</li>
          <li lang="cs">Akceptovat vzdálená umístění při výběru souborů</li>
          <li lang="ca">Fa que el selector de fitxers accepti ubicacions no locals</li>
          <li lang="bg">Файловия браузър има възможност да избира не-локални местоположение</li>
          <li lang="ar">اجعل منتقي الملفات يقبل المواقع غير المحلية</li>
          <li>
      Add right-click menu entry for looping a single file
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">增加循环播放单个文件的右键菜单项</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано пункт контекстного меню для повторення одного файлу</li>
          <li lang="tr">Tek bir dosyayı yinelemek için sağ tıklatma menüsü girişi ekle</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додат је унос изборника десног клика за понављање једне датотеке</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add right-click menu entry for looping a single file</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлен элемент контекстного меню для циклического воспроизведения отдельного файла</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionada um item ao menu de contexto para repetir um único ficheiro</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionar menu de contexto no botão direito para fazer a repetição de um único arquivo</li>
          <li lang="pl">Powtarzanie jednego pliku w menu pod prawym przyciskiem</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Legg til høyreklikksmenyoppføring for gjentagelse av én fil</li>
          <li lang="ko">단일 파일을 반복하기위한 오른쪽 클릭 메뉴 항목 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta una voce nel menù clic-destro per ripetere un singolo file</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan entri menu klik kanan untuk mengulang satu file</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana je stavka izbornika lijevog klika u svrhu ponavljanja jedne datoteke</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout d’une option dans le menu contextuel pour lire un fichier en boucle</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää hiiren kakkospainikkeella merkintä yksittäisen kappaleen silmukointi</li>
          <li lang="eu">Fitxategi bakarra begiztan jartzeko sarrera gehitu eskuineko botoiko laster-menuan</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade una entrada en el menú contextual para reproducir en bucle un único archivo</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni dekstraklakan menueron por ripetado de unu dosiero</li>
          <li lang="de">Neues Rechtsklickmenü um einzelne Datei in Schleife zu spielen</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj menupunkt ved højreklik for at afspille en enkelt fil i løkke</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána položka kontextové nabídky pro přehrávání souboru ve smyčce</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix una entrada al menú contextual per reproduir en bucle un únic fitxer</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавяне на елемент в менюто при десен бутон на мишката за превъртане на единичен файл</li>
          <li lang="ar">أضف إدخال قائمة النقر بزر الماوس الأيمن لتكرار ملف واحد</li>
          <li>
      Handle property change events for fullscreen and window-scale
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">处理全屏和窗口大小的属性变化事件</li>
          <li lang="uk">Обробляти події зміни властивостей для повноекранного режиму і масштабу вікна</li>
          <li lang="tr">Tam ekran ve pencere ölçeği için özellik değiştirme olaylarını işle</li>
          <li lang="sr">Ради се са догађајима промене својства за цео екран и сразмеру прозора</li>
          <li lang="sl">Handle property change events for fullscreen and window-scale</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обработка событий изменения свойств для полноэкранного и оконного масштаба</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Manipulação de eventos de alteração da propriedade para ecrã inteiro e escala de janela</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Manipular eventos de mudança de propriedade para tela inteira e escala de janela</li>
          <li lang="pl">Obsługa zdarzeń zmiany własności dla pełnego ekranu i skalowania okna</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Håndter egenskapsendringshendelser for fullskjerm- og vindus-skalering</li>
          <li lang="ko">전체 화면 및 창 크기에 대한 속성 변경 이벤트 처리</li>
          <li lang="it">Gestione degli eventi di modifica delle proprietà per fullscreen e window-scale</li>
          <li lang="id">Menangani peristiwa perubahan properti untuk layar penuh dan skala jendela</li>
          <li lang="hr">Rukovanje događajima svojstava promjene za cjelozaslonski ili prikaz u prozoru</li>
          <li lang="fr">Support des changements de propriétés pour le plein écran et la taille de fenêtre</li>
          <li lang="fi">Muuttaa koko näytön ja ikkunan mittakaavan tapahtumia</li>
          <li lang="eu">Pantaila osoa eta leihoa eskalatzea kudeatzeko aldaketa gertaerak kudeatu</li>
          <li lang="es">Maneja los eventos de cambio de propiedad para la pantalla completa y la escala de la ventana</li>
          <li lang="eo">Trakti okazojn de ecaj ŝanĝoj por « fullscreen » kaj « window-scale »</li>
          <li lang="de">Korrekte Handhabung von property change events für den Vollbildmodus und bei Fenstersklaierung</li>
          <li lang="da">Håndter hændelser af egenskabsændring for fuldskærm og vinduesskalering</li>
          <li lang="cs">Ovládat události změn vlastností pro režim celé obrazovky a pro měřítko okna</li>
          <li lang="ca">Gestiona els esdeveniments de canvi de propietat per a la pantalla completa i l'escala de la finestra</li>
          <li lang="bg">Обработване на събития за промяна на свойствата за цял екран и мащаб на прозореца</li>
          <li lang="ar">التعامل مع أحداث تغيير الخاصية لملء الشاشة ومقياس النافذة</li>
          <li>
      Add option to autohide mouse cursor in windowed mode
     </li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">增加选项以在窗口模式下自动隐藏鼠标指针</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано параметр автоматичного приховування курсора миші у віконному режимі</li>
          <li lang="tr">Pencere kipinde fare imlecini otomatik gizle</li>
          <li lang="sv">Lägg till alternativet att dölja muspekaren automatiskt i fönsterläge</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додата је опција за самоскривање курзора миша у режиму прозора</li>
          <li lang="sl">Add option to autohide mouse cursor in windowed mode</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлена настройка автоматического скрытия курсора в оконном режиме</li>
          <li lang="pt_PT">Adicionada uma opção para ocultar automaticamente o cursor do rato no modo de janela</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adic. opção auto-ocultar o ponteiro do mouse no modo tela cheia</li>
          <li lang="pl">Opcja automatycznego ukrywania kursora w trybie okna</li>
          <li lang="nb_NO">Legg til innstilling for autoskjuling av musepeker i vindusmodus</li>
          <li lang="ko">창 모드에서 마우스 커서 자동 숨기기 옵션 추가</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta opzione per nascondere automaticamente il cursore nella modalità finestra</li>
          <li lang="id">Tambahkan opsi untuk menyembunyikan kursor mouse secara otomatis dalam mode jendela</li>
          <li lang="hr">Dodana je mogućnost za automatsko sakrivanje pokazivača miša u prozorskom načinu prikaza</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout d’une option pour masquer automatiquement le curseur de la souris en mode fenêtré</li>
          <li lang="fi">Lisää vaihtoehto hiiren kohdistimen automaattiseen piilottamiseen ikkunatilassa</li>
          <li lang="eu">Leiho moduan saguaren kurtsorea automatikoki ezkutatzeko aukera gehitu</li>
          <li lang="es">Añade una opción para ocultar automáticamente el cursor del ratón en el modo ventana</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni opcion por aŭtomata kaŝo de musmontrilo en fenestra reĝimo</li>
          <li lang="de">Mauszeiger im Fenstermodus automatisch ausblenden</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføjet valgmulighed for automatisk at skjule musemarkøren i vinduestilstand</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána možnost pro automatické skrývání kurzoru myši v režimu okna</li>
          <li lang="ca">Afegeix una opció per amagar automàticament el punter del ratolí al mode finestra</li>
          <li lang="bg">Добавена е опция за скриване на курсора на мишката в прозоречен режим</li>
          <li lang="ar">إضافة خيار لإخفاء مؤشر الماوس تلقائيًا في وضع الإطارات</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
     This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.
    </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個清單不是完整的。請到 git log 中檢視完整的變更記錄。</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个列表不完整。请到 git log 中查看完整的 changelog。</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей перелік не повний. Вичерпний перелік змін перегляньте у журналі git.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu liste eksik. Değişikliklerin tamamı için git günlüğüne bakın.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här listan är ofullständig. Se git-loggen för fullständig ändringslogg.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Овај списак је непотпун. Видите гитов дневник за потпуни дневник измена.</p>
        <p lang="sl">This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Это не полный список. Полный список изменений см. в журнале git.</p>
        <p lang="pt_PT">Esta lista está incompleta. Consulte o registo git para ver todas as alterações.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta listagem está incompleta. Veja log git para changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta lista jest niepełna. Polecenie „git log” wyświetli pełną listę zmian.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze lijst is onvolledig. Zie git log voor volledige changelog.</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 목록은 불완전합니다. 전체 변경 로그는 git 로그를 참조하십시오.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa lista è incompleta. Consultare git log per il changelog completo.</p>
        <p lang="id">Daftar ini tidak lengkap. Lihat catatan git untuk daftar perubahan yang lengkap.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovaj popis je nepotpun. Pogledajte git zapis za potpuni pregled promjena.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette liste n’est pas complète. Pour voir tous les changements utilisez git log.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä luettelo on puutteellinen. Katso täydellinen git-muutosloki.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Zerrenda hau osatugabea da. Ikusi git log aldaketen zerrenda osorako.</p>
        <p lang="es">Este listado está incompleto. Consulte el registro de Git para obtener un registro de cambios completo.</p>
        <p lang="eo">La listo estas nekompleta. Uzu la komandon 'git log' por plena ŝanĝaro.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η καταχώρηση είναι ατελής. Δες την καταγραφή (log) του git για την πλήρη καταγραφή των αλλαγών (changelog).</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Liste ist unvollständig. Eine detaillierte Übersicht bietet das Changelog.</p>
        <p lang="da">Listen er ikke komplet. Se git-loggen for en komplet ændringslog.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tento seznam je neúplný. Úplný přehled změn najdete v git logu.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquest llistat és incomplet. Consulteu el registre del Git per obtenir un registre de canvis complet.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Списъкът не е завършен. Вижте Git лога за пълния списък с промени.</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذه القائمة غير مكتملة. انظر سجل بوابة التغيير الكامل.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-10-13" version="0.13" />
  </releases>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://celluloid-player.github.io/images/screenshot-0.png</image>
      <caption>The main window showing the application in action</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">顯示執行中應用程式的主視窗</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">显示运行中应用的主窗口</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Головне вікно тепер показує застосунок у дії</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Uygulamayı çalışırken gösteren ana pencere</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Главни прозор приказује програм у акцији</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">The main window showing the application in action</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Главное окно, показывающее приложение в действии</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_PT">Janela principal a mostrar a aplicação em ação</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Mostrando o aplicativo em ação na janela principal</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Główne okno przedstawiające działanie programu</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Het hoofdvenster dat de applicatie in actie laat zien</caption>
      <caption lang="nb_NO">Hovedvinduet som viser programmet i funksjon</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">작동중인 애플리케이션을 보여주는 기본 창</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La finestra principale in funzione</caption>
      <caption lang="is">Aðalglugginn sýnir virkni forritsins</caption>
      <caption lang="ie">Li fenestre principal del activ application</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Jendela utama menunjukkan aplikasi dalam aksi</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Az alkalmazás működés közben</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Glavni prozor prikazuje aplikaciju u akciji</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">La fenêtre principale montrant l’application en action</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Pääikkuna, joka näyttää sovelluksen olevan toiminnassa</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Leiho nagusia aplikazioa lanean erakusten</caption>
      <caption lang="es">La ventana principal con la aplicación en acción</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">La ĉefa fenestro montras la funkciantan aplikaĵon</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Das Hauptfenser von Celluloid</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Hovedvinduet som viser programmet i funktion</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Hlavní okno a aplikace v akci</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">La finestra principal amb l'aplicació en acció</caption>
      <caption lang="bg">Основният прозорец показва програмата в действие</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">النافذة الرئيسية تظهر التطبيق أثناء العمل</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://celluloid-player.github.io/images/screenshot-1.png</image>
      <caption>The main window with CSD disabled</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">關閉了 CSD 的主視窗</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">关闭了 CSD 的主窗口</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Вимкнено CSD головного вікна</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">CSD'nin devre dışı bırakıldığı ana pencere</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Huvudfönstret med CSD inaktiverat</caption>
      <caption lang="sr@latin">Glavni prozor sa onemogućenim CSD-om</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Главни прозор са онемогућеним „CSD“-ом</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">The main window with CSD disabled</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Главное окно с отключённым CSD</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_PT">Janela principal com decorações 'client side' desativadas</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Janela principal com CSD desativado</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Główne okno programu z wyłączonym wyświetlaniem obramowania okna po stronie klienta</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Het hoofdvenster met CSD uitgeschakeld</caption>
      <caption lang="nb_NO">Hovedvindu med overleggsmeny avskrudd</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">CSD가 비활성화 된 기본 창</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La finestra principale con le decorazioni client-side disattivate</caption>
      <caption lang="is">Aðalglugginn með CSD óvirkt</caption>
      <caption lang="ie">Li primari fenestre sin CSD</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Jendela utama dengan CSD dinonaktifkan</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">A főablak letiltott díszítésekkel</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Glavni prozor s onemogućenim CSD-om</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">La fenêtre principale avec CSD désactivé</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Pääikkuna, jossa CSD on poistettu käytöstä</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Leiho nagusia CSD desgaituta</caption>
      <caption lang="es">La ventana principal con las decoraciones del lado del cliente desactivadas</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">La ĉefa fenestro kun malŝaltitaj klient-flankaj ornamaĵoj</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Das Hauptfenster ohne CSD-Titelleiste</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Hovedvinduet med deaktiveret skærmdisplay</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Hlavní okno s vypnutými dekoracemi na straně klienta</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">La finestra principal amb les decoracions del client desactivades</caption>
      <caption lang="bg">Главният прозорец с изключен CSD</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">النافذة الرئيسية مع تعطيل CSD</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://celluloid-player.github.io/images/screenshot-2.png</image>
      <caption>The main window with playlist open</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">打開了播放清單的主視窗</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">打开了播放列表的主窗口</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Головне вікно з відкритою добіркою</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Oynatma listesi açık olan ana pencere</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Huvudfönstret med spelningslista öppen</caption>
      <caption lang="sr@latin">Glavni prozor sa otvorenom listom puštanja</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Главни прозор са отвореним списком пуштања</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">The main window with playlist open</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Главное окно с открытым списком воспроизведения</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_PT">Janela principal com uma lista de reprodução aberta</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Janela principal com a lista de reprodução aberta</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Główne okno programu z listą odtwarzania</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Het hoofdvenster met een afspeellijst open</caption>
      <caption lang="nb_NO">Hovedvindu med åpen spilleliste</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">재생 목록이 열려있는 기본 창</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La finestra principale con la playlist visualizzata</caption>
      <caption lang="is">Aðalglugginn með spilunarlistann opinn</caption>
      <caption lang="ie">Li fenestre principal con li apertet playlist</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Jendela utama dengan daftar putar terbuka</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">A főablak megnyitott lejátszási listával</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Glavni prozor s otvorenim popisom izvođenja</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">La fenêtre principale avec la liste de lecture ouverte</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Pääikkuna, jossa soittolista on auki</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Leiho nagusia erreprodukzio-zerrenda irekita</caption>
      <caption lang="es">La ventana principal con la lista de reproducción abierta</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">La ĉefa fenestro kun malfermita spektolisto</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Das Hauptfenster mit Wiedergabeliste</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Hovedvinduet med åben afspilningsliste</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Hlavní okno s otevřeným seznamem přehrávání</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">La finestra principal amb la llista de reproducció oberta</caption>
      <caption lang="bg">Главният прозорец с отворен спъсък за изпълнение</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">النافذة الرئيسية مع قائمة التشغيل مفتوحة</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">http://celluloid-player.github.io</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">http://github.com/celluloid-player/celluloid/issues</url>
  <url type="translate">http://translate.zanata.org/project/view/celluloid</url>
  <update_contact>gnome-mpv_at_teknik.io</update_contact>
</component>