<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>cinnamon.xreader</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">xreader.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="cached" height="64" width="64">xreader.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">xreader.png</icon>
  <id>xreader.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Document Viewer</name>
  <summary>A Document Viewer</summary>
  <summary lang="af">'N Dokumentkyker</summary>
  <summary lang="am">ሰነድ መመልከቻ</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">عارض المستندات</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Прагляднік дакументаў</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Четец на документи</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Un visualitzador de documents</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Un visualitzador de documents</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Prohlížeč dokumentů</summary>
  <summary lang="cy">Dangosydd Dogfennau</summary>
  <summary lang="da">En dokumentfremviser</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Ein Dokumentenbetrachter</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Μια Εφαρμογή Προβολής Εγγράφων</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">A Document Viewer</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Rigardilo por dokumentoj</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Un visor de documentos</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Dokumendinäitaja</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Dokumentu-ikustailea</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Tiedostokatselin</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Visionneur de documents</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Un visualizador de documentos</summary>
  <summary lang="he">משקף מסמכים</summary>
  <summary lang="hi">एक दस्तावेज़ प्रदर्शक</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Preglednik dokumenata</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Dokumentum-megjelenítő</summary>
  <summary lang="ia">Un visor del documentos</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Penampil dokumen</summary>
  <summary lang="ie">Un visor de documentes</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Skjalaskoðari</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Un visore di documenti</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">ドキュメントビューア</summary>
  <summary lang="kab">Tameskant n isemliyen</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">Құжаттарды Қарағыш</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">문서 뷰어</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Dokumentų žiūryklė</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Paparan Dokumen</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Dokument Leser</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Een documentenkijker</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Un afichador de documents</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Przeglądarka dokumentów</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Visualizador de documentos</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Um visualizador de documentos</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Vizualizator de documente</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Просмотрщик документов</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Prehliadač dokumentov</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Ogledovalnik dokumentov</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Прегледач докумената</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Pregledač dokumenata</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">En Dokumentvisare</summary>
  <summary lang="th">โปรแกรมดูเอกสาร</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Belge Görüntüleyici</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Переглядач документів</summary>
  <summary lang="ur">دستاویزات دیکھنے کے لیے پروگرام</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">一个文档查看器</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_HK">文件檢視器</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">文件檢視器</summary>
  <description>
    <p> Xreader is a simple multi-page document viewer. It can display and print PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS and Portable Document Format (PDF) files, as well as comic book archive files. When supported by the document, it also allows searching for text, copying text to the clipboard, hypertext navigation and table-of-contents bookmarks. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="am">
    <p> Xአንባቢ ቀላል የሆነ የ በርካት-ገጽ ሰነድ መመልከቻ ነው: ማሳየት እና ማተም ይቻላል የ PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS and Portable Document Format (PDF) ፋይሎች: እንዲሁም የ ኮሚክ መጽሀፎችን ፋይሎችን ማህደር: ሰነዱ የሚደገፍ ከሆነ: እንዲሁም ጽሁፍ መፈለግ ያስችላል: ጽሁፎችን ኮፒ ማድረግ ወደ ቁራጭ ሰሌዳ: hypertext መቃኛ እና የ ሰንጠረዥ-በ-ይዞታዎች ውስጥ ምልክት ማድረግ ይችላል: </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p> Xreader هو عارض مستندات بسيط متعدد الصفحات. يمكنه عرض وطباعة ملفات PostScript، و مغلفة PostScript (EPS)، وDJVU، وDVI، وXPS، وتنسيق المستند المحمول (PDF)، بالإضافة إلى ملفات أرشيف الكتاب الهزلي. عندما يدعمها المستند، ويسمح أيضًا بالبحث عن النص، ونسخ النص إلى الحافظة، وتنقل النص التشعبي، والإشارات المرجعية لجدول المحتويات.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p> Xreader - гэта просты прагляднік шматстаронкавых дакументаў. Ён умее паказваць і друкаваць файлы PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS, PDF і комікс-архівы. Дазваляе шукаць па тэксце, капіяваць у буфер абмену, карыстацца ўнутранымі спасылкамі і закладкамі ў змесце (калі дакумент гэта падтрымлівае). </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p> Xreader е опростен четец на документи. Той може да показва и разпечатва файлове с формати PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS and Portable Document Format (PDF), а също така и комикси. Когато е възможно, може да търсите текст в документа, да копирате текст, да отваряте връзки и да добавяте отметки.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p> X Reader és un senzill visualitzador de documents multipàgina. Pot visualitzar i imprimir fitxers PostScript (PS), PostScript encapsulat (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS i PDF, així com els fitxers tipus Comic Book. Si el document ho permet, també es pot buscar text i copiar-lo al porta-retalls, navegar per hipertext i utilitzar marcadors de taules de contingut. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p> Xreader je jednoduchý prohlížeč vícestránkových dokumentů. Zobrazuje a tiskne formáty PostStript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS, Portable Document Format (PDF) a soubory knih komixů. Pokud je podporováno dokumentem, je možné vyhledávat, kopírovat do schránky, používat hypertextovou navigaci a tabulku obsahu. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cy">
    <p>Mae Xreader yn ddangosydd dogfennau aml-dudalen syml. Gall ddangos ac argraffu ffeiliau PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS a Fformat Dogfen Gludadwy (PDF), yn ogystal â ffeiliau archif llyfrau comig. Pan mae'r ddogfen yn ei gefnogi, mae hefyd yn caniatáu chwilio am destun, copïo testun i'r clipfwrdd, llywio hyperdestun a nodau tudalen tabl-cynnwys.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p> Xreader er et program til visning af flersidede dokumenter. Det kan vise og udskrive filer af typen PostScript (PS), indkapslet PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS og Portable Document Format (PDF) så vel som tegneserie-arkivfiler. Hvis det understøttes af dokumentet, kan der søges efter tekst, kopieres tekst til udklipsholderen, foretages navigation i hypertekst og indholdsfortegnelsesbogmærker. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p> Xreader ist ein einfacher Dokumentenbetrachter für mehrere Seiten. Er kann Dateien in den Formaten PostScript (PS), eingekapseltes PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS und portables Dokumentenformat (PDF) sowie Comic-Archivdateien anzeigen und drucken. Wenn es durch das Dokument unterstützt wird, dann kann das Suchen nach Text, das Kopieren von Text in Zwischenablage, Hypertext-Navigation und Inhaltsverzeichnislesezeichen benutzt werden. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p> Το Xreader είναι μια απλή εφαρμογή προβολής πολυσέλιδων εγγράφων. Μπορεί να προβάλλει και να εκτυπώσει αρχεία PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS και Portable Document Format (PDF), καθώς και αρχεία αρχειοθετημένων βιβλίων κόμικ. Όταν υποστηρίζεται από το έγγραφο, επιτρέπει επίσης αναζήτηση για κείμενο, αντιγραφή κειμένου στο πρόχειρο, πλοήγηση υπερ-κειμένου και δημιουργία σελιδοδεικτών για τον πίνακα περιεχομένων. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p> Xreader is a simple multi-page document viewer. It can display and print PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS and Portable Document Format (PDF) files, as well as comic book archive files. When supported by the document, it also allows searching for text, copying text to the clipboard, hypertext navigation and table-of-contents bookmarks. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p> Xreader estas simpla mult-paĝa dokumentrigardilo. Ĝi povas vidigi kaj presi dosierojn kun aranĝo PostScript (PS), Enkapsuligita PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS kaj Portebla Dokument-Formo (PDF), same kiel komikslibraj arkivdosieroj. Se subtenata de la dokumento, ĝi ankaŭ permesas serĉadon pri teksto, kopiadon de teksto al tondujo, hipertekstan navigadon kaj enhavtabel-legosignojn. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p> Xreader es un sencillo visor de documentos multipágina. Puede mostrar e imprimir archivos PostScript (PS), PostScript encapsulado (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS y PDF, así como archivadores de cómics. Cuando el documento lo admite, también permite buscar texto, copiar texto en el portapapeles, navegar por hipertexto y usar marcadores de índice. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p> Xreader on lihtne mitmeleheküljeliste dokumentide kuvaja. See avab ja prindib PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS ja PDF faile, samuti koomiksiraamatu arhiivifaile. Kui dokument seda võimaldab, on võimalik otsida teksti, kopeerida seda lõikelauale, kasutada linke ja sisukorra järjehoidjaid. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Xreader orri anitzeko dokumentu-ikustaile sinplea da. PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS eta Portable Document Format (PDF) formatuetako fitxategiak eta komiki artxibo fitxategiak bistaratu eta inprimatu ditzake. Dokumentuak onartzen duenean testuan bilaketak egin, testua arbelera kopiatu, hipertestu bidez nabigatu eta aurkibideko laster-markak erabil ditzake. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>XReader on yksinkertainen useampisivuisen tiedoston katselin. Se osaa näyttää ja tulostaa PostScript-, EPS-, DJVU-, DVI-, XPS- ja PDF-tiedostoja samoin kuin sarjakuva-arkistotiedostoja. Jos tiedosto ominaisuutta tukee, ohjelma osaa etsiä tekstiä ja kopioida sitä leikepöydälle, liikkua tiedostossa hypertekstinä ja merkitä kirjanmerkkejä sisällykseen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p> Xreader est un simple visionneur de document multi-page. Il peut afficher et imprimer des fichiers PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS et des Portable Document Format (PDF), ainsi que des fichiers comic book archive (Bandes dessinées). Lorsque le document le permet, il permet aussi la recherche de texte, la copie de texte vers le presse-papier, la navigation vers un hyperlien and l'utilisation d'une table des matières. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p> Xreader é un sinxelo visualizadorbde documentos multi-páxina. Pode visualizar e imprimir PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS e arquivos Portable Document Format (PDF), do mesmo xeito que comic book archive files. Cando o documento o soporta, tamén soporta a búsqueda de texto, copia de texto no portapapeis, navegación por hipertexto e marcas na tabla de contidos. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p> Xreader הוא מציג מסמכים, רב-עמודי, פשוט. הוא יכול להציג ולהדפיס קבצי פוסטסקריפט (PS),  פוסטסקריפט כמוס (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS ו- תַּסְדִּיר מסמכים נייד (PDF), כמו גם קבצי ארכיב קומיקס. כשהמסמך תומך בכך, הוא מאפשר גם חיפוש מלל, העתקת מלל ללוח, ניווט היפרטקסט וסימניות תוכן עניינים. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hi">
    <p> एक्स-रीडर एक सरल एकाधिक पृष्ठ युक्त प्रलेख प्रदर्शक है। आप इसके द्वारा पोस्टस्क्रिप्ट (PS), संक्षिप्त पोस्टस्क्रिप्ट (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS व पीडीएफ (PDF) फाइलों के अतिरिक्त कॉमिक संग्रह फाइलें प्रदर्शित व प्रिंट कर सकते हैं। प्रलेख अनुसार लेख खोज व क्लिपबोर्ड पर कॉपी करना, हाइपरटेक्स्ट परिचालन एवं विषय-सूची पृष्ठ-स्मृति भी समर्थित है।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p> Xreader je jednostavan višestranični preglednik dokumenata. Može prikazivati i ispisivati PostSkripte (PS), Zatvorene PostSkripte (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS i Prijenosni Dokumentni Format (PDF) datoteke, kao i arhivirane datoteke stripa. Kada je podržano dokumentom, isto tako omogućuje pretraživanje teksta, kopiranje teksta u međuspremnik, navigaciju hiperteksta i tablicu sadržaja zabilješki. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p> Az Xreader egy egyszerűen használható több oldalas dokumentum-megjelenítő. Képes megjeleníteni és nyomtatni a PostScript (PS), az Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), a DJVU, a DVI, az XPS és a Portable Document Format (PDF) fájlok mellett a képregény archívumokat is. Ha egy dokumentum támogatja, lehetővé teszi a szöveges keresést, a szövegek másolását a vágólapra, a hiperhivatkozások használatát és a tartalomjegyzék könyvjelzőket is. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ia">
    <p> Xreader es un simple visor de documentos plure-pagina. Illo pote monstrar e stampar files PostScript (PS),PostScript Incapsulate (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS e PDF, assi como files archivo de libro comic. Quando supportate per le documento, illo alsi permitte de cercar pro texto, copiar texto al area de transferentia, navigation de hypertexto e marcapaginas de tabula del contentos. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p> Xreader adalah penampil dokumen multi halaman yang sederhana. Bisa menampilkan dan mencetak PostScript(PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS dan file Portable Document Format (PDF), juga file archive buku komik. Ketika dokumen telah mendukung, juga dapat mencari kata, menyalin kata,navigasi hypertext dan tabel isi dari penanda halaman. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>Evince er einfalt forrit sem birtir skjöl skjöl. Það getur bæði birt og prentað PostScript-skrár (PS), Encapsulated PostScript-skrár (EPS), DJVU-skrár , DVI-skrár, XPS-skrár og Portable Document Format-skrár (PDF) auk nokkurra tegunda myndasögusafnskráa. Það getur líka leitað að texta í skjölum, afritað textann, styður stiklutexta og bókamerki í efnisyfirliti.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p> Xreader è un visore di documenti semplice e multi-pagina. Può mostrare file nei formati seguenti: Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS, Portable Document Format (PDF) e comic book archive. Se consentito dal documento, può effettuare ricerche di testo, copiare testo, esplorazione di ipertesto, e fissare riferimenti all'indice. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p> Xreaderは、シンプルなマルチページのドキュメントビューアです。PostScript(PS)、Encapsulated PostScript(EPS)、DJVU、DVI、XPSおよびPDF(Portable Document Format)ファイル、およびコミックブックアーカイブファイルを表示および印刷できます。ドキュメントでサポートされている場合、テキストの検索、テキストのクリップボードへのコピー、ハイパーテキストナビゲーション、目次ブックマークも使用できます。 </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="kab">
    <p> Xreader d taskant n usmel aget-asebter afessas. Iskanay-d sakin isaggaz PostScript (PS), PostScript Ittwagebren (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS  akked ifuyla n ismal ittwarfaden s umasal (PDF), daɣ ifuyla n uḥraz n udlis. Mi ara ittusefrak isemli, ittmudaɣ-d tagnit i unadi n uḍris, anɣal akked usenṭeḍ n uḍris ɣer "ɣef ufus", tunigin gar ugbur n ticcra n iccaren.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <р> Xreader бұл қарапайым көпбетті құжаттарды көретін бағдарлама. Ол PostScript (КС), Инкапсуландырылған PostScript (EPS) және форматы djvu және DVI, және XPS, (PDF) файлдарды қарап және басып шағарады, сондай-ақ комикс-мұрағат файлдар. Қашан құжат ашылғанда, ол сондай-ақ мәтін бойынша іздестіру, көшіру сақтағышқа гипертекстті навигация және мазмұндары қалауға мүмкіндік береді. </р>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p> 엑스리더는 간편한 여러 쪽 문서 뷰어입니다.  엑스리더는 포스트스크립트(PS), 캡슐화된 포스트스크립트(EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS와 휴대용 문서 형식(PDF) 파일 등과 만화책용 문서 파일(cbaf)을 보여주고 출력할 수 있습니다. 문서에서 지원하면, 텍스트 검색, 클립보드로 복사하기, 하이퍼텍스트 검색과 북마크 사이드바 설정 등을 할 수 있습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p> Xreader yra paprasta dokumentų žiūryklė. Ji gali rodyti ir spausdinti PostScript (PS), uždarus PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS ir Portable Document Format (PDF) failus, o taip pat komiksų archyvų failus. Kuomet tai palaiko dokumentas, programa leidžia atlikti teksto paiešką, kopijuoti tekstą į iškarpinę ir palaiko hiperteksto naršymą bei turinio žymes. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p> Xreader adalah satu paparan dokumen pelbagai mukasurat yang mudah. Ia boleh papar dan cetak fail-fail PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS dan Portable Document Format (PDF), dan juga fail arkib buku komik. Bila dokumen itu disokong, ia juga membenarkan untuk mencari teks, menyalin teks ke clipboard, navigasi hyperteks dan penanda buku table-of-contents. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p> Xreader is een eenvoudige multipagina-documentkijker. Hij kan de volgende soorten bestanden weergeven en afdrukken: PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS en Portable Document Format (PDF) files en stripboekarchiefbestanden. Indien ondersteund door het document kan hij ook tekst doorzoeken, tekst kopiëren naar het klembord, navigeren via koppelingen en inhoudsopgave-bladwijzers. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p> Xreader jest prostą, wielostronicową przeglądarką dokumentów. Może wyświetlać oraz drukować pliki PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS oraz Portable Document Format (PDF), jak również zarchiwizowane pliki komiksów. W sytuacji obsługiwania przez dokument, umożliwia również na wyszukiwanie tekstu, kopiowanie tekstu do schowka, obsługę nawigacji hipertekstowej oraz zakładek spisu treści.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p> Xreader é um visualizador de documentos simplista. Pode mostrar e imprimir ficheiros PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS, Portable Document Format (PDF) e ficheiros de banda desenhada. Quando suportado pelo documento, também é possível procurar um texto, copiar o texto para a área de transferência, navegar hipertextos e marcadores para os índices. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p> Xreader é um visualizador de documentos simples multi-páginas. Ele pode exibir e imprimir PostScript (PS), Encapsulado PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS e arquivos Portable Document Format (PDF), bem como arquivos de histórias em quadrinhos. Quando suportado pelo documento, ele também permite procurar um texto, copiar o texto para a área de transferência, navegação hipertexto e marcadores de mesa-de-conteúdo. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p> Xreader este un vizualizator simplu de documente cu pagini multiple. Poate afișa și tipări fișiere PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS și Portable Document Format (PDF), dar și benzi desenate. Când documentul permite, poate, de asemenea, să caute în text, să copieze text în clipboard, să facă navigare hypertext și să pună semne de carte în conținut. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p> Xreader - это простой многостраничный просмотрщик документов. Он может отображать и распечатывать файлы PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS и Portable Document Format (PDF), а также файлы архивов комиксов. Если документ поддерживает такую возможность, Xreader также позволяет искать и копировать текст в буфер обмена, пользоваться гипертекстовой навигацией и закладками. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <P> Xreader je jednoduchý viacstránkový prehliadač dokumentov. Je možné zobrazovať a tlačiť PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS a súbory Portable Document Format (PDF), rovnako ako komiksové súbory. Pokiaľ túto funkciu podporuje dokument, tiež umožňuje vyhľadávanie textu, kopírovanie textu do schránky, navigáciu v hypertexte a v záložkách obsahu. </P>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p> Xreader je enosaven ogledovalnik dokumentov z več stranmi. Prikaže in natisne lahko datoteke PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS in Portable Document Format (PDF), pa tudi arhivske stropovske datotek. Če to podpira sam dokument, omogoča tudi iskanje besedila, kopiranje besedila na odložišče, hipertekstovno krmarjenje in zaznamke kazala vsebine. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p> Икс читач је једноставан вишестранични прегледач докумената. Може да прикаже и да штампа датотеке PostScript (PS), Затворене PostSkripte (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS и Преносни Документни Формат (PDF), као и архивне датотеке стрипова. Када документ подржава, такође омогућава тражење текста, умножавање истог у списку исечака, навигацију хипертекстом и забележавање табеле садржаја. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p> Xreader je jednostavan višestranični pregledač dokumenata. Može prikazivati i ispisivati PostSkripte (PS), Zatvorene PostSkripte (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS i Prenosni Dokumentni Format (PDF) datoteke, kao i arhivirane datoteke stripa. Kada je podržano dokumentom, isto tako omogućuje pretraživanje teksta, kopiranje teksta u međuspremnik, hipertekstualnu navigacijua i tabelu sadržaja beleške. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p> Xreader är en enkel multi-sids dokumentvisare. Den kan visa och printa PostScript (PS), Inkapslad PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS och Portabelt Dokument Format (PDF) filer, likaväl som comic book arkivfiler. När dokumentet stöder det, så kan det också tillåta sökning efter text, att kopiera text till klippbordet, hypertext navigering och innehållstabells bokmärken. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="th">
    <p> Xreader เป็นโปรแกรมดูเอกสารหลายหน้าที่ใช้งานง่าย สามารถแสดงและดูเอกสารแบบ PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS และ Portable Document Format (PDF) ได้ รวมถึงแฟ้มจัดเก็บหนังสือการ์ตูนด้วย เมื่อถูกรองรับโดยเอกสาร มันจะอนุญาตการค้นหาข้อความ การคัดลอกข้อความไปยังคลิปบอร์ด การนำทางไฮเปอร์เทกซ์ และที่คั่นหน้าจากสารบัญ </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p> Xreader basit çok-sayfalı bir belge görüntüleyicisidir. PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS ve Portable Document Format (PDF) dosyaları yanı çizgi roman arşiv dosyalarını görüntüleyebilir. Desteklenen bir belgede metin araması, metnin panoya kopyalanması, bağlantılı metin gezinmesi ve içerik tablosunun yer imlemesini destekler. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p> Xreader — це простий багатосторінковий переглядач документів. Він може показувати та друкувати файли форматів PostScript (PS), Encapsulated PostScript (EPS), DJVU, DVI, XPS і Portable Document Format (PDF), а також коміксів. Щораз, коли це можливо, Ви можете шукати текст у документі, копіювати текст, відкривати посилання та додавати закладки.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p> Xreader 是一个简单的多页文档查看器。它可以显示和打印 PostScript (PS)，Encapsulated PostScript (EPS)，DJVU，DVI，XPS，便携式文档格式 (PDF)，以及 Comic Book 文档。 当文档支持时，它还有搜索文本，将文本复制到剪贴板，超文本导航，目录书签等功能。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_HK">
    <p> Xreader 是一個簡單的多頁文件檢視器。可顯示並列印 PostScript (PS)、Encapsulated PostScript (EPS)、DJVU、DVI、XPS、PDF檔案，以及漫畫書壓縮檔。其允許在支援的文件搜尋文字、複製文字至剪貼簿、超文字導航和製作目錄書籤。 </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p> Xreader 是簡單的多頁文件檢視器。其可顯示並列印 PostScript (PS)，Encapsulated PostScript (EPS)，DJVU，DVI，XPS，PDF，與漫畫書壓縮檔。其允許在支援的文件搜尋文字，複製文字至剪貼簿，超文字導航與製作目錄書籤。 </p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://github.com/linuxmint/xreader</url>
  <project_group>Linux Mint</project_group>
</component>