<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>dfeet</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.dfeet.desktop</launchable>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">org.gnome.dfeet.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" width="128" type="cached">org.gnome.dfeet.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.dfeet.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="uk">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="tr">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="sv">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">D-stopa</name>
  <name lang="sr">Д-стопа</name>
  <name lang="sl">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="ru">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="ro">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="pt">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="pl">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="oc">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="nl">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="nb">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="lv">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="id">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="hu">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="hr">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="gl">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="fur">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="fr">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="fi">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="eu">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="es">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="el">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="de">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="da">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="cs">D-Feet</name>
  <name lang="bs">D-Feet</name>
  <summary>Debug D-Bus applications</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">调试 D-Bus 应用程序</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Діагностика програм із D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">D-Bus uygulamalarında hata ayıkla</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Felsök D-Bus-program</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Pročistite programe D-sabirnice</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Прочистите програме Д-сабирнице</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Razhroščevanje programov vodila D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Отладка приложений D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Aplicații de depanare D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Depure aplicativos D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Depure aplicações D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Debugowanie programów D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Desbuga las aplicacions D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Debug D-Bus-toepassingen</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Feilsøk D-Bus-programmer</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Atkļūdo D-Bus lietotnes</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Mengawakutu aplikasi-aplikasi D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">D-Bus alkalmazások hibakeresése</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Aplikacija D-Bus otklanjanja grešaka</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Aplicativos de depuración de D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Fâs il debug des aplicazions D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Débogue les applications D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Jäljitä vikoja D-Bus-sovelluksista</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Araztu D-Bus aplikazioak</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Depurar aplicaciones de D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Debug D-Bus applications</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Αποσφαλμάτωση εφαρμογών D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Fehlerdiagnose für D-Bus-Anwendungen</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Fejlsøg D-Bus-programmer</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Laďte aplikace používající sběrnici D-Bus</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Traženje grešaka za programe D-Bus</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      A simple application for debugging the message bus system D-Bus.
      D-Feet can be used to inspect D-Bus interfaces of running programs and
      invoke methods on those interfaces.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Jednostavna aplikacija za otklanjanje grešaka u sistemu poruks D-Bus. D-Feet može da se koristi za inspekciju D-BUS interfejss za pokrenutih programa i pozove metode na tim interfejsima.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Jednoduchá aplikace sloužící k ladění systémové sběrnice zpráv D-Bus. D-Feet se používá ke sledování rozhraní D-Bus u běžících aplikací a k volání metod těchto rozhraní.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Et simpelt program til fejlsøgning af meddelelsesbussystemet D-Bus. D-Feet kan bruges til inspicere D-Bus grænseflader af kørende programmer og kalde metoder hos disse grænseflader.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Eine einfache Anwendung zur Fehlerdiagnose von D-Bus, einer Software zur Interprozesskommunikation (IPC). D-Feet kann zur Untersuchung von D-Bus-Schnittstellen laufender Programme verwendet werden und Methoden dieser Schnittstellen aufrufen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Μια απλή εφαρμογή για την αποσφαλμάτωση μηνυμάτων του διάυλου συστήματος D-Bus. Το D-Feet μπορεί να χρησιμοποιηθεί για να επιθεωρήσει τις διεπαφές D-Bus των εκτελούμενων προγραμμάτων καθώς και τον μεθόδων των διεπαφών.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>A simple application for debugging the D-Bus message bus system. D-Feet can be used to inspect the D-Bus interfaces of running programs and invoke methods on those interfaces.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Una sencilla aplicación para depurar el bus de mensajes del sistema D-Bus. D-Feet se puede usar para inspeccionar interfaces D-Bus de programas en ejecución y para invocar métodos en esas interfaces.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>D-Bus mezuen bus-sistema arazteko aplikazio sinplea. D-Feet exekuzioan dauden programen D-Bus interfazeak ikuskatzeko eta interfaze horien metodoak deitzeko erabili daiteke.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Yksinkertainen sovellus D-Bus-viestiväyläjärjestelmän vianjäljitykseen. D-Feetiä voi käyttää käynnissä olevian ohjelmien D-Bus-liittymien tutkimiseen kutsumalla eri menetelmiä.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Une application simple pour déboguer le bus de message système D-Bus. D-Feet peut être utilisé pour inspecter les interfaces D-Bus des programmes en cours d’exécution et pour appeler les méthodes sur ces interfaces.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Une semplice aplicazion par fâ il debug dal bus dai messaçs di sisteme D-Bus. D-Feet al pues jessi doprât par ispezionâ lis interfacis D-Bus dai programs in esecuzion e invocâ metodis su chês interfacis.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Un aplicativo sinxelo para depurar o bus de mensaxes do sistema D-Bus. D-Feet pode usarse para inspeccionar interfaces de D-Bus dos programas en execución e invocar métodos nesas interfaces.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Jednostavna aplikacija za otklanjanje grešaka poruka D-Bus sabirnice sustava. D-Feet se može koristiti za provjeru D-Bus sučelja pokrenutih aplikacija i načina pozivanja na tim sučeljima.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>Egy egyszerű alkalmazás a D-Bus üzenetbusz-rendszer hibakereséséhez. A D-Feet használható a futó programok D-Bus csatolóinak megfigyeléséhez és metódusok meghívásához azokon a csatolókon.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Suatu aplikasi sederhana untuk mengawakutu sistem bus pesan D-Bus. D-Feet dapat dipakai untuk memeriksa antar muka D-Bus dari program-program yang berjalan dan memanggil metode-metode pada antar muka tersebut.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Een eenvoudige toepassing voor het debuggen van het berichtbussysteem D-Bus. D-Feet kan worden gebruikt voor het inspecteren van D-Bus-interfaces van programma’s die worden uitgevoerd, en methodes inroepen op deze interfaces.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>Una aplicacion simpla per desbugar lo bus de messatge sistèma D-Bus. D-Feet pòt èsser utilizat per inspectar las interfàcias D-Bus dels programas en cors d’execucion e per apelar los metòdes sus aquestas interfàcias.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Prosty program do debugowania systemowej magistrali komunikatów D-Bus. D-Feet może być używany do badania interfejsów D-Bus uruchomionych programów i wywoływania metod na tych interfejsach.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Uma aplicação simples para depuração do sistema de barramento de mensagens D-Bus. D-Feet pode ser usado para inspecionar interfaces D-Bus de programas em execução e chamar métodos naquelas interfaces.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Um aplicativo simples para depuração do sistema de barramento de mensagens D-Bus. D-Feet pode ser usado para inspecionar interfaces D-Bus de programas em execução e chamar métodos naquelas interfaces.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>O aplicație simplă pentru depanarea D-Bus-ului sistemului magistralei de mesaje. D-Feet poate fi utilizat pentru a inspecta interfețe D-Bus ale programelor care rulează și poate invoca metode pe acele interfețe.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Enostaven program za razhroščevanje sporočil sistema vodila D-Bus. Program D-Feet je mogoče uporabiti za nadzor vmesnikov D-Bus zagnanih programov in za upravljanje.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Једноставан програм за прочишћавање система сабирнице порука Д-сабирнице. Д-стопа може бити употребљена за проверу сучеља Д-сабирнице покренутих програма и за призивање поступака на тим сучељима.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Jednostavan program za pročišćavanje sistema sabirnice poruka D-sabirnice. D-stopa može biti upotrebljena za proveru sučelja D-sabirnice pokrenutih programa i za prizivanje postupaka na tim sučeljima.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Ett enkelt program för att felsöka meddelandebussystemet D-Bus. D-Feet kan användas för att inspektera D-Bus-gränssnitt för körande program och anropa metoder på dessa gränssnitt.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>İleti veriyolu sistemi D-Bus’da hata ayıklama için basit uygulama. D-Feet, çalışan programların D-Bus arabirimlerini inceleme ve bu arabirimlerdeki yöntemleri çalıştırmada kullanılır.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Проста програма для діагностики системи шини повідомлень D-Bus. D-Feet можна скористатися для інспектування інтерфейсів D-Bus запущених програм і виклику методів на цих інтерфейсах.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot height="787" type="default" width="1400">
      <image>https://git.gnome.org/browse/d-feet/plain/data/screenshots/d-feet-overview.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/DFeet</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugzilla.gnome.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=d-feet</url>
  <url type="donation">http://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <update_contact>thomasbechtold_at_jpberlin_de</update_contact>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <translation type="gettext">d-feet</translation>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="0.3.16" date="2021-05-07">
      <description>
        <p>Introspection data is now loaded asynchronously, which avoids D-Feet locking up when a complicated service like systemd is selected.</p>
        <p>You can now pass ‘--address ADDRESS’ on the command line to connect to a bus by address.</p>
        <p>Properties whose values contain the ‘&amp;’ character are now handled correctly.</p>
        <p>New and updated translations for:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Basque</li>
          <li>Croatian</li>
          <li>Czech</li>
          <li>Danish</li>
          <li>Dutch</li>
          <li>English (United Kingdom)</li>
          <li>Finnish</li>
          <li>Friulian</li>
          <li>German</li>
          <li>Hungarian</li>
          <li>Indonesian</li>
          <li>Polish</li>
          <li>Portuguese (Brazil)</li>
          <li>Romanian</li>
          <li>Serbian</li>
          <li>Slovenian</li>
          <li>Spanish</li>
          <li>Swedish</li>
          <li>Turkish</li>
          <li>Ukrainian</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.3.15" date="2019-08-06">
      <description>
        <p>D-Feet 0.3.15 is here, with various cosmetic improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Restructure menus to follow GNOME 3.32 menu guidelines</li>
          <li>New app icon as part of the GNOME 3.32 icon redesign</li>
          <li>Add OARS content-rating data</li>
          <li>Many translation updates</li>
          <li>New Meson-based build system</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>