<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <description>
    <p>
        digiKam is an advanced open-source digital photo management application that runs on Linux, Windows, and MacOS.
        The application provides a comprehensive set of tools for importing, managing, editing, and sharing photos and raw files.
        You can use digiKam’s import capabilities to easily transfer photos, raw files, and videos directly from your camera
        and external storage devices (SD cards, USB disks, etc.). The application allows you to configure import settings and rules
        that process and organize imported items on-the-fly.
    </p>
    <p>
        digiKam organizes photos, raw files, and videos into albums. But the application also features powerful tagging tools
        that allow you to assign tags, ratings, and labels to photos and raw files. You can then use filtering functionality to quickly
        find items that match specific criteria.
    </p>
    <p>
        In addition to filtering functionality, digiKam features powerful searching capabilities that let you search the photo library
        by a wide range of criteria. You can search photos by tags, labels, rating, data, location, and even specific EXIF, IPTC, or XMP metadata.
        You can also combine several criteria for more advanced searches. digiKam rely on Exiv2 library to handle metadata tag contents
        from files to populate the photo library.
    </p>
    <p>
        digiKam can handle raw files, and the application uses the excellent LibRaw library for decoding raw files. The library is actively
        maintained and regularly updated to include support for the latest camera models.
        digiKam can also manage video files for cataloging purpose, and the application uses the couple FFmpeg and QtAv libraries to extract
        metadata and play media.
    </p>
    <p>
        The application provides a comprehensive set of editing tools. This includes basic tools for adjusting colors, cropping, and sharpening
        as well as advanced tools for, curves adjustment, panorama stitching, and much more. A special tool based on Lensfun library permit
        to apply lens corrections automatically on images.
    </p>
    <p>
        Extended functionality in digiKam is implemented via a set of tools based of plugins mechanism (named DPlugins for digiKam Plugins).
        Plugins can be written to import and export contents to remote web-services, add new features to edit image, and batch process photo.
    </p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organization of photos in albums and sub-albums (with tags and comments support)</li>
      <li>Support for Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li>SQLite or Mysql powered storage for the album contents and its metadata with advanced search tools</li>
      <li>Support for filtering and sorting albums</li>
      <li>Import from more than 1100 digital camera devices</li>
      <li>Support for more than 900 RAW format pictures</li>
      <li>Light Table to compare photo side by side</li>
      <li>Extended features using extra tools</li>
      <li>Share your photos using HTML or publishing them to remote web services</li>
      <li>Image editor included with advanced tools to fix photo quickly</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>دجيكام هو تطبيق متقدم مفتوح المصدر لإدارة الصور الرقمية يعمل على لينكس و ويندوز و ماك أوس. يوفر التطبيق مجموعة شاملة من الأدوات لاستيراد الصور والملفات الخام وإدارتها وتحريرها ومشاركتها. يمكنك استخدام إمكانات استيراد دجيكام لنقل الصور والملفات الأولية ومقاطع الفيديو بسهولة مباشرةً من الكاميرا وأجهزة التخزين الخارجية (بطاقات SD وأقراص USB وما إلى ذلك). يتيح لك التطبيق تكوين إعدادات وقواعد الاستيراد التي تعالج العناصر المستوردة وتنظمها أثناء التنقل.</p>
    <p>ينظم دجيكام الصور والملفات الخام ومقاطع الفيديو في ألبومات. زيادة على ذلك يمتلك التطبيق أدوات  قوية تتيح لك تعيين الوسوم  والتصنيفات والتسميات للصور والملفات الخام. يمكنك بعد ذلك استخدام وظيفة التصفية للعثور بسرعة على العناصر التي تطابق معايير معينة.</p>
    <p>بالإضافة إلى وظيفة التصفية ، تتميز دجيكام بقدرات بحث قوية تتيح لك البحث في مكتبة الصور بواسطة مجموعة واسعة من المعايير. يمكنك البحث في الصور عن طريق العلامات، والتسميات، والتصنيف، والبيانات، والموقع، وحتى بيانات تعريف EXIF أو IPTC أو XMP محددة. يمكنك أيضًا الجمع بين عدة معايير لإجراء عمليات بحث أكثر تقدمًا. يعتمد دجيكام على مكتبة Exiv2 للتعامل مع البيانات الوصفية للصور لتعبئة مكتبة الصور.</p>
    <p>يمكن لدجيكام التعامل مع الملفات الخام ، ويستخدم التطبيق مكتبة LibRaw الممتازة لفك تشفير الملفات الخام. تتم صيانة المكتبة بشكل نشط وتحديثها بانتظام لتشمل دعمًا لأحدث طرازات الكاميرا. يمكن لدجيكام أيضًا إدارة ملفات الفيديو لغرض الفهرسة ، ويستخدم التطبيق مكتبتي FFmpeg و QtAv لاستخراج البيانات الوصفية وتشغيل الوسائط. </p>
    <p>يوفر التطبيق مجموعة شاملة من أدوات التحرير. يتضمن ذلك الأدوات الأساسية لضبط الألوان والاقتصاص والشحذ بالإضافة إلى الأدوات المتقدمة لتعديل المنحنيات وخياطة البانوراما وغير ذلك الكثير. تسمح الأداة الخاصة القائمة على مكتبة Lensfun بتطبيق تصحيحات العدسة تلقائيًا على الصور.</p>
    <p>تنفذ الوظائف الموسعة في دجيكام عبر مجموعة من الأدوات القائمة على آلية المكونات الإضافية (تسمى DPlugins لملحقات دجيكام). يمكن كتابة ملحقات لاستيراد وتصدير المحتويات إلى خدمات الويب البعيدة، وإضافة ميزات جديدة لتحرير الصورة، ومعالجة بالدفعات للصور.</p>
    <p>الميزات:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>تنظيم الصّور في ألبومات وألبومات فرعيّة (بدعم الوسوم والتّعليقات)</li>
      <li>دعم Exif و Iptc و Xmp و Makernotes</li>
      <li>مخزن تدعم «SQLite» أو Mysql للألبومات وبياناتها الوصفيّة مع أدوات بحث متقدمة</li>
      <li>دعم ترشيح الألبومات وفرزها</li>
      <li>الاستيراد من أكثر من 1100 كمرة رقميّة</li>
      <li>دعم يصل حتّى 300 نسق للصّور الخامّ</li>
      <li>الطاولة الضوئيّة لمقارنة الصورة جنبا لجنب</li>
      <li>ميزات موسعة باستخدام أدوات إضافية</li>
      <li>مشاركة الصّور عبر HTML أو نشرها إلى مواقع الوبّ الاجتماعيّة</li>
      <li>وجود محرّر صور مضمّن بمزايا متقدّمة لإصلاح الصورة بسرعة</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Svojstva:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organizacija fotografija u albume i podalbume (sa podrškom za označavanje i komentarisanje)</li>
      <li>Podrška za Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li>Podrška za filtriranje i sortiranje albuma</li>
      <li>Uvoz iz više od 1100 digitalnih kamera uređaja</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El digiKam és una aplicació avançada de codi obert de gestió de fotos digitals que funciona al Linux, Windows i MacOS. L'aplicació proporciona un conjunt integrat d'eines per a importar, gestionar, editar i compartir fotos i fitxers RAW. Podeu utilitzar les capacitats d'importació del digiKam per a transferir fotos fàcilment, fitxers RAW i vídeos directament des de la càmera i de dispositius externs d'emmagatzematge (targetes SD, discos USB, etc.). L'aplicació permet configurar paràmetres i regles d'importació que processen i organitzen els elements importats al vol.</p>
    <p>El digiKam organitza les fotos, els fitxers RAW i els vídeos en àlbums. Però l'aplicació també té eines potents d'etiquetatge que permeten assignar etiquetes, valoracions i rètols a les fotos i als fitxers RAW. Després es pot usar la funcionalitat de filtratge per a trobar ràpidament elements que coincideixin amb criteris concrets.</p>
    <p>Addicionalment a la funcionalitat de filtratge, el digiKam té capacitats potents de cerca que permeten cercar la biblioteca de fotos per un ampli ventall de criteris. Es poden cercar fotos per etiquetes, rètols, valoracions, dates, ubicacions i inclús metadades específiques Exif, IPTC o XMP. També es poden combinar diversos criteris per a cerques més avançades. El digiKam compta amb la biblioteca Exiv2 per a gestionar el contingut de les etiquetes de metadades dels fitxers per a omplir la biblioteca de fotos.</p>
    <p>El digiKam pot gestionar fitxers RAW, i l'aplicació usa l'excel·lent biblioteca LibRaw per a descodificar els fitxers RAW. La biblioteca està mantinguda activament i actualitzada regularment per a incloure el suport per als darrers models de càmeres. El digiKam també pot gestionar fitxers de vídeo per a la catalogació, i l'aplicació usa el parell de biblioteques FFmpeg i QtAv per a extreure les metadades i reproduir els fitxers multimèdia.</p>
    <p>L'aplicació proporciona un conjunt integrat d'eines d'edició. Això inclou eines bàsiques per a ajustar colors, retallar i definir, així com eines avançades per a ajustar corbes, muntar panorames i molt més. Hi ha una eina especial basada en la biblioteca Lensfun que permet aplicar automàticament correccions de les lents a les imatges.</p>
    <p>Al digiKam s'implementen funcionalitats ampliades a través d'un conjunt d'eines basades en mecanismes de connectors (anomenats DPlugins per «digiKam Plugins»). Els connectors es poden escriure per a importar i exportar contingut a serveis web remots, afegir funcionalitats noves per a editar imatges, i processar fotos en lots.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organització de les fotografies en àlbums i subàlbums (amb implementació per a les etiquetes i comentaris)</li>
      <li>Implementació per a notes Exif, IPTC, XMP i del fabricant</li>
      <li>Emmagatzematge basat en SQLite o Mysql per als continguts dels àlbums i les seves metadades amb eines de cerca avançades</li>
      <li>Implementació pel filtratge i classificació dels àlbums</li>
      <li>Importa des de més de 1.100 dispositius de càmeres digitals</li>
      <li>Admet més de 900 formats d'imatge RAW</li>
      <li>Taula de llum per a comparar les fotografies costat a costat</li>
      <li>Característiques ampliades usant eines addicionals</li>
      <li>Compartiu les vostres fotografies usant HTML o publicant-les a serveis web remots</li>
      <li>Inclou un editor d'imatges amb eines avançades per a esmenar ràpidament les fotografies</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>El digiKam és una aplicació avançada de codi obert de gestió de fotos digitals que funciona al Linux, Windows i MacOS. L'aplicació proporciona un conjunt integrat d'eines per a importar, gestionar, editar i compartir fotos i fitxers RAW. Podeu utilitzar les capacitats d'importació del digiKam per a transferir fotos fàcilment, fitxers RAW i vídeos directament des de la càmera i de dispositius externs d'emmagatzematge (targetes SD, discos USB, etc.). L'aplicació permet configurar paràmetres i regles d'importació que processen i organitzen els elements importats al vol.</p>
    <p>El digiKam organitza les fotos, els fitxers RAW i els vídeos en àlbums. Però l'aplicació també té eines potents d'etiquetatge que permeten assignar etiquetes, valoracions i rètols a les fotos i als fitxers RAW. Després es pot usar la funcionalitat de filtratge per a trobar ràpidament elements que coincidisquen amb criteris concrets.</p>
    <p>Addicionalment a la funcionalitat de filtratge, el digiKam té capacitats potents de cerca que permeten cercar la biblioteca de fotos per un ampli ventall de criteris. Es poden cercar fotos per etiquetes, rètols, valoracions, dates, ubicacions i inclús metadades específiques Exif, IPTC o XMP. També es poden combinar diversos criteris per a cerques més avançades. El digiKam compta amb la biblioteca Exiv2 per a gestionar el contingut de les etiquetes de metadades dels fitxers per a omplir la biblioteca de fotos.</p>
    <p>El digiKam pot gestionar fitxers RAW, i l'aplicació usa l'excel·lent biblioteca LibRaw per a descodificar els fitxers RAW. La biblioteca està mantinguda activament i actualitzada regularment per a incloure el suport per als darrers models de càmeres. El digiKam també pot gestionar fitxers de vídeo per a la catalogació, i l'aplicació usa el parell de biblioteques FFmpeg i QtAv per a extreure les metadades i reproduir els fitxers multimèdia.</p>
    <p>L'aplicació proporciona un conjunt integrat d'eines d'edició. Això inclou eines bàsiques per a ajustar colors, retallar i definir, així com eines avançades per a ajustar corbes, muntar panorames i molt més. Hi ha una eina especial basada en la biblioteca Lensfun que permet aplicar automàticament correccions de les lents a les imatges.</p>
    <p>Al digiKam s'implementen funcionalitats ampliades a través d'un conjunt d'eines basades en mecanismes de connectors (anomenats DPlugins per «digiKam Plugins»). Els connectors es poden escriure per a importar i exportar contingut a serveis web remots, afegir funcionalitats noves per a editar imatges, i processar fotos en lots.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organització de les fotografies en àlbums i subàlbums (amb implementació per a les etiquetes i comentaris)</li>
      <li>Implementació per a notes Exif, IPTC, XMP i del fabricant</li>
      <li>Emmagatzematge basat en SQLite o Mysql per als continguts dels àlbums i les seues metadades amb eines de cerca avançades</li>
      <li>Implementació pel filtratge i classificació dels àlbums</li>
      <li>Importa des de més de 1.100 dispositius de càmeres digitals</li>
      <li>Admet més de 900 formats d'imatge RAW</li>
      <li>Taula de llum per a comparar les fotografies costat a costat</li>
      <li>Característiques ampliades usant eines addicionals</li>
      <li>Compartiu les vostres fotografies usant HTML o publicant-les a serveis web remots</li>
      <li>Inclou un editor d'imatges amb eines avançades per a esmenar ràpidament les fotografies</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>digiKam organizuje fotografie, soubory raw a videa do alb. Aplikace rovněž obsahuje mocné značkovací nástroje, které vám umožňují přidělit k fotografiím a souborům raw značky, hodnocení a popisky. Poté můžete využít filtrovací schopnosti k rychlému nalezení položek odpovídajícím zadaným kritériím.</p>
    <p>Vlastnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organizace fotografií do alb a podřízených alb s podporou značek a komentářů</li>
      <li>Podpora pro Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li>Ukládání informace o albech do databáze založené na SQLite nebo MySQL s pokročilými vyhledávacími nástroji</li>
      <li>Podpora řazení a filtrování alb</li>
      <li>Import z více než 1100 typů digitálních fotoaparátů</li>
      <li>Podpora více než 900 obrázků ve formátu RAW</li>
      <li>Prohlížecí stolek pro porovnání fotografií vedle sebe</li>
      <li>Rozšířené vlastnosti pomocí extra nástrojů</li>
      <li>Sdílení fotografií vytvořením HTML galerie nebo přímým publikováním na vzdálených webových službách</li>
      <li>Editor obrázků zahrnutý v pokročilých nástrojích pro rychlé opravy fotek</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>digiKam ist ein Open-Source-Verwaltungsprogramm digitaler Bilder auf Linux, Windows und MacOS. Es bietet umfangreiche Werkzeuge zum Importieren, Verwalten, Bearbeiten und teilen von Bildern und RAW-Dateien. Mit digiKam’s Fähigkeiten importieren Sie einfach Bilder, RAW-Dateien und Videos direkt von Ihrer Kamera oder externen Speichermedien wie SD-Karten, USB-Speicher, usw. Die Anwendung gestattet es die Regeln zum Importieren,Bearbeiten und Organisieren der Elemente im laufenden Betrieb einzustellen.</p>
    <p>digiKam organisiert Fotos, RAW-Dateien und Videos in Alben. Die Anwendung bietet mächtige Werkzeuge, um den Bildern und RAW-Dateien Stichwörter, Bewertungen oder Markierungen zuzuweisen. Sie können Filterfunktionen verwenden, um Elemente sehr schnell gemäß bestimmter Kriterien zu finden.</p>
    <p>Neben den Filterfunktionen unterstützt digiKam leistungsstarke Funktionen zum Durchsuchen der Alben nach verschiedensten Kriterien. Sie können Bilder suchen gemäß deren Stichwörtern, Markierungen, Bewertungen oder gemäß bestimmter Exif-, IPTC- oder XMP-Metadaten. Sie können diese Suchkriterien auch kombinieren. digiKam basiert auf Exiv2, um Metadaten zu bearbeiten und in die Datenbasis aufzunehmen.</p>
    <p>digiKam entwickelt RAW-Dateien mit Hilfe der ausgezeichneten Bibliothek LibRaw. Diese Bibliothek wird aktuell weiterentwickelt, um die jeweils neuesten Kameramodelle zu unterstützen. digiKam kann auch Video-Dateien verwalten. Mit Hilfe von FFmpeg und QtAv werden Metadaten gelesen und die Medien abgespielt.</p>
    <p>Die Anwendung bietet umfangreiche Werkzeuge zur Bildbearbeitung. Dies umfasst Basiswerkzeuge zur Farbanpassung, zum Zuschneiden und Schärfen, genauso wie erweiterte Werkzeuge zum Regulieren der Farbkurven, Erstellen von Panoramas und einiges mehr. Ein besonderes Werkzeug ist LensFun, das es erlaubt Objektivfehler automatisch zu korrigieren.</p>
    <p>Erweiterte Funktionen sind in digiKam realisiert mit Hilfe von Werkzeugen auf Basis eines Modul-Mechanismus (DPlugins). Solche Module können erstellt werden für den Im- und Export zu Webdiensten, für neue Funktionen zur Bildbearbeitung und zur Stapelverarbeitung.</p>
    <p>Funktionen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organisation von Fotos in Alben und Unteralben mit Unterstützung für Stichwörter und Kommentare</li>
      <li>Unterstützung für Exif, IPTC und XMP und Herstellerdaten</li>
      <li>Speicherung der Alben und Metadaten in einer SQLite- oder MySQL-Datenbank mit erweiterten Suchwerkzeugen</li>
      <li>Unterstützung für das Filtern und Sortieren von Alben</li>
      <li>Import von mehr als 1100 digitalen Kameras</li>
      <li>Unterstützung für mehr als 900 RAW-Bildformate</li>
      <li>Leuchttisch zum Vergleichen von Fotos nebeneinander</li>
      <li>Erweiterte Leistungsmerkmale mit besonderen Werkzeugen</li>
      <li>Teilen Sie Ihre Fotos über HTML oder veröffentlichen Sie sie auf Webdiensten</li>
      <li>Bildbearbeitung mit erweiterten Korrekturfunktionen</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Οργάνωση φωτογραφιών σε άλμπουμ και υπο-άλμπουμ (με υποστήριξη για ετικέτες και σχόλια)</li>
      <li>Υποστήριξη για Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li>Αποθηκευτικός χώρος με SQLite ή Mysql για τα άλμπουμ και τα μεταδεδομένα τους με προηγμένα εργαλεία αναζήτησης</li>
      <li>Υποστήριξη για φιλτράρισμα και ταξινόμηση των άλμπουμ</li>
      <li>Εισαγωγή από περισσότερες από 1100 ψηφιακές κάμερες</li>
      <li>Υποστήριξη για περισσότερους από 900 τύπους RAW εικόνων</li>
      <li>Ελαφρύς πίνακας για σύγκριση φωτογραφιών κατ' αντιπαράθεση</li>
      <li>Επεκτάσεις χαρακτηριστικών με χρήση επιπλέον εργαλείων</li>
      <li>Μοιραστείτε τις φωτογραφίες σας με HTML ή με δημοσίευση σε απομακρυσμένες υπηρεσίες ιστού</li>
      <li>Περιλαμβάνεται επεξεργαστής εικόνων με προηγμένα εργαλεία για γρήγορη διόρθωση φωτογραφιών</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>digiKam is an advanced open-source digital photo management application that runs on Linux, Windows, and MacOS. The application provides a comprehensive set of tools for importing, managing, editing, and sharing photos and raw files. You can use digiKam’s import capabilities to easily transfer photos, raw files, and videos directly from your camera and external storage devices (SD cards, USB disks, etc.). The application allows you to configure import settings and rules that process and organise imported items on-the-fly.</p>
    <p>digiKam organises photos, raw files, and videos into albums. But the application also features powerful tagging tools that allow you to assign tags, ratings, and labels to photos and raw files. You can then use filtering functionality to quickly find items that match specific criteria.</p>
    <p>In addition to filtering functionality, digiKam features powerful searching capabilities that let you search the photo library by a wide range of criteria. You can search photos by tags, labels, rating, data, location, and even specific EXIF, IPTC, or XMP metadata. You can also combine several criteria for more advanced searches. digiKam rely on Exiv2 library to handle metadata tag contents from files to populate the photo library.</p>
    <p>digiKam can handle raw files, and the application uses the excellent LibRaw library for decoding raw files. The library is actively maintained and regularly updated to include support for the latest camera models. digiKam can also manage video files for cataloguing purpose, and the application uses the couple FFmpeg and QtAv libraries to extract metadata and play media.</p>
    <p>The application provides a comprehensive set of editing tools. This includes basic tools for adjusting colours, cropping, and sharpening as well as advanced tools for, curves adjustment, panorama stitching, and much more. A special tool based on Lensfun library permit to apply lens corrections automatically on images.</p>
    <p>Extended functionality in digiKam is implemented via a set of tools based of plugins mechanism (named DPlugins for digiKam Plugins). Plugins can be written to import and export contents to remote web-services, add new features to edit image, and batch process photo.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organisation of photos in albums and sub-albums (with tags and comments support)</li>
      <li>Support for Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li>SQLite or Mysql powered storage for the album contents and its metadata with advanced search tools</li>
      <li>Support for filtering and sorting albums</li>
      <li>Import from more than 1100 digital camera devices</li>
      <li>Support for more than 900 RAW format pictures</li>
      <li>Light Table to compare photo side by side</li>
      <li>Extended features using extra tools</li>
      <li>Share your photos using HTML or publishing them to remote web services</li>
      <li>Image editor included with advanced tools to fix photo quickly</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>digiKam es una avanzada aplicación de código abierto para la gestión de fotografías digitales que se puede ejecutar en Linux, Windows y MacOS. La aplicación proporciona un completo conjunto de herramientas para importar, gestionar, editar y compartir fotos y archivos RAW. Puede usar las funciones de importación de digiKam para transferir fácilmente fotos, archivos RAW y vídeos directamente de la cámara y de dispositivos de almacenamiento externos (como tarjetas SD, discos USB, etc.). La aplicación le permite configurar las preferencias y las reglas de importación para procesar y organizar los elementos importados al vuelo.</p>
    <p>digiKam organiza fotos, archivos RAW y vídeos en álbumes. También proporciona potentes herramientas de etiquetado que le permiten asignar etiquetas, valoraciones y emblemas a las fotos y a los archivos RAW. Tras ello podrá usar la funcionalidad de filtrado para encontrar rápidamente elementos que cumplan criterios específicos.</p>
    <p>Además de la funcionalidad de filtrado, digiKam dispone de potentes funciones de búsqueda que le permiten consultar su colección de fotos por una amplia variedad de criterios. Puede buscar fotos por etiquetas, emblemas, valoraciones, datos, ubicación e incluso por metadatos específicos EXIF, IPTC y XMP. También puede combinar varios criterios para realizar búsquedas avanzadas. digiKam depende de la biblioteca Exiv2 para manejar el contenido de las etiquetas de metadatos de los archivos para rellenar la colección de fotos.</p>
    <p>digiKam puede manejar archivos RAW. Para ello usa la excelente biblioteca LibRaw para descodificar archivos RAW. Esta biblioteca se mantiene de forma activa y se actualiza regularmente para permitir el uso de los últimos modelos de cámaras. digiKam también puede manejar archivos de vídeo con el objetivo de catalogarlos. Para ello usa la pareja de bibliotecas FFmpeg y QtAv para extraer metadatos y reproducir multimedia.</p>
    <p>La aplicación proporciona un completo conjunto de herramientas de edición, que incluye herramientas básicas para ajustar colores, recortar y enfocar, así como herramientas avanzadas para ajustar curvas y componer panoramas, entre otras cosas. Una herramienta especial que usa la biblioteca Lensfun permite aplicar correcciones de lentes a las imágenes de forma automática.</p>
    <p>Es posible implementar funcionalidades extendidas en digiKam mediante un conjunto de herramientas basadas en el mecanismo de complementos (llamadas «DPlugins», complementos de digiKam). Se pueden escribir complementos para importar y exportar contenido a servicios web remotos, añadir nuevas funcionalidades para editar imágenes y para procesar fotos por lotes.</p>
    <p>Funciones:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organización de fotos en álbumes y álbumes anidados (con uso de etiquetas y comentarios)</li>
      <li>Uso de Exif, Iptc, Xmp y notas del fabricante</li>
      <li>Almacenamiento basado en SQLite o Mysql para los álbumes y sus metadatos con herramientas de búsqueda avanzadas</li>
      <li>Implementación de filtrado y ordenación de álbumes</li>
      <li>Permite importar de más de 1100 cámaras digitales</li>
      <li>Permite imágenes en más de 900 formatos RAW</li>
      <li>Mesa de luz para comparar fotos una junto a otra</li>
      <li>Funciones extendidas mediante herramientas adicionales</li>
      <li>Compartir fotos usando HTML o publicándolas en servicios web remotos</li>
      <li>Editor de imágenes incluido con herramientas avanzadas para corregir las fotos de forma rápida</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Omadused:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Fotode paigutamine albumitesse ja alamalbumitesse (toetatud on sildid ja kommentaarid)</li>
      <li>Exif'i, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes'i toetus</li>
      <li>SQLite'i või Mysql'i baasil salvesti albumite sisule ja metaandmetele ühes võimsa otsingutööriistaga</li>
      <li>Albumite filtreerimise ja sortimise toetus</li>
      <li>Import enam kui 1100 digitaalkaamerast</li>
      <li>Enam kui 900 toorpildivormingu toetus</li>
      <li>Valguslaud fotode vahetuks võrdlemiseks</li>
      <li>Avarad võimalused lisatööriistade abil</li>
      <li>Fotode jagamine HTML-i vahendusel või nende avaldamine veebiteenustes</li>
      <li>Pildiredaktor võimsate tööriistadega fotode kiireks parandamiseks</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Ezaugarriak:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Albumak iragazi eta sailkatzeko euskarria du</li>
      <li>1100 kamera digital gailu baino gehiagotatik inportatzea</li>
      <li>900 RAW formatuko irudi baino gehiagoren euskarria du</li>
      <li>Argazkiak alboz-albo alderatzeko argi-mahaia</li>
      <li>Ezaugarri hedatuak tresna gehigarriak erabiliz</li>
      <li>Partekatu zure argazkiak HTML erabiliz edo urrutiko web zerbitzuetan argitaratuz</li>
      <li>Irudi-editorea barne, argazkia azkar konpontzeko tresna aurreratuekin</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>digiKam on kehittynyt avoimen lähdekoodin valokuvanhallintasovellus, joka toimii Linuxissa, Windowsissa ja macOSissa. Se tarjoaa laajan joukon työkaluja valokuvien ja RAW-tiedostojen tuontiin, hallintaan, muokkaamiseen ja jakamiseen. digiKamin tuontiominaisuuksilla voi helposti siirtää valokuvia, RAW-tiedostoja ja videoita suoraan kamerasta ja ulkoisista tallennusvälineistä (SD-kortit, USB-levyt jne.). Kuvien tuontiasetukset sekä käsittelyn ja järjestämisen ajonaikaiset säännöt ovat muokattavissa.</p>
    <p>digiKam järjestää valokuvat, RAW-tiedostot ja videot albumeiksi. Ohjelmalla on myös tehokkaat luokitustyökalut luokitusten, arvostelujen ja selitteiden lisäämiseksi valokuviin ja RAW-tiedostoihin. Määräehtoja vastaavat kohteet voi sitten nopeasti löytää suodatustoiminnolla.</p>
    <p>Suodintoimintojen lisäksi digiKamilla on tehokkaat hakuominaisuudet valokuvakokoelmasta etsimiseksi eri ehdoin. Valokuvia voi etsiä luokituksen, selitteen, arvostelun, datan, sijainnin ja jopa Exif-, IPTC- tai XMP-metatiedon perusteella. Edistyneisiin hakuihin voi yhdistää eri ehtoja. Metatietojen luokitussisällön lukemisessa tiedostoista valokuvakirjastoon digiKam luottaa Exiv2-kirjastoon.</p>
    <p>digiKam osaa käsitellä RAW-tiedostoja, joiden lukemiseen se käyttää erinomaista LibRaw-kirjastoa. Kirjastoa kehitetään aktiivisesti ja siihen päivitetään säännöllisesti viimeisimpien kameramallien tuki. digiKam hallitsee luettelointitarkoituksessa myös videotiedostot, joiden metatiedon purkamiseen ja toistamiseen se käyttää FFmpeg- ja QtAv-kirjastoja.</p>
    <p>Sovellus tarjoaa laajan joukon muokkaustyökaluja, niin perustyökaluja kuten värien säädön, rajauksen ja terävöityksen, kuin edistyneitä työkaluja käyrien säätöön, panoraamakuvien koostamiseen ja muuhun. Lensfun-kirjastoon perustuvalla erikoistyökalulla kuviin voi tehdä linssikorjauksen automaattisesti.</p>
    <p>digiKamin lisätoiminnot on toteutettu liitännäismekanismiin (”DPlugins”) perustuvin työkaluin. Liitännäiset voivat tuoda ja viedä etäverkkopalvelujen sisältöä, lisätä uusia muokkausominaisuuksia ja eräkäsitellä valokuvia.</p>
    <p>Ominaisuuksia:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Valokuvien järjestely albumeiksi ja alialbumeiksi (tunniste- ja kommenttituella)</li>
      <li>Exif-, IPTC-, XMP ja Makernotes-tuki</li>
      <li>SQLite- tai MySQL-tallennustila albumien sisällölle ja matatiedoille sekä edistyneet hakutyökalut</li>
      <li>Albumien suodatuksen ja lajittelun tuki</li>
      <li>Tuontituki yli 1100 eri digikameralle</li>
      <li>Yli 900 RAW-kuvamuodon tuki</li>
      <li>Valotaulu kuvien vertailemiseksi rinnakkain</li>
      <li>Lisää ominaisuuksia lisätyökaluilla</li>
      <li>Valokuvien jako HTML:ksi tai julkaisu etäverkkopalvelimiin</li>
      <li>Lisätyökaluissa kuvamuokkain kuvien pikakorjauksiin</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>digiKam est une application « Open-source » de gestion de photos numériques, fonctionnant sous Linux, Windows et MacOS. L'application fournit un ensemble complet d'outils pour l'importation, la gestion, la modification et le partage de photos et de fichiers natifs. Vous pouvez utiliser les fonctionnalités d'importation de digiKam pour transférer facilement des photos, des fichiers natifs et des vidéos, directement venant de votre appareil photo et de périphériques externes de stockage comme cartes « SD », disques « USB » etc. L'application vous permet de régler les paramètres et les règles d'importation permettant de traiter et d'organiser les éléments importés à la volée.</p>
    <p>DigiKam organiser les photos, les fichiers natifs et les vidéos en albums. Mais, l'application possède aussi de puissants outils de marquage, vous permettant d'affecter des étiquettes, des notes et des labels aux photos et aux fichiers natifs. Vous pouvez aussi utiliser ensuite, des fonctionnalités de filtrage pour retrouver rapidement des éléments correspondant à des critères spécifiques.</p>
    <p>En plus des fonctionnalités de filtrage, digiKam propose de puissantes fonctions de recherche, vous permettant de chercher dans une bibliothèque de photos selon une large sélection de critères. Vous pouvez rechercher des photos par étiquette, par label, par note, par données de position et en cours plus spécifiquement par métadonnées « EXIF », « IPTC » ou « XMP ». Vous pouvez aussi combiner plusieurs critères pour des recherches encore plus avancées. DigiKam utilise la bibliothèque « exiv2 » pour la gestion des contenus des étiquettes de métadonnées, à partir des fichiers pour diffuser une bibliothèque de photos.</p>
    <p>DigiKam peut gérer des fichiers natifs. L'application utilise l'excellente bibliothèque « LibRaw » pour le décodage des fichiers natifs. Cette bibliothèque est activement maintenue et mise à jour régulièrement por la prise en charge des derniers modelés d'appareil photos. DigiKam peut aussi gérer des fichiers de vidéo pour les besoins du catalogage. L'application utiliser le couple de bibliothèques « FFmpeg » et « QtAv » pour extraire les métadonnées et pour jouer le média.</p>
    <p>L'application fournit un ensemble complet d'outils de modification. Cela comprend les outils de base pour ajuster les couleurs, le centrage et le découpage, mais aussi des outils avancés pour les ajustements de courbes, la production de panorama et bien plus encore. Un outil spécial construit à partie de la bibliothèque « Lensfun » permet l'application de corrections automatiquement de lentilles sur les images.</p>
    <p>La fonctionnalité étendue de digiKam est intégrée par un ensemble d'outils fonctionnant à partir de mécanismes de type module externe nommé « DPlugins » pour « DigiKam Plugin ». Les modules externes peuvent être écrits pour l'importation ou l'exportation de contenus pour des services Internet distants, des ajouts de nouvelles fonctionnalités pour modifier des images ou traiter des photos par lot.</p>
    <p>Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organisation de photos en albums et sous-albums (avec prise en charge des étiquettes et des commentaires)</li>
      <li>Prise en charge des données EXIF, IPTC, XMP, MakerNotes</li>
      <li>Stockage du contenu des albums et des métadonnées fonctionnant avec SQLite ou MySQL et des outils de recherche avancée</li>
      <li>Prise en charge du filtrage et du tri des albums</li>
      <li>Importe à partir de plus de 1100 appareils photos numériques</li>
      <li>Prise en charge de plus de 900 formats d'image RAW</li>
      <li>Table lumineuse pour comparer des photos côte-à-côte</li>
      <li>Fonctionnalités étendues par des outils externes</li>
      <li>Permet de partager vos photos avec des pages HTML ou de les publier sur des services web distants</li>
      <li>Éditeur d'images inclus, avec des fonctionnalités pour réparer rapidement une photo</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organización de fotos en álbums e subálbums (con funcionalidade de etiquetas e comentarios).</li>
      <li>Compatíbel con Exif, Iptc, Xmp e Makernotes.</li>
      <li>Almacenamento mediante SQLite ou MySQL para o contido dos álbums e os seus metadatos con ferramentas de busca avanzadas.</li>
      <li>Permite filtrar e ordenar os álbums.</li>
      <li>Permite importar desde máis de 1100 dispositivos de cámara dixital.</li>
      <li>Compatíbel con imaxes en máis de 900 formatos en cru (RAW).</li>
      <li>Táboa de luz para comparar fotos unha ao lado da outra.</li>
      <li>Funcionalidades estendidas usando ferramentas adicionais.</li>
      <li>Permite compartir imaxes usando HTML ou publicándoas en servizos web remotos.</li>
      <li>Inclúe un editor de imaxes con ferramentas avanzadas para arranxar fotos rapidamente.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>digiKam adalah aplikasi pengelolaan foto digital sumber terbuka tingkat lanjut yang berjalan di Linux, Windows, dan MacOS. Aplikasi ini menyediakan seperangkat alat lengkap untuk mengimpor, mengelola, mengedit, dan berbagi foto dan file mentah. Kamu bisa menggunakan kemampuan impor digiKam secara mudah mentransfer foto, file mentah, dan video langsung dari kamera dan perangkat penyimpanan eksternal (kartu SD, disk USB, dll.). Aplikasi ini memungkinkan kamu untuk mengonfigurasi pengaturan dan peraturan impor yang memproses dan mengatur item yang diimpor dengan cepat.</p>
    <p>digiKam mengatur foto, file mentah, dan video ke dalam album. Tetapi aplikasi ini juga dilengkapi alat penandaan yang kuat yang memungkinkan kamu untuk menetapkan tanda, peringkat, dan label ke foto dan file mentah. Kemudian kamu bisa menggunakan fungsi pemfilteran untuk menemukan item yang cocok dengan kriteria tertentu dengan cepat.</p>
    <p>Selain fungsionalitas pemfilteran, digiKam memiliki kemampuan pencarian canggih yang memungkinkan kamu mencari perpustakaan foto dengan berbagai kriteria. Kamu bisa mencari foto berdasarkan tag, label, peringkat, data, lokasi, dan bahkan metadata EXIF, IPTC, atau XMP tertentu. Kamu juga bisa menggabungkan beberapa kriteria untuk pencarian lebih lanjut. digiKam mengandalkan perpustakaan Exiv2 untuk menangani konten tag metadata dari file untuk mengisi perpustakaan foto.</p>
    <p>digiKam bisa menangani file mentah, dan aplikasi menggunakan perpustakaan LibRaw yang sangat baik untuk mendekode file mentah. Perpustakaan secara aktif dipelihara dan diperbarui secara berkala untuk menyertakan dukungan untuk model kamera terbaru. digiKam juga bisa mengelola file video untuk tujuan pembuatan katalog, dan aplikasi menggunakan pasangan FFmpeg dan perpustakaan QtAv untuk mengekstrak metadata dan memutar media.</p>
    <p>Aplikasi ini menyediakan seperangkat alat pengeditan yang lengkap. Ini termasuk alat dasar untuk menyesuaikan warna, memangkas, dan mempertajam serta alat canggih untuk, penyesuaian kurva, penggabungan panorama, dan banyak lagi. Alat khusus berdasarkan izin pustaka Lensfun untuk menerapkan koreksi lensa secara otomatis pada citra.</p>
    <p>Fungsionalitas yang diperluas di digiKam diimplementasikan melalui seperangkat alat berdasarkan mekanisme plugin (dinamai DPlugins untuk digiKam Plugins). Plugin bisa ditulis untuk mengimpor dan mengekspor konten ke layanan web jarak jauh, menambahkan fitur baru untuk mengedit gambar, dan foto proses seabrek.</p>
    <p>Fitur:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organisasi foto dalam album dan sub-album (dengan dukungan tag dan komentar)</li>
      <li>Mendukung Exif. Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li>Penyimpanan yang diberdayakan SQLite atau Mysql untuk konten album dan metadatanya dengan alat pencarian tingkat-lanjut</li>
      <li>Mendukung pemfilteran dan pengurutan album</li>
      <li>Impor dari lebih dari 110 perangkat kamera digital</li>
      <li>Mendukung lebih dari 900 gambar format RAW</li>
      <li>Table Terang untuk membandingkan foto sisi demi sisi</li>
      <li>Fitur yang diperluas menggunakan peralatan extra</li>
      <li>Bagikan fotomu menggunakan HTML atau mempublikasikannya ke layanan web jarak jauh</li>
      <li>Tersemat editor citra dengan alat tingkat-lanjut untuk memperbaiki foto secara cepat</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>digiKam er fullkomið umsýslukerfi stafrænna ljósmynda með opinn grunnkóða sem keyrir á Linux, Windows og MacOS. Hugbúnaðurinn gefur kost á skilvirku safni verkfæra til að flytja inn, skipuleggja, myndvinna og deila bæði ljósmyndum og RAW-skrám. Þú getur notað innflutningseiginleika digiKam til að flytja myndskrár og myndskeið beint af stafrænum myndavélum og milli utanáliggjandi geymslumiðla (SD-minniskort, USB-lyklar, o.s.frv.). Hugbúnaðurinn gerir kleift að setja upp reglur og stillingar við innflutning þannig að atriði séu skipulögð og unnin  um leið.</p>
    <p>digiKam raðar ljósmyndum, RAW-skrám og myndskeiðum í albúm. En hugbúnaðurinn býr einnig yfir öflugum tólum til merkinga (tags) sem gera þér kleift að útluta merkjum, einkunnum og skýringum á myndskrár. Þar með geturðu nýtt þér einstaklega öflugar síur til að finna myndir sem samsvara tilteknum skilyrðum.</p>
    <p>Auk síunar býr digiKam yfir einstaklega öflugum leitarverkfærum sem gera þér kleift að finna myndir í söfnum út frá margbreytilegum skilyrðum. Þú getur leitað eftir merkjum, skýringum, einkunn, dagsetningum, staðsetningu ásamt sérhæfðum skilyrðum úr EXIF, IPTC eða XMP lýsigögnum. Þú getur líka sameinað mörg skilyrði í ítarlegri leitir. digiKam reiðir sig á Exiv2-aðgerðasafnið til að meðhöndla efni í lýsigögnum og myndasöfnum.</p>
    <p>digiKam getur meðhöndlað RAW-skrár og styðst við hið framúrskarandi LibRaw-aðgerðasafn til að afkóða þær. Aðgerðasafninu er sífellt viðhaldið og reglulega uppfært með stuðningi við nýjustu gerðir myndavéla. digiKam getur einnig sýslað með myndskeið til flokkunar, styðst hugbúnaðurinn við FFmpeg og QtAv-aðgerðasöfnin til að yfirfæra lýsigögn og að spila efnið.</p>
    <p>Hugbúnaðurinn kemur með ágætu safni myndvinnsluverkfæra. Þar má telja ýmis grunnverkfæri til að laga liti, til utansníðingar og skerpingar, auk ítarlegri verkfæra til að laga litferla, setja saman víðmyndir og margt fleira. Sérstakt verkfæri sem byggir á Lensfun-aðgerðasafninu gerir kleift að beita linsuleiðréttingum sjálfvirkt á myndir.</p>
    <p>Hægt er að útvíkka ýmsa virkni í digiKam í gegnum kerfi fyrir forritsviðbætur (kallað DPlugins fyrir digiKam-viðbætur). Hægt er að skrifa viðbætur sem sjá um flutning mynda til og frá fjartengdum vefþjónustum, til að bæta við aðferðum við myndvinnslu og til magnvinnslu mynda.</p>
    <p>Eiginleikar:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Skipulag mynda í albúmasöfn og undiralbúm (með stuðningi við merki og athugasemdir)</li>
      <li>Stuðningur við EXIF, IPTC, XMP, Makernotes</li>
      <li>SQLite eða Mysql gagnageymsla fyrir efni myndaalbúma og lýsigögn þeirra ásamt öflugum leitartólum</li>
      <li>Stuðningur við síun og röðun albúma</li>
      <li>Innflutningur frá meira en 1100 gerðum stafrænna myndavéla</li>
      <li>Stuðningur við meira en 900 RAW-myndasnið</li>
      <li>Ljósaborð til að bera saman myndir hlið við hlið</li>
      <li>Viðbótareiginleikar með fleiri verkfærum</li>
      <li>Deildu myndunum þínum með HTML eða sendu þær beint á fjartengdar vefþjónustur</li>
      <li>Innifalið öflugt myndvinnsluforrit með þróuðum verkfærum til að laga myndir fljótt og vel</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>digiKam è un'applicazione avanzata open source per la gestione delle fotografie digitali che funziona in Linux, Windows e MacOS. L'applicazione fornisce un set completo di strumenti per importare, gestire, modificare e condividere le foto e i file RAW. Puoi usare le funzionalità di importazione di digiKam per trasferire in modo semplice fotografie, file RAW e filmati direttamente dalla tua fotocamera e da dispositivi di memorizzazione esterni (schede SD, dischi USB, ecc.). L'applicazione ti permette di configurare le impostazioni di importazione e le regole che elaborano e organizzano al volo gli elementi importati.</p>
    <p>digiKam organizza fotografie, file RAW e filmati in album. L'applicazione offre inoltre strumenti avanzati per l'assegnazione di tag, valutazioni ed etichette alle fotografie e i file RAW. Puoi anche utilizzare la funzionalità di filtraggio per trovare rapidamente elementi che corrispondono a specifici criteri di ricerca.</p>
    <p>Oltre la funzione di filtraggio, digiKam possiede avanzate capacità di ricerca tramite un'ampia gamma di criteri all'interno della libreria fotografica. Puoi ricercare foto per tag, etichette, valutazione, dati, posizione e persino per metadati specifici EXIF, IPTC o XMP. Puoi combinare anche vari criteri per ricerche più avanzate. digiKam si basa sulla libreria Exiv2 per gestire il contenuto dei tag dei metadati presenti nei file e popolare la libreria fotografica.</p>
    <p>digiKam è in grado di gestire i file RAW utilizzando l'eccellente libreria LibRaw per decodificarli. La libreria è attivamente sviluppata e regolarmente aggiornata per includere il supporto agli ultimi modelli di fotocamere. digiKam è in grado di gestire anche file video a scopo di catalogazione, utilizzando insieme le librerie FFmpeg e QtAv per estrarre i metadati e riprodurre i file multimediali.</p>
    <p>L'applicazione fornisce un set completo di strumenti di modifica. Esso include strumenti di base per la regolazione dei colori, il ritaglio e la nitidezza e strumenti avanzati per la regolazione delle curve, la composizione dei panorami e molto altro. Uno strumento speciale basato sulla libreria Lensfun permette di applicare automaticamente correzioni focali sulle immagini.</p>
    <p>Ulteriori funzionalità sono implementata in digiKam grazie a un insieme di strumenti basato su un meccanismo di estensioni (chiamato DPlugins, ossia digiKam Plugins). Possono essere create estensioni per importare ed esportare contenuto ai servizi web remoti, aggiungere nuove funzionalità per la modifica delle immagini e per l'elaborazione in serie delle fotografie.</p>
    <p>Caratteristiche:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organizzazione di foto in album e sotto-album (con supporto per le etichette e i commenti)</li>
      <li>Supporto per Exif, IPTC, XMP, Makernotes</li>
      <li>Memorizzazione del contenuto degli album e dei suoi metadati tramite SQLite o MySQL, con strumenti di ricerca avanzati</li>
      <li>Supporto per il filtraggio e l'ordinamento degli album</li>
      <li>Importazione da più di 1.100 dispositivi fotografici digitali</li>
      <li>Supporto per più di 900 immagini in formato RAW</li>
      <li>Tavolo luminoso per confrontare le foto fianco a fianco</li>
      <li>Funzionalità estese tramite strumenti aggiuntivi</li>
      <li>Condivisione delle foto tramite HTML o loro pubblicazione nei servizi web remoti</li>
      <li>Editor delle immagini con strumenti avanzati inclusi per la correzione rapida delle foto</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>기능:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>앨범 및 하위 앨범으로 사진 정렬(태그와 주석 지원)</li>
      <li>EXIF, IPTC, XMP, 메이커 노트 지원</li>
      <li>SQLite 및 MySQL 기반 앨범과 메타데이터 저장소 및 고급 검색 도구</li>
      <li>앨범 필터링 및 정렬</li>
      <li>1100종 이상의 디지털 카메라에서 사진 가져오기</li>
      <li>900종 이상의 RAW 사진 형식 지원</li>
      <li>사진을 양쪽으로 비교하는 조명 테이블</li>
      <li>추가 도구로 기능 확장</li>
      <li>HTML로 사진 공유 및 웹 서비스에 올리기</li>
      <li>사진을 빠르게 편집할 수 있는 고급 기능이 있는 그림 편집기</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>digiKam is een geavanceerd opensource digitale toepassing voor fotobeheer die werkt op Linux, Windows en MacOS. De toepassing biedt een uitgebreide set hulpmiddelen voor importeren, beheren, bewerken en delen van foto's en raw-bestanden. U kunt de mogelijkheden voor importen van digiKam gebruiken om foto's, raw-bestanden en video's direct vanaf uw camera en externe opslagapparaten (SD kaarten, USB-sticks, etc.) gemakkelijk te transporteren. De toepassing biedt u importinstellingen en regels te configureren geïmporteerde items bewerken en organiseren on-the-fly.</p>
    <p>digiKam organiseert foto's, raw-bestanden en video's in albums. Maar de toepassing heeft ook krachtige hulpmiddelen voor tags die het toekennen van tags, waarderings en labels aan foto's en raw-bestanden. U kunt dan functies voor filtering gebruiken om snel items te vinden die overeenkomen met specifieke criteria.</p>
    <p>Naast functies voor filteren heeft digiKam krachtige functies voor zoeken die u laten zoeken in de fotobibliotheek met een brede reeks van criteria. U kunt foto's zoeken op tags, labels, waardering, gegevens, locatie en zelfs specifieke EXIF, IPTC of XMP metagegevens. U kunt ook verschillende criteria combineren voor meer geavanceerd zoeken. digiKam is afhankelijk van de Exiv2-bibliotheek om de inhoud van metagegevenstags uit bestanden te behandelen om de fotobibliotheek te bevolken.</p>
    <p>digiKam kan raw-bestanden behandelen en de toepassing gebruikt de excellente LibRaw-bibliotheek voor het decoderen van raw-bestanden. De bibliotheek wordt actief onderhouden en regelmatig bijgewerkt om ondersteuning voor de nieuwste cameramodellen te bevatten. digiKam kan ook videobestanden beheren voor het catalogiseren en de toepassing gebruikt het koppel FFmpeg- en QtAv-bibliotheken om metagegevens op te halen en media af te spelen.</p>
    <p>De toepassing biedt een uitgebreide set hulpmiddelen voor bewerking. Dit omvat basis hulpmiddelen voor aanpassen van kleuren, bijsnijden en verscherpen evanals geavanceerde hulpmiddelen voor, aanpassen van krommen, aan elkaar breien voor een panorama en nog veel meer. Een speciaal hulpmiddel gebaseerd op de Lensfun-bibliotheek biedt het automatisch toepassen van lenscorrecties op afbeeldingen.</p>
    <p>Uitgebreide functionaliteit in digiKam is geïmplementeerd via een set hulpmiddelen gebaseerd op plug-in-mechanismes (genaamd DPlugins voor digiKam Plugins). Plug-ins kunnen geschreven worden om inhoud van en naar web-services op afstand te im- en exporteren, nieuwe functies toe te voegen om afbeeldingen te bewerken en foto's in bulk te behandelen .</p>
    <p>Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organiseren van foto's in albums en sub-albums (met tags en ondersteuning van commentaar)</li>
      <li>Ondersteuning voor Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li>Op SQLite of Mysql gebaseerde opslag voor de inhoud van albums en zijn metagegevens met geavanceerde zoekhulpmiddellen</li>
      <li>Ondersteuning voor filtering en sorteren van albums</li>
      <li>Importeren uit meer dan 1100 digitale camera's</li>
      <li>Ondersteuning voor 900 RAW-format afbeeldingen</li>
      <li>Lichttafel om foto's naast elkaar te vergelijken</li>
      <li>Uitgebreide mogelijkheden met extra hulpmiddelen</li>
      <li>Uw foto's delen met HTML of ze publiceren op websites op afstand</li>
      <li>Bewerker van afbeeldingen met geavanceerde hulpmiddelen om foto's snel te repareren</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>Funksjonar:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organisering av bilete i album og underalbum (med støtte for merkelappar og kommentarar)</li>
      <li>Støtte for Exif, Iptc, Xmp og Makernotes</li>
      <li>SQLite- eller MySQL-basert lagring for album og metadata, med avanserte søkjeverktøy</li>
      <li>Støtte for filtrering og sortering av album</li>
      <li>Støtte for importering av bilete frå meir enn 1 100 ulike kameramodellar</li>
      <li>Støtte for meir enn 900 ulike råbiletformat</li>
      <li>Lysbord for å samanlikna bilete ved sida av kvarandre</li>
      <li>Programtillegg som gjev ekstrafunksjonar</li>
      <li>Kan dela bileta med HTML eller publisera dei på ulike nett-tenester</li>
      <li>Innebygd biletredigering med avanserte verktøy for å forbetra bileta</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pa">
    <p>ਫੀਚਰ:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>digiKam to rozbudowany program do zarządzania zdjęciami cyfrowymi tworzony na zasadzie otwartego źródła, który działa na Linuksie, Windowsie oraz MacOS. Program zapewnia rozbudowany zestaw narzędzi do importowania, zarządzania, zmiany oraz udostępniania zdjęć i plików raw. Możesz skorzystać z możliwości importowania digiKama do łatwego przesyłania zdjęć, plików raw oraz filmów bezpośrednio z twojego aparatu lub zewnętrznego urządzenia przechowywania (karty SD, dyski USB, itp.). Program umożliwia nadanie ustawień importu oraz zasad do przetwarzania i porządkowania rzeczy w locie.</p>
    <p>digiKam porządkuje zdjęcia, plik raw oraz filmy w albumy. Program ma także rozbudowane narzędzia znaczników, które umożliwiają przypisywanie, znaczników, ocen oraz etykiet zdjęciom i plikom raw. W późniejszym czasie możesz skorzystać z filtrowania, aby szybko znaleźć rzeczy, których poszukujesz.</p>
    <p>W dodatku do możliwości filtrowania, digiKam daje rozbudowane możliwości szukania, które umożliwiają przeszukiwanie biblioteki zdjęć wg szerokiego zakresu kryteriów. Możesz przeszukiwać zdjęcia po znacznikach, etykietach, ocenie, danych, miejscu, a nawet poszczególnych metadanych EXIF, IPTC lub XMP. Możesz także łączyć kilka kryteriów w bardziej rozbudowane poszukiwania. digiKam opiera się na bibliotece Exiv2 do obsługi treści znaczników metadanych do wypełniania biblioteki zdjęć.</p>
    <p>digiKam obsługuje pliki raw, a program używa doskonałej biblioteki LibRaw do dekodowania plików raw. Biblioteka jest wciąż utrzymywania i uaktualniania tak, aby zawierała obsługę najnowszych modeli aparatów. digiKam może także zarządzać plikami filmów do celów katalogowania, a program używa pary bibliotek FFmpeg oraz QtAv do wydobywania metadanych oraz odtwarzania treści.</p>
    <p>Program zapewnia rozbudowany zestaw narzędzi do zmiany obrazów. Zawierają się w tym narzędzia do dostosowywania barw, przycinania i wyostrzania, a także rozbudowane narzędzia do dostosowywania krzywych, zszywania w panoramę oraz wiele więcej. osobne narzędzie stworzone na podstawie biblioteki Lensfun umożliwia nakładanie poprawek soczewki na obrazy.</p>
    <p>Rozszerzone możliwości w digiKam znajdują się w zestawie narzędzi w wtyczkach (zwanych DWtyczki lub wtyczki digiKama). Wtyczki można pisać, aby dodać importowanie i eksportowanie treści do zdalnych usług sieciowych, dodać nowe możliwości zmiany obrazów oraz umożliwić przetwarzanie obrazów w kolejce.</p>
    <p>Możliwości:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Grupowanie zdjęć w albumy i podalbumów (z obsługą znaczników i komentarzy)</li>
      <li>Obsługa Exif, Iptc, Xmp, notatek twórcy</li>
      <li>Przechowalnia dla albumów i ich metadanych z zaawansowanymi narzędziami wyszukiwania jest napędzana SQLite lub Mysql</li>
      <li>Obsługa filtrowania i sortowania albumów</li>
      <li>Importowanie z więcej niż 1100 aparatów cyfrowych</li>
      <li>Obsługa dla więcej niż 900 postaci zdjęć RAW</li>
      <li>Podświetlarka do porównywania zdjęć jedno obok drugiego</li>
      <li>Rozszerzone funkcje używające dodatkowych narzędzi</li>
      <li>Udostępnianie zdjęć przy użyciu HTML lub publikowanie ich poprzez usługi sieciowe</li>
      <li>Dołączony edytor obrazów o zaawansowanych narzedziach do szybkiego poprawiania zdjęć</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O digiKam é uma aplicação de gestão de fotografias digitais em código aberto que funciona no Linux, Windows e MacOS. A aplicação oferece um conjunto abrangente de ferramentas para importar, gerir, editar e partilhar fotografias e ficheiros RAW. Poderá usar as capacidades de importação do digiKam para transferir facilmente as fotografias, ficheiros RAW e vídeos directamente da sua maquina fotográfica e dos dispositivos de armazenamento externos (cartões SD, discos USB, etc.). A aplicação permite-lhe configurar as opções de importação e as regras que processam e organizam os itens importados na hora.</p>
    <p>O digiKam organiza as fotos, os ficheiros RAW e os vídeos em álbuns. Contudo, a aplicação também oferece ferramentas poderosas de marcação que lhe permitem atribuir marcas, classificações e legendas às fotografias e ficheiros RAW. Poderá então usar a funcionalidade de filtragem para encontrar rapidamente os itens que correspondam a um dado critério.</p>
    <p>Para além da funcionalidade de filtragem, o digiKam oferece funcionalidades de pesquisa poderosas que lhe permitem consultar a biblioteca de fotografias de acordo com uma grande variedade de critérios. Poderá pesquisar as fotografias por marcas, legendas, classificações, dados, localização e até mesmo alguns meta-dados específicos de EXIF, IPTC ou XMP. Poderá também combinar vários critérios para pesquisas mais avançadas. O digiKam baseia-se na biblioteca Exiv2 para tratar dos conteúdos de marcas dos meta-dados a partir dos ficheiros para preencher a biblioteca de fotografias.</p>
    <p>O digiKam consegue lidar com ficheiros RAW e a aplicação usa a excelente biblioteca LibRaw para descodificar os ficheiros RAW. A biblioteca é mantida de forma activa e é actualizada regularmente para incluir o suporte para os últimos modelos  de máquinas fotográficas. O digiKam consegue também lidar com ficheiros de vídeo para fins de catalogo e a aplicação usa o par de bibliotecas FFmpeg e QtAv para extrair os meta-dados e reproduzir os conteúdos.</p>
    <p>A aplicação oferece um conjunto abrangente de ferramentas de edição. Isto inclui ferramentas básicas para ajustar as cores, recortar e aumentar a nitidez, assim como ferramentas avançadas para o ajuste de curvas, o recorte de panoramas e muito mais. Uma ferramenta especial, baseada na biblioteca Lensfun, permite aplicar as correcções de lentes automaticamente nas imagens.</p>
    <p>Está implementada uma funcionalidade estendida no digiKam através de um conjunto de ferramentas baseadas num mecanismo de 'plugins' (chamado de DPlugins para 'digiKam Plugins'). Os 'plugins' podem ser criados para importar e exportar os conteúdos para serviços Web remotos, adicionar novas funcionalidades para editar as imagens e processar as fotografias em lote.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organização das fotografias por álbuns e sub-álbuns (com o suporte para marcas e comentários)</li>
      <li>Suporte para o EXIF, IPTC, XMP e notas do fabricante</li>
      <li>Armazenamento baseado em SQLite ou MySQL para o conteúdo dos álbuns e os seus meta-dados com ferramentas de pesquisa avançadas</li>
      <li>Suporte para filtrar e ordenar os álbuns</li>
      <li>Importar a partir de mais de 1100 máquinas digitais</li>
      <li>Suporte para mais de 900 formatos de imagens RAW</li>
      <li>Mesa de Luz para comparar as fotografias lado-a-lado</li>
      <li>Funcionalidades estendidas com ferramentas extra</li>
      <li>Partilhar as suas fotos por HTML ou publicá-las em serviços Web remotos</li>
      <li>Editor de imagens que inclui ferramentas avançadas para corrigir rapidamente as fotografias</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organização de fotos em álbuns e subálbuns (com suporte a etiquetas e comentários)</li>
      <li>Suporte a EXIF, IPTC, XMP e Notas do Fabricante</li>
      <li>Armazenamento baseado em SQLite ou MySQL para o conteúdo dos álbuns e seus metadados com ferramentas de pesquisa avançadas</li>
      <li>Suporte a filtragem e ordenação de álbuns</li>
      <li>Importação de mais de 1.100 câmeras digitais</li>
      <li>Suporte a mais de 900 formatos de imagem RAW</li>
      <li>Mesa de Luz para comparação de fotos lado a lado</li>
      <li>Funcionalidades estendidas com ferramentas extras</li>
      <li>Compartilhamento de fotos usando HTML ou publicação em serviços remotos</li>
      <li>Editor de imagens com funcionalidades avançadas para correção de fotos</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>DigiKam — приложение для управления коллекциями цифровых фотографий с открытым исходным кодом, работающее по управлением Linux, Windows и MacOS. Приложение содержит полный набор инструментов для импорта, управления, редактирования и обмена фотографиями и цифровыми негативами (RAW-файлами). DigiKam позволяет переносить фотографии, цифровые негативы и видео с камер и внешних устройств хранения, таких как SD-карты, USB-диски и прочих. Приложение позволяет настраивать параметры и правила, которые обрабатывают и систематизируют объекты непосредственно во время импорта.</p>
    <p>Для упорядоченного хранения фотографий, файлов цифровых негативов и видео в digiKam используются альбомы. Но приложение также содержит инструменты  классификации, позволяющие назначать теги, рейтинги и метки фотографиям и файлам цифровых негативов. Фильтры позволяют быстро отбирать объекты по заданным критериям.</p>
    <p>В дополнение к фильтрам, в digiKam реализована функциональная система поиска изображений с использованием широкого набора критериев. Возможно выполнять поиск по меткам, ярлыкам отбора, рейтингу, данным, местоположениям и даже указанным метаданным EXIF, IPTC и XMP. Возможен расширенный поиск с одновременным использованием нескольких критериев. Для получения метаданных изображений digiKam использует библиотеку Exif2.</p>
    <p>Поддержка работы с файлами цифровых негативов (RAW) обеспечена отличной библиотекой LibRaw. Эта библиотека активно развивается, в том числе в части поддержки последних моделей цифровых камер. Кроме того, digiKam также поддерживает получение сведений из видеофайлов с использованием библиотеки FFmpeg и их воспроизведение с использованием библиотек QtAv.</p>
    <p>Приложение содержит исчерпывающий набор инструментов редактирования изображений, начиная от простых, предназначенных для исправления цветов, кадрирования и повышения чёткости изображений и заканчивая расширенными инструментами для настройки уровней цветов, склеивания панорам и множеством других. Инструмент, основанный на библиотеке Lensfun, позволяет исправлять искажения, внесённые объективом.</p>
    <p>Набор поддерживаемых функций digiKam реализован в виде подключаемых модулей (DPlugings для digiKam). Подключаемые модули могут выполнять импорт и экспорт изображений в различные службы, расположенные в интернете, добавлять новые возможности редактирования и пакетной обработки изображений.</p>
    <p>Возможности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Упорядочивание фотографий с использованием иерархических альбомов, меток и комментариев;</li>
      <li>Поддержка метаданных EXIF, IPTC, XMP и MakerNote;</li>
      <li>Использование баз данных SQLite и MySQL для хранения метаданных и информации о содержимом альбомов позволяет выполнять расширенный поиск и отбор требуемых изображений;</li>
      <li>Отбор и сортировка альбомов;</li>
      <li>Поддержка импорта более чем с 1100 моделей цифровых камер;</li>
      <li>Поддержка более 900 форматов цифровых негативов (RAW);</li>
      <li>Световой стол для сравнения изображений;</li>
      <li>Расширенные возможности дополнительных инструментов;</li>
      <li>Публикация фотографий созданием галерей в формате HTML а также на различных интернет-ресурсах;</li>
      <li>Редактор изображений с расширенными инструментами для быстрого исправления фотографий.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Funkcie:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organizácia fotiek v albumoch a podalbumoch (so značkami a komentármi)</li>
      <li>Podpora pre Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li>Podpora pre filtrovanie a triedenie albumov</li>
      <li>Import z viac ako 1100 digitálnych fotoaparátov</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>digiKam je napredni odprtokodni program za upravljanje digitalnih fotografij, ki deluje v sistemih Linux, Windows in MacOS. Program ponuja celovit nabor orodij za uvoz, upravljanje, urejanje in skupno rabo fotografij in surovih datotek. Za lažji prenos fotografij lahko uporabite funkcije uvoza digiKam, surove datoteke in videoposnetke neposredno iz fotoaparata in zunanjih pomnilniških naprav (SD kartice, USB diski itd.). Program omogoča nastavitev uvoza in pravil, ki sproti obdelujejo in organizirajo uvožene predmete.</p>
    <p>digiKam organizira fotografije, surove datoteke in videoposnetke v albume. Program pa vsebuje tudi močna orodja za označevanje, ki vam omogočajo dodelitev značk, ocene in oznake za fotografije in surove datoteke. Uporabite lahko tudi filtriranje za hitro iskanje elementov, ki ustrezajo določenim kriterijem.</p>
    <p>Poleg filtriranja digiKam odlikuje močne zmožnosti iskanja, ki omogočajo iskanje po knjižnici fotografij po številnih kriterijih. Po fotografijah lahko iščete po značkah, oznakah, ocenah, podatkih, lokaciji in celo specifičnih metapodatkih EXIF, IPTC ali XMP. Kombinirate lahko tudi večkriterijev za bolj napredna iskanja. digiKam se zanaša na knjižnico Exiv2 za obdelavo oznak metapodatkov iz datotek ureditev knjižnice fotografij.</p>
    <p>digiKam lahko obdeluje surove datoteke, tako da uporablja odlično knjižnico LibRaw za dekodiranje surovih datotek. Knjižnica je aktivno vzdrževana in redno posodobljena, tako da zagotavlja podporo najnovejšim modelom kamer. digiKam lahko tudi upravlja tudi z video datotekami za namene katalogizacije in program uporablja par knjižnic FFmpeg in QtAv za pridobivanje metapodatkov in predvajanje medijev.</p>
    <p>Program nudi obsežen nabor orodij za urejanje. To vključuje osnovna orodja za prilagajanje barv, obrezovanje in ostrenje kot tudinapredna orodja za nastavitev krivulj, "šivanje panoram" in še veliko več. Posebno orodje, ki temelji na knjižnici Lensfun, omogoča uporabo samodejni popravkov lečja na slikah.</p>
    <p>Razširjena funkcionalnost v digiKamu se izvaja prek nabora orodij, ki temeljijo na mehanizmu vtičnikov (imenovani DPlugins za digiKam Plugins). Vtičniki so lahko napisani za uvoz in izvoz vsebin v oddaljene spletne storitve, dodajanje novi funkcij za urejanje slik in paketno obdelavo fotografij.</p>
    <p>Zmožnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organizacija fotografij v albumih in pod-albumih (s podporo oznakam in opombam)</li>
      <li>Podpora Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes</li>
      <li>Shramba SQLite ali Mysql za albume in metapodatke ter napredna iskalna orodja</li>
      <li>Podpora filtriranju in razvrščanju albumov</li>
      <li>Uvažanje iz več kot 1100 digitalnih fotoaparatov</li>
      <li>Podpora več kot 900 vrstam surovih slik (RAW)</li>
      <li>Osvetlitvena miza za primerjavo fotografij</li>
      <li>Razširjene zmožnosti preko dodatnih orodij</li>
      <li>Delite vaše fotografije s pomočjo HTML-ja ali pa jih objavite na oddaljenih storitvah</li>
      <li>Vgrajen urejevalnik slik z naprednimi orodji za hitre popravke fotografij</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Digikam är ett avancerat digitalt fotohanteringsprogram med öppen källkod som kör på Linux, Windows och MacOS. Programmet tillhandahåller en omfattande verktygsuppsättning för att importera, hantera, redigera och dela foton och obehandlade filer. Du kan använda Digikams importmöjligheter för att enkelt överföra foton, obehandlade filer och videor direkt från din kamera eller externa lagringsenheter (SD-kort, USB-minnen, etc.). Programmet låter dig anpassa importinställningar och regler som behandlar och organiserar importerade objekt i farten.</p>
    <p>Digikam organiserar foton, obehandlade filer och videor i album. Men programmet erbjuder också kraftfulla verktyg för etikettering som låter dig tilldela etiketter, betyg och beteckningar till foton och obehandlade filer. Du kan sedan använda filtreringsfunktionerna för att snabbt hitta objekt som motsvarar specifika kriterier.</p>
    <p>Förutom filtreringsfunktionaliteten, tillhandahåller Digikam kraftfulla sökmöjligheter som låter dig söka i fotobiblioteket med ett stort antal olika kriterier. Du kan söka efter foton enligt etiketter, beteckningar, data, plats och till och med specifika EXIF-, IPTC- eller XMP-metadata. Du kan också kombinera olika kriterier för mer avancerade sökningar. Digikam förlitar sig på biblioteket Exiv2 för att hantera innehållet i metadatataggar från filer för att fylla i fotobiblioteket.</p>
    <p>Digikam kan hantera obehandlade filer, och programmet använder det utmärkta biblioteket LibRaw för att avkoda obehandlade filer. Biblioteket underhålls aktivt och uppdateras regelbundet för att  inkludera stöd för de senaste kameramodellerna. Digikam kan också hantera videofiler i katalogiseringssyfte, och programmet använder de två biblioteken FFmpeg och QtAv för att extrahera metadata och spela upp media.</p>
    <p>Programmet tillhandahåller en omfattande uppsättning redigeringsverktyg. Det inkluderar grundverktyg för att justera färger, beskära och förbättra skärpa samt avancerade verktyg för kurvjustering, panoramasammanställning, med mera. Ett specialverktyg baserat på biblioteket Lensfun tillåter att linskorrektion automatiskt utförs för bilder.</p>
    <p>Utökad funktionalitet i Digikam implementeras via en uppsättning verktyg baserat på insticksmekanismen (benämnda DPlugins). Insticksprogram kan skrivas för att importera och exportera innehåll till webbtjänster på nätet, lägga till nya funktioner för att redigera bilder och för att behandla foton i bakgrunden.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organisation av foton i album och delalbum (med stöd för etiketter och kommentarer)</li>
      <li>Stöd för EXIF, IPTC, XMP, tillverkaranteckningar</li>
      <li>Lagring driven av SQLite eller MySQL för album och deras metadata med avancerade sökverktyg</li>
      <li>Stöd för filtrering och sortering av album</li>
      <li>Import från mer än 1100 digitalkameror</li>
      <li>Stöd för 900 obehandlade bildformat</li>
      <li>Ljusbord för att jämföra foton sida vid sida</li>
      <li>Utökade funktioner med användning av extra verktyg</li>
      <li>Dela foton genom att använda HTML eller publicera dem på webbtjänster</li>
      <li>Bildeditor med avancerade funktioner ingår för att snabbt förbättra foton</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Özellikler:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Resimler albüm ya da alt albümlerde düzenleme (etiket ve yorum desteğiyle)</li>
      <li>Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes desteği</li>
      <li>Albüm içeriği ve meta verileri için gelişmiş arama araçlarıyla, SQLite veya Mysql destekli depolama</li>
      <li>Albümleri filtreleme ve sıralama desteği</li>
      <li>1100den fazla kamera cihazından içe aktarma</li>
      <li>900'den fazla RAW biçimli resim desteği</li>
      <li>Fotoğrafı yan yana karşılaştırmak için Tabloyu Işıklandır</li>
      <li>Ekstra araçlar kullanan genişletilmiş özellikler</li>
      <li>Resimlerinizi HTML kullanarak paylaşın veya onları uzak web servislerinde yayımlayın</li>
      <li>Fotoğrafı hızla düzeltmek için gelişmiş araçlar içeren resim editörü</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>digiKam — програма для керування цифровими фотографіями із відкритим кодом і широкими можливостями. Програмою можна скористатися у Linux, Windows та MacOS. У програмі передбачено повний набір інструментів для імпортування, керування, редагування та оприлюднення фотографій та файлів цифрових негативів. Ви можете скористатися можливостями digiKam з імпортування для спрощення передавання фотографій, файлів цифрових негативів та відео безпосередньо з камери або зовнішніх пристроїв для зберігання даних (карток SD, дисків USB тощо). У програмі передбачено можливість налаштовування параметрів імпортування та правил динамічної обробки та упорядковування імпортованих записів.</p>
    <p>У digiKam фотографії, файли цифрових негативів та відео упорядковуються за альбомами. Але, крім того, у програмі передбачено потужні засоби встановлення міток, за допомогою яких ви можете призначати мітки, оцінки та позначки для фотографій і файлів цифрових негативів. Далі, можна скористатися функціональними можливостями з фільтрування для швидкого пошуку записів, які відповідають певним критеріям.</p>
    <p>Окрім функціональних можливостей із фільтрування, у digiKam передбачено потужні можливості з пошуку, за допомогою яких ви можете виконувати пошук у фотобібліотеці за широким діапазоном критеріїв. Ви можете шукати фотографії за мітками, позначками, оцінками, даними, місцем зйомки і навіть певними метаданими EXIF, IPTC або XMP. Ви також можете поєднувати декілька критеріїв, створюючи складні пошуки. Для обробки вмісту міток метаданих з файлів і заповнення даних фотобібліотеки у digiKam використано бібліотеку Exiv2.</p>
    <p>digiKam може працювати із файлами цифрових негативів. Програма використовує чудову бібліотеку LibRaw для декодування файлів цифрових негативів. Ця бібліотека активно розвивається і регулярно оновлюється з метою включення підтримки найсвіжіших моделей цифрових фотоапаратів. Крім того, digiKam може керувати відеофайлами з метою їхньої каталогізації. Програма використовує поєднання бібліотек FFmpeg та QtAv для видобування метаданих та відтворення відео.</p>
    <p>Програма постачається із повним набором засобів для редагування. До цього набору включено інструменти для коригування кольорів, обрізання та збільшення різкості зображення, а також профільні інструменти для коригування кривих, створення панорам тощо. За допомогою спеціального інструмента, заснованого на бібліотеці Lensfun, можна автоматично застосовувати виправлення викривлень, які спричинено оптичними недоліками об'єктива.</p>
    <p>Додаткові функціональні можливості digiKam реалізовано у форматі набору засобів на основі механізмів додатків (які називаються DPlugin, тобто додатки (Plugin) digiKam). Ви самі можете створювати додатки для імпортування та експортування даних на віддалені вебслужби, додавати нові можливості для редагування зображень та пакетної обробки фотографій.</p>
    <p>Можливості:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>упорядковування фотографій за альбомами і підальбомами з підтримкою міток та коментарів;</li>
      <li>підтримка Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotes;</li>
      <li>сховище даних на основі SQLite або MySQL для вмісту альбомів та метаданих із розширеними можливостями пошуку;</li>
      <li>підтримка фільтрування та упорядковування альбомів;</li>
      <li>можливість імпортування даних з понад 1100 цифрових фотоапаратів;</li>
      <li>підтримка понад 900 форматів цифрових негативів (RAW);</li>
      <li>стіл із підсвічуванням для порівняння фотографій;</li>
      <li>розширення можливостей за допомогою додаткових інструментів;</li>
      <li>можливість оприлюднення фотографій на віддалених службах у інтернеті;</li>
      <li>редактор зображень із додатковими можливостями для швидкого виправлення фотографій;</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxdigiKam is an advanced open-source digital photo management application that runs on Linux, Windows, and MacOS. The application provides a comprehensive set of tools for importing, managing, editing, and sharing photos and raw files. You can use digiKam’s import capabilities to easily transfer photos, raw files, and videos directly from your camera and external storage devices (SD cards, USB disks, etc.). The application allows you to configure import settings and rules that process and organize imported items on-the-fly.xx</p>
    <p>xxdigiKam organizes photos, raw files, and videos into albums. But the application also features powerful tagging tools that allow you to assign tags, ratings, and labels to photos and raw files. You can then use filtering functionality to quickly find items that match specific criteria.xx</p>
    <p>xxIn addition to filtering functionality, digiKam features powerful searching capabilities that let you search the photo library by a wide range of criteria. You can search photos by tags, labels, rating, data, location, and even specific EXIF, IPTC, or XMP metadata. You can also combine several criteria for more advanced searches. digiKam rely on Exiv2 library to handle metadata tag contents from files to populate the photo library.xx</p>
    <p>xxdigiKam can handle raw files, and the application uses the excellent LibRaw library for decoding raw files. The library is actively maintained and regularly updated to include support for the latest camera models. digiKam can also manage video files for cataloging purpose, and the application uses the couple FFmpeg and QtAv libraries to extract metadata and play media.xx</p>
    <p>xxThe application provides a comprehensive set of editing tools. This includes basic tools for adjusting colors, cropping, and sharpening as well as advanced tools for, curves adjustment, panorama stitching, and much more. A special tool based on Lensfun library permit to apply lens corrections automatically on images.xx</p>
    <p>xxExtended functionality in digiKam is implemented via a set of tools based of plugins mechanism (named DPlugins for digiKam Plugins). Plugins can be written to import and export contents to remote web-services, add new features to edit image, and batch process photo.xx</p>
    <p>xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>xxOrganization of photos in albums and sub-albums (with tags and comments support)xx</li>
      <li>xxSupport for Exif, Iptc, Xmp, Makernotesxx</li>
      <li>xxSQLite or Mysql powered storage for the album contents and its metadata with advanced search toolsxx</li>
      <li>xxSupport for filtering and sorting albumsxx</li>
      <li>xxImport from more than 1100 digital camera devicesxx</li>
      <li>xxSupport for more than 900 RAW format picturesxx</li>
      <li>xxLight Table to compare photo side by sidexx</li>
      <li>xxExtended features using extra toolsxx</li>
      <li>xxShare your photos using HTML or publishing them to remote web servicesxx</li>
      <li>xxImage editor included with advanced tools to fix photo quicklyxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>digiKam 是一款功能先进的自由开源数字照片管理程序，包含了对照片和 RAW 图像文件进行导入、管理、编辑和分享的全套工具。它支持 Linux、Windows 和 macOS。您可以使用 digiKam 的导入功能从数码相机或者外部存储设备 (SD 卡、U 盘等) 向本机传输照片、RAW 图像文件和视频，操作简单轻松。你还可以随时配置导入选项，为已导入的照片更改处理和整理规则。</p>
    <p>digiKam 可以将照片、RAW 图像文件和视频整理成相册。它还带有功能强大的标签工具，您可以对照片和 RAW 图像文件指定标签、进行评分和附加标记，并按照这些条件进行筛选，快速查找符合条件的项目。</p>
    <p>除了筛选功能外，digiKam 还内建了强大的搜索功能。您可以使用各种条件来对照片库中的内容进行搜索，如标签、标记、评价、数据、地理位置，甚至特定的 EXIF、IPTC 或者 XMP 元数据。您还可以合并使用多个条件来进行更加深入的搜索。digiKam 通过 Exiv2 程序库来处理来自文件元数据的标签内容，并将它们整合到照片库中。</p>
    <p>digiKam 可以处理 RAW 图像文件，它通过功能强大的 LibRaw 程序库来对 RAW 图像文件进行解码。该程序库的开发工作相当活跃，它会定期更新以支持最新型号的数码相机。digiKam 也支持对视频文件进行编目管理，它通过 FFmpeg 和 QtAv 两个程序库来提取媒体的元数据并播放它们。</p>
    <p>digiKam 内建了一套功能齐全的图像编辑工具，不但包括了基本的颜色调整、裁剪、锐化工具，还包括了颜色曲线调整、全景图拼接等高级工具。它还有一个基于 Lensfun 程序库的自动镜头畸变校正工具。</p>
    <p>digiKam 支持通过插件来扩展其功能 。digiKam 插件又称 DPlugins 工具，它们可以让您将内容导入/导出到各种在线服务，还可以带来图像编辑和批处理的更多功能。</p>
    <p>程序功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>在相册和子相册中组织照片 (支持标签和注释)</li>
      <li>支持 EXIF、IPTC、XMP、Makernotes</li>
      <li>通过 SQLite 或者 MySQL 为保存的相册内容及其元数据提供高级搜索工具</li>
      <li>支持对相册进行筛选和排序</li>
      <li>支持从 1100 多款数码相机设备导入照片</li>
      <li>支持超过 900 种 RAW 图像格式</li>
      <li>提供了用于并排比较照片的看片台工具</li>
      <li>通过插件扩展额外功能</li>
      <li>使用 HTML 共享照片，或者将其发布到远程 WEB 服务</li>
      <li>图像编辑器提供了用于快速修复照片的各种高级工具</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-TW">
    <p>功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>支援 EXIF、IPTC、XMP 和 Makernotes</li>
      <li>支援篩選和排序相簿</li>
      <li>能從超過 1100 個數位相機裝置匯入</li>
      <li>支援超過 900 個 RAW 格式圖片</li>
      <li>使用延伸工具得到延伸功能</li>
      <li>使用 HTML 分享圖片或將圖片發布到遠端網路服務</li>
      <li>包含進階工具的圖片編輯器以快速修復圖片</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>digikam</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.digikam.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" type="cached" height="64">digikam.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" height="128" type="cached">digikam.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.digikam.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>digiKam</name>
  <name lang="ar">دِجي‌كام</name>
  <name lang="bs">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="ca">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="cs">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="da">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="de">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="el">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="es">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="et">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="eu">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="fi">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="fr">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="gl">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="id">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="is">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="it">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="ko">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="nl">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="nn">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਡਿਜਿਕੈਮ</name>
  <name lang="pl">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="pt">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="ru">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="sk">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="sl">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="sv">Digikam</name>
  <name lang="tr">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="uk">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxdigiKamxx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">digiKam</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">digiKam</name>
  <summary>Photo Management Program</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">برنامج لإدارة الصور</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Programa per a la gestió de les fotografies</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Programa per a la gestió de les fotografies</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Program pro správu fotografií</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Fotoverwaltung</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Πρόγραμμα διαχείρισης φωτογραφιών</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Photo Management Program</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Programa de gestión de fotos</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Fotohalduse rakendus</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Argazkiak kudeatzeko programa</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Valokuvahallintaohjelma</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Application de gestion de photos</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Xestor de álbums de fotos</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Program Pengelolaan Foto</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Ljósmyndaumsýsluforrit</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Programma di gestione delle foto</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">사진 관리 프로그램</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Fotobeheerprogramma</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Fotohandsamingsprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="pa">ਫੋਟੋ ਇੰਤਜ਼ਾਮ ਲਈ ਪਰੋਗਰਾਮ</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Zarządzanie zdjęciami</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Programa de Gestão de Fotografias</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Programa de gerenciamento de fotos</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Программа для управления фотографиями</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Program za upravljanje fotografij</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Fotohanteringsprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Resim Düzenleme Programı</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Програма для керування фотографіями</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxPhoto Management Programxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">照片管理程序</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-TW">圖片管理程式</summary>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.digikam.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=digikam</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=digikam</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.digikam.org/donation</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>digiKam Batch Queue Manager</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">دجيكام مدير طوابير الدفعات</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Gestor de la cua de lots del digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Gestor de la cua de lots del digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Správce dávkového zpracování digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="de">digiKam-Stapelverarbeitung</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">digiKam Batch Queue Manager</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Gestor de la cola de procesos por lotes de digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">digiKam sorta ilara kudeatzailea</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">digiKam – Eräajon hallinta</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Gestionnaire de files de tâches de digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Pengelola Antrean Seabrek digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="is">digiKam Magnvinnslustjóri</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Gestore elaborazione in serie di digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Takenwachtrijbeheer van digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="nn">Køhandsamar i digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Zarządzanie kolejką w digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Gestor da Fila de Processamento em Lote do digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Gerenciador de fila em lotes do digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Диспетчер очередей пакетной обработки digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">digiKam upravljalnik čakalnih vrst paketnih obdelav</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Digikams köhantering för bakgrundsbehandling</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Керування чергою пакетної обробки digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxdigiKam Batch Queue Managerxx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-CN">digiKam 批处理管理器</caption>
      <image>https://www.digikam.org/img/content/about/overview_bqm.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>digiKam Image Editor</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">دجيكام محرّر الصّور</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Editor d'imatges del digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Editor d'imatges del digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Editor obrázků digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="de">digiKam-Bildbearbeitung</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">digiKam Image Editor</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Editor de imágenes de digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">digiKam irudi-editorea</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">digiKam – Kuvamuokkain</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Éditeur d'images de digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Pengedit Citra digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="is">digiKam Myndvinnsluforrit</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Editor delle immagini di digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Afbeeldingsbewerker van digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="nn">Biletredigering i digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Edytor obrazów digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Editor de Imagens do digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Editor de imagens do digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Редактор изображений digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">digiKam urejevalnik slik</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Digikams  bildeditor</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Редактор зображень digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxdigiKam Image Editorxx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-CN">digiKam 图像编辑器</caption>
      <image>https://www.digikam.org/img/content/about/overview_imageeditor.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>digiKam Import From Camera</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">استيراد من الكمرة لدجيكام</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Importació des de càmera del digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Importació des de càmera del digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="de">digiKam-Kameraimport</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">digiKam Import From Camera</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Importación de cámara de digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">digiKam kameratik inportatzea</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">digiKam – Tuonti kamerasta</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Importation depuis un appareil photo de digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Impor Dari Kamera digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="is">digiKam Innflutningur úr myndavél</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Importa da fotocamera di digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Importeren uit camera van digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="nn">Import frå kamera i digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Importowanie z kamery w digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Importação de Máquinas Fotográficas do digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Importar da câmera do digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Импорт фотографий камеры в digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">digiKam uvoz iz kamere</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Digikams import från kamera</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Імпортування з камери у digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxdigiKam Import From Cameraxx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-CN">digiKam 导入相机照片</caption>
      <image>https://www.digikam.org/img/content/about/overview_import.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>digiKam Light Table</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">الطاولة الضوئيّة لدجيكام</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Taula de llum del digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Taula de llum del digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Prohlížecí stolek digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="de">digikam-Leuchttisch</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">digiKam Light Table</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Mesa de luz de digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">digiKam argi-mahaia</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">digiKam – Valotaulu</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Table lumineuse de digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Tabel Light digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="is">digiKam Ljósaborð</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Tavolo luminoso di digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Lichttafel van digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="nn">Lysbord i digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Podświetlarka digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Mesa de Luz do digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Mesa de luz do digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Световой стол digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">digiKam osvetljevalna miza</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Digikams ljusbord</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Стіл із підсвічуванням digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxdigiKam Light Tablexx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-CN">digiKam 看片台</caption>
      <image>https://www.digikam.org/img/content/about/overview_lighttable.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>digiKam Tags View</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">عرض وسوم دجيكام</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Vista d'etiquetes del digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Vista d'etiquetes del digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Pohled na značky digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="de">digiKam-Stichwortansicht</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">digiKam Tags View</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Visor de etiquetas de digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">digiKam etiketa erakuslea</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">digiKam – Luokitusnäkymä</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Afficheur des étiquettes de digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Tampilan Tag digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="is">digiKam Merkjaskoðun</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Vista tag di digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Weergave van tags van digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="nn">Merkelappvising i digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Widok znaczników digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Área de Marcas do digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Visualizador de etiquetas do digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Просмотр меток в digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Pogled digiKamovih značk</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Digikams etikettvy</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Панель перегляду міток digiKam</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxdigiKam Tags Viewxx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-CN">digiKam 标签视图</caption>
      <image>https://www.digikam.org/img/content/about/overview_tagsview.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-06-24" version="7.7.0" />
    <release date="2022-03-06" version="7.6.0" />
    <release date="2022-01-16" version="7.5.0" />
    <release version="7.4.0" date="2021-12-18" />
    <release version="7.3.0" date="2021-07-11" />
    <release date="2021-03-22" version="7.2.0" />
    <release version="7.1.0" date="2020-09-06" />
    <release version="7.0.0" date="2020-07-19" />
    <release date="2019-11-09" version="6.4.0" />
    <release version="6.3.0" date="2019-09-08" />
    <release date="2019-08-04" version="6.2.0" />
    <release date="2019-04-14" version="6.1.0" />
    <release date="2019-02-10" version="6.0.0" />
    <release version="5.9.0" date="2018-03-25" />
    <release version="5.8.0" date="2018-01-12" />
    <release date="2017-08-27" version="5.7.0" />
    <release version="5.6.0" date="2017-06-11" />
    <release date="2017-03-12" version="5.5.0" />
    <release date="2017-01-08" version="5.4.0" />
    <release version="5.3.0" date="2016-11-06" />
    <release version="5.2.0" date="2016-09-18" />
    <release date="2016-08-07" version="5.1.0" />
    <release date="2016-07-03" version="5.0.0" />
    <release date="2015-10-11" version="4.14.0" />
    <release version="4.13.0" date="2015-08-30" />
    <release date="2015-07-26" version="4.12.0" />
    <release version="4.11.0" date="2015-06-14" />
    <release date="2015-05-10" version="4.10.0" />
    <release version="4.9.0" date="2015-04-05" />
    <release version="4.8.0" date="2015-02-22" />
    <release version="4.7.0" date="2015-01-25" />
    <release date="2014-12-14" version="4.6.0" />
    <release date="2014-11-09" version="4.5.0" />
    <release version="4.4.0" date="2014-10-06" />
    <release version="4.3.0" date="2014-09-08" />
    <release date="2014-08-03" version="4.2.0" />
    <release date="2014-06-22" version="4.1.0" />
    <release version="4.0.0" date="2014-05-11" />
    <release version="3.5.0" date="2013-09-29" />
    <release version="3.4.0" date="2013-09-01" />
    <release version="3.3.0" date="2013-08-04" />
    <release version="3.2.0" date="2013-05-12" />
    <release date="2013-03-10" version="3.1.0" />
    <release date="2013-02-06" version="3.0.0" />
    <release version="2.9.0" date="2012-09-02" />
    <release date="2012-08-05" version="2.8.0" />
    <release date="2012-07-08" version="2.7.0" />
    <release version="2.6.0" date="2012-05-06" />
    <release version="2.5.0" date="2012-01-08" />
    <release date="2011-12-04" version="2.4.0" />
    <release date="2011-11-06" version="2.3.0" />
    <release date="2011-10-02" version="2.2.0" />
    <release version="2.1.0" date="2011-09-04" />
    <release version="2.0.0" date="2011-07-24" />
    <release version="1.9.0" date="2011-02-19" />
    <release date="2011-01-23" version="1.8.0" />
    <release date="2010-12-19" version="1.7.0" />
    <release date="2010-11-22" version="1.6.0" />
    <release date="2010-10-10" version="1.5.0" />
    <release date="2010-08-22" version="1.4.0" />
    <release date="2010-06-07" version="1.3.0" />
    <release date="2010-03-28" version="1.2.0" />
    <release date="2010-01-31" version="1.1.0" />
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2009-12-20" />
    <release date="2009-05-30" version="0.10.0" />
    <release version="0.9.5" date="2009-03-15" />
    <release version="0.9.4" date="2008-07-16" />
    <release date="2007-12-23" version="0.9.3" />
    <release version="0.9.2" date="2007-06-13" />
    <release version="0.9.1" date="2007-03-04" />
    <release version="0.9.0" date="2006-12-18" />
    <release version="0.8.0" date="2006-07-10" />
    <release date="2005-05-21" version="0.7.0" />
    <release date="2003-12-08" version="0.6.0" />
    <release date="2002-10-03" version="0.5.0" />
    <release date="2002-05-10" version="0.4.0" />
    <release version="0.3.0" date="2002-06-07" />
    <release version="0.2.0" date="2002-03-03" />
    <release date="2001-12-24" version="0.1.0" />
  </releases>
  <developer_name>digiKam Team</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ar">فريق دِجي‌كام</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">Equip del digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca-valencia">Equip del digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Team digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">digiKam-Team</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en-GB">digiKam Team</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Equipo de digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">digiKam taldea</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">digiKam-työryhmä</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">L'équipe de digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Tim digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="is">digiKam þróunarteymið</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">La squadra di digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Team van digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nn">digiKam-laget</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Zespół digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Equipa do digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt-BR">Equipe do digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Команда разработчиков digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Skupina digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">Digikam-gruppen</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Команда digiKam</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="x-test">xxdigiKam Teamxx</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh-CN">digiKam 开发团队</developer_name>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>digikam</binary>
  </provides>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="money-advertising">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>