<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>drawing</pkgname>
  <icon height="64" width="64" type="cached">com.github.maoschanz.drawing.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">com.github.maoschanz.drawing.png</icon>
  <id>com.github.maoschanz.drawing</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>UserDocs</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <custom>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">workstation</value>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">mobile</value>
  </custom>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <name>Drawing</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">Drawing</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">Drawing</name>
  <name lang="tr">Çizim</name>
  <name lang="sv">Drawing</name>
  <name lang="ru">Drawing</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Drawing</name>
  <name lang="pl">Rysunek</name>
  <name lang="oc">Dessenh</name>
  <name lang="nl">Tekenen</name>
  <name lang="ko">그림판</name>
  <name lang="ja">Drawing</name>
  <name lang="it">Drawing</name>
  <name lang="hu">Rajzolás</name>
  <name lang="hr">Crtanje</name>
  <name lang="he">ציור</name>
  <name lang="fr">Dessin</name>
  <name lang="fi">Piirtäminen</name>
  <name lang="eu">Drawing</name>
  <name lang="es">Dibujo</name>
  <name lang="de">Zeichnung</name>
  <name lang="da">Drawing</name>
  <name lang="cs">Kreslení</name>
  <name lang="ca">Dibuix</name>
  <!-- IMPORTANT: the summarized description of the application. -->
  <!-- https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/Initiatives/-/wikis/App-Metadata -->
  <summary>Edit screenshots or memes</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Ekran görüntülerini veya memleri düzenleyin</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Redigera skärmklipp eller memes</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Редактировать скриншоты или мемы</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Editar capturas de tela ou memes</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Edytuj zrzuty ekranu lub memy</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Bewerk schermfoto's en memes</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Modifica screenshot o meme</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Uredi snimke ekrana ili memova</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Éditez des captures d'écran ou des mèmes</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Editatu pantaila-argazkiak edo memeak</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Editar capturas de pantalla o memes</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Bearbeiten von Bildschirmfotos oder Memes</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Upravte snímky obrazovek</summary>
  <!--     123456789 123456789 123456789 12345 -->
  <description>
    <p>
      This basic image editor can resize, crop, or rotate an image, apply simple
      filters, insert or censor text, and manipulate a selected portion of the
      picture (cut/copy/paste/drag/…)
    </p>
    <p>
      And of course, you can draw! Using tools such as the pencil, the straight
      line, the curve tool, many shapes, several brushes, and their various
      colors and options.
    </p>
    <p>Supported file types include PNG, JPEG and BMP.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Tento základní editor obrázků umí zvětšovat, ořezávat nebo otáčet s obrázky, používat základní filtry, vložit nebo cenzurovat text a manipulovat s vybranou sekcí obrázku</p>
    <p>A samozřejmě, lze i kreslit použitím nástrojů jako například Tužka, Čára, Křivka, ale i pomocí mnoha tvarů, štětců a jejich barev a možností</p>
    <p>Mezi podporované typy souborů patří PNG, JPEG a BMP</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Dieses einfache Bildbearbeitungsprogramm kann die Größe von Bildern ändern, sie zuschneiden oder drehen, einfache Filter anwenden oder auch Text einfügen oder unkenntlich machen. Es lässt sich auch eine bestimmte Auswahl im Bild bearbeiten (Ausschneiden/Kopieren/Einfügen/Ziehen/…)</p>
    <p>Und natürlich können Sie auch zeichnen! Verwenden Sie Werkzeuge, wie den Bleistift, verschiedene Pinsel, viele Formen, gerade Linien oder das Bogenwerkzeug. Und das alles in den verschiedensten Farben und Optionen.</p>
    <p>Die unterstützten Dateitypen sind PNG, JPEG und BMP.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Este editor de imágenes básico puede cambiar el tamaño, recortar o girar una imagen, aplicar filtros sencillos, insertar o censurar texto y manipular una parte seleccionada de la imagen (cortar/copiar/pegar/arrastrar/...)</p>
    <p>Y, por supuesto, ¡puede dibujar! Utilizando herramientas como el lápiz, la línea recta, la herramienta de curva, muchas formas, varios pinceles, y sus diversos colores y opciones.</p>
    <p>Los tipos de archivo admitidos son PNG, JPEG y BMP.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Oinarrizko irudi-editore honek irudi baten tamaina aldatu, moztu edo biratu dezake,iragazkiak aplikatu, testua txertatu eta irudiaren zati bat manipulatu(moztu/kopiatu/itsatsi/arrastatu/...)</p>
    <p>Eta, noski, marraztu dezakezu! Erabili dezakezu hainbat tresna: arkatza, lerro zuzena, kurba, forma asko, hainbat pintzel kolore eta aukeraanitzekin.</p>
    <p>Onartutako fitxategi motak PNG, JPEG eta BMP dira.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Cet éditeur d'images basique peut redimensionner, rogner, ou pivoter une image, appliquer des filtres simples, insérer ou censurer du texte, et manipuler une portion sélectionnée de l'image (couper/copier/coller/déplacer/…)</p>
    <p>Et bien sûr, vous pouvez dessiner ! Avec des outils tel que le crayon, la ligne droite, de nombreuses formes, plusieurs pinceaux, et leurs diverses couleurs et options.</p>
    <p>Les types de fichiers supportés incluent PNG, JPEG et BMP.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Ovaj osnovni uređivač slika može promijeniti veličinu, obrezati ili okrenuti sliku, primijeniti jednostavne filtre, umetnuti ili cenzurirati tekst te manipulirati odabranim dijelom slike (izrezati/kopirati/umetnuti/povući/…)</p>
    <p>I naravno, moguće je crtati! Korištenjem alata poput olovke, ravne crte, alata za krivulje, mnogih oblika, raznih kistova i njihovih različitih boja i opcija.</p>
    <p>Podržane vrste datoteka uključuju PNG, JPEG i BMP.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Questo editor di immagini di base può ridimensionare, ritagliare o ruotare un'immagine, applica semplici filtri, inserisce o censura il testo e manipola una parte selezionata dell' immagine (taglia/copia/incolla/trascina/…)</p>
    <p>E, naturalmente, puoi disegnare! Usando strumenti come la matita, la linea dritta, lo strumento curva, molte forme, diversi pennelli e i loro vari colorie opzioni.</p>
    <p>I tipi di file supportati includono PNG, JPEG e BMP.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Met deze afbeeldingsbewerker kun je afbeeldingen bijsnijden, draaien, de grootte aanpassen, filters toepassen, tekst invoegen of censureren en delen bewerken (knippen/kopiëren/plakken/verplaatsen…)</p>
    <p>En, niet te vergeten, tekenen! Dit kan onder meer met het potlood, rechte lijnen, curven, verschillende vormen en kwasten en verschillende kleuropties.</p>
    <p>Ondersteunde bestandstypes: png, jpeg en bmp.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Ten podstawowy edytor obrazów może zmieniać rozmiar, przycinać lub obracać obraz, stosować proste filtry, wstawiać lub cenzurować tekst i manipulować wybraną częścią obrazu (wytnij/kopiuj/wklej/przeciągnij/…)</p>
    <p>Oczywiście możesz również rysować! Używaj narzędzi, takich jak ołówek, linia prosta, narzędzie krzywej, wiele kształtów, kilka pędzli i ich różne kolory i opcje.</p>
    <p>Obsługiwane typy plików to PNG, JPEG i BMP.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Este editor de imagens básico pode redimensionar, cortar ou girar uma imagem, aplicar filtros simples, inserir ou censurar texto e manipular uma parte selecionada da imagem (cortar/copiar/colar/arrastar/…)</p>
    <p>E, claro, você pode desenhar! Usando ferramentas como o lápis, a linha reta, a ferramenta de curva, muitas formas, vários pincéis e suas várias cores e opções.</p>
    <p>Os tipos de arquivo suportados incluem PNG, JPEG e BMP.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Этот базовый редактор изображений может изменять размер, обрезать или вращать изображение, применять простые фильтры, вставлять или подвергать цензуре текст, а также управлять выделенной частью изображения (вырезать/копировать/вставлять/перемещать/…)</p>
    <p>И, конечно же, ты можешь рисовать! Используя такие инструменты, как карандаш, прямая линия, кривая линия, множество фигур, несколько кистей, а также различные цвета и параметры.</p>
    <p>Поддерживаемые типы файлов включают PNG, JPEG и BMP.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Den här grundläggande bildredigeraren kan ändra storlek, beskära eller rotera en bild, tillämpa enkla filter, infoga eller censurera text och ändra en markerad del av bilden (klipp ut/kopiera/klistra in/dra/...)</p>
    <p>Och självklart kan du rita! Med hjälp av verktyg som pennan, den raka linjen, kurvverktyget, många former, flera penslar och deras olika färger och alternativ.</p>
    <p>Filtyper som stöds är PNG, JPEG och BMP.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Bu temel görüntü düzenleyici, bir görüntüyü yeniden boyutlandırabilir, kırpabilir veya döndürebilir, basit filtreler uygulayabilir, metin ekleyebilir veya sansürleyebilir ve resmin seçilen bir bölümünü değiştirebilir (kes/kopyala/yapıştır/sürükle/…)</p>
    <p>Ve elbette çizebilirsin! Kurşun kalem, düz çizgi, eğri aracı, birçok şekil, birkaç fırça ve bunların çeşitli renk ve seçenekleri gibi araçları kullanma.</p>
    <p>Desteklenen dosya türleri PNG, JPEG ve BMP'yi içerir.</p>
  </description>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2022-03-26">
      <description>
        <p>
          Version 1.0.0 improves rendering performance, which is visible when
          editing large images with a poor CPU.
        </p>
        <p lang="tr">Sürüm 1.0.0, büyük görüntüleri zayıf bir CPU ile düzenlerken görülebilen işleme performansını iyileştirir.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Version 1.0.0 förbättrar renderingsprestandan, vilket är synligt när du redigerar stora bilder med en dålig CPU.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Версия 1.0.0 улучшает производительность рендеринга, что заметно при редактировании больших изображений на слабом процессоре.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">A versão 1.0.0 melhora o desempenho de renderização, o que é visível ao editar imagens grandes com uma CPU de baixo desempenho.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Wersja 1.0.0 poprawia wydajność renderowania, co jest widoczne podczas edycji dużych obrazów przy wykorzystaniu słabego procesora.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Nieuw in versie 1.0.0: verbeterde weergaveprestaties tijdens het bewerken van grote afbeeldingen op een langzame cpu.</p>
        <p lang="ja">バージョン 1.0.0 では、レンダリングのパフォーマンスが向上しました。処理能力の低い CPU で大きな画像を編集すると、その違いをより体感できます。</p>
        <p lang="it">La versione 1.0.0 migliora le prestazioni di rendering, che sono visibili durante la modifica di immagini grandi con una CPU scadente.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Verzija 1.0.0 poboljšava performanse iscrtavanja, što je vidljivo pri uređivanju velikih slika sa slabim CPU-om.</p>
        <p lang="fr">La version 1.0.0 améliore les performances de rendu, ce qui est visible quand on édite de grandes images avec un CPU nul.</p>
        <p lang="eu">1.0.0 bertsioak errendatze-errendimendua hobetzen du, PUZ eskas baten bidez irudi handiak editatzean nabaritzen dena.</p>
        <p lang="es">La versión 1.0.0 mejora el rendimiento de la renderización, lo que es visible cuando se editan imágenes grandes con una CPU poco potente.</p>
        <p lang="de">Version 1.0.0 verbessert die Rendering-Leistung. Das macht sich besonders bemerkbar beim Bearbeiten großer Bilder mit einem schwachen Prozessor.</p>
        <p lang="da">Version 1.0.0 forbedrer visnings ydeevne, som kan ses når man redigere store billeder med en langsom CPU.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Verze 1.0.0 zlepšuje výkon vykreslování, což se projeví při úpravách velkých obrázků se slabým procesorem.</p>
        <p lang="ca">La versió 1.0.0 millora el rendiment de la representació, que és visible quan s'editen imatges grans amb una CPU modesta.</p>
        <p>
          You can now use the new "skew" tool, to tilt an image from a rectangle
          to a parallelogram. Such a deformation can be applied horizontally or
          vertically.
        </p>
        <p lang="tr">Artık bir görüntüyü bir dikdörtgenden bir paralel kenara eğmek için yeni "eğrilik" aracını kullanabilirsiniz. Böyle bir deformasyon yatay veya dikey olarak uygulanabilir.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Du kan nu använda det nya "skevningsverktyget" för att luta en bild från en rektangel till ett parallellogram. En sådan deformation kan appliceras horisontellt eller vertikalt.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Теперь вы можете использовать новый инструмент "Наклон", чтобы наклонить изображение из прямоугольника в параллелограмм. Такое изменение можно проводить горизонтально или вертикально.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Agora você pode usar a nova ferramenta "Inclinar" para modificar uma imagem de um retângulo para um paralelogramo. Essa deformação pode ser aplicada horizontalmente ou verticalmente.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Możesz teraz używać nowego narzędzia „Zniekształcacz”, aby przechylać obraz z prostokąta do równoległoboku. Taka deformacja może być zastosowana poziomo lub pionowo.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Je kunt nu het nieuwe rechtzetgereedschap gebruiken om schuingemaakte foto's recht te zetten. Dit kan zowel horizontaal als verticaal.</p>
        <p lang="ja">新しい "傾斜" ツールでは、四角形の画像を傾けて、平行四辺形の画像を作ることができます。このような変形は水平・垂直の両方向に適用可能です。</p>
        <p lang="it">Ora puoi usare il nuovo strumento "inclina", per inclinare un'immagine da un rettangolo a un parallelogramma. Tale deformazione può essere applicata orizzontalmente o verticalmente.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Sada se može koristiti novi alat „Ukosi” za naginjanje slike iz pravokutnika u paralelogram. Ta se deformacija može primijeniti vodoravno ili okomito.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Vous pouvez maintenant utiliser le nouvel outil "incliner", pour faire pencher une image, d'un rectangle vers un paralèllogramme.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Orain "okertu" tresna berria erabil dezakezu irudi bat laukizuzen batetik paralelogramo batera okertzeko. Deformazio hori horizontalean edo bertikalean aplika daiteke</p>
        <p lang="es">Ahora puede utilizar la nueva herramienta "sesgar", para inclinar una imagen de un rectángulo a un paralelogramo. Dicha deformación puede aplicarse horizontal o verticalmente.</p>
        <p lang="de">Sie können jetzt ein neues Werkzeug namens Verzerren verwenden, um ein Bild von einem Rechteck zu einem Parallelogramm zu neigen. So eine Verformung kann horizontal und vertikal angewendet werden.</p>
        <p lang="da">Du kan nu bruge det nye "Vrid" værktøj til at tilte til billede fra et rektangel til et parallelogram. Sådan en deformation kan påføres vandret eller lodret.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Nyní můžete použít nový nástroj "zkosení", který nakloní obrázek z obdélníku na rovnoběžník. Takovou deformaci lze použít ve vodorovném i svislém směru.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Ara podeu utilitzar la nova eina «Inclinar», per a inclinar una imatge des d'un rectangle a un paral·lelogram. Aquesta deformació es pot aplicar horitzontalment o verticalment.</p>
        <p>
          You can select tools with keyboard accelerators (Alt+letter). This may
          not work yet with languages using a non-latin alphabet.
        </p>
        <p lang="tr">Klavye hızlandırıcılı (Alt+harf) araçları seçebilirsiniz. Bu, latin olmayan bir alfabe kullanan dillerde henüz çalışmayabilir.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Du kan välja verktyg med tangentbordsacceleratorer (Alt+bokstav). Detta kanske inte fungerar ännu med språk som använder ett icke-latinskt alfabet.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Вы можете выбирать инструменты с помощью ускорителей клавиатуры (Alt+буква). Это ещё может не работать с языками, в которых используется нелатинский алфавит.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Você pode selecionar ferramentas com aceleradores de teclado (Alt+letra). Isso pode não funcionar ainda com idiomas que usam um alfabeto não-latino.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Możesz wybierać narzędzia za pomocą akceleratorów klawiaturowych (Alt + litera). Mogą one jeszcze nie działać w przypadku języków używających alfabetu innego niż łaciński.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Je kunt gereedschap kiezen met Alt+letter. Let op: mogelijk werkt dit nog niet goed in talen met een niet-Latijns alfabet.</p>
        <p lang="it">Puoi selezionare strumenti con acceleratori da tastiera (Alt+lettera). Questo potrebbe non funzionare ancora con le lingue usando un alfabeto non latino.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Alati se mogu birati pomoću tipkovnih prečaca (Alt+slovo]. Ovo možda još neće raditi s jezicima koji ne koriste latiničnu abecedu.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Vous pouvez activer les outils avec des accélérateurs clavier (Alt+lettre). Cela pourrait ne pas encore fonctionner avec les langues utilisant un alphabet non-latin.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Teklatu azeleragailuekin tresnak hauta ditzakezu (Alt+letra). Baliteke honek oraindik ez funtzionatzea latindarra ez den alfabetoa erabiltzen duten hizkuntzekin.</p>
        <p lang="es">Puede seleccionar herramientas con aceleradores de teclado (Alt+letra). Es posible que esto no funcione todavía con los idiomas que usan un alfabeto no latino.</p>
        <p lang="de">Sie können Werkzeuge mit Tastenkürzeln (Alt+Buchstabe) auswählen. Dies funktioniert möglicherweise noch nicht mit Sprachen, die ein nicht-lateinisches Alphabet verwenden.</p>
        <p>
          Pressing "ctrl" will display the cursor coordinates in a tooltip. If
          you do it while using a tool, it may display additional data, for
          example the dimensions of the shape you're drawing!
        </p>
        <p lang="tr">"Ctrl" tuşuna basmak, imleç koordinatlarını bir araç ipucunda görüntüler. Bunu bir araç kullanırken yaparsanız, örneğin çizdiğiniz şeklin boyutları gibi ek verileri görüntüleyebilir!</p>
        <p lang="sv">Om du trycker på "Ctrl" visas markörkoordinaterna i ett knappbeskrivning. Om du gör det när du använder ett verktyg kan det visa ytterligare data, till exempel dimensionerna på formen du ritar!</p>
        <p lang="ru">Нажатие «ctrl» отобразит координаты курсора в тултипе. Если вы сделаете это во время использования инструмента, то могут быть отображены дополнительные данные, например, размеры фигуры, которую вы рисуете!</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Ao pressionar "Ctrl", serão exibidas as coordenadas do cursor em uma dica de ferramenta. Se você fizer isso enquanto utiliza uma ferramenta, ela pode exibir dados adicionais, por exemplo, as dimensões da forma que você está desenhando!</p>
        <p lang="pl">Naciśnięcie „Ctrl” wyświetli współrzędne kursora w podpowiedzi. Jeśli zrobisz to podczas korzystania z narzędzia, może wyświetlić dodatkowe dane, na przykład wymiary rysowanego kształtu!</p>
        <p lang="nl">Druk op Ctrl om de cursorcoördinaten te tonen in een hulpballon. Als je dit doet tijdens het gebruik van een stuk gereedschap, dan wordt er tevens aanvullende informatie getoond, zoals de afmetingen.</p>
        <p lang="it">Premendo "ctrl" verranno visualizzate le coordinate del cursore in una descrizione del comando. Se lo fate durante l'utilizzo di uno strumento, potrebbe visualizzare dati aggiuntivi, ad esempio le dimensioni della forma che stai disegnando!</p>
        <p lang="hr">Pritiskom tipke „ctrl” prikazat će se koordinate kursora u opisu alata. Ako to učiniš dok koristiš alat, prikazat će se dodatni podaci, na primjer dimenzije oblika koji crtaš!</p>
        <p lang="fr">Presser "ctrl" affichera les coordonnées du curseur dans une info-bulle. Si vous le faites en utilisant un outil, ça pourrait afficher des données supplémentaires, comme par exemple les dimensions de la forme que vous dessinez !</p>
        <p lang="eu">"ctrl" sakatzean kurtsorearen koordenatuak bistaratuko dira. Tresna bat erabiltzen duzun bitartean egiten baduzu, baliteke datu gehigarriak bistaratzea, adibidez marrazten ari zaren formaren neurriak!</p>
        <p lang="es">Al pulsar "ctrl" se mostrarán las coordenadas del cursor en un consejo sobre la herramienta. Si lo hace mientras usa una herramienta, puede mostrar datos adicionales, por ejemplo, ¡las dimensiones de la forma que está dibujando!</p>
        <p lang="de">Drücken von "Strg" zeigt die Cursor-Koordinaten in einer Minihilfe an. Bei der Verwendung eines Werkzeugs kann es zusätzliche Infos anzeigen, wie beispielsweise die Abmessungen der gerade zu zeichnenden Form!</p>
        <p lang="cs">Stisknutím klávesy "ctrl" zobrazíte souřadnice kurzoru. Pokud to uděláte běhen práce s nástrojem, můžou se také zobrazit data navíc, například rozměry tvaru kterým kreslíte</p>
        <p>
          Pressing "shift", or "alt" when using a tool enables specific options,
          such as locking the direction for the "line" tool, or changing the
          filling style of a shape.
        </p>
        <p lang="tr">Bir araç kullanırken "shift" veya "alt" tuşuna basmak, "çizgi" aracının yönünü kilitleme veya bir şeklin doldurma stilini değiştirme gibi belirli seçenekleri etkinleştirir.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Genom att trycka på "Skift" eller "Alt" när du använder ett verktyg aktiveras specifika alternativ, till exempel att låsa riktningen för "linjeverktyget" eller ändra fyllningsstilen för en form.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Нажатие «shift» или «alt» при использовании инструмента включает определенные параметры, такие как закреплённое направление для инструмента «линия» или изменение стиля заливки формы.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Pressionar "Shift" ou "Alt" ao usar uma ferramenta ativa opções específicas, como bloquear a direção da ferramenta "Linha" ou alterar o estilo de preenchimento de uma forma.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Naciśnięcie klawisza „Shift” lub „Alt” podczas korzystania z narzędzia włącza określone opcje, takie jak blokowanie kierunku narzędzia „Linia” lub zmiana stylu wypełniania kształtu.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Door op Ctrl, Shift op Alt te drukken bij gebruik van een gereedschap, kun je verschillende opties instellen, zoals ‘Toevoegen aan selectie’ bij het selectiegereedschap.</p>
        <p lang="it">Premendo "shift" o "alt" quando si utilizza uno strumento si abilitano opzioni specifiche, come bloccare la direzione per lo strumento "linea" o cambiare il riempimento stile di una forma.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Pritiskom tipke „shift” ili „alt” za vrijeme korištenja alata, omogućuju se određene opcije, kao što je zaključavanje smjera za alat „crta” ili mijenjanje stila ispunjavanja oblika.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Presser "maj" ou "alt" en utilisant un outil activera désormais des options spécifiques, tel que verrouiller la direction pour l'outil "ligne", ou changer le style de remplissage d'une forme.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Tresna bat erabiltzean "shift", edo "alt" sakatzean aukera zehatzak gaitzen dira, hala nola, "lerroa" tresnaren norabidea blokeatzea edo forma baten betetze estiloa aldatzea.</p>
        <p lang="es">Al pulsar "mayúsculas" o "alt" cuando se usa una herramienta se activan opciones específicas, como bloquear la dirección de la herramienta "línea" o cambiar el estilo de relleno de una forma.</p>
        <p lang="de">Das Drücken von "Shift" oder "Alt" beim Verwenden eines Werkzeuges aktiviert bestimmte Optionen, wie z.B. das Sperren der Richtung beim Werkzeug "Linie" oder das Wechseln der Füllmethode bei Formen.</p>
        <p>
          Using the "scale" tool, you may optionally set the new size as a
          relative percentage rather than an absolute value in pixels.
        </p>
        <p lang="tr">"Ölçek" aracını kullanarak, isteğe bağlı olarak yeni boyutu piksel cinsinden mutlak bir değer yerine göreli yüzde olarak ayarlayabilirsiniz.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Med verktyget "skala" kan du välja att ställa in den nya storleken som en relativ procentandel i stället för ett absolut värde i pixlar.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Используя инструмент «Масштаб», вы можете дополнительно устанавливать новый размер в процентах, а не только в виде абсолютных значений в пикселях.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Ao usar a ferramenta "Escala" você pode, ocasionalmente, definir o novo tamanho como uma porcentagem relativa em vez de um valor absoluto em pixels.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Używając narzędzia „Skalowanie”, możesz opcjonalnie ustawić nowy rozmiar jako względny procent, a nie wartość bezwzględną w pikselach.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Met het vernieuwde schaalgereedschap kun je afmetingen instellen door een percentage op te geven in plaats van pixelwaardes.</p>
        <p lang="ja">"伸縮" ツールを使うと、従来の直接的なピクセル指定に加え、相対的な比率で自由に画像サイズを変更できます。</p>
        <p lang="it">Utilizzando lo strumento "scala", puoi opzionalmente impostare la nuova dimensione con relativa percentuale piuttosto che un valore assoluto in pixel.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Pomoću alata „Skaliraj” može se po želji postaviti nova veličina kao relativan postotak, umjesto kao apsolutna vrijednost u pikselima.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Avec l'outil "redimensionner", vous pouvez optionnellement donner la nouvelle taille sous la forme d'un pourcentage relatif, plutôt qu'une valeur absolue.</p>
        <p lang="eu">"Eskala" tresna erabiliz, aukeran ezar dezakezu tamaina berria portzentaje erlatibo gisa eta ez pixeletan balio absolutu gisa.</p>
        <p lang="es">Con la herramienta "escala", puede establecer opcionalmente el nuevo tamaño como un porcentaje relativo en lugar de un valor absoluto en píxeles.</p>
        <p lang="de">Mit dem Werkzeug "Skalieren" können Sie die neue Größe optional als relativen Prozentsatz statt als absoluten Wert in Pixeln festlegen.</p>
        <p lang="da">Når du bruger "Skaler" værktøjet, kan du valgfrit indstille den nye størrelse som en relativ procentdel frem for en absolut værdi i pixels.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Pomocí nástroje "měřítko" můžete volitelně nastavit novou velikost jako relativní procento, nikoli jako absolutní hodnotu v pixelech.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Utilitzant l'eina «Escalar», podeu establir opcionalment la mida nova com a percentatge relatiu en lloc d'un valor absolut en píxels.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.5" date="2021-12-04">
      <description>
        <!-- very generic release notes i use for ALL minor updates, please -->
        <!-- translate this one! -->
        <p>
          Version 0.8.5 features several minor bug fixes, and various new
          translations.
        </p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">0.8.5 版修復了一些小的錯誤，增加了新的翻譯。</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">0.8.5 版修复了一些小的错误，增加了新的翻译。</p>
        <p lang="tr">Sürüm 0.8.5, birkaç küçük hata düzeltmesi ve çeşitli yeni çeviriler içermektedir.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Version 0.8.5 innehåller ett flertal mindre felkorrigeringar, och diverse nya översättningar.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Версия 0.8.5 содержит несколько мелких исправлений и несколько новых переводов.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">A versão 0.8.5 apresenta diversas correções de erros e várias traduções.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Wersja 0.8.5 zawiera kilka drobnych poprawek błędów i nowe tłumaczenia.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Versie 0.8.5 bevat verschillende kleine foutoplossingen en nieuwe vertalingen.</p>
        <p lang="ko">버전 0.8.5에는 몇 가지 사소한 버그 수정과 다양한 새로운 번역이 있습니다.</p>
        <p lang="ja">バージョン 0.8.5 では、いくつかのバグ修正と、新しい言語の追加が行われました。</p>
        <p lang="it">La versione 0.8.5 presenta diverse correzioni di bug minori e varie nuove traduzioni. </p>
        <p lang="hu">A 0.8.5 verzió számos kisebb hibajavítást, és új felhasználói felület nyelvi fordításokat hozott.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Verzija 0.8.5 sadrži nekoliko ispravki manjih programskih grešaka i razne nove prijevode.</p>
        <p lang="fr">La version 0.8.5 comporte plusieurs correctifs de bugs mineurs, et diverses nouvelles traductions.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Versio 0.8.5 sisältää useita pieniä virhekorjauksia ja uusia käännöksiä.</p>
        <p lang="eu">0.8.5 bertsioak errore txiki batzuen zuzenketa eta itzulpen berriak biltzen ditu.</p>
        <p lang="es">La versión 0.8.5 presenta varias correcciones de errores menores y varias traducciones nuevas.</p>
        <p lang="de">Die Version 0.8.5 enthält mehrere kleine Fehlerbehebungen und verschiedene neue Übersetzungen.</p>
        <p lang="da">Version 0.8.5 har adskillige mindre fejlrettelser og diverse nye oversættelser.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Verze 0.8.5 obsahuje několik drobných oprav chyb a různé nové překlady.</p>
        <p lang="ca">La versió 0.8.5 presenta diverses correccions d'errors menors i diverses traduccions noves.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <developer_name translatable="no">Romain F. T.</developer_name>
  <update_contact>rrroschan@gmail.com</update_contact>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/maoschanz/drawing/issues</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://maoschanz.github.io/drawing</url>
  <url type="donation">https://paypal.me/maoschannz</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">
        https://raw.githubusercontent.com/maoschanz/drawing/master/docs/screenshots/1.0/gnome_menu.png
      </image>
      <!-- Caption of a screenshot, for appstores -->
      <caption>
        The window and its primary menu
      </caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Pencere ve birincil menüsü</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Fönstret och dess primära meny</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Окно и его главное меню</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">A janela e seu menu principal</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Okno i jego główne menu</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Het venster en hoofdmenu</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">창 및 기본 메뉴</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">ウィンドウと主要メニュー</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La finestra e il suo menu principale</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Prozor i njegov glavni izbornik</caption>
      <caption lang="he">החלון והתפריט הראשי שלו</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">La fenêtre et son menu principal</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Leihoa eta bere menu nagusia</caption>
      <caption lang="es">La ventana y su menú principal</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Das Fenster mit dem Hauptmenü</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Vinduet og dets primære menu</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Okno a jeho hlavní menu</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">La finestra i el seu menú principal</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">
        https://raw.githubusercontent.com/maoschanz/drawing/master/docs/screenshots/1.0/gnome_selection.png
      </image>
      <!-- Caption of a screenshot, for appstores -->
      <caption>
        The selection and the actions associated with it
      </caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Seçim ve onunla ilişkili eylemler</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Markeringen och de åtgärder som associeras med den</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Выделение и связанные с ним действия</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">A seleção e as ações associadas a ela</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Zaznaczanie i związane z nim czynności</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">De selectie en bijbehorende acties</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">선택 및 관련 작업</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">画像の選択とアクション</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La selezione e le azioni ad essa associate</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Odabir i s njime povezane radnje</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">La sélection et les actions qui y sont associées</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Hautapena eta horrekin lotutako ekintzak</caption>
      <caption lang="es">La selección y las acciones asociadas a ella</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Die Auswahl und die damit verknüpften Aktionen</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Markeringen og de handlinger den er tilknyttet</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Výběr a akce s ním spojené</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">La selecció i les accions associades</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">
        https://raw.githubusercontent.com/maoschanz/drawing/master/docs/screenshots/1.0/gnome_tools_preview.png
      </image>
      <!-- Caption of a screenshot, for appstores -->
      <caption>
        Zooming in various shapes
      </caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Çeşitli şekillerde yakınlaştırma</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Zooma i olika figurer</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Масштабирование различных форм</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Ampliando em várias formas</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Powiększanie w różnych kształtach</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Verschillende soorten zoom</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">다양한 모양 확대</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">ズーム表示</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Zoom in varie forme</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Zumiranje u raznim oblicima</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Zoomer sur divers formes</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Hainbat formaren zooma</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Hacer zoom de varias formas</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Zoomen in verschiedenen Formen</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Zooming i diverse forme</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Přiblížení v různých tvarech</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Amplia en formes diverses</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">
        https://raw.githubusercontent.com/maoschanz/drawing/master/docs/screenshots/1.0/gnome_new.png
      </image>
      <!-- Caption of a screenshot, for appstores -->
      <caption>
        The "new image" menu opened
      </caption>
      <caption lang="tr">"Yeni resim" menüsü açıldı</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Menyn "Ny bild" öppnas</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Меню "Новое изображение" было открыто</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">O menu "Nova imagem" aberto</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Otworzyło się menu „nowy obraz”</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Het menu ‘Nieuwe afbeelding’</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">"새 이미지" 메뉴가 열립니다</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">"新しい画像" メニュー</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La "nuova immagine" menu aperto</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Izbornik „Nova slika” otvoren</caption>
      <caption lang="he">נפתח תפריט „תמונה חדשה”</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Le menu "nouvelle image" ouvert</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">"irudi berria" menu irekia</caption>
      <caption lang="es">El menú de "imagen nueva" se abrió</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Menü "Neues Bild" geöffnet</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Den åbnede menu "nyt billede"</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Otevřeno menu "nový obrázek" </caption>
      <caption lang="ca">S'ha obert el menú «nova imatge»</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <translation type="gettext">drawing</translation>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.github.maoschanz.drawing.desktop</launchable>
  <provides>
    <binary>drawing</binary>
  </provides>
</component>