<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <description>
    <p>Browse the Internet in private without leaving a trace of history on your computer. Ephemeral is a stripped down private browser that's perfect for avoiding persistent cookies or web trackers. Close the window and all traces of your browsing are removed from your device.</p>
    <p>Handy features:</p>
    <p>Useful keyboard shortcuts and gestures:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Navigate back or forward with a two-finger swipe on your trackpad</li>
      <li lang="uk">Переходьте вперед чи назад провівши двома пальцями по вашому трекпаду</li>
      <li lang="pt">Navegue para trás ou para a frente deslizando dois dedos no trackpad</li>
      <li lang="es">Avance o retroceda deslizando dos dedos en el panel táctil</li>
      <li>Open page in another browser with Ctrl+O</li>
      <li>Add a website to the URL suggestions with the ⭐️ icon or Ctrl+D</li>
      <li lang="uk">Додайте вебсайт до пропозицій URL-адрес натисканням на піктограму ⭐️ або Ctrl+D</li>
      <li lang="tr">⭐️ simgesi veya Ctrl + D ile URL önerilenlere ekleyin</li>
      <li lang="pt">Adicione um website às sugestões de endereço com o ícone ⭐️ ou Ctrl + D</li>
      <li lang="nl">Voeg een website toe aan de URL-suggesties middels het ⭐️-pictogram of Ctrl+D</li>
      <li lang="it">Aggiungi un sito web ai suggeriti con l'icona ⭐️ o Ctrl+D</li>
      <li lang="fr">Ajoutez un site Web aux suggestions d'URL avec l'icône ⭐️ ou Ctrl+D</li>
      <li lang="es">Añada un sitio web a las sugerencias de URL con el icono ⭐️ o Ctrl+D</li>
      <li>Find text on the page with Ctrl+F</li>
      <li lang="uk">Шукайте текст на сторінці натиснувши Ctrl+F</li>
      <li lang="tr">Ctrl+F ile sayfadaki metni bulun</li>
      <li lang="pt">Encontre o texto na página com Ctrl + F</li>
      <li lang="nl">Zoek naar tekst op een pagina middels Ctrl+F</li>
      <li lang="it">Trova testo nella pagina con Ctrl+F</li>
      <li lang="fr">Recherchez du texte sur la page avec Ctrl+F</li>
      <li lang="es">Busque texto en la página con Ctrl+F</li>
      <li>Zoom in or out with Ctrl+Plus and Ctrl+Minus</li>
      <li lang="uk">Збільшуйте або зменшуйте масштаб натисканням Ctrl+Плюс and Ctrl+Мінус</li>
      <li lang="pt">Aumente ou diminua o zoom com Ctrl+Mais e Ctrl+Menos</li>
      <li lang="es">Amplíe o reduzca la visualización mediante Ctrl + y Ctrl −</li>
      <li>Open a new window with Ctrl+N</li>
      <li lang="uk">Відкривайте нове вікно натисканням Ctrl+N</li>
      <li lang="pt">Abra uma nova janela com Ctrl+N</li>
      <li lang="es">Abra una ventana nueva con Ctrl + N</li>
      <li>Hit Ctrl+W to close the current window or Ctrl+Q to quit all windows</li>
      <li lang="uk">Натисніть Ctrl+W, щоб закрити поточне вікно чи Ctrl+Q, щоб закрити усі вікна</li>
      <li lang="tr">Geçerli pencereyi kapatmak için Ctrl + W tuşlarına veya tüm pencerelerden çıkmak için Ctrl + Q tuşlarına basın.</li>
      <li lang="ru">Нажмите Ctrl+W, чтобы закрыть текущее окно, или Ctrl+Q, чтобы закрыть все окна.</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Aperte Ctrl+W para fechar a janela atual ou Ctrl+Q para fechar todas as janelas</li>
      <li lang="pt">Prima Ctrl+W para fechar a janela atual ou Ctrl+Q para fechar todas as janelas</li>
      <li lang="pl">Naciśnij Ctrl + W aby zamknąć aktywne okno lub Ctrl + Q aby zamknąć wszystkie okna</li>
      <li lang="nl">Gebruik Ctrl+W om het huidige venster te sluiten of Ctrl+Q om alle vensters te sluiten</li>
      <li lang="it">Premi Ctrl+Q per chiudere tutte le finestre mentre Ctrl+W per quella corrente</li>
      <li lang="fr">Appuyez sur Ctrl+W pour fermer la fenêtre courante ou Ctrl+Q pour quitter toutes les fenêtres.</li>
      <li lang="es">Presione Ctrl + W para cerrar la ventana actual, o bien, Ctrl + Q para cerrarlas todas</li>
      <li lang="de">Drücken Sie Strg+W um das aktuelle Fenster zu schließen oder Strg+Q um alle Fenster zu schließen</li>
      <li lang="ca">Premeu Ctrl+W per tancar la finestra actual o Ctrl+Q per tancar-les totes</li>
    </ul>
    <ul>
      <li>Navigate back or forward with a two-finger swipe on your trackpad</li>
      <li>Open page in another browser with Ctrl+O</li>
      <li>Add a website to the URL suggestions with the ⭐️ icon or Ctrl+D</li>
      <li>Find text on the page with Ctrl+F</li>
      <li>Zoom in or out with Ctrl+Plus and Ctrl+Minus</li>
      <li>Open a new window with Ctrl+N</li>
      <li>Hit Ctrl+W to close the current window or Ctrl+Q to quit all windows</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Ephemeral protects you in five key ways:</p>
    <p>1️⃣ Always incognito. From the second you open an Ephemeral window until you close it (or hit the Erase button), Ephemeral is in private browsing mode. That means history, cookies, local storage, passwords, etc. are all blown away as soon as you leave.</p>
    <p>2️⃣ Sandboxed. Each window uses a separate instance of the browser engine, domains inside each window are rendered using different processes, and the engine’s processes are sandboxed from one another to keep you safe. Sign into a service in one window, and sites in other windows will have no idea.</p>
    <p>3️⃣ No third-party cookies. Ephemeral blocks cookies from third-party sources, which cuts down on advertising cookies and other unwanted forms of cross-site tracking.</p>
    <p>4️⃣ No telemetry. Ephemeral does not touch the network until you explicitly load a web page or perform a search. Even then, no usage data is ever collected—I have no idea what you do with Ephemeral, and I don't want to know!</p>
    <p>5️⃣️ Ephemeral uses DuckDuckGo—the search engine that doesn’t track you—by default to avoid as much Google tracking as possible. You can also choose StartPage.com from the menu if that’s your preference, or even set your own entirely custom search engine.</p>
    <p>Make privacy a habit by opening links in Ephemeral by default, knowing you can always jump back into a traditional browser like Epiphany, Firefox, Chrome, Opera, Brave—or any other installed browser—with one click. Perfect in case you want to use saved passwords or other extensions.</p>
    <p>Remember, Ephemeral and any browser's incognito or private mode can only do so much: they mitigate some tracking and don't store data on your device, but they won't stop your ISP, government, or determined websites from tracking you.</p>
    <p>For the best protection, always use a VPN.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Navegueu per Internet en mode privat sense deixar restes a l'historial del vostre ordinador. Ephemeral és un navegador privat simplificat perfecte per evitar les cookies persistents i els rastrejadors. Tanqueu la finestra i totes les traces de la vostra navegació s'esborraran de l'ordinador.</p>
    <p>Característiques útils:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Obriu fàcilment pàgines a qualsevol altre navegador instal·lat</li>
      <li>Cerqueu directament des de la barra d'adreces</li>
      <li>Escolliu entre els cercador respectuosos amb la privadesa del menú</li>
    </ul>
    <ul>
      <li>Premeu Ctrl+W per tancar la finestra actual o Ctrl+Q per tancar-les totes</li>
    </ul>
    <p>1️⃣ Sempre d'incògnit. Des de l'instant que obriu una finestra d'Ephemeral fins que la tanqueu (o premeu «Esborra»), Ephemeral està en mode de navegació privada: l'historial, les «galetes», l'emmagatzemament local, les contrasenyes… tot s'ho emporta el vent tan prompte com eixiu del programa.</p>
    <p>4️⃣ Res de telemetria. Ephemeral no toca la xarxa fins que carregueu explícitament una pàgina web o realitzeu una cerca. Encara llavors, no se guarda cap dada d'ús: no tinc cap idea de què féu amb Ephemeral, i no tinc cap interés en saber-ho!</p>
    <p>Teniu present que Ephemeral i els modes privats de qualsevol altre navegador tenen límits: tot i que disminueixen algunes formes de rastreig i prevenen l'emmagatzemametent local de dades, no poden parar el vostre proveïdor de servei, el govern o determinats llocs web.</p>
    <p>Per la millor protección, utilitzeu sempre una VPN.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Suchen Sie privat im Internet, ohne Spuren auf Ihrem Computer zu hinterlassen. Ephemeral ist ein vereinfachter, privater Browser - perfekt um bleibende Cookies oder Verfolger zu vermeiden. Schließen Sie das Fenster und alle Spuren werden von Ihrem Gerät entfernt.</p>
    <p>Nützliche Funktionen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Öffnen Sie Seiten mühelos in jedem anderen installierten Browser</li>
      <li>Suchen Sie direkt in der URL-Leiste</li>
    </ul>
    <ul>
      <li>Drücken Sie Strg+W um das aktuelle Fenster zu schließen oder Strg+Q um alle Fenster zu schließen</li>
    </ul>
    <p>1️⃣ Immer inkognito. Von der Sekunde, in der Sie ein Ephemeral-Fenster öffnen, bis Sie es schließen (oder den Löschen-Button drücken) ist Ephemeral im privaten Modus. Das heißt, dass der Verlauf, Cookies, lokal gespeicherte Passwörter und sonstiges weg sind, sobald Sie ihn beenden.</p>
    <p>4️⃣ Keine Telemetrie. Ephemeral greift nicht auf das Netzwerk zu, bis Sie explizit eine Webseite aufrufen oder nach etwas suchen. Selbst dann werden nie Daten gesammelt—Ich habe keine Ahnung, was Sie mit Ephemeral machen und ich will es auch nicht wissen!</p>
    <p>Denken Sie daran, dass Ephemeral und der Inkognito-Modus oder private Modus in jedem anderen Browser nur so viel tun können: Sie können die Verfolgung ein wenig eingrenzen und keine Daten auf Ihrem Gerät speichern, aber sie werden Ihren Internetanbieter, die Regierung oder hartnäckigere Seiten nicht davon abhalten, Sie zu verfolgen.</p>
    <p>Benutzen Sie immer ein VPN für den besten Schutz.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Explore Internet en privado sin dejar rastros de histórico en el equipo. Ephemeral es un navegador personal simplificado, ideal para rehuir de las «cookies» persistentes y los rastreadores. Al cerrar la ventana, todos los vestigios de su navegación desaparecerán del dispositivo.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades útiles:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Abra con facilidad sitios en otros navegadores instalados</li>
      <li>Realice búsquedas directamente desde el cuadro de URL</li>
      <li>Escoja un buscador respetuoso de su privacidad en el menú</li>
      <li>Desactive o vuelva a activar JavaScript rápidamente desde el menú</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Atajos de teclado y gestos útiles:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Avance o retroceda deslizando dos dedos en el panel táctil</li>
      <li>Añada un sitio web a las sugerencias de URL con el icono ⭐️ o Ctrl+D</li>
      <li>Busque texto en la página con Ctrl+F</li>
      <li>Amplíe o reduzca la visualización mediante Ctrl + y Ctrl −</li>
      <li>Abra una ventana nueva con Ctrl + N</li>
      <li>Presione Ctrl + W para cerrar la ventana actual, o bien, Ctrl + Q para cerrarlas todas</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Ephemeral lo protege de cinco maneras fundamentales:</p>
    <p>1️⃣ Siempre incógnito. Desde el instante que abre una ventana de Ephemeral hasta que la cierra (o pulsa en «Borrar»), Ephemeral está en modo de navegación privada: el histórico, las «cookies», el almacenamiento local, las contraseñas… todo se lo lleva el viento tan pronto como salga del programa.</p>
    <p>2️⃣ Confinado. Cada ventana utiliza una instancia separada del motor del navegador, los dominios dentro de cada ventana se generan mediante diferentes procesos, y los procesos del motor se mantienen aislados unos de otros para asegurar su privacidad. Acceda a un servicio en una ventana, y las demás ventanas no se darán cuenta de lo ocurrido.</p>
    <p>3️⃣ Sin «cookies» de terceros. Ephemeral bloquea las «cookies» de orígenes terceros, lo que reduce la publicidad persistente y otras formas indeseables de rastreo a través de varios sitios.</p>
    <p>4️⃣ Nada de telemetría. Ephemeral no toca la red hasta que usted explícitamente cargue una página web o realice una búsqueda. Aun entonces, no se recopila ningún dato de uso: no tengo idea de lo que hace con Ephemeral, ¡y no me interesa enterarme!</p>
    <p>5️⃣️ Ephemeral utiliza DuckDuckGo —⁠el buscador que no le rastrea— de manera predeterminada para evitar a Google tanto como se pueda. Si lo prefiere, también puede elegir StartPage.com desde el menú o incluso definir su propio buscador.</p>
    <p>Haga de la privacidad un hábito al abrir enlaces en Ephemeral por omisión, sabiendo que basta una sola pulsación del ratón para volver a un navegador tradicional como Epiphany, Firefox, Chrome, Opera, Brave o cualquier otro que haya instalado. Esto es práctico si quiere hacer uso de contraseñas guardadas u otras extensiones.</p>
    <p>Tenga presente que Ephemeral y los modos privados de cualquier otro navegador tienen límites: aunque mitigan ciertas formas de rastreo y previenen el almacenamiento local de datos, no pueden contra su proveedor de servicio, el gobierno o sitios web tenaces.</p>
    <p>Para la mejor protección, utilice siempre una VPN.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Naviguez sur Internet en privé sans laisser de traces d'historique sur votre ordinateur. Ephemeral est un navigateur privé épuré qui est parfait pour éviter les cookies persistants ou les traqueurs sur le web. Fermez la fenêtre et toutes les traces de votre navigation sont supprimées de votre appareil.</p>
    <p>Fonctions pratiques :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ouvrez facilement des pages dans n'importe quel autre navigateur installé</li>
      <li>Cherchez directement dans la barre d'URL</li>
      <li>Choisissez parmi les moteurs de recherche respectueux de la vie privée dans le menu</li>
      <li>Désactivez ou réactivez rapidement JavaScript dans le menu</li>
    </ul>
    <ul>
      <li>Ajoutez un site Web aux suggestions d'URL avec l'icône ⭐️ ou Ctrl+D</li>
      <li>Recherchez du texte sur la page avec Ctrl+F</li>
      <li>Appuyez sur Ctrl+W pour fermer la fenêtre courante ou Ctrl+Q pour quitter toutes les fenêtres.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Ephemeral vous protège de cinq façons principales :</p>
    <p>1️⃣ Toujours incognito. Dès que vous ouvrez une fenêtre Ephemeral et jusqu'à ce que vous la fermiez (ou appuyez sur le bouton Effacer), Ephemeral est en mode navigation privée.Cela signifie que l'historique, les cookies, le stockage local, les mots de passe, etc. sont effacés dès que vous partez.</p>
    <p>4️⃣ Pas de télémétrie. Ephemeral ne touche pas le réseau tant que vous n'avez pas explicitement chargé une page Web ou effectué une recherche. Même là, aucune donnée d'utilisation n'est jamais recueillie — Je n'ai aucune idée de ce que vous faites avec Ephemeral, et je ne veux pas savoir !</p>
    <p>N'oubliez pas qu'Ephemeral et le mode incognito ou privé de n'importe quel navigateur ne peuvent pas faire grand-chose : ils atténuent le suivi et ne stockent pas de données sur votre appareil, mais ils n'empêchent pas votre FAI, le gouvernement ou des sites web déterminés de vous suivre.</p>
    <p>Pour une protection optimale, utilisez toujours un VPN.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Naviga il web in privato senza lasciare traccia della cronologia del tuo computer. Ephemeral è un browser per la navigazione privata ridotto all'essenziale che è perfetto per evitare cookie persistenti o web tracking. Chiudi la finestra e tutte le tracce della tua navigazione verranno rimosse dal tuo dispositivo.</p>
    <p>Funzioni utili:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Apre facilmente le pagine in ogni altro browser</li>
      <li>Effettua ricerche direttamente dalla barra di navigazione</li>
      <li>Scegli nel menu tra i motori di ricerca che rispettano la privacy</li>
      <li>Disattiva e ri-attiva JavaScript in modo rapido dal menu</li>
    </ul>
    <ul>
      <li>Aggiungi un sito web ai suggeriti con l'icona ⭐️ o Ctrl+D</li>
      <li>Trova testo nella pagina con Ctrl+F</li>
      <li>Premi Ctrl+Q per chiudere tutte le finestre mentre Ctrl+W per quella corrente</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Ephemeral ti protegge in cinque modi chiave:</p>
    <p>1️⃣ Sempre in incognito. Dall'istante in cui apri una finestra di Ephemeral finché non la chiudi (o premi il tasto Elimina), Ephemeral è in modalità navigazione in incognito. Questo significa che la cronologia, i cookie, l'archiviazione locale, le password, ecc... verranno tutti spazzati via non appena te ne vai.</p>
    <p>4️⃣ Nessuna telemetria. Ephemeral non tocca la rete fino a che non sei tu a caricare esplicitamente una pagina od effettuare una ricerca. Anche in questo caso, nessun dato di utilizzo viene raccolto — non ho idea e non voglio sapere di cosa tu faccia con Ephemeral!</p>
    <p>Ricorda, Ephemeral ed ogni altro browser in modalità in incognito o privata può fare solo questo: attenua il tracciamento e non memorizza i dati sul tuo dispositivo, ma non impedisce al tuo ISP, al tuo governo o a determinati siti di tracciarti.</p>
    <p>Per una protezione migliore utilizza sempre una VPN.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Surf op het internet zonder ook maar iets achter te laten op je computer. Ephemeral is een eenvoudige privé-webbrowser die gemaakt is voor het vermijden van permanente cookies of websites die je volgen. Sluit het venster en al je surfgedrag wordt verwijderd van je apparaat.</p>
    <p>Handige functies:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Open pagina's snel in een andere geïnstalleerde browser</li>
      <li>Zoek direct vanuit de locatiebalk</li>
      <li>Kies een privacy-respecterende zoekmachine in het menu</li>
      <li>Schakel JavaScript snel in en uit middels het menu</li>
    </ul>
    <ul>
      <li>Voeg een website toe aan de URL-suggesties middels het ⭐️-pictogram of Ctrl+D</li>
      <li>Zoek naar tekst op een pagina middels Ctrl+F</li>
      <li>Gebruik Ctrl+W om het huidige venster te sluiten of Ctrl+Q om alle vensters te sluiten</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Ephemeral beschermt je op vijf manieren:</p>
    <p>1️⃣ Altijd privé. Vanaf het moment dat je Ephemeral opent totdat je afsluit (of op de knop Wissen drukt) staat Ephemeral in privémodus. Dat betekent dat je geschiedenis, cookies, lokale opslag, wachtwoorden, etc. gewist worden zodra je de browser afsluit.</p>
    <p>4️⃣ Geen telemetrie. Ephemeral doet niks met je netwerk totdat je ervoor kiest om een webpagina te laden of een zoekopdracht uit te voeren. En zelfs dan worden er geen gebruiksgegevens verzameld. Ik heb geen idee wat je doet met Ephemeral en ik wil het niet weten ook!</p>
    <p>Let op: Ephemeral en andere browsers met een privé-/incognitomodus kunnen niet alles voorkomen. De meeste manieren van volgen worden vermeden en er wordt niks opgeslagen op je apparaat, maar je provider, overheid of bepaalde daarvoor bestemde websites kunnen je nog steeds volgen.</p>
    <p>Als je dat ook wilt voorkomen, gebruik dan een VPN.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Przeglądaj internet prywatnie bez zostawiania śladu na Twoim komputerze. Ephemeral jest odchudzoną przeglądarką idealną do unikania trwałych ciasteczek oraz trackerów. Po zamknięciu okna wszystkie ślady Twojego przeglądania zostają usunięte z komputera.</p>
    <p>Przydatne funkcje:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Z łatwością otwieraj strony w innych zainstalowanych przeglądarkach</li>
      <li>Wyszukuj prosto z paska adresu</li>
      <li>Wybieraj spomiędzy wyszukiwarek szanujących Twoją prywatność</li>
    </ul>
    <ul>
      <li>Naciśnij Ctrl + W aby zamknąć aktywne okno lub Ctrl + Q aby zamknąć wszystkie okna</li>
    </ul>
    <p>1️⃣ Zawsze incognito. Od chwili uruchomienia Ephemeral aż do jego zamknięcia (albo kliknięcia przycisku Wymaż) przeglądarka jest w trybie prywatnym. Oznacza to że historia, ciasteczka, lokalne pliki stron, hasła itd. są uprzątnięte od razu, gdy wychodzisz.</p>
    <p>4️⃣ Żadnej telemetrii. Ephemeral nie łączy się z internetem dopóki nie załadujesz strony internetowej lub nie wykonasz wyszukiwania. Nawet wtedy żadne informacje na temat użytkowania nie są zbierane — nie mam pojęcia, co robisz z Ephemeral i nie chcę tego wiedzieć!</p>
    <p>Pamiętaj, Ephemeral czy tryb prywatny jakiejkolwiek innej przeglądarki nie może wszystkiego: blokuje część śledzenia i nie przechowuje danych na Twoim urządzeniu, ale nie powstrzyma Twojego dostawcy, rządu czy najbardziej upartych stron przed śledzeniem Cię.</p>
    <p>Dla pełnej ochrony zawsze korzystaj z VPN.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Navegue na Internet em privado sem deixar vestígios ou histórico no computador. O Ephemeral é um navegador privado despojado que é perfeito para evitar cookies persistentes ou rastreadores da web. Feche a janela e todos os vestígios da sua navegação serão removidos do seu dispositivo.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades úteis:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Abra facilmente páginas em qualquer outro navegador instalado</li>
      <li>Pesquise diretamente da barra de endereço</li>
      <li>Escolher entre motores de busca que respeitam a privacidade a partir do menu</li>
      <li>Desativar ou reativar rapidamente o JavaScript a partir do menu</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Atalhos e gestos de teclado úteis:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Navegue para trás ou para a frente deslizando dois dedos no trackpad</li>
      <li>Adicione um website às sugestões de endereço com o ícone ⭐️ ou Ctrl + D</li>
      <li>Encontre o texto na página com Ctrl + F</li>
      <li>Aumente ou diminua o zoom com Ctrl+Mais e Ctrl+Menos</li>
      <li>Abra uma nova janela com Ctrl+N</li>
      <li>Prima Ctrl+W para fechar a janela atual ou Ctrl+Q para fechar todas as janelas</li>
    </ul>
    <p>O Ephemeral protege-o de cinco maneiras chave:</p>
    <p>1️⃣ Sempre incógnito. Desde o segundo em que abre uma Janela Ephemeral até a fechar (ou premir o botão Apagar), o Ephemeral está em modo de navegação privada. Isto significa que todo o histórico, cookies, armazenamento local, palavras-passe, etc. são apagados assim que sair.</p>
    <p>2️⃣ Em sandbox. Cada janela usa uma instância separada do mecanismo do navegador, os domínios dentro de cada janela são renderizados usando processos diferentes e os processos do mecanismo são isolados um do outro para mantê-lo seguro. Inicie sessão de um serviço numa janela e os websites das outras janelas não terão ideia.</p>
    <p>3️⃣ Sem cookies de terceiros. O Ephemeral bloqueia cookies de terceiros, o que reduz cookies provindos de anúncios e outros modos de rastreio com dados cruzados.</p>
    <p>4️⃣ Sem telemetria. O Ephemeral não utiliza ligação de internet até que explicitamente abra uma página da web ou realize uma pesquisa. Mesmo assim, nenhum dado será recolhido—Não tenho ideia do que fará com o Ephemeral, e não quero saber!</p>
    <p>5️⃣️ O Ephemeral utiliza o DuckDuckGo—motor de busca que não o segue por predefinição para evitar o maior número possível de seguimentos no Google. Também pode escolher o StartPage.com a partir do menu se for essa a sua preferência, ou mesmo definir o seu próprio motor de busca totalmente personalizado.</p>
    <p>Faça da privacidade um hábito ao abrir ligações no Ephemeral por predefinição, ao saber que pode sempre saltar para um navegador tradicional como Epiphany, Firefox, Chrome, Opera, Brave—ou qualquer outro navegador instalado - com um clique. Perfeito no caso de querer utilizar palavras-passe guardadas ou outras extensões.</p>
    <p>Lembre-se, o Ephemeral e modo incógnito ou privado de qualquer outro navegador por si só: conseguem impedir algum rastreio e não armazenam dados no dispositivo, mas não vão impedir o seu ISP, governo, ou determinados websites de o rastrear.</p>
    <p>Para a melhor proteção, utilizar sempre uma VPN.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Navegue na internet privadamente sem deixar rastros ou histórico no seu computador. Ephemeral é um enxuto navegador privado que é perfeito para evitar cookies persistentes ou rastreadores da web. Feche a janela e todos os rastros da sua navegação serão removidos do seu dispositivos.</p>
    <p>Recursos úteis:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Abra facilmente as páginas em qualquer outro navegador instalado</li>
      <li>Pesquise diretamente da barra de endereço</li>
    </ul>
    <ul>
      <li>Aperte Ctrl+W para fechar a janela atual ou Ctrl+Q para fechar todas as janelas</li>
    </ul>
    <p>1️⃣ Sempre em modo incógnito. Do segundo em que você abre uma Janela Ephemeral até fechá-la (ou apertar o botão Apagar), Ephemeral estará em modo de navegação privada. Isso significa que histórico, cookies, armazenamento local, senhas, etc. sumirão imediatamente quando você sair.</p>
    <p>4️⃣ Sem telemetria. Ephemeral não usa a conexão de internet até que você explícitamente abra uma página da web ou realize uma pesquisa. Mesmo assim, nenhum dado será coletado—Não tenho ideia do que você fará com o Ephemeral, e não quero saber mesmo assim!</p>
    <p>Para uma proteção melhor, use sempre um serviço de VPN.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Просматривайте интернет приватно, не оставляя следов истории на вашем компьютере. Ephemeral — это приватный браузер, который идеально подходит для предотвращения постоянных куки-файлов или веб-трекеров. Закройте окно, и все следы вашего просмотра будут удалены с вашего устройства.</p>
    <p>Удобные функции:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Без труда открывайте страницы в любом другом установленном браузере</li>
      <li>Поиск прямо из адресной строки</li>
      <li>Выберите из меню между поисковыми системами уважающими частную жизнь</li>
    </ul>
    <ul>
      <li>Нажмите Ctrl+W, чтобы закрыть текущее окно, или Ctrl+Q, чтобы закрыть все окна.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>1️⃣ Как только вы откроете окно в Ephemeral и пока не закроете его (или не нажмете кнопку «Стереть»), Ephemeral будет находится в приватном режиме просмотра. Это означает, что история, куки-файлы, локальное хранилище, пароли и т.д. будут тотчас уничтожены когда вы закончите.</p>
    <p>4️⃣ Нет телеметрии. Ephemeral не отправляет никакие запросы в сеть, пока вы явно не загрузите веб-страницу или не выполните поиск. Даже в этом случае никакие данные об использовании никогда не собираются — я понятия не имею, что вы делаете с Ephemeral, и не хочу знать!</p>
    <p>Помните, что Ephemeral и режим инкогнито или приватный режим другого браузера могут сделать очень многое, но не всё: они уменьшают некоторое отслеживание и не сохраняют данные на вашем устройстве, но они не помешают вашему провайдеру, правительству или определенным веб-сайтам отслеживать вас.</p>
    <p>Для лучшей защиты всегда используйте VPN.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Bilgisayarınızda herhangi bir geçmiş izi bırakmadan internette gizli olarak gezinin.Ephemeral, aşağıdakiler için mükemmel olan özel bir tarayıcıdır.Kalıcı çerezlerden veya web izleyicilerinden kaçınmak. Pencereyi ve tüm izleri kapatırgöz atma sürenizi cihazınızdan kaldırılır.</p>
    <p>Kullanışlı özellikler:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Sayfaları yüklü başka bir tarayıcıda kolayca açın</li>
      <li>Doğrudan URL çubuğundan arayın</li>
      <li>Menüden arama motorları arasından seçim yapın</li>
      <li>Menüden JavaScript'i hızla devre dışı bırakın veya yeniden etkinleştirin</li>
    </ul>
    <ul>
      <li>⭐️ simgesi veya Ctrl + D ile URL önerilenlere ekleyin</li>
      <li>Ctrl+F ile sayfadaki metni bulun</li>
      <li>Geçerli pencereyi kapatmak için Ctrl + W tuşlarına veya tüm pencerelerden çıkmak için Ctrl + Q tuşlarına basın.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Ephemeral sizi beş temel yolla korur:</p>
    <p>1️⃣ Her zaman gizli. Saniyeler içinede geçici pencere açın veyakapatın (veya Sil düğmesine basın), Ephemeral özel tarama modunda, geçmiş, çerezler, yerel depolama, şifreler vb. kapatır kapatmaz hepsi silinir.</p>
    <p>4️⃣ Telemetri yok. Ephemeral, siz açıkça belirtmedikçe ağa dokunmazbir web sayfası yükleyin veya bir arama yapın. O zaman bile hiçbir kullanım verisi toplamaz — Ephemeral ile ne yaptığınız hakkında hiçbir fikrim yok.</p>
    <p>Unutmayın, Ephemeral ve herhangi bir tarayıcının gizli veya özel modundan daha fazlası: izlemeyi azaltırlar ve cihazınıza veri depolamazlar,ancak ISS'nizi, hükümeti veya belirli web siteleriniseni izliyor.</p>
    <p>En iyi koruma için her zaman bir VPN kullanın.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Переглядайте в Інтернеті у приватному режимі не залишаючи й сліду від історії перегляду на вашому комп'ютері. Ephemeral є полегшеним приватним переглядачем Інтернету, який ідеально підходить для запобігання встановленню сторонніх кук та протидії елементам стеження. Закрийте вікно і всі сліди перегляду видаляться з пристрою.</p>
    <p>Зручні функції:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Легко відкривайте сторінки у будь-якому іншому встановленому переглядачі</li>
      <li>Вводьте пошукові запити прямо у панель адреси</li>
      <li>Вибирайте з-поміж засобів пошуку, які поважають вашу приватність, у меню</li>
      <li>Швидко вмикайте або вимикайте JavaScript у меню</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Корисні комбінації клавіш та рухи:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Переходьте вперед чи назад провівши двома пальцями по вашому трекпаду</li>
      <li>Додайте вебсайт до пропозицій URL-адрес натисканням на піктограму ⭐️ або Ctrl+D</li>
      <li>Шукайте текст на сторінці натиснувши Ctrl+F</li>
      <li>Збільшуйте або зменшуйте масштаб натисканням Ctrl+Плюс and Ctrl+Мінус</li>
      <li>Відкривайте нове вікно натисканням Ctrl+N</li>
      <li>Натисніть Ctrl+W, щоб закрити поточне вікно чи Ctrl+Q, щоб закрити усі вікна</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Ephemeral захищає вас п'ятьма основними способами:</p>
    <p>1️⃣ Завжди потаємний режим. Коли ви вдруге відкриєте вікно Ephemeral, доки не закриєте його (або не натиснете кнопку Стерти), Ephemeral знаходиться в режимі приватного перегляду. Це означає, що історія перегляду, куки, локальне сховище, паролі тощо все зникне, як тільки ви закриєте його.</p>
    <p>2️⃣ Ізольовано в пісочниці. Кожне вікно є окремим екземпляром рушія переглядача, домени всередині кожного вікна обробляються за допомогою окремих процесів, а процеси рушія ізольовано один від одного, щоб захистити вас. Якщо увійти до служби в одному вікні, то сайти в інших вікнах не матимуть уявлення, що в ньому відбувається.</p>
    <p>3️⃣ Жодних сторонніх кук. Ephemeral блокує куки зі сторонніх джерел, що зменшує кількість рекламних кук та інших небажаних форм стеження між сайтами.</p>
    <p>4️⃣ Жодного надсилання даних телеметрії. Ephemeral не з'єднується з мережею, доки ви явно не завантажите вебсторінку або не здійсните пошук. Навіть тоді, жодні дані про користування ніколи не збираються — я уявлення не маю, що ви робите з Ephemeral та не хочу знати!</p>
    <p>5️⃣️ Ephemeral типово застосовує DuckDuckGo — засіб пошуку, що не стежить за вашими діями — для якнайбільшого уникнення можливості стеження Google. Ви, також, можете вибрати StartPage.com у меню, якщо він вам до вподоби, або, навіть, додати ваш власний спеціалізований рушій пошуку.</p>
    <p>Зробіть звичкою, завжди відкривати посилання за допомогою Ephemeral, знаючи, що ви можете одним натисканням кнопки перейти до перегляду у традиційному переглядачі, наприклад Epiphany, Firefox, Chrome, Opera, Brave, або будь-якому іншому встановленому переглядачі. Ідеально підходить вам, якщо ви хочете користуватися збереженими паролями чи іншими розширеннями.</p>
    <p>Пам’ятайте, що Ephemeral та потаємний чи приватний режим будь-якого переглядача мережі можуть зробити лише наступне: блокують деякі елементи стеження та не зберігають дані на вашому пристрої, але вони не зупинять вашого провайдера, уряду чи певні вебсайти від стеження за вами.</p>
    <p>Для кращого захисту завжди користуйтеся VPN.</p>
  </description>
  <pkgname>ephemeral</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.github.cassidyjames.ephemeral.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" height="64" type="cached">com.github.cassidyjames.ephemeral.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" type="cached" height="128">com.github.cassidyjames.ephemeral.png</icon>
  <id>com.github.cassidyjames.ephemeral</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Ephemeral</name>
  <name lang="uk">Ephemeral</name>
  <name lang="tr">Ephemeral</name>
  <name lang="ru">Ephemeral</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Ephemeral</name>
  <name lang="pt">Ephemeral</name>
  <name lang="pl">Ephemeral</name>
  <name lang="nl">Ephemeral</name>
  <name lang="it">Ephemeral</name>
  <name lang="fr">Ephemeral</name>
  <name lang="es">Ephemeral</name>
  <name lang="de">Ephemeral</name>
  <name lang="ca">Ephemeral</name>
  <summary>The always-incognito web browser</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Переглядач, який завжди в потаємному режимі</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Her zaman gizli web tarayıcınız</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Браузер, который всегда в режиме инкогнито</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">O navegador que está sempre em modo incógnito</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">O navegador web sempre incógnito</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Zawsze–prywatna przeglądarka internetowa</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">De webbrowser waarmee je altijd privé surft</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Il browser web sempre in modalità in incognito</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Le navigateur web toujours incognito</summary>
  <summary lang="es">El navegador web que siempre va de incógnito</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Der Webbrowser, mit dem man immer inkognito surft</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">El navegador sempre d'incògnit</summary>
  <provides>
    <binary>com.github.cassidyjames.ephemeral</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="7.1.0" date="2021-03-25">
      <description>
        <p>Automatically Open Sites Externally</p>
        <p>You can now always open chosen sites externally, bypassing Ephemeral! On a page, open the "Open page in…" menu and check the new "Automatically Open This Site Externally". Opening a link to that site will now open in your selected other browser instead of in Ephemeral; super handy for things like Twitter or GitHub where you always want to be logged in. To revert it, just open the site in Ephemeral and uncheck "Automatically Open This Site Externally" from the "Open page in…" menu.</p>
        <p>Improved reliability of setting the window title; the title seen in the Dock menu or Multitasking View should now more reliably match the page's title, especially when updated with JavaScript.</p>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-01-15" version="7.0.5">
      <description>
        <p>Translation updates</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translated to Portuguese thanks to Hugo Carvalho</li>
          <li>Updated Dutch translations thanks to Quinten</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="7.0.4" date="2020-10-01">
      <description>
        <p>Developers, Developers, Developers!</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Access WebKit Web Inspector and developer tools via Inspect Element</li>
          <li>New hard refresh action (bypassing the cache) with Shift+Ctrl+R</li>
          <li>Support for elementary OS 6, including the dark style preference</li>
          <li>Several new site suggestions</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Translation updates</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translated to Ukranian thanks to Ihor Hordiichuk</li>
          <li>Updated Brazilian Portuguese translations thanks to Karl Prieb</li>
          <li>Updated Turkish translations thanks to Safak GENISOL</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="6.4.1" date="2020-04-30">
      <description>
        <p>Updated Spanish translations thanks to Adolfo Jayme-Barrientos</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-04-29" version="6.4.0">
      <description>
        <p>Sandboxing</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Enabled WebKit’s subprocess sandboxing</li>
          <li>Enabled WebKit’s process swapping on cross-site navigation, meaning separate domains are sandboxed from one another</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Search engine changes</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Switched to DuckDuckGo search by default since it supports a dark style</li>
          <li>Enabled strict Safe Browsing by default for DuckDuckGo to avoid unwanted results</li>
          <li>StartPage.com remains an available option in the menu</li>
          <li>Other search engines or configurations can be added under “Custom Search Engine…” in the menu, as always</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-04-28" version="6.3.4">
      <description>
        <p>Updated Italian translations thanks to Mirko Brombin</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="6.3.3" date="2020-04-01">
      <description>
        <p>Fool me twice…</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Remove sometimes-problematic dark style workaround CSS since it was fixed in WebKit</li>
          <li>Ensure correct browser icon size is set</li>
          <li>Remove dark style toggle when forcing a -dark stylesheet</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-03-27" version="6.3.2">
      <description>
        <p>Minor Fixes</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix entry selection color when using the light style</li>
          <li>Improve styling on other platforms/stylesheets by being less ambitious</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="6.3.1" date="2020-03-13">
      <description>
        <p>Helping Hand</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Suggest turning on "Close when opening externally" if Ephemeral notices you frequently doing it yourself</li>
          <li>Turkish translations thanks to Safak GENISOL</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="6.2.1" date="2020-02-17">
      <description>
        <p>Translation updates</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation system improved thanks to @NathanBnm</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="6.2.0" date="2020-01-30">
      <description>
        <p>Dark Style Rises</p>
        <ul>
          <li>A new toggle lets you choose light or dark style for sites, assuming they support the `prefers-color-scheme` CSS query</li>
          <li>Stopped defaulting to dark style by default since it can break some sites</li>
          <li>Set the window title to help distinguish different pages from the dock</li>
          <li>Simplified "Open page in…" menu and logic to always expose all options</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Translation updates</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Updated Dutch translations thanks to Heimen Stoffels</li>
          <li>Updated French translations thanks to @NathanBnm</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-11-05" version="6.1.1">
      <description>
        <p>Minor updates</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixed checkbox and radio button styling</li>
          <li>Treat “localhost” as a valid domain</li>
          <li>Improved dark styling when building with newer versions of WebKit</li>
          <li>Under the hood changes to make translations easier</li>
          <li>Updated Spanish translations thanks to Adolfo Jayme-Barrientos and @riesp</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="6.1.0" date="2019-10-17">
      <description>
        <p>🎉️ Emoji (and international character) support for domains! Punycode means domains like i❤tacos.ws will show up properly in the URL entry, while phishing domains should still show up like xn--80ak6aa92e.com</p>
        <p>Translation updates</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Updated Dutch translations thanks to Heimen Stoffels</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-10-13" version="6.0.0">
      <description>
        <p>Adding Some Polish 💅️</p>
        <ul>
          <li>💻️ Touchpad gesture navigation: Use a two-finger swipe to move back or forward through your browsing history</li>
          <li>🔗️ More room for the URL entry to breathe: spacing on each side plus a maximum width means the window is easier to grab and move around</li>
          <li>UI styling fixes, plus dark style fixes for newer versions of WebKit</li>
          <li>Code cleaning to keep things fresh and clean</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="5.4.0" date="2019-09-17">
      <description>
        <p>McSipes</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Quickly disable or re-enable JavaScript from the menu</li>
          <li>Use Ctrl+D to add/remove a site from the suggestions</li>
          <li>Find text on the page with Ctrl+F</li>
          <li>New Paste and Go item in the URL bar context menu</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="5.3.2" date="2019-09-16">
      <description>
        <p>Translation updates</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Updated Dutch translations thanks to Heimen Stoffels</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="5.3.1" date="2019-09-13">
      <description>
        <p>Translation updates</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Updated Italian translations thanks to @meliurwen</li>
          <li>Updated Spanish translations thanks to Adolfo Jayme-Barrientos</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-08-29" version="5.3.0">
      <description>
        <p>Hello from Thessaloniki</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixed window closing: now closing the first window does not close the rest</li>
          <li>Simplified “Erase” to always close the window instead of sometimes opening a new one</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="5.2.1" date="2019-07-28">
      <description>
        <p>Summer cleaning! Because that’s a thing, right?</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixed the “Open Link in New Window” menu item to actually do what it says</li>
          <li>Fixed opening target="_blank" links in a new window with Ctrl- or middle-click</li>
          <li>Updated the base color in menus and dialog windows from the default elementary slate-ish black to a new deep, dark blue-ish purple</li>
          <li>Tweaked the “Open Link Externally” dialog to better isolate protocols like “mailto” or “tel”</li>
          <li>Significantly cleaned up and reorganized the codebase to make future features and fixes easier</li>
          <li>Updated Dutch translations thanks to Heimen Stoffels</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="5.1.1" date="2019-06-24">
      <description>
        <p>Translation updates</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Updated Catalán and Spanish translations thanks to Mario Rodrigo</li>
          <li>Updated French translations thanks to @NathanBnm</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="5.1.0" date="2019-05-15">
      <description>
        <p>Some great UI refinements!</p>
        <ul>
          <li>URL entry suggestions are much snazzier thanks to Hannes Schulze</li>
          <li>JavaScript alerts now follow the elementary HIG thanks to David Hewitt</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Translation updates</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Ciao! Translated to Italian thanks to @meliurwen</li>
          <li>Updated French translations thanks to @NathanBnm</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="5.0.3" date="2019-04-08">
      <description>
        <p>Updated Catalan translations thanks to Mario Rodrigo.</p>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="5.0.2" date="2019-04-02">
      <description>
        <p>Minor updates</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Updated Spanish translations thanks to Adolfo Jayme-Barrientos</li>
          <li>Code cleanup</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="5.0.1" date="2019-04-02">
      <description>
        <p>Translation updates</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Updated Dutch translations thanks to Heimen Stoffels</li>
          <li>Updated Russian translations thanks to Artem Polishchuk</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Additional translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-04-01" version="5.0.0">
      <description>
        <p>No foolin'. Two major new features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>🔍️ New Custom Search Engine setting in the Menu</li>
          <li>⭐️ Add your own websites to the suggestions using the new button in the URL entry</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Plus the usual iterative improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Various URL entry fixes and tweaks</li>
          <li>Updated Dutch translations thanks to Heimen Stoffels</li>
          <li>Updated French translations thanks to @NathanBnm</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Translations for new features will appear in future updates as translators have a chance to do their thing.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-03-22" version="4.2.1">
      <description>
        <p>Translation updates</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Cześć! Translated to Polish thanks to Paweł Jerzy Przybysz</li>
          <li>Updated French translations thanks to @NathanBnm</li>
          <li>Updated Lithuanian translations thanks to @welaq</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-02-23" version="4.2.0">
      <description>
        <p>Blaze It</p>
        <ul>
          <li>New option to close the window when opening a page in an external browser</li>
          <li>The web view is now focused when navigating</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-02-22" version="4.1.2">
      <description>
        <p>URL Entry Fixes</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Updated and corrected several autocomplete domains</li>
          <li>No longer attempt to force HTTPS on protocol-less domains—fixes several popular sites</li>
          <li>Strip whitespace from URL entry before navigating—fixes instances where trying to navigate to a domain would perform a search</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-02-21" version="4.1.1">
      <description>
        <p>URL Suggestion Fixes</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Corrected joinmastodon.org TLD</li>
          <li>Added additional useful sites</li>
          <li>Added descriptions for more sites</li>
          <li>Removed dead sites</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-02-15" version="4.1.0">
      <description>
        <p>All New Search + Suggestions</p>
        <ul>
          <li>The URL entry will offer to complete over 400 popular sites*</li>
          <li>New Search Engine choice in the Menu</li>
          <li>Switched to Startpage.com by default</li>
          <li>Happy birthday, Katie!</li>
        </ul>
        <p>*This data is all shipped with Ephemeral itself, and Ephemeral still does not touch the network until you explicitly navigate somewhere. The list of domains is heavily inspired by a similar feature in Firefox Focus. Domains being included in completion suggestions are not an endorsement, it simply means that domain is relatively popular.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-02-12" version="4.0.4">
      <description>
        <p>Guten Tag! German translations thanks to Hannes Schulze</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.0.3" date="2019-02-05">
      <description>
        <p>Здравствуйте! Russian translations thanks to Artem Polishchuk</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.0.2" date="2019-01-28">
      <description>
        <p>More translations:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Lithuanian translations thanks to @welaq</li>
          <li>Updated Dutch translations thanks to Heimen Stoffels</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-01-27" version="4.0.1">
      <description>
        <p>Fixed some missed translations and updated French translations. Thanks again, @NathanBnm!</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.0.0" date="2019-01-23">
      <description>
        <p>Lots o' goodies:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>The last-used browser is remembered for next time</li>
          <li>New "Reset Preferences" menu item and dialog</li>
          <li>Ctrl+O to open the current page in another browser</li>
          <li>Refined (ever-so-subtly less flat) HeaderBar design</li>
          <li>Ephemeral is now translatable!</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Translations:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>¡Hola! Spanish translations thanks to Adolfo Jayme-Barrientos and Mario Rodrigo</li>
          <li>salut! French translations thanks to Nathan (@NathanBnm)</li>
          <li>Olá! Brazilian Portuguese translations thanks to Lucas Sanchez dos Anjos</li>
          <li>Hallo! Dutch translations thanks to Heimen Stoffels</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-01-22" version="3.2.2">
      <description>
        <p>Styling fixes for non-native platforms.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.2.1" date="2019-01-22">
      <description>
        <p>Fixed a few small issues with zoom:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Zoom controls are now only sensitive when the web view is visible</li>
          <li>Reported zoom level is now correct when opening a new window</li>
          <li>Reported zoom level is now kept in sync across open windows</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-01-21" version="3.2.0">
      <description>
        <p>Zoom! And more…</p>
        <ul>
          <li>A new menu to keep the UI tidy and balanced</li>
          <li>Zoom in, out, and default from the new menu or with the keyboard</li>
          <li>New Window action moved into the menu</li>
          <li>Added a Quit All Windows action to the menu</li>
          <li>Smooth scrolling when using the keyboard or a scrollwheel</li>
          <li>Fixed Twitch livestreams</li>
          <li>Fixed YouTube resolution support: now up to 4K!</li>
          <li>Code cleaning to keep things fresh and clean</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.1.0" date="2019-01-14">
      <description>
        <p>Better error handling and quality of life improvements all around:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>New approval dialogs for external apps, e.g. appstream or ftp protocols</li>
          <li>New warning when no network connection</li>
          <li>Prettier errors using native views</li>
          <li>Stopped throwing away text when unfocusing URL entry</li>
          <li>Stopped searching when the URL entry is empty</li>
          <li>Code cleaning to keep things smelling fresh</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-01-12" version="3.0.0">
      <description>
        <p>Fresh styles to keep things funky, plus more:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>The new start page makes Ephemeral faster and makes it not touch the network until you're ready to browse</li>
          <li>Middle- or Ctrl-click a link to open it in a new window</li>
          <li>Displayed URLs are kept in sync for pages that manually update the URL without a page load</li>
          <li>Local HTML files can now be opened</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.0.1" date="2019-01-10">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>More informative "set as default" infobar</li>
          <li>Tweaked "set as default" infobar styling</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.0.0" date="2019-01-10">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Search from URL entry!</li>
          <li>Asks (politely!) to be set as the default browser</li>
          <li>Open unsupported links (like AppCenter ones) in the OS-default app</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.2.0" date="2019-01-09">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Add "New Window" to headerbar, app launcher, and keyboard shortcuts</li>
          <li>Collapse external browsers into a menu when there's more than one</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.0" date="2019-01-08">
      <description>
        <p>Add several useful keyboard and mouse shortcuts</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.1" date="2019-01-08">
      <description>
        <p>Fix links that try to open in a new window</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2019-01-08">
      <description>
        <p>Initial release for AppCenter</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/cassidyjames/ephemeral/main/data/screenshot@2x.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/cassidyjames/ephemeral/main/data/screenshot-many-browsers.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/cassidyjames/ephemeral/main/data/screenshot-menu@2x.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/cassidyjames/ephemeral/main/data/screenshot-menu-dark@2x.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-desecration">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-slavery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-worship">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-homosexuality">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-prostitution">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-adultery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-appearance">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <developer_name>Cassidy James Blaede</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Cassidy James Blaede</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">Cassidy James Blaede</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Cassidy James Blaede</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">Cassidy James Blaede</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Cassidy James Blaede</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Cassidy James Blaede</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Cassidy James Blaede</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Cassidy James Blaede</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Cassidy James Blaede</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Cassidy James Blaede</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Cassidy James Blaede</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">Cassidy James Blaede</developer_name>
  <url type="homepage">https://cassidyjames.com</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/cassidyjames/ephemeral/issues</url>
  <url type="translate">https://github.com/cassidyjames/ephemeral/tree/main/po#readme</url>
  <url type="donation">https://cassidyjames.com/pay</url>
  <url type="help">https://cassidyjames.com/support</url>
  <!-- url type="contact">https://cassidyjames.com/support</url -->
  <custom>
    <value key="x-appcenter-color-primary">#3b2a7d</value>
    <value key="x-appcenter-color-primary-text">#fff</value>
    <value key="x-appcenter-suggested-price">9</value>
  </custom>
</component>