<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>fragments</pkgname>
  <icon width="64" height="64" type="cached">de.haeckerfelix.Fragments.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" width="128" type="cached">de.haeckerfelix.Fragments.png</icon>
  <id>de.haeckerfelix.Fragments</id>
  <name>Fragments</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="vi">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="uk">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="tr">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="sv">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="sr">Фрагменти</name>
  <name lang="sl">Fragmenti</name>
  <name lang="sk">Fragmenty</name>
  <name lang="ru">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="ro">Fragmente</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="pt">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="pl">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="oc">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="nl">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="ko">프래그먼츠</name>
  <name lang="ja">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="it">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="id">Fragment</name>
  <name lang="hu">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="hr">Fragmenti</name>
  <name lang="gl">Fragmentos</name>
  <name lang="fur">Framents</name>
  <name lang="fr">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="fi">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="eu">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="es">Fragmentos</name>
  <name lang="eo">Fragmentoj</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="el">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="de">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="da">Fragments</name>
  <name lang="cs">Fragmenty</name>
  <name lang="ca">Fragments</name>
  <summary>A BitTorrent Client</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">一个 BitTorrent 客户端</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Một trình khách BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Клієнт BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">BitTorrent İstemcisi</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">En BitTorrent-klient</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Бит-торент клијент</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Odjemalec BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Klient protokolu BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Клиент BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Un client BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Um cliente BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Um cliente BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Klient sieci BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Un client BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Een BitTorrent-cliënt</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">비트토렌트 클라이언트</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">BitTorrent クライアント</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Un client BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Klien BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Egy BitTorrent kliens</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">BitTorrent klijent</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Un cliente de BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Un client BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Un client BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">BitTorrent-sovellus</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">BitTorrent bezeroa</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Un cliente de BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">BitTorrent-kliento</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">A BitTorrent Client</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Ένας πελάτης BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Ein BitTorrent-Client</summary>
  <summary lang="da">En BitTorrent-klient</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Klient pro BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Un client BitTorrent</summary>
  <translation type="gettext">fragments</translation>
  <developer_name>Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="vi">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="oc">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fur">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">Felix HÄCKER</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">Felix Häcker</developer_name>
  <update_contact>haeckerfelix@gnome.org</update_contact>
  <metadata_license>CC0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0" />
  <launchable type="desktop-id">de.haeckerfelix.Fragments.desktop</launchable>
  <description>
    <p>
      Fragments is an easy to use BitTorrent client for the GNOME desktop
      environment. It is usable for receiving files using the BitTorrent
      protocol, which enables you to transmit huge files, like videos or
      installation images for Linux distributions.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Fragment és un client BitTorrent fàcil d'usar per a l'entorn d'escriptori GNOME. És usable per rebre fitxers usant el protocol BitTorrent, el qual permet la transmissió de fitxers grans, com vídeos o imatges d'instal·lació de distribucions Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Fragmenty je snadno použitelný klient pro BitTorrent zaměřený na uživatelské prostředí GNOME. Je vhodný pro stahování souborů pomocí protokolu BitTorrent, který umožňuje přenášet objemově velké soubory, jako jsou videa nebo instalační obrazy linuxových distribucí.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Fragments er en BitTorrent-klient til GNOME-skrivebordsmiljøet, som er let at bruge. Den kan bruges til at modtage filer med BitTorrent-protokollen, hvilket giver dig mulighed for at overføre meget store filer såsom videoer eller installationsaftryk til Linux-distributioner.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Fragments ist ein einfach zu verwendender BitTorrent-Client für die GNOME-Arbeitsumgebung. Es ist für den Dateiempfang über das BitTorrent-Protokoll verwendbar, welches Ihnen die Übertragung sehr großer Dateien ermöglicht, wie Videos oder Installationsabbilder für Linux-Distributionen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το Fragments είναι ένας εύχρηστος πελάτης BitTorrent για το GNOME. Μπορείτε να το χρησιμοποιήσετε για τη λήψη αρχείων με το πρωτόκολλο BitTorrent, το οποίο σας επιτρέπει να μεταδίδετε τεράστια αρχεία, όπως βίντεο ή εικόνες εγκατάστασης για διανομές Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Fragments is an easy to use BitTorrent client for the GNOME desktop environment. It is usable for receiving files using the BitTorrent protocol, which enables you to transmit huge files, like videos or installation images for Linux distributions.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p>Fragmentoj estas facile uzebla BitTorrent-kliento por la GNOME labortablo. Oni povas uzi ĝin por elŝuti dosierojn per la BitTorrent-protokolo, kiu ebligas transmetadon de grandegaj dosieroj kiel videoj kaj diskokopioj de Linuksaj distribuaĵoj.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Fragmentos es un cliente de BitTorrent sencillo de usar para el entorno de escritorio GNOME. Se puede usar para recibir archivos usando el protocolo BitTorrent, que le permite transmitir archivos muy grandes como vídeos o imágenes de instalación de distribuciones Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Fragments erabiltzeko erraza den BitTorrent bezero bat da, GNOME mahaigainerako sortua. BitTorrent protokoloa erabilita fitxategiak jasotzeko erabil daiteke. Horrela, fitxategi handiak parteka ditzakezu, adibidez bideoak eta Linux banaketen instalazio-irudiak.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Fragments on helppokäyttöinen BitTorrent-sovellus Gnome-työpöydälle. Sitä voi käyttää tiedostojen vastaanottamiseen BitTorrent-protokollan välityksellä, mikä taas mahdollistaa suurten tiedostojen, kuten videoiden tai Linux-jakelujen, siirtämisen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Fragments est un client BitTorrent simple à utiliser pour l’environnement de bureau GNOME. On peut l’utiliser pour recevoir des fichiers avec le protocole BitTorrent, ce qui permet de transmettre de gros fichiers tels que des vidéos ou des images d’installation pour les distributions Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Framents al è un client BitTorrent facil di doprâ pal ambient di scritori GNOME. Si pues doprâ par ricevi file doprant il protocol BitTorrent, che ti permet di trasmeti file grancj,come videos o imagjins di instalazion pes distribuzions Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Fragmentos é un cliente de BitTorrent doado de usar para o ambiente de escritorio GNOME. É útil para recibir ficheiros usando o protocolo BitTorrent, o cal lle permite transmitir ficheiros grandes, como vídeos ou imaxes de instalación de distribucións Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Fragmenti je jednostavan za korištenje BitTorrent klijent za GNOME radno okruženje. Koristan je za preuzimanje datoteka pomoću BitTorrent protokola, koji vam omogućuje prijenos većih datoteka, poput video snimaka ili instalacijskih slika Linux distribucija.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Fragments egy egyszerűen használható BitTorrent kliens a GNOME asztali környezethez. A BitTorrent protokoll használatával történő fájlok fogadásához használható, ami lehetővé tesz hatalmas fájlok átvitelét, mint például videókat vagy Linux disztribúciók telepítési lemezképeit.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Fragment adalah klien BitTorrent yang mudah digunakan untuk lingkungan destop GNOME. Dapat digunakan untuk menerima berkas menggunakan protokol BitTorrent, yang memungkinkan Anda untuk mengirimkan berkas besar, seperti video atau citra instalasi untuk distribusi Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Fragments è un client BitTorrent facile da usare per l'ambiente grafico GNOME. È utilizzabile per ricevere file usando il protocollo BitTorrent, che consente di trasmettere file di grandi dimensioni, come video o immagini di installazione di distribuzioni Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>Fragments は GNOME デスクトップ環境向けの使いやすい BitTorrent クライアントです。動画や Linux ディストリビューションのインストールイメージのようなサイズの非常に大きいファイルを、BitTorrent プロトコルで送受信することができます。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>프래그먼츠는 그놈 데스크톱 환경용으로 사용하기 쉬운 비트토렌트 클라이언트입니다. 비트토렌트 프로토콜로 파일을 수신할 수 있으며, 동영상 파일 또는 리눅스 배포판 설치 이미지 등 대용량 파일을 전송할 수 있습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Fragments is een eenvoudig te gebruiken BitTorrent-cliënt voor de Gnome-bureaubladomgeving. Fragments kan bestanden ontvangen met het BitTorrent-protocol, waardoor u enorme bestanden kunt verplaatsen, zoals video’s of installatiebestanden voor Linux-distributies.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>Fragments es un client BitTorrent de bon utilizat per l’environament de burèu GNOME. Servís a recebre de fichièrs en utilizant lo protocòl BitTorrent, que vos permet de transmetre de fichièrs pesucs, coma de vidèos o d’imatges d’installacion per las distribucions Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Fragments to łatwy w użyciu klient sieci BitTorrent dla środowiska GNOME. Można go używać do pobierania plików za pomocą protokołu BitTorrent, co umożliwia przesyłanie wielkich plików, takich jak filmy lub obrazy instalacyjne dystrybucji systemu Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Fragments é um cliente BitTorrent fácil de usar para o ambiente gráfico GNOME. Pode ser usado para receber ficheiros utilizando o protocolo BitTorrent, que permite transmitir ficheiros enormes, como vídeos ou imagens de instalação para distribuições Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Fragments é um cliente BitTorrent fácil de usar para o ambiente GNOME. Ele pode ser usado para receber arquivos usando o protocolo BitTorrent, que permite transmitir arquivos enormes, como vídeos ou imagens de instalação para distribuições Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Fragmente este un client BitTorrent ușor de utilizat pentru mediul de desktop GNOME. Este utilizabil pentru primirea de fișiere utilizând protocolul BitTorrent, care vă permite să transmiteți fișiere uriașe, precum video-urile sau imaginile de instalare pentru distribuțiile Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Fragments - это простой в использовании клиент BitTorrent для среды рабочего стола GNOME. Он может использоваться для скачивания файлов с использованием протокола BitTorrent, который позволяет передавать огромные файлы, такие как видео или установочные образы для дистрибутивов Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Aplikácia Fragmenty je jednoduchým klientom protokolu BitTorrent pre pracovné prostredie GNOME. Je možné ju použiť na prijímanie súborov pomocou protokolu BitTorrent, čo vám umožňuje prenášať veľké súbory ako sú videá, alebo inštalačné obrazy distribúcií systému Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Program Fragmenti je enostaven, a zmogljiv odjemalec za prenos datotek po protokolu BitTorrent v okolju GNOME. Omogoča prejem in pošiljanje velikih datotek, kot so videoposnetki ali odtisi distribucij Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Фрагменти је лаган Бит-торент клијент за Гномово радно окружење. Може се користити за примање датотека преко Бит-Торент протокола који вам дозвољава пренос великих датотека као што су видео записи или инсталациони дискови Линукс дистрибуција.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Fragments är en lättanvänd BitTorrent-klient för GNOME-skrivbordsmiljön. Den är användbar för att ta emot filer med BitTorrent-protokollet, vilket låter dig överföra enorma filer, så som videoklipp eller installationsavbilder för Linux-distributioner.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Fragments, GNOME masaüstü ortamı için kullanımı kolay BitTorrent istemcisidir. Linux dağıtımlarında, video veya kurulum kalıbı gibi büyük dosyaları BitTorrent iletişim kuralını kullanarak almanızı sağlar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Fragments — простий у користуванні клієнт BitTorrent для стільничного середовища GNOME. Він знадобиться для завантаження файлів за допомогою протоколу BitTorrent, який уможливлює передавання величезних файлів, зокрема відео та образів для встановлення дистрибутивів Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="vi">
    <p>Fragments là một ứng dụng BitTorrent dễ sử dụng cho môi trường máy tính để bàn GNOME. Nó có thể sử dụng để nhận các tập tin bằng cách sử dụng giao thức BitTorrent, cho phép bạn truyền các tập tin cực lớn, như video hoặc ảnh cài đặt cho các bản phân phối Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>Fragments 是一个为 GNOME 桌面环境开发的简单易用的 BitTorrent 客户端。它可以用来通过 BitTorrent 协议接收文件，允许您传输巨大的文件，比如视频或 Linux 发行版的安装映像。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="1022" height="822">https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Fragments/-/raw/main/data/screenshots/1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image width="1022" height="822">https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Fragments/-/raw/main/data/screenshots/2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image width="1022" height="822">https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Fragments/-/raw/main/data/screenshots/3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image height="822" width="1022">https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Fragments/-/raw/main/data/screenshots/4.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Fragments</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Fragments/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://liberapay.com/haecker-felix</url>
  <url type="translate">https://l10n.gnome.org/module/Fragments/</url>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>Notifications</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <custom>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">workstation</value>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">mobile</value>
  </custom>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
  <recommends>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  <releases>
    <release version="2.0.2" date="2022-02-12" />
    <release date="2022-02-06" version="2.0.1" />
    <release version="2.0" date="2022-02-05">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fragments 2.0 is a major update with many new features and improvements. Fragments has been rebuilt from the scratch, and now uses Rust, GTK4 and the new GNOME Libadwaita library under the hood.
        </p>
        <p>
          Notable new features / improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fragments can now be used as a client to control remote Fragments / Transmission sessions</li>
          <li>Statistics about the current session can now be viewed (e.g. network speed, total up and downloaded data, etc.)</li>
          <li>New torrent dialog window which displays information more clearly</li>
          <li>The magnet link of already added torrents can now be copied to the clipboard</li>
          <li>New context menu which allows quick access to important actions</li>
          <li>Updated user interface which is optimized for the new GNOME/Libadwaita design</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
          The preferences have also been completely reworked and now offer more options:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Automatically start torrents after adding them</li>
          <li>Enable / disable download queue</li>
          <li>Custom location for incomplete torrents</li>
          <li>Customizable peer limits</li>
          <li>Random or specific network port</li>
          <li>Enable / disable automatic port forwarding</li>
          <li>Built-in check to test the network port</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.9.2" date="2022-02-01">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is the second beta release of Fragments 2.0
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-12-06" version="1.9.1">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is the first beta release of Fragments 2.0
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.5" date="2020-09-13">
      <description>
        <p>
          New features / changes:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Show notifications when a new torrent is added, or when a download is complete</li>
          <li>The encryption mode can now be configured (Forced, Optional, Disabled)</li>
          <li>New menu entry to remove all downloaded torrents</li>
          <li>Refreshed user interface / Updated application icon</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4" date="2019-03-24">
      <description>
        <p>
          New features / changes:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>New application icon + theme</li>
          <li>New 'Open' button to open downloaded torrents faster</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
          <li>Several bug fixes</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.3" date="2018-12-31">
      <description>
        <p>
          New features / changes:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>New adaptive settings dialog</li>
          <li>Small interface improvements</li>
          <li>Update libtransmission backend to 3.00</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-09-16" version="1.2">
      <description>
        <p>
          New features / changes:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Adaptive interface (Ready for Librem5!)</li>
          <li>Move AppMenu to headerbar</li>
          <li>Added translations: cs, de, fr, nb_NO, nl, tr</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-04-22" version="1.1">
      <description>
        <p>
          This version contains minor technical changes.
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix blurry welcome image</li>
          <li>Updated transmission submodule</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-04-06" version="1.0">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is the first stable release of Fragments.
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Support for torrent files</li>
          <li>Support for magnet links</li>
          <li>Automatically detects magnet links in your clipboard</li>
          <li>Simple queue management. Torrents can be reordered using drag and drop.</li>
          <li>Clean and structured user interface</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>