<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>gammastep</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">gammastep-indicator.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="cached" height="64" width="64">gammastep.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" width="128" type="cached">gammastep.png</icon>
  <id>gammastep-indicator.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Gammastep Indicator</name>
  <summary>Adjust display hue to outside lighting conditions</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Adjusts the color temperature of your screen according to your surroundings. This may help your eyes hurt less if you are working in front of the screen at night.</p>
    <p>The color temperature is set according to the position of the sun. A different color temperature is set during night and daytime. During twilight and early morning, the color temperature transitions smoothly from night to daytime temperature to allow your eyes to slowly adapt.</p>
    <p>This program provides a status icon that allows the user to control color temperature.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Каляровая тэмпература прызначаецца ў адпаведнасці са становішчам сонца. Розная каляровая тэмпература прызначаецца ў начны час і днём. Падчас змяркання і на золку, каляровая тэмпература паступова пераходзіць ад тэмпературы ночы да тэмпературы ў дзённы час, каб вашыя вочы паступова прызвычаіліся.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>La temperatura de color s'estableix segons la posició del sol. S'estableix una temperatura diferent durant el dia i durant la nit. Durant el capvespre i l'alba, la temperatura de color canvia suaument, de temperatura diürna a temperatura nocturna o viceversa, per permetre que els ulls s'adaptin lentament.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Barevná teplota je nastavována dle pozice Slunce na obloze. Jiná barevná teplota je nastavena během noci a jiná během dne. Při stmívání a rozednívání, barevná teplota pozvolna přejde z jednoho režimu do druhého, aby se oči stačily přizpůsobit.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Farvetemperaturen bliver sat i forhold til solens position og temperaturen ændrer sig fra dag til nat. Omkring solnedgang og solopgang sker der en glidende overgang mellem nattemperatur og dagtemperatur som langsomt lader dine øjne vænne sig til den ændrede farvetemperatur.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Die Farbtemperatur wird entsprechend zum Stand der Sonne eingestellt. In der Nacht und am Tag werden verschiedene Farbtemperaturen verwendet. Während der Dämmerung und am frühen Morgen wird die Farbtemperatur weich von Nacht auf Tag umgestellt, damit sich Ihre Augen langsam anpassen können.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>The colour temperature is set according to the position of the Sun. A different colour temperature is set during night and daytime. During twilight and early morning, the colour temperature transitions smoothly from night to daytime temperature to allow your eyes to slowly adapt.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Ajusta la temperatura de color de la pantalla de acuerdo con el entorno. Este ajuste puede ayudar a reducir el dolor de ojos si trabaja frente una pantalla por la noche.</p>
    <p>La temperatura de color se establece según la posición del sol. Se establece una temperatura distinta para el día y para la noche. Durante el atardecer y el amanecer, la temperatura de color cambia suavemente, de temperatura diurna a temperatura nocturna o viceversa, para permitir que los ojos se adapten lentamente.</p>
    <p>Este programa proporciona un ícono de notificación que permite al usuario controlar la temperatura de color</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>La température de couleur est définie en fonction de la position du soleil. Une température de couleur différente est appliquée durant le jour ou la nuit. Lors du lever ou du coucher du soleil, la température de couleur change doucement pour permettre à vos yeux de s'adapter.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A színhőmérsékletet a nap helyzetéhez igazítja. Különböző színhőmérsékletet állít be nappal és éjszaka. Szürkületben és kora reggel a színhőmérséklet átmenete az éjszakiról a nappali hőmérsékletre lehetővé teszi, hogy a szem lassan alkalmazkodhasson.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>La temperatura del colore è impostata in base alla posizione del sole. Vengono impostate temperature di colore differenti per la notte e per il giorno. Al crepuscolo e al mattino presto, la temperatura del colore passa delicatamente da quella notturna a quella diurna per consentire alla vista di abituarsi in modo graduale.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>色温度は太陽の位置に応じて設定されます。昼と夜とでは異なる色温度が設定されます。夕暮れ時や早朝の間は、 色温度は滑らかに変化してゆっくり目を慣れさせることができます。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Spalvos temperatūra nustatoma pagal Saulės vietą. Dienos metu ir nakties metu yra nustatomos skirtingos spalvos temperatūros. Sutemus ir ankstų rytą, spalvos temperatūra glotniai pereina iš nakties temperatūros į dienos temperatūrą, taip leisdama jūsų akims po truputį prisitaikyti.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Fargetermperaturen blir satt i henhold til solas posisjon. Fargetermperaturen er forskjellig for natt og dagtid. I skumringen og tidlig på morgenen toner fargetemperaturen mykt over i dagtermperatur for å la øyene dine tilpasse seg.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>De kleurtemperatuur wordt ingesteld aan de hand van de positie van de zon. Bij nacht wordt er een andere kleurtemperatuur ingesteld dan bij dag. Als het schemert of vroeg in de ochtend is, wordt de kleurtemperatuur geleidelijk en soepel van nacht naar dag gebracht, zodat uw ogen er langzaam aan kunnen wennen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Temperatura barwowa jest ustawiana w zależności od pozycji słońca. Różni się w dzień i w nocy. Podczas zmierzchania (i świtania), temperatura łagodnie zmienia się z dziennej na nocną (i odwrotnie), pozwalając oczom na powolne przyzwyczajanie się.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Gammastep ajusta a temperatura da cor de sua tela de acordo com o seu ambiente. Isso poder ajudar a irritar menos os olhos se você está trabalhando em frente a uma tela à noite.</p>
    <p>A temperatura da cor é definida de acordo com a posição do Sol. Diferentes temperaturas de cores são utilizadas durante a noite e o dia. Ao anoitecer e ao amanhecer, ocorre uma transição suave entre a temperatura de cor da noite para o dia para que seus olhos lentamente se adaptem.</p>
    <p>Esse programa exibe um ícone de status para que permite ao usuário controlar a temperature de cor.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Цветовая температура устанавливается в зависимости от положения солнца. Ночью и днём используется различная цветовая температура. В сумерки и ранним утром цветовая температура плавно переходит от ночных настроек к дневным, позволяя глазам постепенно адаптироваться.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Температура боје се се подешава у складу са положајем сунца. Другачија температура боје се поставља ноћу а другачија дању. У сумрак и рано јутро температура боје лагано прелази из ноћне у дневну температуру да би се вашим очима омогућило лакше привикавање.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Färgtemperaturen ställs in beroende på positionen av solen. En annan färgtemperatur sätts under natten och dagen. Under skymning och tidigt på morgonen övergår färgtemperaturen smidigt från natt till dagtidstemperatur för att ge dina ögon tid att långsamt anpassa sig.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Ekranınızın renk sıcaklığını çevrenize göre ayarlar. Bu, geceleri ekranın önünde çalışıyorsanız gözlerinizin daha az ağrımasına yardımcı olabilir. </p>
    <p>Renk sıcaklığı güneşin konumuna göre ayarlanır. Gece ve gündüz farklı bir renk sıcaklığı ayarlanır. Alacakaranlıkta ve sabahın erken saatlerinde, gözlerinizin yavaşça uyum sağlamasına izin vermek için renk sıcaklığı gece sıcaklığından gündüz sıcaklığına yumuşak bir şekilde geçiş yapar.</p>
    <p>Bu program, kullanıcının renk sıcaklığını denetlemesini sağlayan bir durum simgesi sağlar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Колірна температура налаштовується відповідно до позиції сонця. Різна колірна температура відображення монітору вмикається у залежності від періоду доби. Під час настання сутінків чи сходу сонця, колірна температура повільно переходить із нічної до денної температури, що дозволяє вашим очам повільно адаптуватися.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>该软件可以根据日照位置、日夜变化来设置屏幕色温，随着时间推移，色温会逐渐转变，保证让您的眼睛能够舒舒服服地适应。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>根據太陽位置日夜變化來設置螢幕色溫。隨著日夜交替時間轉換，色溫設置則會逐漸變化，可讓您的眼睛能夠漸漸地適應。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://gitlab.com/chinstrap/gammastep</url>
</component>