<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <description>
    <p>
      gitg is a graphical user interface for git. It aims at being a small,
      fast and convenient tool to visualize the history of git repositories.
      Besides visualization, gitg also provides several utilities to manage your
      repository and commit your work.
    </p>
    <p>Goals:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Browse local git repositories</li>
      <li>Clone local and remote git repositories</li>
      <li>Commit files</li>
      <li>Retrieve patch from a commit</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El gitg és una interfície gràfica d'usuari pel git. El seu objectiu és ser una eina ràpida i còmode per a visualitzar l'historial de dipòsits git. A banda de la visualització, el gitg també incorpora diverses utilitats per a gestionar els dipòsits i publicar els vostres canvis.</p>
    <p>Objectius:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Navega pels dipòsits git locals</li>
      <li>Clona dipòsits git tant locals com remots</li>
      <li>Publica els fitxers</li>
      <li>Recupera pedaços d'una publicació</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>gitg je grafické uživatelské rozhraní pro git. Záměrem je malý, rychlý a praktický nástroj pro grafickou prezentaci historie repozitářů git. Mimo toho také poskytuje několik pomůcek pro správu repozitářů a zařazování vaší práce do nich.</p>
    <p>Zaměřuje se na:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Procházení místních repozitářů git</li>
      <li>Klonování místních a vzdálených repozitářů git</li>
      <li>Zařazování souborů</li>
      <li>Vytváření záplat</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>gitg er en grafisk brugerflade til git. Den bestræber sig på at være et lille, hurtigt og bekvemt værktøj til at visualisere historikken af git-arkiver. Udover visualisering har gitg også adskillige redskaber til at håndtere dit arkiv og committe dit arbejde.</p>
    <p>Mål:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Gennemse lokale git-arkiver</li>
      <li>Klon lokale og remote git-arkiver</li>
      <li>Commit filer</li>
      <li>Hent patch fra et commit</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>gitg ist eine grafische Benutzeroberfläche für Git. Es möchte ein kleines, schnelles und bequemes Werkzeug sein, um die Chronik von Git-Repositorys darzustellen. Neben der Darstellung bietet Gitg verschiedene Werkzeuge, um Ihr Repository zu verwalten und Ihre Änderungen zu commiten.</p>
    <p>Ziele:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Lokale Git-Repositorys durchstöbern</li>
      <li>Lokale und entfernte Git-Repositorys klonen</li>
      <li>Dateien commiten</li>
      <li>Einen Patch eines Commits erstellen</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Στόχοι:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Περιήγηση τοπικών αποθετηρίων git</li>
      <li>Δημιουργία κλώνου τοπικού και απομακρυσμένου αποθετηρίου git</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>gitg is a graphical user interface for git. It aims at being a small, fast and convenient tool to visualise the history of git repositories. Besides visualisation, gitg also provides several utilities to manage your repository and commit your work.</p>
    <p>Goals:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Browse local git repositories</li>
      <li>Clone local and remote git repositories</li>
      <li>Commit files</li>
      <li>Retrieve patch from a commit</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p>gitg estas grafika fasado por git. Ĝi celas esti eta, rapida, kaj kunvena ilo por bildigi la historion de git-deponejoj. Krom bildigo, gitg ankaŭ provizas kelkajn ilojn por mastrumi vian deponejon kaj enmeti vian laboron.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Foliumi lokajn git-deponejojn</li>
      <li>Klonigi lokajn kaj deforajn git-deponejojn</li>
      <li>Enmeti dosierojn</li>
      <li>Ricevi flikaĵon de la enmetaĵo</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>gitg es una interfaz gráfica de usuario para git. Pretende ser una herramienta pequeña, rápida y adecuada para ver el histórico de repositorios git. Más allá de la visualización gitg proporciona varias utilidades para gestionar su repositorio y aplicar su trabajo.</p>
    <p>Objetivos:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Examinar repositorios git locales</li>
      <li>Clonar repositorios git locales y remotos</li>
      <li>Aplicar cambios en archivos</li>
      <li>Obtener el parche de un «commit»</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>gitg git erabiltzeko erabiltzaile-interfaze grafikoa da. Tresna txikia, azkarra eta egokia izateko asmoz sortu zen, eta git biltegien historia bistaratzeko balio du. Bisualizazioaz gain, gitg-k zenbait tresna ditu zure biltegia kudeatzeko eta zure lana egikaritzeko.</p>
    <p>Helburuak:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Arakatu git biltegi lokalak</li>
      <li>Klonatu git biltegi lokalak eta urrunekoak</li>
      <li>Egikaritu fitxategiak</li>
      <li>Atzitu adabakia egikaritze batetik</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>gitg on graafinen käyttöliittymä gitiin. Sen on tarkoitus olla pieni, nopea ja kätevä työkalu git-tietovarastojen historian visualisointiin. Visualisoinnin lisäksi gitg tarjoaa useita työkaluja tietovarastojen hallintaan ja tekemäsi työn kommitointiin.</p>
    <p>Tavoitteet:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Selaa paikallisia git-tietovarastoja</li>
      <li>Kloonaa paikallisia ja etä-git-tietovarastoja</li>
      <li>Kommitoi tiedostoja</li>
      <li>Luo paikka kommitista</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>gitg est une interface graphique pour git. Il vise à être un outil simple, rapide et pratique pour visualiser l’historique des dépôts git. Outre la visualisation, gitg fournit également plusieurs utilitaires permettant de gérer votre dépôt et de valider votre travail.</p>
    <p>Objectifs :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Naviguer dans les dépôts locaux</li>
      <li>Cloner des dépôts git locaux et distants</li>
      <li>Commiter les fichiers</li>
      <li>Créer un correctif à partir d’un commit</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>gitg al è une interface utent grafiche par git. Al ponte a jessi un piçul, svelt e util imprest par visualizâ la cronologjie dai dipuesits di git. Sore a dâ une visualizazion, gitg al furnìs ancje diviersis utilitâts par gjestî il to dipuesit e consegnâ il to lavôr.</p>
    <p>Obietîfs:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Eplore i dipuesits git locâi</li>
      <li>Clone i dipuesits git locâi e lontans</li>
      <li>Cree un blec partint di une consegne</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>gitg é unha interface gráfica para git. Intenta ser unha ferramenta pequena, rápida e conveniente para visualizar o historial de repositorios git. Ademais da visualización, gitg tamén lle fornece varias utilidades para xestionar o seu repositorio e remitir o seu traballo.</p>
    <p>Obxectivos:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Explorar repositorios git locais</li>
      <li>Clonar repositorios git locais e remotos</li>
      <li>Remitir ficheiros</li>
      <li>Obter un parche desde un commit</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>יעדים:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>עיון במאגרי git מקומיים</li>
      <li>הגשת קבצים</li>
      <li>אחזור טלאי ממאגר</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A gitg egy grafikus felhasználói felület a git verziókezelőhöz. Célja, hogy egy kicsi, gyors és kényelmes eszköz legyen a git tárolók előzményeinek megjelenítéséhez. A vizuális megjelenítés mellett a gitg számos segédprogramot is biztosít a tároló kezeléséhez és a munka véglegesítéséhez.</p>
    <p>Célok:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Helyi git tárolók tallózása</li>
      <li>Helyi és távoli git tárolók klónozása</li>
      <li>Fájlok véglegesítése</li>
      <li>Folt lekérése egy véglegesítésből</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>gitg merupakan antarmuka pengguna grafis untuk git. Ini bertujuan untuk menjadi alat yang ringan, cepat dan nyaman untuk memvisualisasikan riwayat repositori git. Selain visualisasi, gitg juga menyediakan beberapa utilitas untuk mengelola repositori Anda dan melakukan pekerjaan Anda.</p>
    <p>Tujuan:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Jelajahi repositori git lokal</li>
      <li>Klon repositori git lokal dan remote</li>
      <li>Berkas komit</li>
      <li>Ambil tambalan dari komit</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>gitg è un'interfaccia grafica per git: uno strumento semplice e veloce per visualizzare la storia di repository git. Oltre alla visualizzazione dei repository, gitg fornisce diversi strumenti per la gestione del lavoro con git.</p>
    <p>Goal:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Esplorare repository git locali</li>
      <li>Clonare repository git locali e remoti</li>
      <li>Eseguire il commit di file</li>
      <li>Recuperare patch da un commit</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <p>gitg — git үшін графикалық пайдаланушы интерфейсі. Ол git репозиторийлер тарихын көрнекілендіру үшін шағын, жылдам әрі ыңғайлы құрал болуға бағытталған. Визуализациядан басқа, gitg сондай-ақ, репозиторийді басқару және өз жұмысыңызды жасау үшін бірнеше утилиталарды ұсынады.</p>
    <p>Мақсаттар:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Жергілікті git репозиторийлерін шолу</li>
      <li>Жергілікті және қашықтағы git репозиторийлерін клондау</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>gitg는 git 그래픽 사용자 인터페이스입니다. git 저장소의 이력을 나타내는 작은 규모의, 빠르고, 편리한 도구를 지향합니다. 시각 표현 기능과 더불어 gitg는 저장소를 관리하고 작업 내용을 제출하는 몇가지 편의 수단을 제공합니다.</p>
    <p>목표:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>로컬 git 저장소 탐색</li>
      <li>로컬 및 원격 git 저장소 복제</li>
      <li>파일 커밋</li>
      <li>커밋에서 패치 가져오기</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>gitg yra git grafinė naudotojo sąsaja. Ji siekia būti paprastu, greitu bei patogiu įrankiu vizualizuoti git saugyklos istoriją. Be vizualizacijos gitg taip pat pateikia įrankių jūsų saugyklai tvarkyti bei darbui patvirtinti.</p>
    <p>Tikslai:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Naršyti vietines git saugyklas</li>
      <li>Klonuoti vietines bei nuotolines git saugyklas</li>
      <li>Patvirtinti failus</li>
      <li>Gauti pataisą pagal patvirtinimą</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>git ialah satu antara muka pengguna bergrafi untuk git. Ia merupakan alat bersaiz kecil, pantas dan mudah untuk visualkan sejarah repositori git. Selain dari pemayaan, gitg juga menyediakan beberapa utiliti untuk mengurus repositori anda dan keterikatan kerja anda.</p>
    <p>Matlamat:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Layar repositori-repositori git setempat</li>
      <li>Klon repositori-repositori setempat dan git jauh</li>
      <li>Ikat fail</li>
      <li>Peroleh tampalan dari satu keterikatan</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ne">
    <p>लक्षहरू:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>कमिटबाट प्याच पुन: प्राप्त गर्नुहोस्</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>gitg is een grafische gebruikersinterface voor git. Het heeft als doel een snel, klein en handig hulpmiddel te zijn om de geschiedenis van git-repository’s te visualiseren. Naast visualisering biedt gitg ook verschillende hulpmiddelen om uw repository te beheren en uw werk te committen.</p>
    <p>Doelen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Lokale git-repository’s doorbladeren</li>
      <li>Kloon lokale en externe git-repository’s</li>
      <li>Bestanden committen</li>
      <li>Patch ophalen uit commit</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>Objectius :</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>gitg to graficzny interfejs użytkownika dla systemu git. To w zamierzeniu małe, szybkie i wygodne narzędzie do wizualizowania historii repozytoriów git. Oprócz tego gitg zapewnia także kilka narzędzi do zarządzania repozytoriami i zatwierdzania swojej pracy.</p>
    <p>Funkcje programu:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Przeglądanie lokalnych repozytoriów git</li>
      <li>Klonowanie lokalnych i zdalnych repozytoriów git</li>
      <li>Zatwierdzanie plików</li>
      <li>Tworzenie łaty z zatwierdzenia</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O gitg é uma interface gráfica do utilizador para o git. Destina-se a ser uma ferramenta pequena, rápida e conveniente para visualizar o histórico de repositórios git. Além da visualização, o gitg também fornece diversos utilitários para gerir o seu repositório e submeter o seu trabalho.</p>
    <p>Objectivos:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Navegar repositórios git locais</li>
      <li>Clonar repositórios gits locais e remotos</li>
      <li>Submeter ficheiros</li>
      <li>Obter um patch de uma submissão</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>O gitg é uma interface gráfica do usuário para o git. Destina-se a ser uma ferramenta pequena, rápida e conveniente para visualizar o histórico de repositórios git. Além da visualização, o gitg também fornece diversos utilitários para gerenciar seu repositório e fazer commit do seu trabalho.</p>
    <p>Finalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Navegar repositórios git locais</li>
      <li>Clonar repositórios gits locais e remotos</li>
      <li>Fazer commits de arquivos</li>
      <li>Obter um patch de um commit</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>gitg este o interfață grafică pentru utilizator pentru git. Își propune să fie o unealtă de mici dimensiuni, rapidă și convenabilă pentru a vizualiza istoricul depozitelor git. În afară de vizualizare, gitg furnizează de asemenea mai multe utilitare pentru a vă administra depozitul și pentru a vă comite munca.</p>
    <p>Obiective:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Navighează depozitele git locale</li>
      <li>Clonează depozitele git locale și la distanță</li>
      <li>Fișierele comitului</li>
      <li>Recuperează un patch de la un comit</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Ciele:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Prehliadanie miestnych git repozitárov</li>
      <li>Klonovanie miestnych a vzdialených repozitárov git</li>
      <li>Začleňovanie súborov</li>
      <li>Získavanie záplat zo začlenení</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Program gitg je uporabniški vmesnik za git. Zasnovan je z mislijo hitrega delovanja in priročnosti za pregled zgodovine skladišč git. Ob vizualizaciji program podpira tudi več pripomočkov z a upravljanje s skladišči in uveljavljanje kode.</p>
    <p>Cilji:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Prebrskaj krajevna skladišča git</li>
      <li>Kloniranje krajevnih in oddaljenih skladišč git</li>
      <li>Uveljavi datoteke</li>
      <li>Pridobi popravek iz izbrane uveljavitve</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Гитг је графичко корисничко сучеље за гит алат. Намера је да буде мала, брза и одговарајућа алатка за визуелизовање историјата гит ризнице. Поред визуелизовања, гитг пружа и пар других алата за управљање вашом ризницом и за предавање вашег рада.</p>
    <p>Циљеви:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Прегледај локалне гит ризнице</li>
      <li>Клонирање локалних и удаљених гит ризница</li>
      <li>Предај датотеке</li>
      <li>Допреми закрпу из предаје</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>gitg är ett grafiskt användargränssnitt för git. Det siktar på att vara ett litet, snabbt och behändigt verktyg för att visualisera historiken för git-arkiv. Förutom visualisering tillhandahåller gitg också flera verktyg för att hantera ditt arkiv och checka in ditt arbete.</p>
    <p>Mål:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Bläddra i lokala git-arkiv</li>
      <li>Klona lokala git-arkiv och fjärrarkiv</li>
      <li>Checka in filer</li>
      <li>Erhåll en patch från en incheckning</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>gitg, git için grafiksel kullanıcı arayüzüdür; depoların geçmişini görselleştirmeyi amaçlayan küçük, hızlı ve kullanışlı araçtır. Bunların yanı sıra deponuzu yönetmeniz ve çalışmanızı işlemeniz için birtakım yardımcı araçlar sunar.</p>
    <p>Amaçlar:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Yerel git depolarına göz at</li>
      <li>Yerel ve uzak git depolarını klonla</li>
      <li>Dosyaları işle</li>
      <li>Bir işlemeden yama al</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>gitg — графічний інтерфейс користувача для git. Програма є компактним, швидким і зручним засобом візуалізації журналу сховищ git. Окрім візуалізації, у gitg передбачено декілька інструментів для керування вашим сховищем та надсилання результатів вашої роботи.</p>
    <p>Призначення:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Навігація локальними сховищами git</li>
      <li>Клонування локальних та віддалених сховищ git</li>
      <li>Внесення файлів до сховищ</li>
      <li>Створення латок на основі внесків</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="vi">
    <p>gitg là lmootj giao diện người dùng dạng đồ họa dành cho git. Nó nhắm đến một công cụ nhỏ, nhanh và thuận tiện cho việc hiển thị trực quan lịch sử của một kho git. Bên cạch tính trực quan, gitg còn cung cấp nhiều tiện ích để quản lý kho và chuyển giao công việc của bạn.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Duyệt các kho git nội bộ</li>
      <li>Nhân bản kho git nội bộ cũng như trên mạng</li>
      <li>Chuyển giao các tập tin</li>
      <li>Lây miếng vá từ lần chuyển giao</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>gitg 是个 git 的图形用户界面。它的目标是成为小型、快速方便的工具，可视化 git 仓库的历史。除了可视化功能，gitg 也提供了多个实用工具来管理你的仓库以及提交你的工作。</p>
    <p>目标：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>浏览本地 git 仓库</li>
      <li>克隆本地和远程 git 仓库</li>
      <li>提交文件</li>
      <li>从提交中提取补丁</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>目標：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>瀏覽本機 git 版本庫</li>
      <li>複製本機及遠端 git 版本庫</li>
      <li>提交檔案</li>
      <li>自提交抓取修補檔 (patch)</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>gitg</pkgname>
  <icon width="64" height="64" type="cached">org.gnome.gitg.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">org.gnome.gitg.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.gitg</id>
  <name>gitg</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">gitg</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">gitg</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">gitg</name>
  <name lang="vi">gitg</name>
  <name lang="uk">gitg</name>
  <name lang="tr">gitg</name>
  <name lang="sv">gitg</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">gitg</name>
  <name lang="sr">гитг</name>
  <name lang="sl">gitg</name>
  <name lang="sk">gitg</name>
  <name lang="ru">gitg</name>
  <name lang="ro">gitg</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">gitg</name>
  <name lang="pt">gitg</name>
  <name lang="pl">gitg</name>
  <name lang="pa">gitg</name>
  <name lang="oc">gitg</name>
  <name lang="nl">gitg</name>
  <name lang="ne">gitg</name>
  <name lang="nb">gitg</name>
  <name lang="ms">gitg</name>
  <name lang="lv">gitg</name>
  <name lang="lt">gitg</name>
  <name lang="ko">gitg</name>
  <name lang="kk">gitg</name>
  <name lang="ja">gitg</name>
  <name lang="it">gitg</name>
  <name lang="id">gitg</name>
  <name lang="hu">gitg</name>
  <name lang="he">gitg</name>
  <name lang="gl">gitg</name>
  <name lang="fur">gitg</name>
  <name lang="fr">gitg</name>
  <name lang="fi">gitg</name>
  <name lang="eu">gitg</name>
  <name lang="es">gitg</name>
  <name lang="eo">gitg</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">gitg</name>
  <name lang="el">gitg</name>
  <name lang="de">gitg</name>
  <name lang="da">gitg</name>
  <name lang="cs">gitg</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">gitg</name>
  <name lang="ca">gitg</name>
  <name lang="bs">gitg</name>
  <name lang="bg">gitg</name>
  <name lang="as">gitg</name>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <summary>Graphical user interface for git</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">git 的圖形使用者介面</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">Git 的图形用户界面</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Графічний інтерфейс користувача для git</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">git için grafiksel kullanıcı arayüzü</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Grafiskt användargränssnitt för git</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Графичко корисничко сучеље за гит</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Grafični uporabniški vmesnik za git</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Grafické používateľské rozhranie pre git</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Interfață grafică pentru utilizator pentru git</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Interface gráfica do usuário para o git</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Uma interface gráfica de utilizador para o git</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Graficzny interfejs użytkownika dla systemu git</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Grafische gebruikersinterface voor git</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Antara muka pengguna bergrafik untuk git</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Grafinė naudotojo sąsaja git įrankiui</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">git 그래픽 사용자 인터페이스</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">Git үшін графикалық пайдаланушы интерфейсі</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Interfaccia grafica per git</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Antarmuka pengguna grafis untuk git</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Grafikus felhasználói felület a Githez</summary>
  <summary lang="he">מנשק משתמש גרפי ל־git</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Interface de usuario gráfica para git&lt;</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Interface utent grafiche par git</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Interface graphique pour git</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Graafinen käyttöliittymä git-versionhallintaan</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Git erabiltzeko erabiltzaile-interfaze grafikoa</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Interfaz gráfica de usuario para git</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Graphical user interface for git</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Γραφική διεπαφή χρήστη για το git</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Eine grafische Oberfläche für git</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Grafisk brugerflade til git</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Grafické uživatelské rozhraní pro git</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Interfície gràfica pel git</summary>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot width="1200" type="default" height="675">
      <image>https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Gitg?action=AttachFile&amp;do=get&amp;target=history.png</image>
      <caption>Browse repository history</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">瀏覽版本庫歷史記錄</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">浏览仓库历史</caption>
      <caption lang="vi">Duyệt lịch sử của kho</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Навігація журналом сховища</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Depo geçmişine göz at</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Bläddra i arkivhistorik</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Прегледај историјат ризнице</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Prebrskaj zgodovino skladišča</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Prehliadanie histórie repozitára</caption>
      <caption lang="ro">Navighează istoricul depozitului</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Navegar o histórico do repositório</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Navegar o histórico do repositório</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Przeglądanie historii repozytorium</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Repository-geschiedenis doorbladeren</caption>
      <caption lang="ms">Layar sejarah repositori</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Naršyti saugyklos istoriją</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">저장소 이력 탐색</caption>
      <caption lang="kk">Репозиторий тарихын шолу</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Sfogliare la cronologia di un repository</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Jelajahi riwayat repositori</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Tároló előzményeinek tallózása</caption>
      <caption lang="he">עיון בהיסטוריית המאגר</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Explorar o historial do repositorio</caption>
      <caption lang="fur">Esplore cronologjie dipuesits</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Naviguer dans l’historique du dépôt</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Selaa tietovaraston historiaa</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Arakatu biltegiaren historia</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Examinar el histórico del repositorio</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">Foliumi deponejan historion</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">Browse repository history</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Περιήγηση ιστορικού αποθετηρίου</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Verlauf des Repositorys durchblättern</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Gennemse arkivets historik</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Procházení historie repozitářů</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Navega per l'historial del dipòsit</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot height="675" width="1200">
      <image>https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Gitg?action=AttachFile&amp;do=get&amp;target=stage.png</image>
      <caption>Staging area to compose your commit</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">要產生提交的暫存區域</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">暂存区，用以撰写你的提交</caption>
      <caption lang="vi">Đưa lên bệ phóng khu vực để soạn lần chuyển giao</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Панель формування записів для створення внесків</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">İşlemenizi oluşturmak için hazırlama alanı</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Köområde för att skapa din incheckning</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Област штекања за састављање ваше предаје</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Območje pripravljenosti za skladanje uveljavitve</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Oblasť prípravy na vytvorenie vášho začlenenia</caption>
      <caption lang="ro">Zona de introducere pentru compunerea comitului</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Área de preparação para compor seu commit</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Área de preparação para compor a sua submissão</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Obszar roboczy do układania zatwierdzenia</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Staging-gebied om uw commit op te stellen</caption>
      <caption lang="ms">Kawasan berperingkat kerja untuk menggubah  anda</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Paruošimo vieta patvirtinimui sukurti</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">커밋을 작성할 스테이지 영역</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Area temporanea per comporre i commit</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Area staging untuk menyusun komit Anda</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Sorba állítási terület a véglegesítés összeállításához</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Área de reserva para compoñer a súa remisión</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Zone de présélection pour composer votre commit</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Valmistelualue kommitin lähettämistä varten</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Zure egikaritzea konposatzeko konfigurazio-area</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Área de reserva para componer sus «commit»</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">Antaŭenmeta areo por kopomni vian enmetaĵon</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">Staging area to compose your commit</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Bereitstellungsbereich zum Zusammenstellen Ihres Commits</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Staging-området til at skabe dit commit</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Oblast s připravenými změnami pro zařazení</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Àrea de «staging» per composar la vostra comissió</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot width="1200" height="675">
      <image>https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Gitg?action=AttachFile&amp;do=get&amp;target=commit.png</image>
      <caption>Commit staged changes</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">提交暫存變更</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">提交暂存的变更</caption>
      <caption lang="vi">Chuyển giao các thay đổi đã trên bệ phóng</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Внесення сформованих змін</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">İşlenmeye hazır değişiklikleri işle</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Checka in köade ändringar</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Предај уштекане предаје</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Uveljavi pripravljene spremembe</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Začlenenie pripravených zmien</caption>
      <caption lang="ro">Comite modificările introduse</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Fazer commit alterações preparadas (stage)</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Submeter alterações preparadas</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Zatwierdzanie zmian będących w przechowalni</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Gestagede wijzigingen committen</caption>
      <caption lang="ms">Perubahan keterikatan berperingkat</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Patvirtinti paruoštus pakeitimus</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">스테이지에 올린 바뀐 내용</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Eseguire il commit delle modifiche indicizzate</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Komit perubahan yang di-stage-kan</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Sorba állított változtatások véglegesítése</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Remitir os cambios reservados</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Commiter les modifications présélectionnées</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Kommitoi valmistellut muutokset</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Egikaritu konfiguratutako aldaketak</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Aplicar cambios reservados</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">Enmeti antaŭenmetitajn ŝanĝojn</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">Commit staged changes</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Bereitgestellte Änderungen commiten</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Commit stagede ændringer</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Zařazování připravených změn</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Comissiona els canvis de «staging»</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot width="1200" height="675">
      <image>https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Gitg?action=AttachFile&amp;do=get&amp;target=projects.png</image>
      <caption>Overview of recently used repositories</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">顯示最近使用版本庫的概覽</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">当前所用仓库的概览</caption>
      <caption lang="vi">Tổng quan của các kho mới dùng gần đây</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Огляд списку нещодавно використаних сховищ</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Son kullanılan depolara genel bakış</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Översikt över senast använda arkiv</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Преглед недавно коришћених ризница</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Pregled nedavno uporabljenih skladišč</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Prehľad nedávno použitých repozitárov</caption>
      <caption lang="ro">Prezentarea generală a depozitelor utilizate recent</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Visão geral de repositórios recentemente usados</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Visão geral de repositórios recentemente usados</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Przegląd ostatnio używanych repozytoriów</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Overzicht van recent gebruikte repository’s</caption>
      <caption lang="ms">Selayang pandang repositori-repositori digunakan baru-baru ini</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Neseniai naudotų saugyklų apžvalga</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">최근 사용한 저장소 목록 개요</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Panoramica dei repository utilizzati di recente</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Tinjauan tentang repositori yang digunakan baru-baru ini</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">A legutóbb használt tárolók áttekintése</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Vista previa dos repositorios usados recentemente</caption>
      <caption lang="fur">Panoramiche dai dipuesits doprâts di resint</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Vue d’ensemble des dépôts récemment utilisés</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Katsaus viimeksi käytettyihin tietovarastoihin</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Azken aldian erabilitzko biltegien ikuspegi orokorra</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Vista general de los repositorios usados recientemente</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">Superrigardo de freŝdate uzataj deponejoj</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">Overview of recently used repositories</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Übersicht der zuletzt verwendeten Repositorys</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Oversigt over senest brugte arkiver</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Přehled naposledy použitých repozitářů</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Vista general dels dipòsits utilitzats recentment</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="3.32.1" type="stable" date="2019-07-25">
      <description>
        <p>Bug fixes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Support repository being null</li>
          <li>Allow copying file names</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-05-23" version="3.32.0" type="stable">
      <description>
        <p>Bug fixes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Detect links in commit messages</li>
          <li>Push action with http/ssh support</li>
          <li>Fix time sort mode</li>
          <li>Add push support</li>
          <li>Add typeahead find feature</li>
          <li>Respect system fonts</li>
          <li>Update submodules at clone</li>
          <li>Add body to patch</li>
          <li>Shorcut to open preferences</li>
          <li>Honor GIT_DIR env</li>
          <li>Update menus for AppMenu removal</li>
          <li>Bump libgit2 to 0.27</li>
          <li>Use Unicode typography in user-visible strings</li>
          <li>Fix shared library paths in typelib files</li>
          <li>Migrate from Intltool to Gettext</li>
          <li>Meson polish</li>
          <li>Removed autotools</li>
          <li>Fixes in documentation</li>
          <li>Fixed several deprecations</li>
          <li>Misc fixes</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release type="stable" date="2018-10-25" version="3.30.1">
      <description>
        <p>Bug fixes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Meson improvements</li>
          <li>Fix parsing title and body for message commit</li>
          <li>Search repositories ignoring case</li>
          <li>Added standalone mode</li>
          <li>Allow to config patience algorithm</li>
          <li>GUI improvements</li>
          <li>Removed autotools buildsystem</li>
          <li>Fixed mac compilation</li>
          <li>Misc fixes</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.gitg.desktop</launchable>
  <update_contact>albfan@gnome.org</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">gitg</translation>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <developer_name>The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">GNOME 專案</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 项目</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="vi">Dự án GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Проєкт GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">GNOME Projesi</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Гном пројекат</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Proiectul GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="oc">Lo projècte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Het Gnome-project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ne">जिनोम परियोजना</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ms">Projek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">GNOME projektas</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">그놈 프로젝트</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="kk">GNOME жобасы</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Il progetto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Proyek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">מיזם GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">O proxecto de GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fur">Il progjet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Le projet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Gnome-projekti</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">GNOME proiektua</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">El Proyecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">La GNOME-Projekto</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Το έργο GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Das GNOME-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Gitg</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gitg/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://wiki.gnome.org/TranslationProject</url>
</component>