<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>gnome-network-displays</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.NetworkDisplays.desktop</launchable>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">org.gnome.NetworkDisplays.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">org.gnome.NetworkDisplays.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.NetworkDisplays.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>GNOME Network Displays</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 网络显示器</name>
  <name lang="uk">Мережеві дисплеї GNOME</name>
  <name lang="tr">GNOME Ağ Ekranları</name>
  <name lang="sv">GNOME Nätverksskärmar</name>
  <name lang="sr">Гномов екран на мрежи</name>
  <name lang="sl">Omrežni zasloni GNOME</name>
  <name lang="ro">Afișaje de rețea GNOME</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">GNOME Tela via Rede</name>
  <name lang="pl">Ekrany sieciowe GNOME</name>
  <name lang="nl">Gnome Netwerkschermen</name>
  <name lang="ja">GNOME ネットワークディスプレイ	</name>
  <name lang="it">GNOME Network Displays</name>
  <name lang="id">Tampilan Jaringan GNOME</name>
  <name lang="hr">GNOME mrežni zasloni</name>
  <name lang="fr">Affichages Réseau GNOME</name>
  <name lang="fi">Gnomen verkkonäytöt</name>
  <name lang="eu">GNOME Sareko Bistaratzeak</name>
  <name lang="es">Pantallas en red de GNOME</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">GNOME Network Displays</name>
  <name lang="de">GNOME Netzwerkbildschirme</name>
  <name lang="cs">Síťové displeje GNOME</name>
  <name lang="ca">Pantalles per xarxa del GNOME</name>
  <summary>Stream the desktop to Wi-Fi Display capable devices</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">将桌面串流至支持 Wi-Fi 显示的设备</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Потокове мовлення стільниці на пристрої дисплеїв із можливостями Wi-Fi</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Masaüstünü Kablosuz Ekran özellikli aygıtlara aktarır</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Strömma skrivbordet till enheter kapabla för Wi-Fi-visning</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Преточите радну површ на уређаје са могућношћу бежичног приказа</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Pretok slike namizja na naprave s podporo zaslonov Wi-Fi</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Streaming a desktopului la dispozitivele capabile de afișaj Wi-Fi</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Transmita do seu computador para dispositivos com capacidade de Wi-Fi Display</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Wyświetlanie pulpitu na urządzeniach obsługujących protokół Wi-Fi Display</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Stream het bureaublad naar apparaten compatibel met Wi-Fi Display</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">デスクトップをWi-Fiディスプレイに対応しているデバイスへストリーム配信	します</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Trasmetti il desktop ai dispositivi compatibili con Wi-Fi Display</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Streaming desktop ke perangkat berkemampuan Display Wi-Fi</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Emitirajte prikaz radne površine na bežične zaslone</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Diffusez le bureau sur des appareils compatibles avec l'affichage via Wi-Fi</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Suoratoista työpöytä Wi-Fi Display -yhteensopiville laitteille</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Bidali mahaigainaren korrontea wifi bidez bistaratzeko gai diren gailuetara</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Enviar el escritorio a dispositivos inalámbricos con pantalla dispoibles</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Stream the desktop to Wi-Fi Display capable devices</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Zeigt den Desktop auf Netzwerkfähigen Bildschirmen an</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Vysílejte svoji plochu na zařízení s podporou displejů Wi-Fi</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Envia l'escriptori a dispositius capaços de mostrar pantalles per Wi-Fi</summary>
  <url type="homepage">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-network-displays</url>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-network-displays</translation>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-network-displays/-/raw/master/data/appdata/device-list.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <description>
    <p>
		GNOME Network Displays allows you to cast your desktop to a remote display. Currently
		implemented is support for casting to Wi-Fi Display capable devices (a.k.a. Miracast).
		</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Pantalles per xarxa del GNOME us permet enviar l'escriptori a una pantalla remota. Actualment està implementat el suport per a enviar a dispositius capaços de mostrar pantalles per Wi-Fi (com Miracast).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Síťové displeje GNOME vám umožní vysílat dění na vaší ploše na vzdálený displej. V současnosti je implementována podpora pro vysílání na zařízení s podporou displejů Wi-Fi (známé také jako Miracast).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>GNOME Netzwerkbildschirme erlaubt die Nutzung von netzwerkfähigen Monitoren. Derzeit werden „Wi-Fi Display“ (Miracast) fähige Monitore unterstützt.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>GNOME Network Displays allows you to cast your desktop to a remote display. Currently implemented is support for casting to Wi-Fi Display capable devices (a.k.a. Miracast).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Pantallas en red de GNOME le permite mostrar su escritorio en una pantalla remota. Actualmente se soporta el envío a dispositivos inalámbricos (Miracast).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>GNOME Sareko Bistaratzeak aplikazioaren bidez, mahaigaina urruneko pantaila batera bidali daiteke. Une honetan, wifi bidez bistaratzeko gai diren gailuetara (alegia, Miracast gailuetara) bideoa bidaltzea onartzen da.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Gnome-verkkonäytöt mahdollistaa työpöydän suoratoistamisen etänäyttöön. Nyt toteutettuna on tuki Wi-Fi Display -yhteensopiville laitteille, jotka tunnetaan myös nimellä Miracast.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Affichages Réseau GNOME vous permet de diffuser votre bureau sur un affichage distant. Actuellement, seule la diffusion sur des appareils compatibles avec l'affichage via Wi-Fi (alias Miracast) est prise en charge.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>GNOME mrežni zasloni omogućuju vam emitiranje vaše radne površine na udaljeni zaslon. Trenutno je implementirana podrška emitiranja na bežične zaslone (poznata kao Miracast)</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Tampilan Jaringan GNOME memungkinkan Anda untuk menyorot desktop Anda ke layar jauh. Yang saat ini diimplementasikan adalah dukungan untuk penyorotan bagi peranti berkemampuan Tampilan Wi-Fi (alias Miracast).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>GNOME Network Display ti consente di trasmettere il tuo desktop a un display remoto. Attualmente è implementato il supporto per il casting su dispositivi compatibili con Wi-Fi Display (a.k.a. Miracast).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>GNOMEネットワークディスプレイは、あなたのデスクトップをリモートのディスプレイに配信することができます。現在、Wi-Fi ディスプレイ対応デバイス(別名 Miracast, ミラーリング)に対応しています。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Gnome Netwerkschermen laat u uw bureaublad streamen naar een extern beeldscherm. Momenteel wordt enkel streamen naar apparaten compatibel met Wi-Fi Display ('Miracast') ondersteund.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Program Ekrany sieciowe GNOME umożliwia wyświetlanie pulpitu na zdalnym ekranie. Obecnie zaimplementowana jest obsługa wyświetlania na urządzeniach zgodnych z protokołem Wi-Fi Display (znanym także jako Miracast).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>GNOME Tela via Rede permite projetar seu computador em uma tela remota. Atualmente está implementado o suporte à projeção em dispositivos compatíveis com o Wi-Fi Display (também conhecido como Miracast).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Afișajele de rețea GNOME vă permite să vă proiectați desktop-ul la un afișaj de la distanță. Implementat în mod curent este suport pentru proiectarea la dispozitive capabile de afișaj Wi-Fi (adică Miracast).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Program Omrežni zasloni GNOME omogoča prikaz namizja na oddaljenem zaslonu. Trenutno je omogočena podpora za prikaz na napravah Wi-Fi (Miracast).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Гномов екран на мрежи вам омогућава да приказујете вашу радну површ на удаљеном екрану. Тренутно примењено је подршка за емитовање на уређаје са могућношћу бежичног приказа (тј. Миракаст).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>GNOME Nätverksskärmar låter dig överföra ditt skrivbord till en fjärrskärm. För närvarande är stöd för casting till enheter kapabla för Wi-Fi-visning implementerat (så kallad Miracast).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>GNOME Ağ Ekranları, masaüstünüzü uzaktaki ekrana aktarmanızı sağlar. Var olan uyarlama Kablosuz Görüntüleme özellikli aygıtlara (Miracast) aktarımı destekler.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>«Мережеві дисплеї GNOME» надають вам змогу транслювати зображення і звук з вашої стільниці на віддалену стільницю. У поточній версії реалізовано підтримку трансляції на пристрої із можливостями отримання даних дисплея Wi-Fi (тобто Miracast).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>GNOME 网络显示器允许您将桌面投射到远程显示器上。目前实现的是支持投射到 Wi-Fi 显示的设备（又称 Miracast）。</p>
  </description>
  <update_contact>bberg@gnome.org</update_contact>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release date="2020-06-22" version="0.90.4" />
    <release version="0.90.3" date="2020-04-29" />
    <release version="0.90.2" date="2019-12-16" />
    <release version="0.90.1" date="2019-07-10" />
    <release version="0.90.0" date="2019-06-17" />
  </releases>
</component>