<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>gnome.gnome-notes</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.Notes.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" height="64" type="cached">org.gnome.Notes.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" height="128" type="cached">org.gnome.Notes.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.Notes.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+ and LGPL-3.0 and LGPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Notes</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">筆記</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">筆記</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">便笺</name>
  <name lang="vi">Ghi chú</name>
  <name lang="uk">Примітки</name>
  <name lang="tr">Notlar</name>
  <name lang="tg">Ёддоштҳо</name>
  <name lang="te">చీటీలు</name>
  <name lang="ta">குறிப்புகள்</name>
  <name lang="sv">Anteckningar</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Beleško</name>
  <name lang="sr">Белешке</name>
  <name lang="sl">Sporočilca</name>
  <name lang="sk">Poznámky</name>
  <name lang="ru">Заметки</name>
  <name lang="ro">Notițe</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Notas</name>
  <name lang="pt">Notas</name>
  <name lang="pl">Notatki</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਨੋਟ</name>
  <name lang="or">ଟିପ୍ପଣୀ</name>
  <name lang="oc">Nòtas</name>
  <name lang="nl">Notities</name>
  <name lang="ne">द्रष्टव्यहरू</name>
  <name lang="nb">Notater</name>
  <name lang="ms">Nota</name>
  <name lang="ml">കുറിപ്പുകള്‍</name>
  <name lang="lv">Piezīmes</name>
  <name lang="lt">Rašteliai</name>
  <name lang="ko">메모</name>
  <name lang="kk">Естеліктер</name>
  <name lang="ja">メモ</name>
  <name lang="it">Note</name>
  <name lang="is">Minnispunktar</name>
  <name lang="id">Catatan</name>
  <name lang="hu">Jegyzetek</name>
  <name lang="hr">Bilješke</name>
  <name lang="he">פתקיות</name>
  <name lang="gl">Notas</name>
  <name lang="ga">Nótaí</name>
  <name lang="fur">Notis</name>
  <name lang="fr">Notes</name>
  <name lang="fi">Muistilaput</name>
  <name lang="fa">یادداشت‌ها</name>
  <name lang="eu">Oharrak</name>
  <name lang="et">Märkmed</name>
  <name lang="es">Notas</name>
  <name lang="eo">Notaro</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Notes</name>
  <name lang="en_AU">Notes</name>
  <name lang="el">Σημειώσεις</name>
  <name lang="de">Notizen</name>
  <name lang="da">Noter</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">Notes</name>
  <name lang="ca">Notes</name>
  <name lang="cs">Poznámky</name>
  <name lang="ckb">تێبینییەکان</name>
  <name lang="bs">Napomene</name>
  <name lang="be">Запісы</name>
  <name lang="as">টোকাসমূহ</name>
  <name lang="ar">ملاحظات</name>
  <name lang="af">Notas</name>
  <summary>Notes for GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">GNOME 筆記本</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">GNOME 的便笺本</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Примітки для GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">GNOME için Notlar</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Anteckningar för GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Белешке за Гном</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Sporočilca za GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Poznámky pre prostredie GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Заметки для GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Note pentru GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Notas para o GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Notas do GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Notatki dla środowiska GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Notities voor Gnome</summary>
  <summary lang="ne">जीनोम नोट</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Notater for GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Nota untuk GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">GNOME piezīmes</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Užrašinė GNOME aplinkai</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">그놈용 메모</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">GNOME үшін естеліктер қолданбасы</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">GNOME 向けメモ</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Note per GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Catatan untuk GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Jegyzetfüzet a GNOME-hoz</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Bilješke za GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="he">פתקיות עבור GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Notas para GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Notis par GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Notes pour GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Muistilaput Gnomelle</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">یادداشت‌ها برای گنوم</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">GNOMEren oharrak</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Notas para GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Notaro por GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Notes for GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Σημειώσεις για το GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Notizen für GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Noter til GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Notes del GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Poznámky pro GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="af">Notas vir GNOME</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      A quick and easy way to make freeform notes or jot down simple lists. Store as many notes as you like and share them by email.
    </p>
    <p>
      You can store your notes locally on your computer or sync with online services like ownCloud.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="af">
    <p>'n Vinnige en maklike manier om notas en eenvoudige lyste te skep. Stoor soveel as wat jy wil en deel hulle per epos.</p>
    <p>Jy kan jou notas plaaslik, op die rekenaar, stoor of sinchroniseer met aanlyn dienste soos Nextcloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Хутка і проста рабіце нататкі ў вольнай форме ці стварайце спісы. Захоўвайце столькі нататак, колікі жадаеце, і дзяліцеся імі праз электронную пошту.</p>
    <p>Вы можаце захоўваць нататкі на вашым камп'ютары ці сінхранізаваць іх з сеціўнымі службамі кшталту ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Una forma ràpida i senzilla de prendre notes o llistes simples. Emmagatzemeu tantes notes com vulgueu i compartiu-les per correu electrònic.</p>
    <p>Podeu emmagatzemar notes localment a l'ordinador o sincronitzar-les amb serveis en línia com ara ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Rychlý a jednoduchý způsob, jak si zapisovat volně psané poznámky nebo krátké bodové myšlenky. Zapište si tolik poznámek, kolik chcete a sdílejte je přes e-mail.</p>
    <p>Své poznámky si můžete uchovávat samostatně na svém počítači, nebo je synchronizovat se službami on-line, jako je ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>En hurtig og let måde at lave ustrukturerede noter eller enkle lister på. Gem så mange noter, som du vil, og del dem på e-mail.</p>
    <p>Du kan gemme dine noter lokalt på din computer eller synkronisere med onlinetjenester som ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Eine schnelle und einfache Möglichkeit, einfache Notizen oder Listen zu erstellen. Speichern Sie beliebig viele Notizen und geben Sie sie per E-Mail frei.</p>
    <p>Sie können Ihre Notizen lokal auf Ihrem Rechner speichern oder mit Onlinediensten wie ownCloud synchronisieren.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Ένας γρήγορος και εύκολος τρόπος για να κάνετε ελεύθερες σημειώσεις ή να καταγράψετε απλές λίστες. Αποθηκεύστε όσες σημειώσεις θέλετε και μοιραστείτε με ηλεκτρονική αλληλογραφία.</p>
    <p>Μπορείτε να αποθηκεύσετε τις σημειώσεις σας τοπικά στον υπολογιστή σας ή να συγχρονίσετε με τις δικτυακές υπηρεσίες όπως το ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>A quick and easy way to make freeform notes or jot down simple lists. Store as many notes as you like and share them by e-mail.</p>
    <p>You can store your notes locally on your computer or sync with online services like ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p>Rapida kaj facila maniero por fari liberformajn notojn aŭ skribi simplajn listojn. Konservu tiom da notoj kiel vi ŝatas, kaj kunhavigu ilin per retpoŝto.</p>
    <p>Vi povas konservi viajn notojn loke sur via komputilo aŭ sinkronigi ilin per retaj servoj kiel ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Una manera rápida y fácil de crear notas o listas sencillas. Guarde todas las notas que quiera y compártalas por correo-e.</p>
    <p>Puede guardar las notas en su equipo o sincronizarlas con servicios en línea como ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Forma libreko oharrak edo zerrenda sinpleak sortzeko modu azkar eta erraza. Gorde itzazu nahi adina ohar eta partekatu itzazu posta elektroniko bidez.</p>
    <p>Oharrak ordenagailuan bertan gorde ditzakezu edo lineako zerbitzuekin, esaterako ownCloud hodeiekin, sinkroniza ditzakezu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fa">
    <p>راهی سریع و آسان برای ساختن یادداشت‌های بی‌ساختار یا نوشتن فهرست‌های ساده. هرتعداد یادداشت که بخواهید نگه داشته و آن‌ها را با رایانامه هم‌رسانی کنید.</p>
    <p>می‌توانید یادداشت‌هایتان را به صورت محلّی روی رایانه‌تان نگه داشته یا با خدمات برخط مثل نکست‌کلود همگام کنید.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Nopea ja helppo tapa tehdä muistiinpanoja tai muistiinpanolistoja. Talleta niin monta muistiinpanoa kuin haluat ja jaa ne sähköpostitse.</p>
    <p>Voit tallettaa muistiinpanot paikallisesti tietokoneellesi tai synkronoida ne verkkopalvelujen, kuten ownCloudin, kanssa.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Un moyen rapide et facile de prendre des notes libres ou de créer des listes simples. Stockez autant de notes que vous le souhaitez et partagez-les par courriel.</p>
    <p>Vous pouvez stocker localement vos notes sur votre ordinateur ou les synchroniser avec des services en ligne comme ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Une maniere facile e veloce par creâ notis o butâ jù listis semplicis. Archivie dutis lis notis che tu vûs e condividilis vie e-mail.</p>
    <p>Si pues archiviâ lis notis in locâl tal computer o sincronizâ cui servizis online come ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Unha forma rápida e doada de tomar notas e anotar listas simples. Almacene tantas notas como queira e compártaas por correo.</p>
    <p>Pode almacenar as súas notas en local no seu computador ou sincroníceas con servizos en liña como ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>דרך מהירה וקלה ליצירת פתקיות בצורה חופשית או לרשום בקצרה רשימות פשוטות. אחסון כמה פתקיות שרק תרצו ושיתוף שלהם בדוא״ל.</p>
    <p>נתן לאחסן את הפתקיות שלך באופן מקומי על המחשב שלך או לתאם אותם עם שרתים מקוונים דוגמת ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Brz i lagan način za stvaranje raznih bilješka ili jednostavnih popisa. Spremite po želji mnogo bilješka i dijelite ih pomoću e-pošte.</p>
    <p>Možete spremiti svoje bilješke lokalno na svojem računalu ili ih uskladiti s mrežnim uslugama poput ownClouda.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>Egy gyors és könnyű módja a szabad stílusú jegyzetek készítésének vagy egyszerű listák leírásához. Tároljon annyi jegyzetet, amennyit csak szeretne, és ossza meg őket e-mailben.</p>
    <p>A jegyzeteket tárolhatja helyben a számítógépén, vagy szinkronizálhat az olyan online szolgáltatásokkal mint az ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Cara cepat dan mudah untuk membuat catatan dalam bentuk bebas atau menuliskan daftar sederhana. Simpan sebanyak mungkin catatan yang Anda inginkan dan bagikan melalui surel.</p>
    <p>Anda dapat menyimpan catatan Anda secara lokal di komputer Anda atau menyinkronkan dengan layanan daring seperti ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>Fljótleg og auðveld leið til að taka niður minnispunkta eða útbúa einfalda lista. Geymdu eins marga lista og þér sýnist og deildu þeim í tölvupósti.</p>
    <p>Þú getur geymt minnispunktana þína á tölvunni þinni eða samstillt þá við þjónustur á netinu eins og til dæmis ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Un modo rapido e semplice per creare note a mano libera o annotare dei semplici elenchi. Salva tutte le note che si vuole e le condivide tramite posta elettronica.</p>
    <p>È possibile salvare le proprie note localmente sul computer o sincronizzarle con dei servizi online come ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <p>Еркін түрдегі естеліктер немесе қарапайым тізімдерді жазып отыруға арналған жылдам әрі ыңғайлы жолы. Өзіңіз қалайтын естеліктер санын сақтап, олармен эл. пошта арқылы бөлісіңіз.</p>
    <p>Естеліктерді жергілікті компьютерде сақтауға, немесе ownCloud сияқты онлайн қызметтермен синхрондауға болады.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>메모를 자유롭게 작성하고 간단한 목록을 적는 간편하고 쉬운 수단입니다. 원하는 만큼 메모를 저장하고 전자메일로 공유하세요.</p>
    <p>컴퓨터에 메모를 저장하거나 오운클라우드 같은 온라인 서비스에 동기화할 수 있습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Greitas ir paprastas būdas parašyti pavienius raštelius ar nedidelius sąrašus. Rašykite kiek norite raštelių ir dalinkitės jais el. paštu.</p>
    <p>Galite įrašyti savo raštelius kompiuteryje arba sinchronizuoti su internetinėmis tarnybomis, pvz. ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>Ātrs un vienkāršs veids, kā veidot brīvas formas piezīmes vai pierakstīt vienkāršus sarakstus. Varat saglabāt cik piezīmes vien vēlaties un dalāties ar tām caur e-pastu.</p>
    <p>Varat saglabāt savas piezīmes lokāli uz sava datora vai sinhronizēt tās ar tādiem pakalpojumiem kā ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Cara pantas dan mudah menulis nota atau apa jua senarai ringkas. Dapat menyimpan banyak nota yang anda suka dan kongsikannya melalui emel.</p>
    <p>Anda boleh menyimpan nota anda secara setempat di dalam komputer anda atau segerak dengan perkhidmatan dalam talian seperti ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>En rask og enkel måte å lage fritekstnotater eller skrible ned enkle lister. Lagre så mange notater du vil og del dem via e-post.</p>
    <p>Du kan lagre notater lokalt på datamaskinen din eller synkronisere med tjenester som ownCloud på nettet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ne">
    <p>फ्रिफर्म नोट हरू बनाउन वा साधारण सूचीहरू तल झार्न छिटो र सजिलो तरिका। तपाईँले मन पराए जति द्रष्टव्यहरू भण्डारण गर्नुहोस् र इमेलद्वारा साझेदारी गर्नुहोस् ।</p>
    <p>तपाईँले आफ्नो द्रष्टव्यहरू स्थानीय रूपमा आफ्नो कम्प्युटरमा भण्डारण गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ वा ownCloud जस्ता अनलाइन सेवाहरूसँग समक्रमण गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ ।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Een snelle en gemakkelijke manier om eenvoudige notities of lijstjes te maken. Sla zoveel notities op als u wilt en deel ze per e-mail.</p>
    <p>U kunt uw notities lokaal op uw computer opslaan of synchroniseren met onlinediensten zoals ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Szybki i łatwy sposób na pisanie notatek i zapisywanie prostych list. Można przechowywać dowolną liczbę notatek i udostępniać je pocztą.</p>
    <p>Można przechowywać notatki lokalnie na komputerze lub synchronizować z serwisami internetowymi, takimi jak ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Uma maneira rápida e fácil de fazer notas de texto simples, ou de anotar listas simples. Armazene quantas notas quiser, e partilhe-as por email.</p>
    <p>Pode guardar as suas notas localmente no seu computador, ou sincronizá-las com serviços da Internet, como o ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Uma maneira rápida e fácil de criar notas livres ou anotar listas simples. Armazene quantas notas quiser e compartilhe-as por e-mail.</p>
    <p>Você pode armazenar suas notas localmente no seu computador ou sincronizar com serviços on-line, como o ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>O metodă rapidă și ușoară de a crea notițe cu formă liberă sau de a însemna liste simple. Stocați cât de multe notițe doriți și partajați-le prin email.</p>
    <p>Puteți stoca notițele local pe calculator sau le puteți sincroniza cu servicii online precum ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Быстрый и легкий способ делать произвольные заметки или записывать простые списки. Храните столько заметок, сколько хотите, и делитесь ими по электронной почте.</p>
    <p>Вы можете хранить свои заметки локально на своем компьютере или синхронизировать с онлайн-сервисами, такими как ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Rýchly a jednoduchý spôsob ako si zapísať poznámky alebo poznačiť zoznamy. Uložiť je možné neobmedzené množstvo poznámok, ktoré je ďalej možné zdieľať emailom.</p>
    <p>Poznámky si môžete uložiť v počítači, alebo ich môžete synchronizovať so službami ako je nextCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Enostaven in hiter način za ustvarjanje sporočilc in seznamov. Pripraviti je mogoče neomejeno število zabeležki in jih pošiljati po elektronski pošti.</p>
    <p>Sporočilca je mogoče shraniti krajevno na računalniku ali pa ga uskladiti s spletnimi storitvami, kot je ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Једноставан и лак начин за писање белешки слободним стилом и стварање једноставних спискова. Сачувајте колико год белешки желите и поделите их електронском поштом.</p>
    <p>Можете складиштити ваше белешке локално на вашем рачунару или их ускладити са мрежним услугама као што су мојОблак (ownCloud).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Ett snabbt och enkelt sätt att göra frihandsanteckningar eller skriva ner enkla listor. Lagra så många anteckningar som du vill och dela dem via e-post.</p>
    <p>Du kan lagra dina anteckningar lokalt på din dator eller synkronisera med nättjänster som ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Serbest biçim notlar veya basit listeler oluşturmanın hızlı ve kolay yolu. İstediğiniz kadar not saklayın ve e-postayla paylaşın.</p>
    <p>Notlarınızı bilgisayarınızda yerel olarak saklayabilir veya ownCloud gibi çevrim içi hizmetlerle eşzamanlayabilirsiniz.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Швидкий і легкий спосіб зробити довільні примітки або записати прості списки. Зберігайте скільки завгодно приміток і діліться ними електронною поштою.</p>
    <p>Ви можете зберігати свої примітки на своєму комп'ютері або синхронізувати з мережевими службами, як-от, ownCloud.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>以快速简便的方式制作任意形式的便笺或者记下简单的列表。可以存储的便笺数量不限并且可以通过电子邮件进行分享。</p>
    <p>您可以将便笺存储在本地计算机上，也可以与 ownCloud 等在线服务同步。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>透過簡單的方式製作自由形式的筆記或記下簡單的清單。儲存您喜歡的任意筆記並透過電子信箱分享筆記。</p>
    <p>您可以把你的筆記儲存在電腦上，或是同步到網路服務，例如 ownCloud。</p>
  </description>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>AppMenu</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>SearchProvider</kudo>
    <kudo>UserDocs</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="800" height="647">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-notes/raw/master/data/appdata/default.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Edit view</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">編輯顯示方式</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">编辑视图</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Перегляд змін</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Düzenleme görünümü</caption>
      <caption lang="ta">காட்சியை திருத்து</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Redigeringsvy</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Уреди приказ</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Urejevalni pogled</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Zobrazenie úprav</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Вид правки</caption>
      <caption lang="ro">Vizualizare de editare</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Visão de edição</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Vista de edição</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Widok redakcji</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Weergave bewerken</caption>
      <caption lang="ne">दृष्य सम्पादन</caption>
      <caption lang="nb">Rediger visning</caption>
      <caption lang="ms">Pandangan sunting</caption>
      <caption lang="ml">തിരുത്തൽ കാഴ്ച</caption>
      <caption lang="lv">Rediģēšanas skats</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Redagavimo rodinys</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">편집 보기</caption>
      <caption lang="kk">Түзету көрінісі</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Visuale di modifica</caption>
      <caption lang="is">Breyta sýn</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Tampilan sunting</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Szerkesztés nézet</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Uredi prikaz</caption>
      <caption lang="he">תצוגת עריכה</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Editar vista</caption>
      <caption lang="fur">Viodude de modifiche</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Vue de modification</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Muokkausnäkymä</caption>
      <caption lang="fa">نمای ویرایش</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Editatu ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Vista de edición</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">Redakti vidon</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">Edit view</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Προβολή επεξεργασίας</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Bearbeitungsansicht</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Redigeringsvisning</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Vista d'edició</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Ukázka úprav</caption>
      <caption lang="be">Выгляд рэдагавання</caption>
      <caption lang="af">Redigeer aansig</caption>
      <image width="800" height="647">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-notes/raw/master/data/appdata/edit.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Select view</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">選取顯示方式</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">选择视图</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Перегляд вибору</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Seçim görünümü</caption>
      <caption lang="ta">காட்சியை தேர்ந்தெடு</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Markeringsvy</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Преглед одабира</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Izbor pogleda</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Zobrazenie výberu</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Вид выбора</caption>
      <caption lang="ro">Vizualizare de selectare</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Visão de seleção</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Vista de seleção</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Widok zaznaczania</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Weergave selecteren</caption>
      <caption lang="ne">चयन गर्ने दृष्य</caption>
      <caption lang="nb">Velg visning</caption>
      <caption lang="ms">Pandangan pilih</caption>
      <caption lang="ml">വീക്ഷണം തിരഞ്ഞെടുക്കുക</caption>
      <caption lang="lv">Atlases skats</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Žymėjimo rodinys</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">선택 보기</caption>
      <caption lang="kk">Таңдау көрінісі</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Visuale di selezione</caption>
      <caption lang="is">Veldu sýn</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Tampilan pilih</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Kijelölés nézet</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Odaberi prikaz</caption>
      <caption lang="he">תצוגת בחירה</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Seleccionar vista</caption>
      <caption lang="fur">Viodude de selezion</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Vue de sélection</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Valintanäkymä</caption>
      <caption lang="fa">نمای گزینش</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Hautatu ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Vista de selección</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">Elekti vidon</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">Select view</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Προβολή επιλογής</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Auswahlansicht</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Vælg visning</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Selecciona una vista</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Ukázka výběru</caption>
      <caption lang="be">Выбраць выгляд</caption>
      <caption lang="af">Kies aansig</caption>
      <image width="800" height="647">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-notes/raw/master/data/appdata/select.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>List view</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">列表顯示方式</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">列表视图</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Перегляд списку</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Liste görünümü</caption>
      <caption lang="ta">காட்சிப்பட்டியல்</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Listvy</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Преглед списком</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Seznamski pogled</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Zobrazenie zoznamu</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Вид списка</caption>
      <caption lang="ro">Vizualizare listă</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Visão de lista</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Lista de notas</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Widok listy</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Lijstweergave</caption>
      <caption lang="ne">सूची दृश्य</caption>
      <caption lang="nb">Listevisning</caption>
      <caption lang="ms">Pandangan senarai</caption>
      <caption lang="ml">പട്ടിക കാഴ്ച</caption>
      <caption lang="lv">Saraksta skats</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Sąrašo rodinys</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">목록 보기</caption>
      <caption lang="kk">Тізім көрінісі</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Visuale ad elenco</caption>
      <caption lang="is">Listasýn</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Tampilan daftar</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Lista nézet</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Zbijeni prikaz</caption>
      <caption lang="he">תצוגת רשימה</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Vista en lista</caption>
      <caption lang="fur">Viodude de liste</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Vue en liste</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Luettelonäkymä</caption>
      <caption lang="fa">نمای فهرستی</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Zerrenda-ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Vista de lista</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">Lista vido</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">List view</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Προβολή λίστας</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Listenansicht</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Listevisning</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Visualització de llista</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Ukázka seznamu</caption>
      <caption lang="ckb">پیشاندانی لیستەیی</caption>
      <caption lang="be">Выгляд спісу</caption>
      <caption lang="af">Lys aangesig</caption>
      <image height="647" width="800">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-notes/raw/master/data/appdata/list.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="40.1" date="2021-05-01">
      <description>
        <p>This release brings the following improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixed e-mail sharing feature</li>
          <li>Fixed issue preventing compiling single source files</li>
          <li>Fixed 40's release date in appdata</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Translations:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>French, Nepali</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Contributors:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Charles Monzat, Felix Riemann, Isaque Galdino, Michael Forney, Pawan Chitrakar</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Thanks to all the contributors and supporters of GNOME Notes!</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-03-20" version="40.0">
      <description>
        <p>This release brings the following improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added bidirectional text support to notes view</li>
          <li>Dropped Zeitgeist support</li>
          <li>Enabled formatting without dependency on selected text</li>
          <li>Improved Help</li>
          <li>Improved Nextcloud support by using Nextcloud Notes API</li>
          <li>Fixed many bugs and improved application code overall</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Translations:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Brazilian Portuguese, Catalan, Czech, French, Galician, German, Hebrew, Hungarian, Indonesian, Korean, Norwegian Bokmål, Polish, Slovenian, Swedish and Ukrainian</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Contributors:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Anders Jonsson, Balázs Úr, Felipe Borges, Fran Dieguez, Guillaume Bernard, Isaque Galdino, Jonathan Kang, Jordi Mas, Kévin Commaille, Kjartan Maraas, Kukuh Syafaat, Marek Černocký, Mario Blättermann, Matej Urbančič, Mohammed Sadiq, Piotr Drąg, Rafael Fontenelle, Sabri Ünal, Seong-ho Cho, Yosef Or Boczko and Yuri Chornoivan</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Thanks to all the contributors and supporters of GNOME Notes!</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Notes</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-notes/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">http://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <url type="help">https://help.gnome.org/users/bijiben/stable/</url>
  <update_contact>py_at_luyten.fr</update_contact>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-notes</translation>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-desecration">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-slavery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-worship">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-homosexuality">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-prostitution">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-adultery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-appearance">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>