<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>gnome-2048</pkgname>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">org.gnome.TwentyFortyEight.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" width="128" type="cached">org.gnome.TwentyFortyEight.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.TwentyFortyEight</id>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA-3.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="uk">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="tr">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="sv">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Gnom 2048</name>
  <name lang="sr">Гном 2048</name>
  <name lang="sl">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="sk">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="ru">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="ro">2048 GNOME</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="pt">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="pl">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="nl">Gnome 2048</name>
  <name lang="nb">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="lt">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="ko">계속 하기(_K)</name>
  <name lang="kk">GNOME 2048 ойыны</name>
  <name lang="it">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="id">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="hu">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="hr">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="he">‏GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="fur">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="fr">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="fi">Gnomen 2048</name>
  <name lang="eu">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="es">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="el">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="de">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="da">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="cs">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="ckb">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="ca">GNOME 2048</name>
  <name lang="bs">Gnom 2048</name>
  <summary>Obtain the 2048 tile</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">获得值为 2048 的方块</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Отримайте плитку 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">2048'i elde edin</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Erhåll 2048-brickan</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Dobijte 2048 pločicu</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Добијте 2048 плочицу</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Cilj je polje 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Získajte dlaždicu 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Получите плитку 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Obțineți dala 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Obtenha o bloco 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Atingir os 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Uzyskaj liczbę 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Bereik de 2048-tegel</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Pasiekti 2048 plytelę</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">2048 타일을 만드세요</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">2048 плиткаларын алу</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Raggiungi il fatidico numero 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Dapatkan ubin 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Szerezze meg a 2048-as csempét</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Složite ploču 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="he">להשיג את האריח 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Oten il bloc 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Obtenir la tuile 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Saavuta 2048-laatta</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Eskuratu 2048 lauza</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Obtener la ficha 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Obtain the 2048 tile</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Φτιάξτε το πλακίδιο 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Erlangen Sie die 2048-Kachel</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Nå flisen med 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Získejte kámen 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Obteniu la casella 2048</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Dobijte 2048 pločicu</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
     Play the highly addictive 2048 game. GNOME 2048 is a clone of the popular
     single-player puzzle game. Gameplay consists of joining numbers in a grid
     and obtain the 2048 tile.
    </p>
    <p>
     Use your keyboard's arrow keys to slide all tiles in the desired direction.
     Be careful: all tiles slide to their farthest possible positions, you cannot
     slide just one tile or one row or column. Tiles with the same value are
     joined when slided one over the other.
    </p>
    <p>
     With every new tile obtained you increase your score. If you think you can easily
     get the 2048 tile, do not let it stop you, the game does not end there, you can
     continue joining tiles and improving your score.
    </p>
    <p>
     Originally created by Gabriele Cirulli, 2048 has gained much popularity
     due to it being highly addictive. Cirulli's 2048 is in turn a clone of
     the 1024 game and includes ideas from other clones.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Igrajte vrlo zaraznu igru 2048. Gnom 2048 je preslik popularne igre slagalica za jednog igrača. Igranje se sastoji od spajanja brojeva u mreži da bi se dobila pločica 2048.</p>
    <p>Koristite strelice na tastaturi da pogurate sve pločice u željenom pravcu. Budite oprezni: sve pločice klize na svoje najudaljenije moguće položaje, ne možete pogurati samo jednu pločicu ili jedan red ili kolonu. Pločice sa istom vrijednošću se spajaju kada skliznu jedna iznad druge.</p>
    <p>Sa svakom novom dobijenom pločicom povećavate rezultat. Ako mislite da možete lako dobiti pločicu 2048, nemojte na tome da se zaustavite, igra se tu ne završava, možete nastaviti sa spajanjem pločica i poboljšavanjem rezultata.</p>
    <p>Izvorno ju je napravio Gabriele Ćiruli, i kao takva 2048 je stekla veliku popularnost zbog same svoje zaraznosti. Ćirulijeva 2048 je zapravo preslik igre 1024 i uključuje ideje iz drugih preslika.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Jugueu a l'altament addictiu joc del 2048. El GNOME 2048 és un clon del popular trencaclosques per a un jugador. El joc consisteix en unir els nombres a una graella per obtenir la casella amb el número 2048.</p>
    <p>Utilitzeu les tecles del cursor per desplaçar les caselles en la direcció desitjada. Totes les caselles es desplacen a les posicions més allunyades possibles, no podeu simplement desplaçar una casella, fila o columna. Les caselles amb el mateix valor s'agrupen quan es desplacen sobre un altre.</p>
    <p>Amb cada casella que obteniu incrementeu la vostra puntuació. Si penseu que podeu obtenir la casella 2048 fàcilment, no us atureu aquí, podeu continuar agrupant caselles per millorar la vostra puntuació.</p>
    <p>Va ser creat originalment per en Gabriele Cirulli. El 2048 ha guanyat molta popularitat per ser altament addictiu. El 2048 de Cirulli és un clon del joc 1024 i inclou idees d'altres clons.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Zahrajte si vysoce návykovou hru 2048. GNOME 2048 je klon populární logické hry pro jednoho hráče. Hraní spočívá ve spojování čísel v mřížce a získání kamene 2048.</p>
    <p>Použijte šipky na klávesnici k přesunu všech kamenů požadovaným směrem. Ale pozor, všechny kameny se přesunou do své nejvzdálenější možné pozice, nemůžete přesunout jen jeden kámen nebo jen jeden řádek nebo sloupec. Kameny se stejnou hodnotou se spojí, když se přesunou jeden přes druhý.</p>
    <p>S každým nově získaným kamenem navýšíte své skóre. Pokud si bude myslet, že můžete kámen 2048 získat snadno, stejně nepřestávejte. Hra zde nekončí, můžete pokračovat ve spojování kamenů a ve vylepšování svého skóre.</p>
    <p>Tato hra, původně vytvořená Gabrielem Cirullim, získala na popularitě díky tomu, že je velmi návyková. Cirulliho 2048 je pro změnu klon hry 1024 a zahrnuje nápady z dalších klonů.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Spil det stærkt vanedannende 2048. GNOME 2048 er en klon af det populære puzzle-spil til én spiller. Spillet går ud på at samle tal i et gitter for at nå flisen med 2048.</p>
    <p>Brug dit tastaturs piletaster til at skubbe alle fliserne i den ønskede retning. Pas på: alle fliserne skubbes til deres fjerneste placering, du kan ikke nøjes med at skubbe én flise, én række eller én kolonne. Fliser med samme værdi samles når de skubbes ovenpå hinanden.</p>
    <p>Hver gang du når en ny flise stiger dit resultat. Hvis du tror det er let at nå til flisen med 2048, så lad det ikke stoppe dig. Spillet slutter ikke der. Du kan fortsætte med at samle fliser og forbedre dit resultat.</p>
    <p>2048 blev oprindeligt skabt af Gabriele Cirulli, og har opnået stor popularitet pga. at det er stærkt vanedannende. Cirullis 2048 er i sig selv en klon af spillet 1024 og inkluderer ideer fra andre kloner.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Spielen Sie das süchtig machende Spiel »2048«. GNOME 2048 ist ein Klon des beliebten Einzelspieler-Puzzles. Ziel des Spiels ist das Zusammenfügen von Zahlen in einem Raster, um die 2048-Kachel zu erlangen.</p>
    <p>Verwenden Sie die Pfeiltasten Ihres Keyboards, um alle auf dem Spielfeld befindlichen Kacheln in die gewünschte Richtung zu bewegen. Aber Vorsicht, alle Kacheln werden so weit wie möglich rutschen. Es ist nicht möglich einzelne Kacheln, Spalten oder Zeilen zu verschieben. Kacheln, die den gleichen Wert haben, werden beim Aufeinandertreffen zusammengefügt und erhalten den addierten Wert.</p>
    <p>Mit jeder neuen Kachel, die auf dem Spielfeld erscheint, erhöhen Sie Ihren Punktestand. Wenn Sie ohne Probleme die 2048 erreichen, können Sie natürlich weiterspielen und weitere Punkte sammeln, um einen noch höheren Punktestand zu erreichen.</p>
    <p>Erfunden von Gabriele Cirulli ist 2048 ist ein allseits beliebtes Spiel, dessen Erfolg auf seinem Suchtfaktor beruht. Cirullis 2048 ist wiederum ein Klon des 1024-Spiels und beinhaltet zusätzlich Ideen anderer Klone.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Παίξτε το εθιστικό παιχνίδι 2048. Το GNOME 2048 είναι ένας κλώνος του δημοφιλούς παιχνιδιού γρίφου. Σκοπός του παιχνιδιού είναι να προσθέσετε τους αριθμούς στο πλέγμα δημιουργώντας το πλακίδιο με τον αριθμό 2048.</p>
    <p>Χρησιμοποιήστε τα βέλη του πληκτρολογίου για να μετακινήσετε τα πλακίδια στην επιθυμητή θέση. Προσοχή όμως: όλα τα πλακίδια μετακινούνται στην μακρύτερη δυναμή θέση, έτσι δεν μπορείτε να το μετακινήσετε κατά μία γραμμή ή στήλη. Τα πλακίδια με τον ίδιο αριθμό προσθέτονται μεταξύ τους όταν συρθεί το ένα πάνω από το άλλο.</p>
    <p>Με κάθε νέο πλακίδιο που δημιουργείτε η βαθμολογία σας αυξάνεται. Αν πιστεύετε πως μπορείτε εύκολα να φτάσετε στο 2048, μην σταματάτε, συνεχίστε να ενώνεται πλακίδια για να βελτιώσετε την βαθμολογία σας.</p>
    <p>Αναπτύχθηκε αρχικά από τον Gabriele Cirulli, το 2048 απέκτησε δημοσιότητα λόγω του ότι ήταν αρκετά εθιστικό. Η έκδοση 2048 του Cirulli είναι κλώνος του παιχνιδιού 1024 και περιέχει επίσης ιδέες από άλλες παραδοχές.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Play the highly addictive 2048 game. GNOME 2048 is a clone of the popular single-player puzzle game. Gameplay consists of joining numbers in a grid and obtain the 2048 tile.</p>
    <p>Use your keyboard's arrow keys to slide all tiles in the desired direction. Be careful: all tiles slide to their furthest possible positions, you cannot slide just one tile or one row or column. Tiles with the same value are joined when slided one over the other.</p>
    <p>With every new tile obtained you increase your score. If you think you can easily get the 2048 tile, do not let it stop you, the game does not end there, you can continue joining tiles and improving your score.</p>
    <p>Originally created by Gabriele Cirulli, 2048 has gained much popularity due to it being highly addictive. Cirulli's 2048 is in turn a clone of the 1024 game and includes ideas from other clones.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Juegue al altamente adictivo 2048. GNOME 2048 es un clon del popular juego de un solo jugador. El objetivo del juego consiste en unir números en una rejilla y obtener la ficha 2048.</p>
    <p>Use las teclas de flecha del teclado para deslizar las fichas en la dirección que quiera. Tenga cuidado: todas las fichas se deslizan a las posiciones disponibles más alejadas, no puede deslizar sólo una ficha ni sólo una fila o una columna. Las fichas con el mismo valor se unen cuando se desliza una sobre la otra.</p>
    <p>Con cada nueva ficha obtenida aumenta su puntuación. Si cree que puede obtener la ficha 2048 fácilmente, no deje que esto le impida continuar, el juego no acaba aquí. Puede seguir uniendo fichas y mejorando su puntuación.</p>
    <p>Creado originalmente por Gabriele Cirulli, 2048 ha ganado mucha popularidad ya que es muy adictivo. La versión de 2048 de Cirulli es de hecho un clon del juego 1024 e incluye ideas de otros clones.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Joka ezazu 3028 jokoarekin. GNOME 2048 jokalari bakarreko puzzle joko ezagunaren klona da. Jokatzeko, zenbakiak elkartu behar dira sareta batean eta 2048 lauza lortu behar da.</p>
    <p>Erabili teklatuaren gezi-teklak lauzak nahi den norabidean irristatzeko. Kontuz: lauza guztiak ahalik eta urrutien irristatzen dira, ezin duzu lauza bakar bat edo errenkada edo zutabe bakar bat irristatu. Balio bera duten lauzak elkartu egingo dira bata bestearen gainean irristatzen direnean.</p>
    <p>Eskuratutako lauza bakoitzeko, zure puntuazioa igo egingo da. 2048 lauza erraz lor dezakezula uste baduzu, ez moteldu abiadura, jokoa ez baita hor amaitzen: lauzak elkartzen eta zure puntuazioa hobetzen jarrai dezakezu.</p>
    <p>Gabriele Cirullik sortu zuen jatorriz 2048 jokoa, eta menpekotasuna sortzen duenez arrakasta handia eskuratu du. Cirulliren 2048 jokoa, berriz, 1024 jokoaren klon bat da eta beste klon batzuetako ideiak ere bildu ditu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Pelaa erittäin koukuttavaa 2048-peliä. Gnomen 2048 on klooni suositusta pulmapelistä, jota pelataan yksin. Pelaaminen koostuu numeroiden liittämisestä toisiinsa ruudukossa, tavoitteena on saavuttaa 2048-laatta.</p>
    <p>Käytä näppäimistön nuolinäppäimiä liu'uttaaksesi laattoja haluamiisi suuntiin. Ole kuitenkin varovainen: kaikki laatat liukuvat kauimpana mahdolliseen olevaan sijaintiin, etkä voi siirtää vain yhtä laattaa, riviä tai saraketta. Samat arvot omaavat laatat liitetään toisiinsa, kun ne kohtaavat.</p>
    <p>Jokainen saavuttamasi laatta nostaa pisteitäsi. Jos 2048-laatan saavuttaminen on mielestäsi helppoa, älä anna sen hidastaa vauhtiasi, sillä peli ei lopu siihen. Voit jatkaa laattojen liittämistä ja parantaa pisteitäsi.</p>
    <p>Alkujaan Gabriele Cirullin kehittämä 2048 on kerännyt paljon suosiota, koska peli on erittäin koukuttava. Cirullin 2048 on klooni 1024-pelistä, ja 2048 sisältää ideoita muista klooneista.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Jouez au jeu addictif 2048. GNOME 2048 est un clone du populaire casse-tête en solo. Le but du jeu consiste à fusionner les nombres d’une grille et d’obtenir la tuile 2048.</p>
    <p>Utiliser les flèches du clavier pour glisser toutes les tuiles dans la direction désirée. Soyez prudent : toutes les tuiles se déplacent vers leur position la plus éloignée possible, vous ne pouvez pas déplacer juste une tuile, une ligne ou une colonne. Les tuiles avec la même valeur sont fusionnées lorsqu’elles sont glissées les unes vers les autres.</p>
    <p>Pour chaque nouvelle tuile obtenue, votre score augmente. Si vous pensez pouvoir facilement obtenir la tuile 2048, ne la laisser pas vous arrêter. Le jeu ne se termine pas là, vous pouvez toujours fusionner les tuiles et augmenter votre score.</p>
    <p>D’abord créé par Gabriele Cirulli, 2048 a gagné en popularité grâce à son côté hautement addictif. Le jeu 2048 de Cirulli est un clone du jeu 1024 et inclus des idées d’autres clones.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Zuie al zûc 2048 che al dâ une vore di dipendence. GNOME 2048 al è un clon dal popolâr gredei a zuiadôr ugnul. Il zûc al consist tal unî numars intune gridele e otegni il bloc 2048.</p>
    <p>Dopre lis frecis de tastiere par movi ducj i blocs inte direzion desiderade. Sta atent: ducj i blocs si movin tes lôr posizions plui pussibil lontanis, nol è pussibil spostâ di nome un bloc o une rie o une colone. I blocs cul stes valôr si unissin cuant che a vegnin spostât un parsore di chel altri.</p>
    <p>Cun ogni gnûf bloc otignût tu aumentis i tiei ponts. Se tu pensis che tu puedis otignî facilmentri il bloc 2048, no stâ lassâ che ti fermi, il zûc nol finìs lì, tu puedis continuâ a unî blocs e miorâ il tô risultât.</p>
    <p>Creât in origjin di Gabriele Cirulli, 2048 al à vuadagnât une vore di popolaritât par vie dal so dâ dipendence. Il 2048 di Cirulli al è a sô volte un clon dal zûc 1024 e al inclût ideis di altris clons.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>לשחק את המשחק הממכר 2048. ‏GNOME 2048 הוא שיבוט של משחק הלוח ליחיד הפופולרי. המשחק מורכב מצירוף מספרים ברשת על מנת להשיג את האריח 2048.</p>
    <p>יש להשתמש במקשי החצים במקלדת שלך על מנת על מנת להחליק את כל האריחים לכיוון הרצוי. יש להיזהר: כל האריחים מוחלקים למקום הרחוק ביותר האפשרי להם, לא ניתן להחליק רק אריח בודד או שורה אחת או עמודה. אריחים עם ערך זהה יצטרפו כאשר יוחלקו אחד אל השני.</p>
    <p>עם כל אריח חדש שמתקבל הניקוד שלך גדל. אם סברת שניתן להגיע בקלות לאריח 2048, אל תיתן לכך לעצור אותך, המשחק לא מסתיים שם, ניתן להמשיך לצרף אריחים ולשפר את הניקוד שלך.</p>
    <p>2048 נוצר במקור על ידי Gabriele Cirulli וצבר פופולריות רבה בשל היותו ממכר. 2048 של Cirulli הוא בתורו שיבוט של המשחק 1024 וכולל רעיונות משיבוטים נוספים.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Igrajte visoko ovisnu 2048 igru. GNOME 2048 je klon popularne igre slagalica. Igranje se sastoji od povezivanja brojeva u mrežu i stvaranja 2048 ploče.</p>
    <p>Koristite svoje tipke strelica kako bi pomicali pločice u željenom smjeru. Budite oprezni: sve se pločice pomiču na njima najbliži mogući položaj, ne možete pomicati samo jednu pločicu redak ili stupac. Pločice s istom vrijednosti se spoje kada se pomaknu jedna preko druge.</p>
    <p>Sa svakom novom složenom pločicom povećavate svoj rezultat. Ako mislite da lagano možete složiti 2048 ploču, ne zaustavljajte se, igra ne završava tamo, možete nastavljati povezivati pločice i poboljšavati svoj rezultat.</p>
    <p>Izvorno stvorena od strane Gabriele Cirulli, 2048 stekla je veliku popularnost i visoko ovisna je. Cirullina 2048 je klon 1024 igre i uključuje ideje iz drugih klonova.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>Játsszon az erősen függőséget okozó 2048 játékkal. A GNOME 2048 a népszerű egyszemélyes kirakós játék klónja. A játékmenet a rácson elhelyezett számok egyesítéséből és a 2048-as csempe megszerzéséből áll.</p>
    <p>A billentyűzet nyíl billentyűi használatával csúsztathatja a csempéket a kívánt irányba. Legyen óvatos: minden csempe a lehető legtávolabbi pozíciójába csúszik, nem lehet csak egyetlen csempét, oszlopot vagy sort csúsztatni. Az azonos értékű csempék egyesülnek, amikor az egyik a másikra lesz csúsztatva.</p>
    <p>Minden új megszerzett csempe növeli a pontszámát. Ha úgy érzi, hogy könnyen el tudta érni a 2048-as csempét, akkor sem hagyjuk, hogy megálljon. A játék itt nem ér véget, folytathatja a csempék egyesítését és a pontszáma növelését.</p>
    <p>Eredetileg Gabriele Cirulli készítette, és a 2048 játék az erős függőség okozása miatt szerzett ilyen nagy népszerűséget. Cirulli 2048 játéka viszont az 1024 játék klónja, valamint egyéb klónokból merített ötleteket is tartalmaz.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Mainkan 2048 yang sangat membuat ketagihan. GNOME 2048 adalah klon permainan tekai-teki pemain tunggal yang populer. Permainan terdiri dari penggabungan angka-angka dalam suatu kisi dan mendapatkan ubin 2048.</p>
    <p>Gunakan tombol panah papan tik Anda untuk menggeser ubin pada arah yang diinginkan. Berhati-hatilah: semua ubin menggeser ke posisi terjauh yang mungkin, Anda tidak bisa menggeser hanya satu ubin atau satu baris atau kolom. Ubin dengan nilai sama akan digabung ketika diadu satu sama lain.</p>
    <p>Dengan diperolehnya setiap ubin baru maka skor Anda naik. Bila Anda pikir Anda dapat dengan mudah memperoleh ubin 2048, jangan biarkan itu menghentikan Anda, permainan tidak berhenti di sana, Anda dapat melanjutkan menggabung ubin dan memperbaiki nilai Anda.</p>
    <p>Aslinya diciptakan oleh Gabriele Cirulli, 2048 sangat meningkat popularitasnya karena sangat membuat kecanduan. 2048 Cirulli adalah klon dari permainan 1024 dan menyertakan ide-ide dari klon lain.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Gioca all'avvincente puzzle 2048. GNOME 2048 è un clone del famoso gioco: aggiungi i vari numeri sulla griglia fino a ottenere 2048.</p>
    <p>Utilizza le frecce direzionali per spostare le varie tessere di gioco nella direzione desiderata. Ma fai attenzione: le tessere si spostano verso la posizione più lontana, non puoi spostarle di una sola riga o colonna. Le tessere con lo stesso valore vengono unite quando sono vicine.</p>
    <p>Ogni volta che ottieni una nuova tessera, il tuo punteggio aumenta. Se pensi di poter raggiungere facilmente 2048, non fermarti lì, il gioco ti consente di andare oltre: continue a unire le tessere per ottenere sempre più punti.</p>
    <p>Creato da Gabriele Cirulli, 2048 è diventato famosissimo in poco tempo. La versione di Cirulli è a sua volta un clone del gioco 1024 che incorpora idee da altri giochi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>중독적인 2048 게임을 해 보세요. 그놈 2048은 인기 있는 1인용 퍼즐 게임의 복제판입니다. 격자 안에 있는 숫자를 합쳐 2048 타일을 만드는 것이 게임의 목표입니다.</p>
    <p>키보드 방향 키를 사용해 타일을 원하는 방향으로 옮기세요. 타일들은 갈 수 있는 한 가장 끝까지 움직이고, 타일 한 개 혹은 한 줄만 옮길 수는 없다는 것에 주의하세요. 같은 숫자가 적혀 있는 타일 두 개를 서로 만나는 방향으로 움직이면 합쳐져서 더 큰 숫자가 적힌 타일이 됩니다.</p>
    <p>새 타일을 만들 때마다 점수가 오릅니다. 2048 타일을 만드는 것이 너무 쉬웠다면, 게임을 끝내지 않고 계속해서 점수를 올릴 수도 있습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Žaiskite įtraukiantį žaidimą 2048. GNOME 2048 yra, populiarios vieno žaidėjo dėlionės, žaidimo klonas. Žaidimo eiga susideda iš tinklelyje esančių skaičių sujungimo ir 2048 plytelės pasiekimo.</p>
    <p>Naudokite savo klaviatūros rodyklių klavišus, kad slankiotumėte visomis plytelėmis norima kryptimi. Būkite atsargūs: visos plytelės slenka į toliausias joms įmanomas vietas, jūs negalite paslinkti tik vienos plytelės ar vienos eilutės, ar vieno stulpelio. Plytelės su tokia pačia reikšme, kai užslenkamos viena ant kitos, yra sujungiamos.</p>
    <p>Su kiekviena pasiekta plytele, jūs didinate savo rezultatą. Jeigu galvojate, kad galite lengvai pasiekti 2048 plytelę, nesustokite, žaidimas tuo nesibaigia, taigi, galite toliau sujunginėti plyteles ir gerinti savo rezultatą.</p>
    <p>Gabriele Cirulli sukurtas žaidimas įgavo didelį populiarumą, kadangi buvo labai įtraukiantis žaidimas. Cirulli žaidimas 2048, savo ruožtu yra žaidimo 1024 klonas, ir įtraukia idėjas iš kitų klonų.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Speel het uiterst verslavende 2048-spel. Gnome 2048 is een kloon van het populaire één-speler puzzelspel. Het doel van het spel is cijfers in een raster bij elkaar te voegen om de 2048-tegel te bereiken.</p>
    <p>Gebruik de pijltjestoetsen op uw toetsenbord om de tegel in de gewenste richting te verschuiven. Let op: alle tegels worden zo ver mogelijk verschoven, u kan niet slechts één tegel, één rij of één kolom verschuiven. Tegels met dezelfde waarde worden samengevoegd wanneer ze over elkaar schuiven.</p>
    <p>Bij elke nieuwe tegel die u bereikt verhoogt uw score. Als u denkt dat u de 2048-tegel makkelijk kan bereiken, laat dat u niet stoppen. Het spel eindigt daar niet, u kan doorgaan met tegels samen te voegen en uw score te verbeteren.</p>
    <p>Oorspronkelijk gemaakt door Gabriele Cirulli is 2048 erg populair geworden omdat het uiterst verslavend is. Cirulli’s 2048 is op zijn beurt een kloon van het 1024-spel en bevat ideeën van andere klonen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Zagraj w bardzo uzależniającą grę „2048”. GNOME 2048 wzoruje się na popularnej grze logicznej dla jednej osoby. Gra polega na przesuwaniu płytek tak, aby na jednej z nich uzyskać liczbę 2048.</p>
    <p>Użyj strzałek na klawiaturze, aby przesuwać płytki. Na początku gry pojawią się dwie płytki z liczbami „2”. Gdy przesunięta płytka znajdzie się obok płytki z taką samą liczbą, połączą się one w jedną płytkę, która będzie miała liczbę będącą sumą liczb znajdujących się na połączonych płytkach (2+2=4, 4+4=8, …, 1024+1024=2048), a na losowej płytce pojawi się nowa liczba. Uwaga: wszystkie płytki przesuną się na najdalszą pozycję, nie można przesunąć tylko jednej płytki albo jednego wiersza czy jednej kolumny.</p>
    <p>Z każdą nową płytką, który uzyskasz, zwiększa się wynik. Jeśli sądzisz, że możesz z łatwością uzyskać płytkę „2048”, nie pozwól, aby to cię powstrzymało, ponieważ możesz kontynuować łączenie płytek i poprawić swój wynik.</p>
    <p>Gra „2048”, stworzona przez Gabriele’a Cirulliego, zdobyła dużą popularność ze względu na to, że jest bardzo uzależniająca. „2048” Cirulliego jest kopią gry „1024” oraz zawiera pomysły z innych kopii tej gry.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Jogue o altamente viciante jogo 2048. O GNOME 2048 é um clone deste popular jogo de um só jogador. Consiste em juntar números numa grelha e obter um mosaico com a soma de 2048.</p>
    <p>Use as teclas de seta para deslizar os mosaicos na direção desejada. Tenha cuidado: todos os mosaicos deslizam para a posição mais distante possível, não pode deslizar só uma linha ou coluna. Mosaicos com o mesmo valor são somados quando deslizados um sobre o outro.</p>
    <p>Com cada novo mosaico obtido, aumenta a sua pontuação. Se pensa que pode ganhar facilmente o mosaico 2048, não deixe que isso o pare. Continue a jogar e a melhorar a sua pontuação.</p>
    <p>Originalmente criado por Gabriele Cirulli, o 2048 ganhou muita popularidade por ser altamente viciante. O 2048 de Cirulli é, por sua vez, um clone do jogo 1024 e inclui ideias de outros clones.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Jogue o altamente viciante jogo 2048. O GNOME 2048 é um clone deste popular jogo de quebra-cabeça de 1 jogador. A partida consiste em juntar números de uma grade e obter o bloco 2048.</p>
    <p>Use as teclas direcionais do teclado para deslizar todos os blocos para a direção desejada. Tenha cuidado: todos os blocos deslizam para as suas respectivas posições mais distantes, deste modo, você não pode deslizar apenas um bloco, uma linha ou uma coluna. Os blocos de mesmo valor são unidos quando deslizados uns sobre os outros.</p>
    <p>Com cada novo bloco obtido, você aumenta sua pontuação. Se você pensa que pode facilmente obter o bloco 2048, não deixe isso parar você, pois o jogo não termina aí: você pode continuar juntando blocos e aumentando sua pontuação.</p>
    <p>Criado originalmente por Gabriele Cirulli, o jogo 2048 ganhou muita popularidade por ser muito viciante. O 2048 de Cirulli é, por sua vez, um clone do jogo 1024 e inclui ideias de outros clones.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Jucați jocul 2048 care creează dependență. 2048 GNOME este o clonă a jocului puzzle popular de un singur jucător. Modul de joc consistă în alăturarea de numere într-o grilă și obținerea dalei 2048.</p>
    <p>Utilizați tastele cu săgeți de pe tastatură pentru a glisa toate dalele în direcția dorită. Aveți grijă: toate dalele alunecă în cele mai îndepărtate poziții posibile ale acestora, nu puteți să glisați doar o singură dală sau un singur rând sau coloană. Dalele cu aceeași valoare sunt unite când sunt glisate una peste cealaltă.</p>
    <p>Cu fiecare dală nou obținută măriți scorul. Dacă credeți că puteți obține ușor dala 2048, nu lăsați asta să vă oprească, jocul nu se termină acolo, puteți continua alăturarea de dale și îmbunătățirea scorului.</p>
    <p>Creat original de Gabriele Cirulli, 2048 a obținut multă popularitate deoarece creează dependență. Jocul 2048 al lui Cirulli este la rândul său o clonă a jocului 1024 și include idei de la alte clone.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Играйте в очень захватывающую игру «2048». GNOME 2048 — это клон популярной однопользовательской головоломки. Геймплей состоит из объединения чисел в сетке и получения плитки 2048.</p>
    <p>Используйте клавиши стрелок на клавиатуре, чтобы переместить все плитки в нужное направление. Будьте осторожны: все плитки перемещаются в возможные положения, вы не можете переместить только одну плитку, строку или столбец.</p>
    <p>С каждой новой плитки вы увеличиваете свой счёт. Если вы получили плитку 2048, не останавливайтесь! Вы можете продолжить игру и улучшить свой счёт.</p>
    <p>Первоначально созданная Габриэле Чирулли, игра «2048» стала очень популярной, так как сильно затягивает. «2048» от Чирулли в свою очередь является клоном игры «1024» и включает идеи других клонов.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Hrajte silno návykovú hru 2048. GNOME 2048 je klon obľúbeného hlavolamu pre jedného hráča. Hranie spočíva zo spájania čísiel v mriežke a získaním dlaždice 2048.</p>
    <p>Použite klávesy šípok na vašej klávesnici na posunutie všetkých dlaždíc v požadovanom smere. Buďte opatrný: všetky dlaždice sa posúvajú do ich najvzdialenejších pozícií. Nemôžete posunúť iba jednu dlaždicu, alebo jeden riadok, alebo stĺpec. Dlaždice s rovnakou hodnotou budú spojené pri posunutí jednej cez druhú.</p>
    <p>S každou novo získanou dlaždicou rastie vaše skóre. Ak si myslíte, že môžete ľahko získať dlaždicu 2048, neprestávajte, pretože hra ešte nekončí. Môžete pokračovať spájaním dlaždíc a zlepšovaním vášho skóre.</p>
    <p>Hru pôvodne vytvoril Gabriele Cirulli. 2048 si získala veľkú obľúbenosť, pretože je silno návyková. Cirulliho 2048 zahŕňa klon hry 1024 a nápady z iných klonov.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Igra Gnome 2048 je klon popularne številske igre. Cilj igre je doseči število 2048 z združevanjem enakih števil v mreži.</p>
    <p>Uporabite smerne tipke za premikanje med polji v želeni smeri. Bodite previdni: ob pritisku smerne tipke, se polje postavi na najbolj oddaljeno mesto v mreži. Ni se mogoče premakniti le za eno polje oziroma le za eno vrstico ali stolpec. Polja z isto vrednostjo števila se seštejejo in natoprekrijejo.</p>
    <p>Z vsakim združenim poljem se poveča trenutni rezultat igre. Če se vam zdi, da je doseči število 2048 enostavno, se lahko preizkusite. Igra se tam sicer še ne konča. Za najvstrajnejše je še veliko prostora.</p>
    <p>Igra 2048, ki jo je ustvaril Gabriele Cirulli, je postala uspešnica zaradi velike zasvojljivosti. Igra vključuje različne ideje tudi drugih podobnih iger.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Играјте врло заразну игру 2048. Гном 2048 је преслик популарне игре слагалица за једног играча. Играње се састоји од спајања бројева у мрежи да би се добила плочица 2048.</p>
    <p>Користите стрелице на тастатури да погурате све плочице у жељеном правцу. Будите опрезни: све плочице клизе на своје најудаљеније могуће положаје, не можете погурати само једну плочицу или један ред или колону. Плочице са истом вредношћу се спајају када склизну једна изнад друге.</p>
    <p>Са сваком новом добијеном плочицом повећавате резултат. Ако мислите да можете лако добити плочицу 2048, немојте на томе да се зауставите, игра се ту не завршава, можете наставити са спајањем плочица и побољшавањем резултата.</p>
    <p>Изворно ју је направио Габриеле Ћирули, и као таква 2048 је стекла велику популарност због саме своје заразности. Ћирулијева 2048 је заправо преслик игре 1024 и укључује идеје из других преслика.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Igrajte vrlo zaraznu igru 2048. Gnom 2048 je preslik popularne igre slagalica za jednog igrača. Igranje se sastoji od spajanja brojeva u mreži da bi se dobila pločica 2048.</p>
    <p>Koristite strelice na tastaturi da pogurate sve pločice u željenom pravcu. Budite oprezni: sve pločice klize na svoje najudaljenije moguće položaje, ne možete pogurati samo jednu pločicu ili jedan red ili kolonu. Pločice sa istom vrednošću se spajaju kada skliznu jedna iznad druge.</p>
    <p>Sa svakom novom dobijenom pločicom povećavate rezultat. Ako mislite da možete lako dobiti pločicu 2048, nemojte na tome da se zaustavite, igra se tu ne završava, možete nastaviti sa spajanjem pločica i poboljšavanjem rezultata.</p>
    <p>Izvorno ju je napravio Gabriele Ćiruli, i kao takva 2048 je stekla veliku popularnost zbog same svoje zaraznosti. Ćirulijeva 2048 je zapravo preslik igre 1024 i uključuje ideje iz drugih preslika.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Spela det mycket beroendeframkallande spelet 2048. GNOME 2048 är en klon av det populära pusselspelet för en person. Spelet går ut på att slå ihop nummer i ett rutnät och erhålla 2048-brickan.</p>
    <p>Använd ditt tangentbords piltangenter för att glida alla brickor i den önskade riktningen. Var försiktig: alla brickor glider så långt som möjligt, du kan inte glida bara en rad eller en kolumn. Brickor med samma värde slås ihop då en av dem glider över den andra.</p>
    <p>Med varje ny bricka du erhåller ökar du din poäng. Om du tror att du lätt kan få 2048-brickan behöver du inte låta det stoppa dig. Spelet slutar inte där, du kan fortsätta slå ihop brickor och förbättra din poäng.</p>
    <p>2048 skapades ursprungligen av Gabriele Cirulli och har uppnått hög popularitet eftersom det är så beroendeframkallande. Cirullis 2048 är i sin tur en klon av spelet 1024 och inkluderar idéer från andra kloner.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Son derece bağımlılık yapan 2048 oyununu oynayın. GNOME 2048, sevilen bulmaca oyununun bir türevidir. Oynanışı sayıları bir ızgarada birleştirmeye ve 2048 elde etmeye dayanmaktadır.</p>
    <p>Kareleri istediğiniz yönde hareket ettirmek için klavyenizin yön tuşlarını kullanın. Dikkatli olun: kareler mümkün olan en uzak noktaya taşınacaklardır, bir kare aşağı veya yukarı taşımak mümkün değildir. Aynı değere sahip kareler kaydırılıp yan yana getirildiğinde birleştirilirler.</p>
    <p>Elde ettiğiniz her döşeme puanınızı arttıracaktır. Eğer kolayca 2048'i elde ettiğinizi düşünüyorsanız, onun sizi durdurmasına izin vermeyin, oyun burada bitmiyor, puanınızı daha yükseğe taşıyabilirsiniz.</p>
    <p>Özgün oyun 2048 Gabriele Cirulli tarafından geliştirilmiş ve çokça bağımlılık yaptığından çok sevilmiştir. Cirulli'nin 2048'i 1024 oyununun bir türevidir ve diğer türev oyunlardan da fikirler içermektedir.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Зіграйте у вкрай захопливу гру 2048. GNOME 2048 є клоном популярної гри для одного гравця. Гра полягає у поєднанні чисел на плитках у ґратці з метою отримання плитки із числом 2048.</p>
    <p>Скористайтеся клавішами зі стрілками на вашій клавіатурі для пересування усіх плиток у бажаному напрямку. Будьте обережні: усі плитки пересуваються до найвіддаленішої можливої позиції — не можна пересунути лише одну плитку або один рядок чи стовпчик плиток. Плитки із однаковими числами під час пересування об'єднуються одна з одною.</p>
    <p>Із отриманням нових плиток зростатиме ваш результат. Якщо вам здається, що отримати плитку 2048 надто просто, ви можете не зупинятися — гра не закінчується на цій плитці — ви можете продовжувати поєднувати плитки і поліпшувати ваш результат.</p>
    <p>Першу версію гри було створено Габіелем Чіруллі. 2048 набула популярності через простоту і захопливість ігрового процесу. 2048 Чіруллі є клоном гри 1024, до якого включено ідеї, запозичені у інших клонів цієї гри.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>玩很容易上瘾的游戏 2048。 GNOME 2048 是一款热门单机益智游戏的克隆版本。游戏玩法是将数字合并到一个网格中而获得2048。</p>
    <p>使用键盘上的箭头键往所需方向滑动所有的方块。要小心：所有的方块将会尽可能滑到最远的位置，你不能滑动单独一个、一行或一列方块。具有相同值的方块在被滑动时将会被合并。</p>
    <p>随着每一个新方块产生，你的分数都将会增加。如果你认为你可以轻松获得值为 2048 的方块，比赛还没有结束，你可以继续合并方块和来提高你的分数。</p>
    <p>2048 最初由 Gabriele Cirulli 编写的，由于本身极容易上瘾，这款游戏已经获得相当的人气。Cirulli 的2048又是游戏1024的模仿品，也借鉴了其他模仿品的思路。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default" width="1248" height="702">
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-2048/raw/master/data/screenshot.png</image>
      <caption>A running game having reached the 2048 tile</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">一个正在运行的游戏已得到值为 2048 的方块</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">У поточній грі досягнуто плитки 2048</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Çalışan bir oyun 2048 döşemesine ulaştı</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Ett körande spel som nått 2048-brickan</caption>
      <caption lang="sr@latin">Pokrenuta igra je dostigla 2048 pločice</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Покренута игра је достигла 2048 плочице</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Igra, pri kateri je treba s seštevanjem doseči število 2048</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Prebiehajúca hra dosiahla dlaždicu 2048</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Запущенная игра достигла плитки 2048</caption>
      <caption lang="ro">Un joc care rulează în care ați ajuns la dala 2048</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Um jogo atingiu o bloco 2048</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Um jogo em execução chegou a 2048</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Gra, w której osiągnięto płytkę z liczbą 2048</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Een spel waarin de 2048-tegel bereikt is</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Veikiantis žaidimas pasiekęs 2048 plytelę</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">하고 있는 게임이 2048 타일에 도달했습니다</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Una partita in cui il giocatore ha raggiunto 2048</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Sebuah permainan yang sedang berjalan telah mencapai 2048 ubin</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Egy futó játék elérte a 2048-as csempét</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Pokrenute igra je dostigla 2048 pločicu</caption>
      <caption lang="he">משחק שהמטרה בו להגיע לאריח 2048</caption>
      <caption lang="fur">Un zûc in esecuzion dulà che si è rivâts al bloc 2048</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Une partie en cours qui a atteint la tuile 2048</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Peli, jossa on saavutettu 2048-laatta</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">2048 lauzara iritsi den jokoa</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Una partida en ejecución que haya alcanzado la ficha 2048</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">A running game having reached the 2048 tile</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Ein Spiel, das gerade die 2048-Kachel erreicht hat</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Et kørende spil som har opnået flisen med 2048</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Rozehraná hra, ve které bylo dosaženo 2048 kamenů</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Una partida en transcurs que ha aconseguit la casella 2048</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <id>org.gnome.gnome-2048.desktop</id>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.TwentyFortyEight.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/2048</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-2048/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://wiki.gnome.org/TranslationProject</url>
  <update_contact>arnaud.bonatti_at_gmail.com</update_contact>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <!-- this is a translatable version of project_group -->
  <developer_name>The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 项目</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Проєкт GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">GNOME Projesi</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr@latin">Gnomov projekat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Гномов пројекат</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Проект GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Proiectul GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Het Gnome-project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb">GNOME prosjektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">GNOME projektas</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">그놈 프로젝트</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="kk">GNOME жобасы</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Il progetto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Proyek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">מיזם GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fur">Il progjet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Le projet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Gnome-projekti</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">GNOME proiektua</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">El Proyecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Das GNOME-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>HighContrast</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-2048</translation>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-desecration">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-slavery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-worship">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-homosexuality">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-prostitution">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-adultery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-appearance">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>

  <releases>
    <!-- should be kept in versioning inverted order -->
    <release date="2020-11-22" type="stable" version="3.38.2" urgency="medium" />
    <release date="2020-08-28" urgency="low" type="development" version="3.37.91" />
  </releases>
  <custom>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">workstation</value>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">mobile</value>
  </custom>
</component>