<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>gnome-solanum</pkgname>
  <icon type="cached" height="64" width="64">org.gnome.Solanum.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" height="128" width="128">org.gnome.Solanum.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.Solanum</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>Solanum</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="uk">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="sv">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="sr">Соланум</name>
  <name lang="sl">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="ro">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="pl">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="oc">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="nl">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="ko">솔라넘</name>
  <name lang="it">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="id">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="gl">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="fr">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="fi">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="eu">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="es">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="de">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="da">Solanum</name>
  <name lang="cs">Solanum</name>
  <summary>Balance working time and break time</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">平衡工作时间和休息时间</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Встановіть оптимальне співвідношення між робочим часом і часом відпочинку</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Balansera arbetstid och rast</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Уравнотежите време рада и време паузе</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Usklajevanje delovnega časa in premorov</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Balansați timpul de lucru și pauzele</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Balanceie o tempo de trabalho e intervalo</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Równowaga między czasem pracy a przerwami</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Equilibri entre temps de trabalh e pausas</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Houd uw werktijd en pauzetijd in balans</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">업무 시간과 쉬는 시간 균형을 맞춥니다</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Bilancia il tempo di lavoro e le pause</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Menyeimbangkan waktu kerja dan waktu istirahat</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Equilibre o tempo de traballo e o de descanso</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Trouvez l’équilibre entre temps de travail et de pause</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Löydä kultainen keskitie työ- ja taukoajan välillä</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Orekatu laneko astia eta etenaldiak</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Equilibrio entre tiempo de trabajo y de descanso</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Balance working time and break time</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Arbeits- und Pausenzeit ausgleichen</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Hold balance mellem arbejdstid og pausetid</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Mějte v rovnováze čas trávený prací a přestávkami</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Solanum is a time tracking app that uses the pomodoro technique. Work in 4 sessions,
      with breaks in between each session and one long break after all 4.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Solanum je aplikace pro sledování času, která používá techniky pomodoro. Pracujte ve 4 cyklech, s přestávkami mezi každým cyklem a jednou dlouhou přestávkou po 4. cyklu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Solanum er et tidtagningsprogram som bruger pomodoroteknikken. Arbejd i 4 sessioner med pauser mellem hver session og en lang pause efter alle 4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Solanum ist eine Zeitmanagement-Anwendung auf Basis der Pomodoro-Technik. Arbeiten Sie in vier Abschitten - dazwischen gibt es kleine Pausen. Nach vier Arbeitsrunden gibt es eine lange Pause.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Solanum is a time tracking app that uses the pomodoro technique. Work in 4 sessions, with breaks in between each session and one long break after all 4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Solanum es una aplicación de gestión del tiempo que usa la técnica Pomodoro. Trabaje en 4 sesiones, con pausas entre cada de ellas y una pausa larga después de las 4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Solanum denbora kudeatzeko aplikazio bat da, Pomodoro teknika erabiltzen duena. Egin lan 4 saiotan, saio artean etenaldi txikiak eta 4 saioen ondoren etenaldi luzea eginda.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Solanum on ajanseurantasovellus, jossa käytetään pomodoro-tekniikkaa. Työskentele neljässä vuorossa, pidä tauko vuorojen välillä ja yksi pidempi tauko kaikkien neljän vuoron jälkeen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Solanum est une application de suivi du temps selon la technique Pomodoro. Travaillez en 4 périodes, avec une pause entre chaque, puis une plus longue pause après les 4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Solaum é unha aplicación de seguimento de tempo que usa a técnica pomodoro. Funciona en 4 sesións, con pausas no mediio de cada sesión e unha pausa larga despois de cada 4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Solanum adalah aplikasi pelacakan waktu yang menggunakan teknik pomodoro. Bekerja dalam 4 sesi, dengan istirahat di antara setiap sesi dan satu istirahat panjang setelah semua 4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Solanum è un'applicazione per la gestione del tempo che usa la tecnica pomodoro. Funziona in 4 sessioni, con pause tra ciascuna sessione e una lunga pausa al termine di tutte e 4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>솔라넘은 포모도로 기술을 활용하는 시간 관리 앱입니다. 4시간 동안 일하되, 각 시간 별로 쉬는 시간을 부여하며 4시간이 지나면 긴 쉬는 시간을 넣습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Solanum is een toepassing die de tijd bijhoudt volgens de pomodoromethode. Werk in 4 sessies, met pauzes tussen elke sessie en een lange pauze wanneer de 4 sessies gedaan zijn.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Solanum to program do planowania czasu używający techniki Pomodoro. Podziel pracę na cztery sesje, z przerwami między każdą sesją lub jedną długą przerwą po wszystkich czterech.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Solanum é um aplicativo de monitoramento de tempo que faz uso da técnica Pomodoro. Trabalhe em quatro sessões com intervalos curtos entre cada uma delas e um intervalo longo depois um ciclo completo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Solanum este o aplicație de urmărire a timpului care utilizează tehnica pomodoro. Lucrați în 4 sesiuni, cu pauze între fiecare sesiune și o pauză lungă după toate cele 4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Program Solanum je namenjen spremljanju časa po tehniki pomodoro. Po tem načinu je delo razdeljeno na 4 dele z vmesnimi krajšimi in enim daljšim premorom po koncu dejavnosti.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Соланум је програм праћења времена који користи помодоро технику. Ради у 4 сесије, са паузама између њих и дужом паузом након свих 4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Solanum är ett program för tidshantering som använder pomodorotekniken. Arbeta i fyra sessioner, med raster mellan varje session och en lång rast efter alla fyra.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Solanum — програма для керування робочим навантаженням за методикою «pomodoro». Робочий час буде розбито на 4 сеанси із короткими перервами та однією довгою перервою до наступної серії сеансів.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>Solanum 是个时间跟踪应用，使用番茄工作法。工作分 4 个时段，在每个时段之间休息，在全部 4 个时段之后有一次长时间休息。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Solanum/-/raw/main/data/screenshots/screenshot-1.png</image>
      <image type="source">https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Solanum/-/raw/main/data/screenshots/screenshot-2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.Solanum.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Solanum</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/Solanum/-/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://patreon.com/chrisgnome</url>
  <!-- Translators: please do NOT translate this -->
  <developer_name>Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Кристофер Дејвис</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="oc">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Christopher Davis</developer_name>
  <update_contact>christopherdavis_at_gnome.org</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">solanum</translation>
  <releases>
    <release version="3.0.1" date="2021-10-28">
      <description>
        <p>The 3.0.1 release of Solanum brings a minor bug fix.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixed an issue where using the skip button would cause laps to repeat (fixed by @pierre-si).</li>
          <li>Added Occitan translation.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.0.0" date="2021-10-22">
      <description>
        <p>The 3.0.0 release of Solanum brings new preferences, updated translations, and minor bug fixes.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Solanum now has preferences to adjust the various timer lengths, as well as how many laps to go through before a long break.</li>
          <li>New and updated translations for the German, Spanish, Slovenian, Dutch, Romanian, Chinese (China), Korean, Galician, Brazilian Portuguese, Ukranian, Swedish, Polish, Czech, and Finish languages.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.1.0" date="2021-02-08">
      <description>
        <p>The 2.1.0 release of Solanum brings translations, bug fixes, and a minor redesign.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Adjust the main window's design to match new styling for applets</li>
          <li>Updated Finnish and Serbian translations</li>
          <li>Disable idle animation when the app is running in the background</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.0.0" date="2020-12-16">
      <description>
        <p>The 2.0.0 release of Solanum brings translations, bug fixes, and a port to GTK 4.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>The UI has been ported to GTK 4, making Solanum one of the first GTK 4 apps.</li>
          <li>Support for translations has been added.</li>
          <li>Added translations for French, Spanish, Swedish, Slovenian, Italian, Indonesian, Polish, Finnish, Brazilian Portuguese, Basque, Czech, Ukranian, and British English</li>
          <li>Fix: The timer state is properly updated when using the skip button.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-09-14" version="1.1.0">
      <description>
        <p>The second stable release of Solanum brings UI tweaks, usability improvements, and new features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>A skip button has been added, so you can use other time tracking methods in addition to Solanum.</li>
          <li>The start button now plays a small chime, so you know that Solanum will give auditory cues as you work.</li>
          <li>Keywords have been added so Solanum can be found more easily on your desktop.</li>
          <li>The entire window is now draggable instead of just the top.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.1" date="2020-09-09" />
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2020-09-05" />
  </releases>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>Notifications</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <provides>org.gnome.Solanum.desktop</provides>
  <custom>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">workstation</value>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">mobile</value>
  </custom>
</component>