<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>gnome.atomix</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">atomix.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">atomix.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">atomix.png</icon>
  <id>atomix.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Atomix</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="wa">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="vi">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="uk">Атомікс</name>
  <name lang="tr">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="th">อะตอมมิกซ์</name>
  <name lang="ta">அட்டாமிக்ச்</name>
  <name lang="sv">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Atomiks</name>
  <name lang="sr">Атомикс</name>
  <name lang="sq">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="sl">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="sk">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="ru">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="ro">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="pt">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="pl">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਐਟਮਿਕਸ</name>
  <name lang="oc">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="nl">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="nb">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="ms">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="mk">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="lv">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="lt">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="ko">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="kn">ಅಟೂಮಿಕ್ಸ್</name>
  <name lang="ka">ატომიქსი</name>
  <name lang="ja">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="it">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="is">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="id">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="hu">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="hi">एटामिक्स</name>
  <name lang="he">אטומיקס</name>
  <name lang="gu">એટોમિક્સ</name>
  <name lang="gl">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="ga">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="fur">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="fr">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="fi">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="fa">اتومیکس</name>
  <name lang="eu">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="et">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="es">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="eo">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="en_CA">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="el">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="dz">ཨེ་ཊོ་མིགསི་</name>
  <name lang="de">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="da">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="cs">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="ca">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="bs">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="bn">অ্যাটোমিক্স</name>
  <name lang="bg">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="be">Atomix</name>
  <name lang="az">Atomiks</name>
  <name lang="am">አቶሚክስ</name>
  <name lang="af">Atomix</name>
  <summary>Build molecules out of single atoms</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Molekülleri, atomlardan oluşturun</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Bygg molekyler av enskilda atomer</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Izgradite molekule od pojedinačnih atoma</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Изградите молекуле од појединачних атома</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Sestavljanje molekul iz prostih atomov!</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Zostavuje molekuly z jednotlivých atómov</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Построение молекул из простых атомов</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Construiește molecule din atomi individual</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Construa moléculas a partir de átomos</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Construir moléculas a partir de átomos simples</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Budowanie cząsteczek z pojedynczych atomów</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Maak moleculen van enkele atomen</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Sudėkite įvairias molekules iš atskirų atomų</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Bangun molekul dari atom-atom tunggal</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Építsen molekulákat egyedülálló atomokból</summary>
  <summary lang="he">בניית מולקולות מאטומים בודדים</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Costruî moleculis tacant dai singui atoms</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Composer des molécules un atome à la fois</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Rakenna molekyylejä yksittäisistä atomeista</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Osatu molekulak atomo bakarretik</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Construir moléculas a partir de átomos sencillos</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Συνθέσετε μόρια από απλά άτομα</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Moleküle aus einzelnen Atomen bauen</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Byg molekyler af enkelte atomer</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Sestavte molekuly z jednotlivých atomů</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Construeix molècules a partir d'àtoms individuals</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Graditi molekule od pojedinih atoma</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Atomix is a puzzle game where your goal is to assemble molecules from
      compound atoms by moving them on the playfield.
      However, atoms don’t just move wherever you want to move them to, they
      slide until they hit either a wall or another atom.
    </p>
    <p>
      Try to build the molecules as fast as you can on each level to earn a
      higher score.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Pokušajte izgraditi molekule što brže možete na svakom nivou da zaradite rekord.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Intenta construir les molècules tan ràpid com et sigui possible en cada nivell per a obtenir una puntuació més alta.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Atomix je logická hra, ve které je cílem sestavit molekuly z jednotlivých atomů jejich přesouváním po hracím poli. Atomy ale nemůžete přesouvat, jak vás napadne. Po udaní směru se samy pohybují, až dokud nenarazí do zdi nebo do jiného atomu.</p>
    <p>Molekuly v jednotlivých úrovních se snažte sestavit co nejrychleji dokážete, abyste dosáhli vyššího skóre.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Atomix er et puslespil, hvor det gælder om at samle molekyler ud fra atomer ved at flytte dem rundt på spilområdet. Atomer flytter sig ikke kun derhen, hvor du ønsker, men glider indtil de enten rammer en væg eller et andet atom.</p>
    <p>Prøv at bygge molekylerne så hurtigt som du kan på hver bane for at få flere point.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Atomix ist ein Puzzle-Spiel mit dem Ziel, Moleküle aus den vorhandenen Atomen durch deren Bewegung auf dem Spielfeld zusammenzubauen. Die Atome bewegen sich allerdings nicht so, wie Sie sie vielleicht bewegen möchten. Sie gleiten, bis sie entweder auf eine Wand oder ein anderes Atom treffen.</p>
    <p>Versuchen Sie, die Moleküle auf jeder Spielstufe so schnell wie möglich zusammenzubauen, um eine höhere Punktzahl zu erhalten.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Δοκιμάστε να συνθέσετε τα μόρια όσο γρήγορα μπορείτε σε κάθε επίπεδο για να κερδίσετε μεγαλύτερη βαθμολογία</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Atomix es un juego tipo puzle en el que el objetivo es ensamblar moléculas a partir de átomos, moviéndolos sobre el tablero del juego. Sin embargo, los átomos no se mueven a donde quiere, sino que se deslizan hasta que encuentran una pared u otro átomo.</p>
    <p>Pruebe a construir las moléculas tan rápido como pueda en cada nivel para ganar más puntos.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Saiatu molekulak ahalik eta azkarren eraikitzen maila bakoitzean puntuazio altuena eskuratzeko.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Atomix on pulmapeli, jossa tavoitteena on koota molekyylejä yksittäisistä atomeista siirtämällä niitä pelialueella. Atomit eivät kuitenkaan liiku juuri sinne, minne haluat, vaan ne liukuvat kunnes osuvat seinämään tai toisiin atomeihin.</p>
    <p>Yritä rakentaa molekyylejä mahdollisimman nopeasti jokaisella tasolla ansaitaksesi huippupisteet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Atomix est un jeu de casse-tête dans lequel le but est d’assembler des molécules à partir de ses composantes atomiques en les déplaçant sur le terrain de jeu. Cependant, les atomes ne bougent pas comme vous le souhaiteriez, ils glissent jusqu’à ce qu’ils rencontrent un autre mur ou un autre atome.</p>
    <p>Essayez d’aller le plus rapidement possible pour concevoir les molécules pour avoir un meilleur score.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Cîr di costruî lis moleculis il plui veloç pussibil a ogni nivel par vuadagnâ un plui ponts.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>יש לנסות לבנות מולקולות מהר ככל האפשר בכל שלב על מנת להשיג מספר נקודות גדול יותר.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>Az Atomix egy kirakós játék, amelynek célja molekulák összerakása az összetevő atomokból a játékmezőn történő mozgatásukkal. Azonban az atomok nem csak arra mozognak, amerre mozgatni szeretné azokat, hanem addig csúsznak, amíg el nem érnek egy falat vagy egy másik atomot.</p>
    <p>Próbálja meg minden szinten a lehető leggyorsabban megépíteni a molekulákat, hogy megszerezze a magasabb pontszámot.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Atomix adalah permainan teka-teki dimana sasaran Anda adalah merakit molekul dari atom kompon dengan memindah mereka pada bidang permainan. Namun atom-atom tidak sekedar bergerak ke manapun Anda mau memindah mereka, mereka meluncur sampai menabrak tembok atau atom lain.</p>
    <p>Cobalah membangun molekul secepat mungkin pada setiap tingkat untuk mendapatkan skor lebih tinggi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Atomix yra galvosūkio žaidimas, kurio tikslas yra sudėti molekules iš atomų, juos stumdant lauke. Tačiau atomai nejuda jums panorėjus, jie slenka iki atsitrenkia į sieną arba vienas į kitą.</p>
    <p>Bandykite sudaryti molekules kiek galima greičiau kiekvienam lygiui ir gaukite daugiau taškų.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Atomix is een puzzelspel met als doel moleculen samen te stellen uit atomen door deze op het speelveld te verplaatsen. Atomen bewegen echter niet zomaar in de richting die u wilt, ze blijven glijden totdat ze tegen een muur of tegen een ander atoom botsen.</p>
    <p>Probeer zo snel mogelijk de moleculen samen te stellen om een hogere score te krijgen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Atomix to gra logiczna, której celem jest złożenie cząsteczek z atomów przez przesuwanie ich na planszy. Jednakże, atomy nie przemieszczają się w dowolny sposób, tylko ślizgają się, aż uderzą w ścianę lub inny atom.</p>
    <p>Należy budować cząsteczki jak najszybciej na każdym poziomie, aby uzyskać jak najwyższy wynik.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Tente construir as moléculas o mais rapidamente possível em cada nível, para conseguir uma pontuação mias alta.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Atomix é um jogo de quebra-cabeça cujo objetivo é conectar moléculas de átomos compostos movendo-as na área do jogo. Porém, átomos não simplesmente se movem para onde você quiser, e sim deslizam até acertar uma parede ou um outro átomo.</p>
    <p>Tente construir as moléculas o mais rápido que você puder em cada nível para obter a melhor pontuação.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Atomix este un joc puzzle unde scopul este să asamblezi molecule din atomi compuși mutându-i pe câmpul de joc. Oricum, atomii nu se pot muta oriunde doriți dumneavoastră, se pot muta până când se lovesc de un zid sau un alt atom.</p>
    <p>Încercați să construiți molecule cât de repete puteți pentru fiecare nivel pentru a câștiga un scor mai mare.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Попробуйте построить молекулы так быстро, как сможете. Чем быстрее вы построите молекулу, тем больше заработаете очков.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Pokúste sa na každej úrovni zostaviť molekuly najrýchlejšie ako viete, aby ste získali čo najvyššie skóre.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Atomix je igra, katere cilj je sestaviti molekule iz atomov, ki se premikajo po zaslonu. Atomi se seveda premikajo povsem naključno, zaletavajo se v zidove ali v druge atome, se odbijajo ...</p>
    <p>Molekulo poskusite sestaviti v čim krajšem času in dosežite visok rezultat.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Атомикс је игра слагалице у којој је ваш циљ да саставите молекуле од основних атома премештајући их по пољу игре. Међутим, атоми једноставно не иду тамо где ви желите да их преместите, већ се померају све док не ударе или у зид или у други атом.</p>
    <p>Покушајте да изградите молекуле што брже можете на сваком нивоу да остварите већи резултат.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Pokušajte da izgradite molekule što brže možete na svakom nivou da ostvarite veći rezultat.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Atomix är ett pusselspel där ditt mål är att sammanställa molekyler från de atomer de består av genom att flytta dem på spelfältet. Atomer rör sig dock inte bara dit du vill, de glider tills de träffar antingen en vägg eller en annan atom.</p>
    <p>Försök bygga molekylerna så fort du kan på varje nivå för att få högre poäng.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Atomix, birleşik atomları oyun alanına taşıyarak ve onları birleştirerek moleküller oluşturduğunuz bir bulmaca oyunudur. Ancak, atomlar onları hareket ettirmek istediğiniz yere hareket etmez, onları bir duvara veya başka bir atoma tutturmak için kaydırmanız gerekir.</p>
    <p>Her bir seviyede, yüksek bir puan kazanmak için, yapabildiğiniz kadar hızlı bir şekilde molekülleri oluşturmayı deneyin.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default" height="557" width="686">
      <image>https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Atomix?action=AttachFile&amp;do=get&amp;target=atomix-screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Atomix</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/atomix/issues/new?issue</url>
  <url type="donation">http://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <update_contact>robert_roth_at_gnome.org</update_contact>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <translation type="gettext">atomix</translation>
  <!-- Generated by  http://apps-xdgapp.rhcloud.com/oars -->
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>