<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>gnome-secrets</pkgname>
  <icon width="64" type="cached" height="64">org.gnome.World.Secrets.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" height="128" type="cached">org.gnome.World.Secrets.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.World.Secrets</id>
  <name>Secrets</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">秘密</name>
  <name lang="vi">Secrets</name>
  <name lang="uk">Секрети</name>
  <name lang="tr">Secrets</name>
  <name lang="sv">Secrets</name>
  <name lang="sr">Тајне</name>
  <name lang="sl">Skrivnosti</name>
  <name lang="ru">Секреты</name>
  <name lang="ro">Secrete</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Secrets</name>
  <name lang="pt">Segredos</name>
  <name lang="pl">Secrets</name>
  <name lang="nl">Wachtwoordkluis</name>
  <name lang="nb">Hemmeligheter</name>
  <name lang="it">Secrets</name>
  <name lang="is">Leyndarmál</name>
  <name lang="id">Secrets</name>
  <name lang="hu">Titkok</name>
  <name lang="he">סודות</name>
  <name lang="gl">Segredos</name>
  <name lang="fr">Secrets</name>
  <name lang="fi">Salaisuudet</name>
  <name lang="eu">Secrets</name>
  <name lang="es">Secretos</name>
  <name lang="de">Secrets</name>
  <name lang="da">Secrets</name>
  <name lang="cs">Secrets</name>
  <name lang="ca">Secrets</name>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.World.Secrets.desktop</launchable>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-only</project_license>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <summary>Manage your passwords</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">管理您的密码</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Quản lý các mật khẩu của bạn</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Керування вашими паролями</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Parolalarınızı yönetin</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Hantera dina lösenord</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Управљајте вашим лозинкама</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Upravljanje z gesli</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Управляйте своими паролями</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Administrați-vă parolele</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Gerencie suas senhas</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Gerir as suas palavras-passe</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Zarządzanie hasłami</summary>
  <summary lang="pa">ਆਪਣੇ ਪਾਸਵਰਡਾਂ ਲਈ ਇੰਤਜ਼ਾਮ</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Uw wachtwoorden beheren</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Administrer dine passord</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Gestione delle password</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Sýslaðu með lykilorðin þín</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Kelola kata sandi Anda</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Kezelje a jelszavait</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Upravljaj lozinkama</summary>
  <summary lang="he">ניהול הססמאות שלך</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Xestionar os seus contrasinais</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Gérez vos mots de passe</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Hallinnoi salasanojasi</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Kudeatu zure pasahitzak</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Gestionar sus contraseñas</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Manage your passwords</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Verwalten Sie Ihre Passwörter</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Håndter dine adgangskoder</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Spravujte svá hesla</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Gestioneu les vostres contrasenyes</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Secrets is a password manager which makes use of the KeePass v.4 format. It integrates perfectly with the GNOME desktop and provides an easy and uncluttered interface for the management of password databases.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El Secrets és un gestor de contrasenyes que usa el format del KeePass v.4. S'integra perfectament amb l'escriptori GNOME i proporciona una interfície fàcil i simple per a la gestió de bases de dades de contrasenyes.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Aplikace Secrets je správce hesel, který používá databáze ve formátu KeePass v.4. Je výborně začleněný do uživatelského prostředí GNOME a nabízí jednoduché a přehledné uživatelské rozhraní pro správu databází hesel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Secrets er et program til håndtering af adgangskoder, som bruger KeePass v.4-formatet. Programmet integrerer perfekt med GNOME-skrivebordet og giver en let og ryddelig brugerflade til håndtering af adgangskodedatabaser.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Secrets ist eine Passwortverwaltung, die das KeePass-Format in Version 4 nutzt. Die Anwendung integriert sich perfekt in die GNOME-Arbeitsumgebung und stellt eine einfache und übersichtliche Schnittstelle für die Verwaltung von Passwortdatenbanken bereit.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Secretos es un gestor de contraseñas que usa el formato Keepass v.4. Se integra perfectamente con el escritorio GNOME y proporciona una interfaz limpia y sencilla para la gestión de bases de datos de contraseñas.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Secrets aplikazioa Keepass v.4 formatua erabiltzen duen pasahitz-kudeatzaile bat da. GNOME mahaigainean ongi integratzen da eta interfaze erraz eta garbia eskaintzen du pasahitzen datu-baseak kudeatzeko.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Salaisuudet on salasanojen hallintasovellus, joka käyttää Keepass v.4 -tiedostomuotoa. Se yhdistyy Gnome-työpöydälle ja tarjoaa selkeän sekä helppokäyttöisen käyttöliittymän salasanatietokantojen hallintaan.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Secrets est un gestionnaire de mots de passe utilisant le format KeePass v. 4. Il s’intègre parfaitement au bureau GNOME et fournit une interface simple et épurée pour la gestion des bases de données de mots de passe.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Segredos é un xestor de contrasinais que fai uso do formado de KeePass v.4. Está integrado perfectamente co escritorio GNOME e fornece unha interface doada e ordenada para a xestión de bases de datos de contrasinais.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>סודות הוא מנהל ססמאות שמשתמש במהדורה .4 של תצורת הקבצים KeePass. הוא משתלב באופן מושלם עם שולחן העבודה GNOME ומספק מנשק פשוט ובלתי עמוס לניהול מסדי נתונים של ססמאות.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Titkok egy jelszókezelő, amely a KeePass v.4 formátumot használja. Tökéletesen beépül a GNOME asztali környezetbe, egyszerű és rendezett felületet biztosít a jelszóadatbázisok kezeléséhez.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Secrets adalah manajer kata sandi yang memanfaatkan format KeePass v.4. Ini terintegrasi sempurna dengan desktop GNOME dan menyediakan sebuah antarmuka yang mudah dan rapi untuk manajemen basis data kata sandi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>Secrets er lykilorðastýring sem nýtir KeePass v.4 sniðið. Það er fullkomlega samtvinnað GNOME-skjáborðinu og kemur með auðveldu og hreinlegu viðmóti til að sýsla með lykilorðagagnagrunna.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>«Secrets» è un gestore di password che sfrutta il formato KeePass v.4. Si integra perfettamente con l'ambiente grafico GNOME e fornisce una semplice interfaccia per la gestione delle proprie password.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Hemmeligheter er en passordbehandler som bruker KeePass v.4-formatet. Den integreres perfekt med GNOME-skrivebordet og gir et enkelt og oversiktlig grensesnitt for å administrere passorddatabaser.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Wachtwoordkluis is een wachtwoordbeheerder die gebruik maakt van het KeePass v.4-formaat. Hij integreert perfect met het Gnome-bureaublad en biedt een eenvoudige en duidelijke interface voor het beheer van wachtwoorddatabases.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Secrets to menedżer haseł używający formatu KeePass v.4. Idealnie integruje się ze środowiskiem GNOME i zapewnia łatwy i prosty interfejs do zarządzania bazami haseł.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Segredos é um gestor de palavras-passe que faz uso dos formatos Keepass v.4. Integra-se perfeitamente com o ambiente gráfico GNOME e fornece uma interface fácil e acessível para a gestão de bases de dados de palavras-passe.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Secrets é um gerenciador de senhas que faz uso do formato Keepass v.4. Ele se integra perfeitamente ao ambiente GNOME e fornece um interface fácil e organizada para gerenciar os bancos de dados de senha.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Secrets este un administrator de parole ce utilizează formatul KeePass v.4. Se integrează perfect cu desktopul GNOME și oferă o interfață ușoară pentru administrarea bazelor de date cu parole.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Секреты — это менеджер паролей, который использует формат Keepass v.4. Он отлично интегрируется с рабочим столом GNOME и предоставляет простой и лаконичный интерфейс для управления базами данных паролей.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Secrets je upravitelj gesel, ki uporablja zapis KeePass v.4. Popolnoma se integrira z namizjem GNOME in omogoča enostaven in pregleden vmesnik za upravljanje zbirk podatkov z gesli.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Тајне је управник лозинки који користи формат „Keepass“ 4. Савршено се уклапа у Гномову радну површ и пружа једноставно и прегледно сучеље за управљање базама лозинки.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Secrets är en lösenordshanterare som använder KeePass v.4-formatet. Den integrerar perfekt med GNOME-skrivbordet och tillhandahåller ett enkelt och stilrent gränssnitt för hantering av lösenordsdatabaser.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Secrets, KeePass v.4 biçimini kullanan parola yöneticisidir. GNOME masaüstüyle kusursuzca tümleşir ve parola veri tabanlarının yönetimi için kolay ve düzenli arayüz sunar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>«Секрети» є програмою для керування паролів, яка використовує для зберігання даних формат KeePass версії 4. Вона чудово інтегрується до стільничного середовища GNOME і надає простий і незахаращений інтерфейс для керування базами даних паролів.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="vi">
    <p>Secrets là một chương trình quản lý mật khẩu sử dụng định dạng Keepass v.4. Nó được tích hợp hoàn hảo với môi trường máy tính để bàn GNOME và cung cấp một giao diện gọn gàng cho quản lý cơ sở dữ liệu mật khẩu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>秘密是一个使用 KeePass v.4 格式的密码管理器。与 GNOME 桌面完美集成并提供简易、整洁的界面来管理密码数据库。</p>
  </description>
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-05-06" version="6.5">
      <description>
        <p>Fix a crash that happens when the native file chooser returns NULL as a file.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="6.4" date="2022-04-14">
      <description>
        <p>Fix a crash when creating a new database under certain
        circumstances.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2022-03-28" version="6.3">
      <description>
        <p>Minor bugfix release.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>New translations</li>
          <li>Save operations are now atomic</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2022-02-14" version="6.2">
      <description>
        <p>Minor bugfix release.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="6.1" date="2022-01-21">
      <description>
        <p>Bugfix release.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="6.0" date="2022-01-14">
      <description>
        <p>New Features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Password Safe is now named Secrets</li>
          <li>New and cleaner unlock window</li>
          <li>Support for OTP tokens</li>
          <li>Support expiration dates</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>The app is now powered by GTK 4 and Libadwaita</li>
          <li>Multiple bug fixes</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="5.0" date="2021-02-07">
      <description>
        <p>New Features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Copy username button with an associated Ctrl-Shift-B shortcut</li>
          <li>Mnemonics support</li>
          <li>Menu to create new entries and groups</li>
          <li>Customization: 10 new icons and one more color to customize entries</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Notifications are no longer system-wide</li>
          <li>General system stability improvements to enhance the user's experience</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.1" date="2021-01-05">
      <description>
        <p>Maintenance release of 4.x series.</p>
        <p>Improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved translations</li>
          <li>Clarify that we don't use Backspace to travel between groups and entries, but ESC</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Bugfix:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixes crash when creating new Safe in password compare function</li>
          <li>Fixes crash when opening file on remote filesystem</li>
          <li>When keyfile is moved or removed, application now won't corrupt database and instead won't save</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Known bugs:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>When application isn't able to save due to a missing keyfile, even over the fact, it says "Database saved" it is not saved. This is correctly fixed in upcoming 5.0.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.0" date="2020-11-30">
      <description>
        <p>We'd like to present you Secrets with new features, many bugfixes and huge refactoring in the background.</p>
        <p>New Features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Password Generator has it's own persistent configuration</li>
          <li>Added new shortcut CTRL-Q which quits the application</li>
          <li>The save dialog now allows to cancel the operation</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved compatibility with Linux phones (Librem 5, PinePhone and others)</li>
          <li>Many performance optimizations, especially for large databases</li>
          <li>Search was improved and settings has been moved into global Settings dialog</li>
          <li>Improved Preferences window</li>
          <li>Some visual polishing has been done</li>
          <li>Huge part of the code-base has been refactored</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Bugfix:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Multiple crashes has been fixed</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.99.2" date="2020-02-17">
      <description>
        <p>Password Safe 3.99.2 is a maintenance release.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix a crash if certain attributes are empty</li>
          <li>Fix search not returning results issue</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-01-19" version="3.99.1">
      <description>
        <p>Password Safe 3.99.1 is a maintenance release.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Updated pykeepass support to 3.2</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-01-19" version="3.99">
      <description>
        <p>Password Safe 3.99 brings small feature additions and bug fixes.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added attachment support</li>
          <li>Added undo/redo support in input fields</li>
          <li>Updated pykeepass support to 3.1</li>
          <li>Fixed various issues</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-03-21" version="3.32">
      <description>
        <p>Password Safe 3.32 brings usability optimizations and some feature additions.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added references for linking of properties between multiple entries</li>
          <li>Added entry and group metadata dialog</li>
          <li>Added notes editor dialog with search utility</li>
          <li>Added entry duplication feature</li>
          <li>Reworked entry and group moving utility</li>
          <li>Improved editing mode performance</li>
          <li>Fixed various issues</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.30" date="2018-10-02">
      <description>
        <p>Password Safe 3.30 brings the basic set of features you expect from a modern password manager.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Create or import a KeePass v.4 safe</li>
          <li>Password, keyfile and composite key authentication</li>
          <li>Create and edit groups and entries</li>
          <li>Assign a color and additional attributes to entries</li>
          <li>Move and delete groups and entries</li>
          <li>Cryptographically strong password and passphrase generator</li>
          <li>Database password and keyfile changing</li>
          <li>Search tool with local, global and fulltext filter</li>
          <li>Automatic database lock during inactivity and session lock</li>
          <li>Responsive UI for both desktop and mobile</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <categories>
    <category>Utility</category>
  </categories>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/secrets/-/raw/master/screenshots/browser.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/secrets/-/raw/master/screenshots/entry.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/secrets/-/raw/master/screenshots/start.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/secrets/-/raw/master/screenshots/unlock.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/secrets/-/raw/master/screenshots/search.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/secrets/-/raw/master/screenshots/edit.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <translation type="gettext">secrets</translation>
  <url type="homepage">https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/secrets</url>
  <url type="translate">https://l10n.gnome.org/module/Secrets/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/World/secrets/-/issues</url>
  <update_contact>fseidl@gnome.org</update_contact>
  <developer_name>Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="vi">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="is">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">פאלק אלכסנדר זיידל</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">Falk Alexander Seidl</developer_name>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
  <recommends>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  <kudos>
    <!--
        GNOME Software kudos:
        https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-software/blob/master/doc/kudos.md
      -->
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <custom>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">workstation</value>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">mobile</value>
  </custom>
</component>