<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>gnome-photos</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.Photos.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="cached" height="64" width="64">org.gnome.Photos.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" type="cached" width="128">org.gnome.Photos.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.Photos.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Photos</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">相片</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">相片</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">照片</name>
  <name lang="vi">Ảnh</name>
  <name lang="uk">Світлини</name>
  <name lang="tr">Fotoğraflar</name>
  <name lang="tg">Суратҳо</name>
  <name lang="te">ఛాయాచిత్రాలు</name>
  <name lang="sv">Foton</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Fotografije</name>
  <name lang="sr">Фотографије</name>
  <name lang="sl">Fotografije</name>
  <name lang="sk">Fotografie</name>
  <name lang="ru">Фотографии</name>
  <name lang="ro">Fotografii</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Fotos</name>
  <name lang="pt">Fotos</name>
  <name lang="pl">Zdjęcia</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਫ਼ੋਟੋ</name>
  <name lang="oc">Fòtos</name>
  <name lang="nl">Foto’s</name>
  <name lang="ne">फोटो</name>
  <name lang="nb">Bilder</name>
  <name lang="ms">Foto</name>
  <name lang="ml">ചിത്രങ്ങള്‍</name>
  <name lang="mjw">Arjan</name>
  <name lang="lv">Fotogrāfijas</name>
  <name lang="lt">Nuotraukos</name>
  <name lang="ko">사진</name>
  <name lang="kn">ಫೋಟೋಸ್</name>
  <name lang="kk">Фотолар</name>
  <name lang="ja">写真</name>
  <name lang="id">Foto</name>
  <name lang="it">Foto</name>
  <name lang="is">Ljósmyndir</name>
  <name lang="hu">Fényképek</name>
  <name lang="hr">Fotografije</name>
  <name lang="he">תמונות</name>
  <name lang="gu">ફોટાઓ</name>
  <name lang="gl">Fotos</name>
  <name lang="gd">Dealbhan</name>
  <name lang="ga">Grianghraif</name>
  <name lang="fur">Fotos</name>
  <name lang="fr">Photos</name>
  <name lang="fi">Kuvat</name>
  <name lang="fa">عکس‌ها</name>
  <name lang="eu">Argazkiak</name>
  <name lang="et">Fotod</name>
  <name lang="es">Fotos</name>
  <name lang="eo">Fotoj</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Photos</name>
  <name lang="el">Φωτογραφίες</name>
  <name lang="de">Fotos</name>
  <name lang="da">Billeder</name>
  <name lang="cs">Fotky</name>
  <name lang="ckb">وێنەکان</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">Fotografies</name>
  <name lang="ca">Fotografies</name>
  <name lang="bs">Fotografije</name>
  <name lang="bg">Снимки</name>
  <name lang="as">ফ'টোসমূহ</name>
  <name lang="ar">الصور</name>
  <name lang="an">Fotos</name>
  <summary>Access, organize and share your photos on GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">存取、管理與分享您在 GNOME 中的相片</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_HK">存取、管理與分享你在 GNOME 中的相片</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">在 GNOME 下访问、管理和分享您的照片</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Truy cập, tổ chức và chia sẻ ảnh của bạn trên GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Доступатись, упорядковувати і ділитись вашими фотографіями у GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">GNOME üzerinde fotoğraflarınıza erişin, yönetin ve paylaşın</summary>
  <summary lang="tg">Суратҳоро дар GNOME кушоед, мураттаб ва мубодила кунед</summary>
  <summary lang="te">గ్నోమ్ పై మీ ఛాయాచిత్రాలను ప్రాప్యించండి, నిర్వహించుకోండి, పంచుకోండి.</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Titta på, organisera och dela dina foton i GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Pristupite, razvrstajte i delite vaše fotografije na Gnomu</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Приступите, разврстајте и делите ваше фотографије на Гному</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Urejanje in izmenjava fotografij za namizje GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Pristupujte k vašim fotografiám, organizujte a sprístupňujte ich v prostredí GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Доступ, управление и обмен фотографиями в GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Accesați, organizați și partajați fotografii în GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Acesse, organize e compartilhe suas fotos no GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Aceda, organize e partilhe as suas fotos no GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Dostęp, organizowanie i udostępnianie zdjęć w środowisku GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਉੱਤੇ ਆਪਣੀਆਂ ਫ਼ੋਟੋ ਵਰਤੋਂ, ਪਰਬੰਧ ਕਰੋ ਅਤੇ ਸਾਂਝੀਆਂ ਕਰੋ</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Accedir, organizar e partejar vòstras fòtos amb GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Uw foto’s bekijken, beheren en delen op Gnome</summary>
  <summary lang="ne">जिनोममा तपाईँको फोटो पहुँच, सङ्गठित र साझेदारी गर्नुहोस्</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Se på, organiser og del bilder i GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Capai, urus dan kongsikan foto-foto anda dengan GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ml">ഗ്നോമിൽ നിങ്ങളുടെ ചിത്രങ്ങൾ അക്സസ്സ് ചെയ്യുക,ചിട്ടപ്പെടുത്തുക,പങ്കിടുക</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Piekļūstiet, organizējiet, dalieties ar fotogrāfijām GNOME vidē</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Pasiekite, tvarkykite ir dalinkitės savo nuotraukomis GNOME aplinkoje</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">그놈에서 사진에 접근하고, 정리하고, 공유합니다</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">GNOME ішінде фотосуреттеріңізге қатынаңыз, реттеңіз және олармен бөлісіңіз</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">GNOME で写真を表示、整理、共有します</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Mengakses, menata, dan berbagai foto Anda pada GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Accede, organizza e condivide le foto su GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Skipuleggðu, njóttu og deildu myndunum þínum í GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Fényképek elérése, rendszerezése és megosztása a GNOME-ban</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Pristupite, organizirajte i dijelite svoje fotografije na GNOMU</summary>
  <summary lang="he">לגשת, לארגן ולשתף את התמונות שלך ב־GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="gu">તમારા ફોટાઓ GNOME પર દાખલ કરો, ગોઠવો અને શૅર કરો</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Acceda, organice e comparta as súas fotos en GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="gd">Inntrig, cuir an rian ’s co-roinn na dealbhan agad air GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ga">Déan rochtain ar, eagraigh, agus comhroinn do chuid ghrianghraif ar GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Dopre, organize e condivît lis tôs fotos su GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Accéder à, organiser et partager vos photos avec GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Hallitse ja jaa kuviasi</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">دسترسی، مدیریت و هم‌رسانی عکس‌هایتان در گنوم</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Atzitu, antolatu eta partekatu zure argazkiak GNOMEn</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Ligipääs fotodele, nende haldamine ja jagamine GNOMEs</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Acceda, organice y comparta sus fotos en GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Aliri, administri kaj kunhavigi viajn fotojn sur GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Access, organise and share your photos on GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Προσπελάστε, οργανώστε και μοιραστείτε τις φωτογραφίες σας στο GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="de">In GNOME auf Ihre Fotos zugreifen, diese verwalten und freigeben</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Tilgå, organisér og del dine billeder i GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Prohlížejte si, roztříďte a sdílejte své fotografie v GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Accediu, organitzeu i compartiu les vostres fotografies amb el GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Accediu, organitzeu i compartiu les vostres fotografies amb el GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Pristupi,organiziraj i podjeli fotografije na GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Преглед, организиране и споделяне на снимките ви в GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="as">GNOME ত আপোনাৰ ফ'টোসমূহ অভিগম, সংঘঠিত আৰু অংশীদাৰী কৰক</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">اعرض و نظّم و شارك صورك في جنوم</summary>
  <summary lang="an">Acceda, organice y comparta as suyas fotos en GNOME</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Access, organize and share your photos on GNOME. A simple and elegant
      replacement for using a file manager to deal with photos. Enhance, crop
      and edit in a snap. Seamless cloud integration is offered through GNOME
      Online Accounts.
    </p>
    <p lang="zh_TW">讓您可以在 GNOME 中存取，管理與分享您的相片。不再使用檔案管理器，改使用簡單而優雅的方式來處理照片。一個瞬間完成增強、裁剪與編輯。透過 GNOME 線上帳號提供無縫的雲端整合。</p>
    <p lang="zh_CN">在 GNOME 下访问、管理和分享您的照片。一个可替代文件管理器来处理照片的简洁优雅应用。快速地增强、裁剪和编辑。并与 GNOME 在线帐号无缝整合。</p>
    <p lang="vi">Truy cập, tổ chức và chia sẻ ảnh của bạn trên GNOME. Đây là ứng dụng đơn giản thay thế cho các bộ quản lý tập tin khi dùng với ảnh. Tăng cường, xén ảnh và sửa trong nháy mắt. Nó được nối thông lên mây thông qua “Tài khoản GNOME Trực tuyến”.</p>
    <p lang="uk">Переглядайте, упорядковуйте та оприлюднюйте ваші світлини в GNOME. Це проста проста і витончена заміна файлового менеджера для роботи з фотографіями. Удосконалюйте, обрізайте і редагуйте фотографії на місці. Також доступна інтеграція з інтернетними службами через мережеві облікові записи у GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="tr">GNOME’da fotoğraflarınıza erişin, düzenleyin ve paylaşın. Dosya yöneticisi kullanmak yerine, fotoğraflarla uğraşmak için basit ve zarif bir seçenek. GNOME Çevrim İçi Hesaplar ile kusursuz bulut tümleşimi sunulmaktadır.</p>
    <p lang="sv">Titta på, organisera och dela dina foton i GNOME. Ett enkelt och elegant alternativ till att använda en filhanterare för att hantera foton. Förbättra, beskär och redigera i ett nafs. Integration med molntjänster erbjuds genom GNOME Nätkonton.</p>
    <p lang="sr">Приступајте, сређујте и делите ваше фотографије на Гному. Једноставна и елегантна замена за коришћење управника датотека за рад са фотографијама. Побољшавајте, одрежите и уређујте слике у тренутку. Неприметно обједињавање облака се нуди кроз Гномове налоге на мрежи.</p>
    <p lang="sl">Enostaven program za urejanje in izmenjavo fotografij na namizju GNOME. Ustvarjen je z namenom, da zamenja običajni upravljalnik datotek pri urejanju fotografij. Program podpira tudi objavljanje fotografij v oblak prek spletnih računov GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="sk">Pristupujte, organizujte a zdieľajte vaše fotografie v prostredí GNOME. Jednoduchá a elegantná náhrada za používanie správcu súborov pri práci s fotografiami. V rýchlosti vylepšujte, orezávajte a upravujte. Samozrejmosťou je prepojenie s cloudom prostredníctvom Účtov služieb pre GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="ru">Доступ, управление и предоставление доступа к вашим фотографиям в GNOME. Простая и элегантная замена для работы с фотографиями по сравнению с обычным файловым менеджером. Улучшение, подрезка и редактирование в одно нажатие. Бесшовная интеграция с облачными службами осуществляется через сетевые учётные записи GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="ro">Accesați, organizați și partajați fotografiile în GNOME. O alternativă simplă și elegantă a unui administrator de fișiere pentru manipularea fotografiilor. Îmbunătățire, decupare și editare într-o clipă. Oferă integrare cloud perfectă prin intermediul aplicației Conturi Online GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="pt_BR">Acesse, organize e compartilhe suas fotos no GNOME. Ele substitui de maneira simples e elegante o gerenciador de arquivos para lidar com fotos. Integração transparente com a nuvem é oferecida por meio do aplicativo de contas on-line do GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="pt">Uma aplicação simples para aceder, organizar e partilhar as suas fotos no GNOME. Pretende ser um substituto simples e elegante à utilização de um gestor de ficheiros para lidar com fotos. Otimizar, recortar e editar facilmente. É possível integração em nuvem através das Contas online do GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="pl">Dostęp, organizowanie i udostępnianie zdjęć w środowisku GNOME. Prosty i elegancki program zastępujący menedżer plików jako sposób na zarządzanie zdjęciami. Błyskawiczne uwydatnianie, kadrowanie i retuszowanie. Integracja z chmurą przez usługę Konta online GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਵਿੱਚ ਤੁਹਾਡੀਆਂ ਫ਼ੋਟੋ ਲਈ ਪਹੁੰਚ, ਉਹਨਾਂ ਦਾ ਪਰਬੰਧ ਅਤੇ ਸਾਂਝਾ ਕਰੋ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਫ਼ੋਟੋ ਦਾ ਪਰਬੰਧ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਫਾਇਲ ਮੈਨੇਜਰ ਦੀ ਬਜਾਏ ਸੌਖਾ ਤੇ ਸਧਾਰਨ ਰੂਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਤਿਆਰ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਝਲਕ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਧਾਰੋ, ਕਰੋਪ ਕਰੋ ਅਤੇ ਸੋਧੋ। ਗਨੋਮ ਆਨਲਾਈਨ ਖਾਤਿਆਂ ਰਾਹੀਂ ਕਲਾਉਡ ਜੋੜ ਨੂੰ ਵੀ ਸੌਖਾ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p lang="oc">Una aplicacion per accedir, organizar e partejar vòstras fòtos amb GNOME. Se vòl èsser una alternativa a l'encòp simpla e eleganta al tradicional gestionari de fichièrs per manipular las fòtos. Una integracion transparenta de la nívol es tanben ofèrta via lo gestionari dels comptes en linha GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="nl">Bekijk, beheer en deel uw foto’s op Gnome. Een eenvoudige en elegante vervanging van een bestandsbeheerprogramma om foto’s te beheren. Verbeter en snijd bij in een handomdraai. Via Gnome Online Accounts wordt een naadloze integratie met de cloud geboden.</p>
    <p lang="ne">जिनोममा तपाईँको फोटो पहुँच, सङ्गठित र साझेदारी गर्नुहोस् । फोटोसँग व्यवहार गर्न फाइल प्रबन्धक प्रयोग गर्नका लागि एउटा सरल र सुरुचिपूर्ण प्रतिस्थापन । सटाउनुहोस्, काटछाँट गर्नुहोस् र सटाउनुहोस्। जिनोम अनलाइन खाता मार्फत सीमलेस क्लाउड इन्टिग्रेसन प्रस्ताव गरिएको छ ।.</p>
    <p lang="nb">Et enkelt program for å se på, organisere og dele bilder med GNOME. Det er ment som en enkel og elegant erstatning for filutforskeren til bildebehandling. Sømløs integrasjon med skytjenester tilbys gjennom GNOME-kontoer på nettet.</p>
    <p lang="ms">Capai, urus dan kongsikan foto-foto anda dengan GNOME. Satu penggantian ringkas dan elegan seperti sebuah pengurus fail yang mengendalikan foto. Tambah baik, kerat dan sunting dengan mudah. Penyepaduan awan tanpa berkelim ditawarkan melalui Akaun Dalam Talian GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="ml">ഗ്നോമിൽ നിങ്ങളുടെ ചിത്രങ്ങൾ അക്സസ്സ് ചെയ്യുക,ചിട്ടപ്പെടുത്തുക,പങ്കിടുക.ഫോട്ടോകൾ കൈകാര്യം ചെയ്യാൻ ഒരു ഫയൽ മാനേജർ ഉപയോഗിക്കുന്നതിനുള്ള ലളിതവും ഗംഭീരവുമായ ഒരു മാർഗം.ഞൊടിയിടയിൽ ചിത്രങ്ങൾ മുറിക്കാം,മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്താം,തിരുത്താം.ഗ്നോം അക്കൗണ്ട് മുഖേന സുഗമമായുള്ള ക്‌ളൗഡ്‌ സംയോജനവും ലഭിക്കുന്നതാണ്.</p>
    <p lang="lv">Piekļūstiet, organizējiet un dalieties ar fotogrāfijām GNOME vidē. Tā ir  datņu pārvaldnieka aizvietotāja darbam ar fotogrāfijām. Ātri uzlabojiet kadrējiet un rediģējiet. Integrāciju ar mākoņpakalpojumiem nodrošina caur GNOME tiešsaistes kontiem.</p>
    <p lang="lt">Paprasta programa GNOME aplinkai nuotraukų tvarkymui ir dalijimuisi jomis. Ji siekia būti paprastu ir elegantišku pakaitalu failų tvarkytuvės naudojimui nuotraukoms. Integracija su debesų technologija siūloma per GNOME internetines paskyras.</p>
    <p lang="ko">그놈에서 사진에 접근하고 정리하며 공유하는 간단한 프로그램입니다. 파일 관리자에서 사진을 다룰 때보다 더 간단하고 세련된 기능이 있습니다. 사진을 자르고 편집하는 기능을 개선했습니다. 그놈 온라인 계정에서 제공하는 감쪽같은 클라우드 통합 기능도 있습니다.</p>
    <p lang="kk">GNOME ішінде фотосуреттеріңізге қатынау, реттеу және олармен бөлісу. Ол фотолармен жұмыс істеуге файлдар басқарушысын алмастыра алатын қолданба ретінде дайындалған. GNOME желідегі тіркелгілері арқылы бұлттық қызметтермен байланыс іске асырылған.</p>
    <p lang="ja">GNOME で写真を表示、整理、共有します。ファイルマネージャーを使用することなく、無駄のない洗練された写真管理ができます。写真を手早く切り抜いたり強調したりすることもできます。GNOME オンラインアカウントを通じて、クラウドとシームレスに連携して利用できます。</p>
    <p lang="id">Akses, atur, dan bagikan foto Anda di GNOME. Pengganti yang sederhana dan elegan bagi pemakaian manajer berkas untuk berurusan dengan foto. Tingkatkan, pangkas, dan sunting dalam sekejap. Integrasi awan yang mulus ditawarkan melalui Akun Daring GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="it">Accede, organizza e condivide le proprie foto su GNOME. Un semplice ed elegante sostituto per l'uso di un gestore di file per trattare con le foto. L'integrazione senza interruzioni del cloud è offerta tramite gli account online di GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="is">Skipuleggðu, njóttu og deildu myndunum þínum í GNOME. Það er hugsað til þess að vera einföld og hreinleg leið til að eiga við myndir án þess að þurfa að nota skráastjóra. Boðið er upp á fljótvirka samhæfni við netský í gegnum 'GNOME Online Accounts'.</p>
    <p lang="hu">Érje el, rendszerezze és ossza meg a képeit GNOME alatt. Egy egyszerű és elegáns helyettesítője a fájlkezelő fényképek kezelésére való használatának. Sima felhőintegráció érhető el a GNOME Online fiókok segítségével.</p>
    <p lang="hr">Pristupite, organizirajte i dijelite svoje fotografije na GNOMU. Jednostavna i elegantna zamjena za rukovanje fotografijama u upravitelju datoteka. Poboljšajte, obrežite i uredite u trenu. Besprijekorna integracija sa oblakom je omogućena putem GNOME mrežnih računa.</p>
    <p lang="he">גישה, ארגון ושיתוף התמונות שלך על GNOME. מהווה תחליף פשוט ומהודר לשימוש בסייר קבצים להתמודדות עם תמונות. נתן להגדיל, לחתוך ולערוך בלחיצה. שילוב חלק של ענן מוצע באמצעות GNOME חשבונות מקוונים.</p>
    <p lang="gl">Acceda, organice e comparta as súas fotos en GNOME. Está pensado para que sexa unha alternativa simple e elegante ao uso do explorador de ficheiros para xestionar as fotos. Mellore, recorte e edite rapidamente. Conta con integración coa nube mediante Conta en liña de GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="fur">Doprâ, organizâ e condividi lis tôs fotos su GNOME. Une semplice e elegante sostituzion a un file manager par ministrâ lis fotos. Miore, cjonce e modifiche in lamp e ton. La integrazion cul cloud e je ufierte vie GNOME Online Accounts.</p>
    <p lang="fr">Accéder à, organiser et partager des photos avec GNOME. Une alternative à la fois simple et élégante au traditionnel gestionnaire de fichiers pour manipuler les photos. Améliorer, rogner et modifier en un clin d’œil. Une intégration transparente du nuage est aussi offerte via le gestionnaire des comptes en ligne GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="fi">Sovellus Gnome-työpöydälle kuvien käyttöä, organisointia ja jakamista varten. Korvaa tiedostonhallinta tällä sovelluksella, kun työskentelet kuvien parissa. Paranna, rajaa ja muokkaa kuvia nopeasti. Saumattoman pilvi-integraation tarjoaa Gnomen verkkotilit.</p>
    <p lang="fa">دسترسی، مرتّب‌سازی و هم‌رسانی عکس‌هایتان روی گنوم. جایگزین ساده و شیک استفاده از مدیر پرونده برای کار با عکس‌ها. بهبود، برش و ویرایش در یک چشم به هم زدن. یکپارچه‌سازی ابری از طریق حساب‌های برخط گنوم.</p>
    <p lang="eu">Atzitu, antolatu eta partekatu zure argazkiak GNOMEn. Argazkiekin aritzeko fitxategi-kudeatzaile baten ordezko xume eta dotorea da. GNOMEren lineako kontuen (GNOME Online Accounts) bidez lainoarekin sinestezineko bateragarritasuna du.</p>
    <p lang="es">Acceder, organizar y compartir sus fotos en GNOME. Está pensada para ser un reemplazo sencillo y elegante del uso de un gestor de archivos para gestionar sus fotos. Mejore, recorte y edite en un momento. Se integra perfectamente con la nube mediante las cuentas en línea de GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="eo">Aliri, administri kaj kunhavigi viajn fotojn sur GNOME. Simpla aplikaĵo por aliri, administri kaj kunhavigi viajn fotojn sur GNOME. Ĝi estas simpla kaj eleganta anstataŭaĵo por uzi dosier-manaĝeron por trakti fotojn. Rekta nuba integrigo estas oferata per GNOME Retaj Kontok.</p>
    <p lang="en_GB">Access, organise and share your photos on GNOME. A simple and elegant replacement for using a file manager to deal with photos. Enhance, crop and edit in a snap. Seamless cloud integration is offered through GNOME Online Accounts.</p>
    <p lang="el">Αποκτήστε πρόσβαση, οργανώστε και διαμοιραστείτε τις φωτογραφίες σας στο GNOME. Ένας απλός και κομψός αντικαταστάτης για την διαχείριση των φωτογραφιών σας από τον διαχειριστή αρχείων. Βελτιώστε, περικόψτε και επεξεργαστείτε πολύ γρήγορα. Προσφέρεται και η ενσωμάτωση με το cloud μέσω των διαδικτυακών λογαριασμών του GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="de">In GNOME auf Ihre Fotos zugreifen, diese verwalten und freigeben. Eine einfache und elegante Alternative zur Organisation von Fotos durch einen Dateimanager. Eine direkte Cloud-Integration wird durch die GNOME-Online-Konten angeboten.</p>
    <p lang="da">Tilgå, organisér og del dine billeder i GNOME. En simpel og elegant erstatning for at bruge en filhåndtering som billedhåndtering. Retouchér, beskær og redigér i et snuptag. Direkte cloud-integrering via GNOME Onlinekonti.</p>
    <p lang="cs">Mějte přístup ke svých fotografií v GNOME, udělejte si v nich pořádek a sdílejte je s ostatními. Jedná se o jednoduchou a elegantní náhradu za používání správce souborů k práci s fotkami. Díky účtům on-line v GNOME se úplně stejně snadno dostanete i ke svým fotkám v cloudu.</p>
    <p lang="ca">Accediu, organitzeu i compartiu les vostres fotografies amb el GNOME. Un substitut simple i elegant del gestor de fitxers en la gestió d'imatges. Milloreu, retalleu i editeu instantàniament. S'integra transparentment amb el núvol mitjançant els comptes en línia del GNOME.</p>
    <p lang="bg">Приложение за намиране, организиране и споделяне на снимки в GNOME. Предназначено е да бъде опростен и елегантен заместник на използването на файловия мениджър при работа със снимки. Лесно ретуширане, оразмеряване, редактиране и отрязване.
Предлага постоянна интеграция с облака чрез регистрациите на GNOME.</p>
    <p>You can:</p>
    <p lang="zh_TW">你可以：</p>
    <p lang="zh_CN">您可以：</p>
    <p lang="vi">Bạn có thể:</p>
    <p lang="uk">Можете зробити так:</p>
    <p lang="tr">Şunları yapabilirsiniz:</p>
    <p lang="sv">Du kan:</p>
    <p lang="sr">Можете:</p>
    <p lang="sl">S programom je mogoče:</p>
    <p lang="sk">Môžete:</p>
    <p lang="ru">Вы можете:</p>
    <p lang="ro">Aveți posibilitatea:</p>
    <p lang="pt_BR">Você pode:</p>
    <p lang="pt">É possível:</p>
    <p lang="pl">Funkcje:</p>
    <p lang="pa">ਤੁਸੀਂ:</p>
    <p lang="oc">Podètz :</p>
    <p lang="nl">U kunt:</p>
    <p lang="ne">तपाईंले सक्नुहुन्छ:</p>
    <p lang="nb">Du kan:</p>
    <p lang="ms">Anda boleh:</p>
    <p lang="ml">നിങ്ങൾക്ക് കഴിയുന്നത്:</p>
    <p lang="lv">Jūs varat:</p>
    <p lang="lt">Jūs galite:</p>
    <p lang="ko">다음을 할 수 있습니다:</p>
    <p lang="kk">Мүмкіндіктеріңіз:</p>
    <p lang="ja">できること:</p>
    <p lang="id">Anda dapat:</p>
    <p lang="it">È possibile:</p>
    <p lang="is">Þú getur:</p>
    <p lang="hu">Ezeket teheti:</p>
    <p lang="hr">Možete:</p>
    <p lang="he">מאפשר לך:</p>
    <p lang="gl">Pode:</p>
    <p lang="fur">Tu puedis:</p>
    <p lang="fr">Vous pouvez :</p>
    <p lang="fi">Voit:</p>
    <p lang="fa">می‌توانید:</p>
    <p lang="eu">Honakoak egin ditzakezu:</p>
    <p lang="es">Puede:</p>
    <p lang="eo">Vi povas:</p>
    <p lang="en_GB">You can:</p>
    <p lang="el">Μπορείτε:</p>
    <p lang="de">Sie können:</p>
    <p lang="da">Du kan:</p>
    <p lang="cs">Můžete:</p>
    <p lang="ca">Podeu:</p>
    <p lang="bg">Получавате:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Automatically find all your pictures</li>
      <li lang="zh_TW">自動尋找你的所有圖片</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">自动查找您所有的图片</li>
      <li lang="vi">Tìm kiếm một cách tự động tất cả các ảnh của bạn</li>
      <li lang="uk">Автоматично знаходить усі ваші фотографії</li>
      <li lang="tr">Tüm fotoğraflarınızı kendiliğiden bulun</li>
      <li lang="sv">Automatiskt hitta alla dina bilder</li>
      <li lang="sr">Аутоматски наћи све ваше слике</li>
      <li lang="sl">samodejno poiskati slike na različnih mestih</li>
      <li lang="sk">Automaticky nájsť všetky vaše obrázky</li>
      <li lang="ru">Автоматически находить все ваши фотографии</li>
      <li lang="ro">Căutați automat toate fotografiile</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Encontrar automaticamente todas as suas fotos</li>
      <li lang="pt">Procurar todas as fotos automaticamente</li>
      <li lang="pl">Automatyczne wyszukiwanie wszystkich zdjęć</li>
      <li lang="pa">ਆਪਣੀਆਂ ਸਾਰੀਆਂ ਤਸਵੀਰਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਆਪਣੇ-ਆਪ ਲੱਭੋ</li>
      <li lang="oc">Trobatz automaticament totas vòstras fòtos</li>
      <li lang="nl">Al uw foto’s automatisch vinden</li>
      <li lang="ne">तपाईँको सबै तस्वीर स्वत: फेला पार्नुहोस्</li>
      <li lang="nb">Finne alle bildene dine automatisk</li>
      <li lang="ms">Cari semua gambar anda secara automatik</li>
      <li lang="ml">നിങ്ങളുടെ എല്ലാ ചിത്രങ്ങളും യാന്ത്രികമായി കണ്ടെത്തുക</li>
      <li lang="lv">Automātiski atrodiet visas savas bildes</li>
      <li lang="lt">Automatiškai rasti visas visas jūsų nutraukas</li>
      <li lang="ko">모든 사진을 자동으로 찾습니다</li>
      <li lang="kk">Барлық суреттеріңізді автоматты түрде табу</li>
      <li lang="ja">あなたの写真を自動的に見つける</li>
      <li lang="id">Secara otomatis menemukan semua foto Anda</li>
      <li lang="it">Trovare automaticamente tutte le foto</li>
      <li lang="is">Fundið allar myndirnar þínar sjálfvirkt</li>
      <li lang="hu">Az összes képe automatikus megkeresése</li>
      <li lang="hr">Automatski pronaći sve svoje slike</li>
      <li lang="he">איתור אוטומטי של כל התמונות שלך</li>
      <li lang="gl">Atopar automaticamente todas as súas fotos</li>
      <li lang="fur">Cjatâ in automatic dutis lis imagjins</li>
      <li lang="fr">Trouver automatiquement toutes vos images</li>
      <li lang="fi">Löytää kaikki kuvasi automaattisesti</li>
      <li lang="fa">یافتن خودکار تمام عکس‌هایتان</li>
      <li lang="eu">Zure irudiak automatikoki aurkitu</li>
      <li lang="es">Buscar automáticamente todas sus fotos</li>
      <li lang="eo">Aŭtomate trovi viajn bildojn</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Automatically find all your pictures</li>
      <li lang="el">Αυτόματη εύρεση όλων των φωτογραφιών σας</li>
      <li lang="de">Automatisch all Ihre Bilder finden</li>
      <li lang="da">Automatisk finde alle dine billeder</li>
      <li lang="cs">Automaticky vyhledávat všechny své obrázky</li>
      <li lang="ca">Trobar automàticament totes les fotografies</li>
      <li lang="bg">Автоматично откриване на всичките ви снимки</li>
      <li>View recent local and online photos</li>
      <li lang="zh_TW">檢視最近使用的本地與線上相片</li>
      <li lang="zh_HK">檢視最近使用的本地與網上相片</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">查看最近的本地或在线照片</li>
      <li lang="vi">Xem các ảnh nội bộ và trực tuyến mới dùng</li>
      <li lang="uk">Переглядати свіжі світлини з комп'ютера та в мережі</li>
      <li lang="tr">Son yerel ve çevrim içi fotoğrafları görüntüleyin</li>
      <li lang="tg">Намоиш додани суратҳои қаблии маҳаллӣ ва онлайн</li>
      <li lang="sv">Visa nya lokala foton och foton från nätkonton</li>
      <li lang="sr@latin">Vidite skorašnje mesne i fotografije na mreži</li>
      <li lang="sr">Видите скорашње месне и фотографије на мрежи</li>
      <li lang="sl">Pregled nedavnih krajevnih in spletnih fotografij</li>
      <li lang="sk">Zobraziť nedávne miestne a internetové fotografie</li>
      <li lang="ru">Просматривать последние локальные фотографии и фотографии в Интернете</li>
      <li lang="ro">Vizualizați fotografiile locale recente și cele online</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Ver fotos recentes locais e on-line</li>
      <li lang="pt">Ver fotos recentes locais e online</li>
      <li lang="pl">Przeglądanie zdjęć lokalnych i w sieci</li>
      <li lang="pa">ਤਾਜ਼ਾ ਲੋਕਲ ਤੇ ਆਨਲਾਈਨ ਫ਼ੋਟੋ ਵੇਖੋ</li>
      <li lang="oc">Veire de fòtos recentas en local o en linha</li>
      <li lang="nl">Recente foto’s, lokaal en online, bekijken</li>
      <li lang="ne">हालैको स्थानीय र अनलाइन फोटोहरू हेर्नुहोस्</li>
      <li lang="nb">Vis nylige bilder lokalt og på nett</li>
      <li lang="ms">Lihat foto-foto setempat baru-baru ini dan juga foto-foto dalam talian</li>
      <li lang="ml">സമീപകാല ലോക്കൽ, ഓൺലൈൻ ഫോട്ടോകൾ കാണുക</li>
      <li lang="lv">Skatiet nesenās lokālās un tiešsaistes fotogrāfijas</li>
      <li lang="lt">Rodyti nesenas vietines ir internetines nuotraukas</li>
      <li lang="ko">최근 로컬 및 온라인 사진을 봅니다</li>
      <li lang="kk">Жуырдағы жергілікті және онлайн фотоларын қарау</li>
      <li lang="ja">ローカルおよびオンラインで最近使用した写真を表示する</li>
      <li lang="id">Melihat foto lokal dan daring baru-baru ini</li>
      <li lang="it">Visualizzare le foto recenti locali e in rete</li>
      <li lang="is">Skoðað nýlegar ljósmyndir á tölvunni eða myndir á netinu</li>
      <li lang="hu">A legutóbbi helyi és online fényképek megtekintése</li>
      <li lang="hr">Pogledati nedavne lokalne ili mrežne fotografije</li>
      <li lang="he">הצגת תמונות מקומיות ומקוונות אחרונות</li>
      <li lang="gl">Ver os cambios recentes e fotos en liña</li>
      <li lang="gd">Dealbhan ionadail ’s air loidhne o chionn goirid a shealltainn</li>
      <li lang="fur">Viôt fotos locâi e online recents</li>
      <li lang="fr">Voir des photos récentes en local ou en ligne</li>
      <li lang="fi">Katsella paikallisia ja verkossa olevia valokuvia</li>
      <li lang="fa">نمایش عکس‌های اخیر محلی و برخط</li>
      <li lang="eu">Ikusi lokaleko eta lineako azken argazkiak</li>
      <li lang="es">Ver fotos locales y en línea recientes</li>
      <li lang="eo">Vidi lastatempajn fotojn, lokajn kaj retajn</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">View recent local and online photos</li>
      <li lang="el">Δείτε τις πρόσφατες τοπικές και διαδικτυακές φωτογραφίες σας</li>
      <li lang="de">Zuletzt verwendete lokale und Online-Fotos ansehen</li>
      <li lang="da">Vis seneste lokale eller online billeder</li>
      <li lang="cs">Prohlížet si nejnovější fotky uložené v počítači i on-line</li>
      <li lang="ca@valencia">Visualitzar les fotos locals i en línia recents</li>
      <li lang="ca">Visualitzar les fotos locals i en línia recents</li>
      <li lang="bs">Pogledaj nedavne lokalne i online fotografije</li>
      <li lang="bg">Преглед на скорошните снимки локално и онлайн</li>
      <li lang="as">শেহতীয়া স্থানীয় আৰু অনলাইন ফ'টোসমূহ চাওক</li>
      <li lang="ar">عرض آخر الملفات المحلية والشبكية</li>
      <li lang="an">Veyer fotos locals y en linia recients</li>
      <li>Access your Facebook or Flickr pictures</li>
      <li lang="zh_TW">存取您的 Facebook 或 Flickr 圖片</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">获取您的 Facebook 或 Flickr 图片</li>
      <li lang="vi">Truy cập các ảnh trên Facebook hay Flickr của bạn</li>
      <li lang="uk">Отримувати доступ до ваших світлин на Facebook або Flickr</li>
      <li lang="tr">Facebook veya Flickr fotoğraflarınıza ulaşın</li>
      <li lang="sv">Komma åt dina bilder på Facebook eller Flickr</li>
      <li lang="sr">Приступите вашим сликама на Фејсбуку или Фликру</li>
      <li lang="sl">dostop do slik na družbenih omrežjih Facebook ali Flickr</li>
      <li lang="sk">Pristupovať k vašim obrázkom na službách Facebook alebo Flickr</li>
      <li lang="ru">Получать доступ к вашим изображениям Facebook или Flickr</li>
      <li lang="ro">Accesați fotografiile de pe Facebook sau Flickr</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Acessar suas fotos do Facebook ou do Flickr</li>
      <li lang="pt">Aceder às fotos no Facebook ou no Flickr</li>
      <li lang="pl">Dostęp do zdjęć w serwisach Facebook i Flickr</li>
      <li lang="pa">ਆਪਣੀ ਫੇਸਬੁੱਕ ਜਾਂ ਫਲਿੱਕਰ ਤਸਵੀਰਾਂ ਵਰਤੋਂ</li>
      <li lang="oc">Accedir a vòstres imatges Facebook o Flickr</li>
      <li lang="nl">Toegang tot uw Facebook- of Flickr-foto’s</li>
      <li lang="ne">तपाईँको फेसबुक वा फ्लिकर तस्वीर पहुँच गर्नुहोस्</li>
      <li lang="nb">Få tilgang til bilder på Facebook eller Flickr</li>
      <li lang="ms">Capai gambar Facebook atau Flickr anda</li>
      <li lang="ml">നിങ്ങളുടെ ഫേസ്ബുക്ക് അല്ലെങ്കിൽ ഫ്ലിക്കർ ചിത്രങ്ങൾ ആക്സസ് ചെയ്യുക</li>
      <li lang="mjw">Facebook mate Flickr arjan chelang me</li>
      <li lang="lv">Piekļūstiet savām Facebook vai Flickr bildēm</li>
      <li lang="lt">Pasiekite savo Facebook ar Flickr nuotraukas</li>
      <li lang="ko">페이스북 또는 플리커 사진에 접근합니다</li>
      <li lang="kk">Өзіңіздің Facebook немесе Flickr суреттеріңізге қатынау</li>
      <li lang="ja">Facebook または Flickr 上のあなたの写真にアクセスする</li>
      <li lang="id">Akses foto Facebook atau Flickr Anda</li>
      <li lang="it">Accedere alle proprie foto di Facebook o Flickr</li>
      <li lang="is">Fengið aðgang að myndunum þínum á Facebook eða Flickr</li>
      <li lang="hu">Hozzáférés a Facebook vagy Flickr képeihez</li>
      <li lang="hr">Pristupiti vašim Facebook ili Flickr slikama</li>
      <li lang="he">גישה לתמונות Facebook או Flickr שלך</li>
      <li lang="gl">Acceda ás súas fotos en Facebook ou Flickr</li>
      <li lang="fur">Doprâ lis tôs imagjins di Facebook o Flickr</li>
      <li lang="fr">Accéder à vos images Facebook ou Flickr</li>
      <li lang="fi">Käyttää Facebook- ja Flickr-sisältöä</li>
      <li lang="fa">دسترسی به عکس‌های فیس‌بوک و فلیکرتان</li>
      <li lang="eu">Atzitu Facebook edo Flickr sareetako zure irudiak</li>
      <li lang="es">Acceder a sus fotos de Facebook o Flickr</li>
      <li lang="eo">Atingi vian Facebook- aŭ Flickr-bildojn</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Access your Facebook or Flickr pictures</li>
      <li lang="el">Αποκτήστε πρόσβαση στις φωτογραφίες σας σε Facebook ή Flickr</li>
      <li lang="de">Auf Ihre Bilder in Facebook oder Flickr zugreifen</li>
      <li lang="da">Tilgå dine Facebook- eller Flickr-billeder</li>
      <li lang="cs">Přistupovat ke svým obrázkům na Facebooku a Flickru</li>
      <li lang="ca">Accedir a les fotografies de Facebook o Flickr</li>
      <li lang="bg">Достъп до снимките във Facebook и Flickr</li>
      <li>View photos on TVs, laptops or other DLNA renderers on your local
          network</li>
      <li lang="zh_TW">在您的區域網路上，用電視、筆電或其他 DLNA 算繪器檢視圖片</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">查看您本地网络中的电视、笔记本或其他 DLNA 媒体渲染器上照片</li>
      <li lang="vi">Hiển thị các ảnh trên các TV, máy tính xách tay hay các bộ hiển thị DLNA trong mạng nội bộ của bạn</li>
      <li lang="uk">Переглядати фотографії на телевізорах, ноутбуках та інших обробниках протоколу DLNA у вашій локальній мережі</li>
      <li lang="tr">Fotoğraflarınızı yerel ağınızdaki TVʼlerde, dizüstülerde veya diğer DLNA işleyicilerde görüntüleyin</li>
      <li lang="sv">Visa foton på TV-apparater, bärbara datorer eller andra DLNA-renderare på ditt lokala nätverk</li>
      <li lang="sr">Погледати слике на ТВ-у, лаптоповима и другим уређајима који подржавају ДЛНА на вашој мрежи</li>
      <li lang="sl">pregledovati slike na TV, računalniku in na drugih izrisovalnikih DLNA na omrežju</li>
      <li lang="sk">Zobraziť fotografie na TV, notebooku alebo inom DLNA prehrávači vo vašej miestnej sieti</li>
      <li lang="ru">Просматривать фотографии на телевизорах, ноутбуках или других обработчиках DLNA в локальной сети</li>
      <li lang="ro">Vizualizați fotografii pe televizoare, laptop-uri sau alte randoare DLNA pe rețeaua locală</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Ver fotos em TVs, laptops e outros dispositivos com DLNA em sua rede local</li>
      <li lang="pt">Ver fotos em televisores, ecrãs de computador ou outros dispositivos na rede local</li>
      <li lang="pl">Wyświetlanie zdjęć na telewizorze, laptopie lub innym urządzeniu zgodnym z DLNA w sieci lokalnej</li>
      <li lang="pa">ਫ਼ੋਟੋਆਂ ਨੂੰ ਟੀਵੀ, ਲੈਪਟਾਪ ਜਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਲੋਕਲ ਨੈੱਟਵਰਕ ਉੱਤੇ DLNA ਰੈਂਡਰ ਉੱਤੇ ਵੇਖ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ</li>
      <li lang="oc">Visualizar de fòtos sus la TV, los portatius o d'autres equipament DLNA de vòstre ret local</li>
      <li lang="nl">Foto’s bekijken op tv’s, laptops of andere DLNA-renderers in uw lokale netwerk</li>
      <li lang="ne">तपाईँको स्थानीय सञ्जालमा टिभी, ल्यापटप वा अन्य DLNA रेन्डररमा फोटोहरू हेर्नुहोस्</li>
      <li lang="nb">Vise bidler på TV, bærbare datamaskiner eller andre DNLA visningsenheter på det lokale nettverket</li>
      <li lang="ms">Lihat foto-foto dalam TV, komputer riba atau lain-lain penerap DLNA dalam rangkaian setempat anda</li>
      <li lang="ml">നിങ്ങളുടെ പ്രാദേശിക നെറ്റ്വർക്കിലെ ടിവികൾ, ലാപ്ടോപ്പുകൾ അല്ലെങ്കിൽ മറ്റ് DLNA റെൻഡററുകളിലെ ഫോട്ടോകൾ കാണുക</li>
      <li lang="lv">Skatiet fotogrāfijas televizorā , klēpjdatorā un citos DLNA attēlotājos jūsu lokālajā tīklā</li>
      <li lang="lt">Rodyti nuotraukas televizoriuose, kompiuteriuose bei kituose DLNA piešimo įrenginiuose vietiniame tinkle</li>
      <li lang="ko">로컬 네트워크의 TV, 랩톱, 기타 DLNA 렌터링 장비의 사진을 봅니다</li>
      <li lang="kk">Фотоларды теледидар, ноутбук немесе желіңіздегі басқа да DLNA қабылдағыштарында қарау</li>
      <li lang="ja">ローカルネットワーク上のテレビやノートパソコン、その他の DLNA レンダラーで写真を表示する</li>
      <li lang="id">Lihat foto di TV, laptop, atau penyaji DLNA lainnya pada jaringan lokal Anda</li>
      <li lang="it">Visualizzare le foto sulle TV, portatili o su altri visualizzatori DLNA della propria rete locale</li>
      <li lang="is">Skoðað myndir á sjónvörpum,fartölvum eða öðrum tækjum sem styðja DLNA á staðarnetinu þínu</li>
      <li lang="hu">Képek megtekintése TV-ken, laptopokon vagy más DLNA megjelenítőkön a helyi hálózaton</li>
      <li lang="hr">Pogledati fotografije na TV-u, prijenosnicima ili drugim DLNA uređajima na vašoj lokalnoj mreži</li>
      <li lang="he">הצגת תמונות בטלוויזיה, במחשב הנייד או במעבד DLNA אחר ברשת המקומית שלך</li>
      <li lang="gl">Ver as fotos na televisión, portátiles ou renderizadores DLNA na súa rede local</li>
      <li lang="fur">Viodi lis fotos su pai televisôrs, portatii e altris visualizadôrs DLNA te tô rêt locâl</li>
      <li lang="fr">Voir des photos sur des téléviseurs, des portables ou tout autre moteur DLNA sur votre réseau local</li>
      <li lang="fi">Katsella kuvia TV:stä, kannettavalta tietokoneelta ja muilla DLNA-laitteilla verkossasi</li>
      <li lang="fa">دیدن عکس‌های روی تلویزیون، لپ‌تاپ یا دیگر پرداختگرها روی شبکهٔ محلّیتان</li>
      <li lang="eu">Ikusi argazkiak zure sare lokaleko telebistan, eramangarrian edo beste edozein DLNA irteeran</li>
      <li lang="es">Ver fotos en la televisión, portátiles u otros dispositivos DLNA en su red local.</li>
      <li lang="eo">Vidi fotojn sur televidoj, klapkomputiloj, kaj aliaj DLNA-iloj sur via loka reto</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">View photos on TVs, laptops or other DLNA renderers on your local network</li>
      <li lang="el">Δείτε φωτογραφίες σε τηλεοράσεις, φορητούς υπολογιστές ή σε άλλες συσκευές με DLNA στο τοπικό σας δίκτυο</li>
      <li lang="de">Fotos auf Fernsehern, Laptops oder anderen DLNA-Geräten in Ihrem Heimnetzwerk ansehen</li>
      <li lang="da">Vise billeder på tv'er, bærbare computere og andre DLNA-enheder på dit lokale netværk</li>
      <li lang="cs">Zobrazovat si fotografie na televizi, notebooku a dalších zařízeních v síti podporujících DLNA</li>
      <li lang="ca">Visualitzar fotografies en televisors, portàtils o altres visualitzadors DNLA de la vostra xarxa</li>
      <li lang="bg">Преглед на снимките на телевизор, лаптоп или друго устройство, предоставящо DLNA, в локалната мрежа</li>
      <li>Set pictures as your desktop background</li>
      <li lang="zh_TW">將圖片設為桌面背景</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">设定图片为您的桌面背景</li>
      <li lang="vi">Đặt ảnh làm nền màn hình</li>
      <li lang="uk">Використовувати зображення як тла стільниці</li>
      <li lang="tr">Fotoğrafları masaüstü arka planınız olarak ayarlayın</li>
      <li lang="sv">Använda bilder som din skrivbordsbakgrund</li>
      <li lang="sr">Постављајте слике за позадине на вашем уређају</li>
      <li lang="sl">nastaviti sliko kot ozadje namizja</li>
      <li lang="sk">Nastavovať obrázky ako pozadie pracovnej plochy</li>
      <li lang="ru">Устанавливать фотографии в качестве фона</li>
      <li lang="ro">Stabiliți fotografii ca fundalul ecranului</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Definir fotos como seu plano de fundo</li>
      <li lang="pt">Definir como fundo do ambiente de trabalho</li>
      <li lang="pl">Ustawianie zdjęć jako tło pulpitu</li>
      <li lang="pa">ਤਸਵੀਰਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਆਪਣੇ ਡੈਸਕਟਾਪ ਬੈਕਗਰਾਊਂਡ ਵਜੋਂ ਲਗਾਓ</li>
      <li lang="oc">Definir l'imatge coma rèireplan del burèu</li>
      <li lang="nl">Foto’s instellen als uw bureaubladachtergrond</li>
      <li lang="ne">छविलाई डेक्सटप पृष्ठभूमिको रूपमा सेट गर्नुहोस्</li>
      <li lang="nb">Sette bilder som bakgrunn på skrivebordet</li>
      <li lang="ms">Tetapkan gambar sebagai latar belakang atas meja anda</li>
      <li lang="ml">നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡെസ്ക്ടോപ്പ് പശ്ചാത്തലമായി ചിത്രങ്ങൾ സജ്ജമാക്കുക</li>
      <li lang="mjw">Arjan phan desktop anung arjan bi kok noi</li>
      <li lang="lv">Iestatiet attēlus kā jūsu darbvirsmas fonu</li>
      <li lang="lt">Nustatyti nuotraukas kaip darbalaukio foną</li>
      <li lang="ko">사진을 데스크톱 배경 화면으로 설정</li>
      <li lang="kk">Суреттерді фон ретінде орнату</li>
      <li lang="ja">写真をデスクトップの背景として設定する</li>
      <li lang="id">Atur gambar sebagai latar belakang desktop Anda</li>
      <li lang="it">Impostare le foto come sfondo della scrivania</li>
      <li lang="is">Sett myndir á skjáborði sem bakgrunnsmynd</li>
      <li lang="hu">Képek beállítása háttérképként</li>
      <li lang="hr">Postaviti slike kao pozadinu vaše radne površine</li>
      <li lang="he">הגדרת תמונות כרקע שולחן העבודה שלך</li>
      <li lang="gl">Estabelecer imaxes como a súa imaxe de escritorio</li>
      <li lang="fur">Meti imagjins come fondâl dal scritori</li>
      <li lang="fr">Définir des images comme arrière-plan de bureau</li>
      <li lang="fi">Asettaa kuvia työpöydän taustakuvaksi</li>
      <li lang="fa">تنظیم عکس‌ها به‌عنوان پس‌زمینهٔ میزکارتان</li>
      <li lang="eu">Ezarri argazkiak zure mahaigainaren atzeko plano gisa</li>
      <li lang="es">Establecer imágenes como fondo de escritorio</li>
      <li lang="eo">Agordi bildojn kiel via ekranfono</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Set pictures as your desktop background</li>
      <li lang="el">Ορίστε τις εικόνες ως φόντο της επιφάνειας εργασίας σας</li>
      <li lang="de">Bilder als Ihren Bildschirmhintergrund festlegen</li>
      <li lang="da">Bruge billeder som din skrivebordsbaggrund</li>
      <li lang="cs">Nastavit si obrázek jako pozadí pracovní plochy</li>
      <li lang="ca">Establir imatges com a fons de l'escriptori</li>
      <li lang="bg">Задаване на снимката като фон</li>
      <li>Print photos</li>
      <li lang="zh_TW">列印相片</li>
      <li lang="zh_HK">列印相片</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">打印照片</li>
      <li lang="vi">In các ảnh</li>
      <li lang="uk">Друкувати фотографії</li>
      <li lang="tr">Fotoğrafları yazdırın</li>
      <li lang="tg">Поп кардани суратҳо</li>
      <li lang="sv">Skriva ut foton</li>
      <li lang="sr@latin">Štampaj fotografije</li>
      <li lang="sr">Штампај фотографије</li>
      <li lang="sl">Natisni fotografije</li>
      <li lang="sk">Tlačiť fotografie</li>
      <li lang="ru">Печатать фотографии</li>
      <li lang="ro">Tipăriți fotografii</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Imprimir fotos</li>
      <li lang="pt">Imprimir fotos</li>
      <li lang="pl">Drukowanie zdjęć</li>
      <li lang="pa">ਫ਼ੋਟੋ ਪਰਿੰਟ ਕਰੋ</li>
      <li lang="oc">Imprimir de fòtos</li>
      <li lang="nl">Foto’s afdrukken</li>
      <li lang="ne">फोटो मुद्रण</li>
      <li lang="nb">Skriv ut bilder</li>
      <li lang="ms">Cetak foto</li>
      <li lang="ml">ചിത്രങ്ങള്‍ അച്ചടിക്കുക</li>
      <li lang="mjw">Arjan ke Print</li>
      <li lang="lv">Drukāt fotogrāfijas</li>
      <li lang="lt">Spausdinti nuotraukas</li>
      <li lang="ko">사진 인쇄</li>
      <li lang="kk">Фотоларды баспаға шығару</li>
      <li lang="ja">写真を印刷する</li>
      <li lang="id">Cetak foto</li>
      <li lang="it">Stampare le foto</li>
      <li lang="is">Prentað ljósmyndir</li>
      <li lang="hu">Fényképek nyomtatása</li>
      <li lang="hr">Ispisivati fotografije</li>
      <li lang="he">הדפסת תמונות</li>
      <li lang="gu">ફોટાઓ છાપો</li>
      <li lang="gl">Imprimir fotos</li>
      <li lang="gd">Dealbhan a chlò-bhualadh</li>
      <li lang="fur">Stampe fotos</li>
      <li lang="fr">Imprimer des photos</li>
      <li lang="fi">Tulostaa valokuvia</li>
      <li lang="fa">چاپ عکس‌ها</li>
      <li lang="eu">Inprimatu argazkiak</li>
      <li lang="es">Imprimir fotos</li>
      <li lang="eo">Presi fotojn</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Print photos</li>
      <li lang="el">Εκτυπώσετε φωτογραφίες</li>
      <li lang="de">Fotos drucken</li>
      <li lang="da">Udskriv billeder</li>
      <li lang="cs">Vytisknout fotky</li>
      <li lang="ca@valencia">Imprimir fotos</li>
      <li lang="ca">Imprimir fotos</li>
      <li lang="bs">Isprintaj slike</li>
      <li lang="bg">Печат на снимки</li>
      <li lang="as">ফ'টোসমূহ প্ৰিন্ট কৰক</li>
      <li lang="ar">طباعة الصور</li>
      <li lang="an">Imprentar fotos</li>
      <li>Select favorites</li>
      <li lang="zh_TW">選取喜愛</li>
      <li lang="zh_HK">選擇喜好</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">选择最喜爱的</li>
      <li lang="vi">Chọn các ảnh ưa thích</li>
      <li lang="uk">Вибрати улюблені</li>
      <li lang="tr">Gözdeleri seçin</li>
      <li lang="tg">Интихоб кардани баргузидаҳо</li>
      <li lang="sv">Välja favoriter</li>
      <li lang="sr@latin">Izaberi omiljene</li>
      <li lang="sr">Изабери омиљене</li>
      <li lang="sl">Izberi priljubljeno</li>
      <li lang="sk">Vybrať obľúbené fotografie</li>
      <li lang="ru">Добавлять фотографии в избранные</li>
      <li lang="ro">Selectați elemente favorite</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Selecionar favoritos</li>
      <li lang="pt">Selecionar as favoritas</li>
      <li lang="pl">Wybieranie ulubionych</li>
      <li lang="pa">ਪਸੰਦੀਦਾ ਚੁਣੋ</li>
      <li lang="oc">Seleccionar de favorits</li>
      <li lang="nl">Favorieten selecteren</li>
      <li lang="ne">मनपर्ने छान्नुहोस्</li>
      <li lang="nb">Velg favoritter</li>
      <li lang="ms">Pilih kegemaran</li>
      <li lang="ml">പ്രിയപ്പെട്ടവ തിരഞ്ഞെടുക്കുക</li>
      <li lang="lv">Izvēlēties izlasi</li>
      <li lang="lt">Pasirinkite mėgiamiausias</li>
      <li lang="ko">즐겨찾기 항목 선택</li>
      <li lang="kk">Таңдамалыларды белгілеу</li>
      <li lang="ja">お気に入りを選択する</li>
      <li lang="id">Pilh favorit</li>
      <li lang="it">Selezionare le preferite</li>
      <li lang="is">Valið eftirlætismyndir</li>
      <li lang="hu">Kedvencek kiválasztása</li>
      <li lang="hr">Odabrati omiljene</li>
      <li lang="he">בחירת מועדפים</li>
      <li lang="gu">પ્રીય વસ્તુઓ પસંદ કરો</li>
      <li lang="gl">Seleccione os favoritos</li>
      <li lang="gd">Annsachdan a thaghadh</li>
      <li lang="fur">Selezione preferîts</li>
      <li lang="fr">Sélectionner des favoris</li>
      <li lang="fi">Valita suosikkeja</li>
      <li lang="fa">گزینش برگزیده‌ها</li>
      <li lang="eu">Hautatu gogokoak</li>
      <li lang="es">Seleccionar favoritos</li>
      <li lang="eo">Elekti ŝatatajn</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Select favourites</li>
      <li lang="el">Επιλέξετε τα αγαπημένα σας</li>
      <li lang="de">Favoriten auswählen</li>
      <li lang="da">Vælg favoritter</li>
      <li lang="cs">Vybírat si oblíbené fotky</li>
      <li lang="ca@valencia">Seleccionar les preferides</li>
      <li lang="ca">Seleccionar les preferides</li>
      <li lang="bs">Označi omiljeni sadržaj</li>
      <li lang="bg">Избор на любими</li>
      <li lang="as">পছন্দসমূহ বাছক</li>
      <li lang="ar">تفضيل الصور</li>
      <li lang="an">Seleccionar favoritos</li>
      <li>Easily edit your pictures in the app, or send to a full featured
          editor for more advanced changes</li>
      <li lang="zh_TW">在應用程式中以簡單的方式編輯圖片，或傳送到完整功能的編輯器來做更多的修改</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">在应用中轻松地编辑，或者发送到全功能的编辑器进行更高级的修改</li>
      <li lang="vi">Dễ dàng sửa các bức ảnh của bạn trong ứng dụng, hoặc gửi cho ứng dụng chỉnh sửa ảnh với tính năng đầy đủ khi muốn thay đổi ở mức cao hơn</li>
      <li lang="uk">Без проблем редагувати ваші зображення у програмі або надсилати їх до повноцінного редактора для складнішого редагування</li>
      <li lang="tr">Fotoğraflarınızı uygulamada kolayca düzenleyin veya daha gelişmiş değişiklikler için tam özellikli düzenleyiciye gönderin</li>
      <li lang="sv">Enkelt redigera dina bilder i programmet, eller skicka till en funktionellt komplett redigerare för mer avancerade förändringar</li>
      <li lang="sr">Олако уређујте ваше слике у програму или их пошаљите у напреднији уређивач за сложеније измене</li>
      <li lang="sl">Enostavno urejanje slik in podpora za napredne možnosti urejevalnika</li>
      <li lang="sk">Jednoducho upravovať vaše obrázky v aplikácii, alebo odosielať do plne funkčného editora pre pokročilejšie úpravy</li>
      <li lang="ru">Легко редактировать свои изображения в приложении или открывать их в полнофункциональных редакторах для расширенного изменения</li>
      <li lang="ro">Editați ușor fotografiile în aplicație, sau trimiteți-le la un editor complet pentru modificări mai avansate</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Editar facilmente suas fotos no app, ou envie-as para um editor repleto de recursos para alterações mais avançadas</li>
      <li lang="pt">Editar fotos facilmente na aplicação ou abrir um editor completo para alterações mais avançadas</li>
      <li lang="pl">Łatwe retuszowanie zdjęć w programie lub wysyłanie ich do rozbudowanego edytora w celu dokonania poważniejszych zmian</li>
      <li lang="pa">ਐਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਆਪਣੀਆਂ ਤਸਵੀਰਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਸੌਖੀ ਤਰ੍ਹਾਂ ਸੋਧੋ ਜਾਂ ਹੋਰ ਤਕਨੀਕੀ ਤਬਦੀਲੀਆਂ ਲਈ ਪੂਰੇ ਫੀਚਰ ਵਾਲੇ ਐਡੀਟਰ ਲਈ ਭੇਜੋ</li>
      <li lang="oc">Modificatz facilament vòstres imatges dins l'aplicacion, o enviatz-los a un editor mai complet per de modificacions mai avançadas</li>
      <li lang="nl">Uw foto’s eenvoudig bewerken in de toepassing, of ze doorgeven aan een uitgebreid fotobewerkingsprogramma voor geavanceerdere wijzigingen</li>
      <li lang="ne">अनुप्रयोगमा सजिलै आफ्नो तस्वीर सम्पादन गर्नुहोस्, वा थप उन्नत परिवर्तनहरूका लागि पूर्ण विशेषता सम्पादकलाई पठाउनुहोस्</li>
      <li lang="nb">Rediger dine bilder enkelt i dette programmet eller åpne i et annet redigeringsprogram for mer avanserte endringer</li>
      <li lang="ms">Sunting gambar anda dengan apl secara mudah, atau hantar ke penyunting berfitur penuh untuk dapatkan perubahan lanjutan</li>
      <li lang="ml">ആപ്പിൽ നിങ്ങളുടെ ചിത്രങ്ങൾ എളുപ്പത്തിൽ എഡിറ്റുചെയ്യുക, അല്ലെങ്കിൽ കൂടുതൽ വിപുലമായ മാറ്റങ്ങൾക്കായി ഒരു പൂർണ്ണ ഫീച്ചർ എഡിറ്ററിലേക്ക് അയയ്ക്കുക</li>
      <li lang="lv">Viegli rediģējiet savas fotogrāfijas lietotnē, vai sūtiet tās uz redaktoru ar plašākām rediģēšanas iespējām</li>
      <li lang="lt">Lengvai redaguokite savo nuotraukas programoje arba siųskite į pilno funkcionalumo redaktorių sudėtingesniems pakeitimams</li>
      <li lang="ko">앱에서 사진을 간편하게 편집하거나 좀 더 고급스런 수준의 편집을 위해 완벽한 기능을 갖춘 편집기로 내보냅니다</li>
      <li lang="kk">Суреттерді қолданбада оңай түзету, немесе кеңейтілген өзгерістерді жасау үшін мүмкіндіктері көбірек түзеткішке жіберу</li>
      <li lang="ja">写真にちょっとした編集を加える、または大掛かりな編集をするために別の高機能な画像エディターに写真を渡す</li>
      <li lang="id">Sunting gambar Anda dengan mudah di aplikasi, atau kirim ke penyunting berfitur lengkap untuk perubahan lebih lanjut</li>
      <li lang="it">Modificare facilmente nell'applicazione le proprie foto, oppure inviarle a un editor più completo per modifiche più avanzate</li>
      <li lang="is">Breyttu myndunum þinum á einfaldan hátt í forritinu, eða sendu þær inn í fullbúin myndvinnsluforrit til að vinna betur með myndirnar</li>
      <li lang="hu">Szerkessze képeit az alkalmazásban könnyedén, vagy a speciálisabb módosításokért küldje át egy teljes funkcionalitású szerkesztőnek</li>
      <li lang="hr">S lakoćom uređivati svoje slike u aplikaciji ili slanje u naprednijeg uređivača fotografija za naprednije promjene</li>
      <li lang="he">עריכה פשוטה של תמונות ביישום, או פתיחה של עורך עשיר בתכונות לשינויים מתקדמים יותר</li>
      <li lang="gl">Editar de forma doada as súas imaxes dentro da aplicación, ou enviala a un editor completo para cambios máis avanzados</li>
      <li lang="fur">Modificâ in maniere semplice lis imagjins di dentri de aplicazion, o inviâ a un editôr complet e cun plui funzions, par fâ modifichis plui complicadis</li>
      <li lang="fr">Modifier facilement les images dans l’application ou les envoyer dans un éditeur pleinement fonctionnel pour les modifications plus poussées</li>
      <li lang="fi">Tehdä pieniä muokkauksia kuviin sovelluksen sisäisesti, tai avata erillisen kuvankäsittelysovelluksen suuria muutoksia varten</li>
      <li lang="fa">ویرایش سادهٔ عکس‌هایتان در کاره، یا فرستادن به یک ویرایشگر پرویژگی برای تغییرات پیش‌رفته‌تر</li>
      <li lang="eu">Editatu zure irudiak modu errazean aplikazioan, edo bidali editore aurreratu batera aldaketa sakonagoak egiteko</li>
      <li lang="es">Edite sus fotos fácilmente en la aplicación o envíelas a un editor completo para cambios más avanzados</li>
      <li lang="eo">Facile redakti viajn bildojn ene de la aplikaĵo, aŭ sendi al plenfunkcia redaktilo por altnivelaj ŝanĝoj</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Easily edit your pictures in the app, or send to a full featured editor for more advanced changes</li>
      <li lang="el">Επεξεργαστείτε εύκολα τις φωτογραφίες σας στην εφαρμογή ή στείλτε σε έναν πλήρη επεξεργαστή για πιο προηγμένες αλλαγές</li>
      <li lang="de">Ihre Bilder einfach in der Anwendung bearbeiten, oder einen voll ausgestatteten Editor für fortgeschrittene Änderungen öffnen</li>
      <li lang="da">Nemt redigere dine billeder i programmet eller sende dem videre til et fuldt billedredigeringsprogram for at udføre mere avancerede ændringer</li>
      <li lang="cs">Provádět jednoduché úpravy obrázků přímo v aplikaci nebo je otevřít v plnohodnotném editoru pro složitějším úpravy</li>
      <li lang="ca">Editar fàcilment les fotografies en l'aplicació o obrir-les en un editor més potent per a fer canvis més avançats</li>
      <li lang="bg">Лесно редактиране на снимките в програмата или ползване на същински редактор за по-сложни промени</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>AppMenu</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>SearchProvider</kudo>
    <kudo>UserDocs</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-03-19" version="42.0">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix crash when importing photos from device</li>
          <li>Fix headerbar getting too big</li>
          <li>Translations updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="40.0" date="2021-03-25">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Port to Tracker 3</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-09-23" version="3.38.0">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Add a new magic filter, Trencin, very similar to Instagram's
              Clarendon filter</li>
          <li>Switch to private instances of the Tracker 2.x daemons</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.34.0" date="2019-09-11">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Update the application icon to be more modern and colorful</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-03-18" version="3.32.0">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Don't attempt to load items from non-UTF-8 paths</li>
          <li>Remove the application menu</li>
          <li>Start adding some unit tests</li>
          <li>Update the application icon for the GNOME 3.32 icon redesign</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-09-06" version="3.30.0">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Delete *.gnome-photos files with XML depicting an empty GEGL
              graph</li>
          <li>Launch Settings in a Flatpak-friendly way</li>
          <li>Port to the Meson build system</li>
          <li>Reduce memory fragmentation in ImageView</li>
          <li>Unbreak the "Empty Trash" button on GNOME >= 3.24</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-photos/raw/HEAD/data/screenshots/photos.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-photos/raw/HEAD/data/screenshots/crop.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-photos/raw/HEAD/data/screenshots/filter.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-photos/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">http://www.gnome.org/friends</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Photos</url>
  <url type="translate">https://wiki.gnome.org/TranslationProject</url>
  <developer_name>The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">GNOME 專案</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 项目</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="vi">Dự án GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Проєкт GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">GNOME Projesi</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr@latin">Gnomov projekat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Гном пројекат</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Проект GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Proiectul GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਪਰੋਜੈੱਕਟ</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="oc">Lo projècte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Het Gnome-project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ne">जिनोम परियोजना</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb">GNOME prosjektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ms">Projek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ml">ഗ്നോം പ്രോജക്ട്</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="mjw">GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lv">GNOME projekts</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">GNOME projektas</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">그놈 프로젝트</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="kk">GNOME жобасы</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Proyek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Il progetto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="is">GNOME verkefnið</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">מיזם GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">O Proxecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gd">Pròiseact GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fur">Il progjet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Le projet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Gnome-projekti</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fa">پروژه گنوم</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">GNOME proiektua</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">El Proyecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">La GNOME-projekto</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Το έργο GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Das GNOME-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca@valencia">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="bg">Проектът GNOME</developer_name>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <update_contact>debarshir_at_gnome.org</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-photos</translation>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-desecration">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-slavery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-worship">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-homosexuality">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-prostitution">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-adultery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-appearance">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>