<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>gnome.gnome-mahjongg</pkgname>
  <icon width="64" height="64" type="cached">org.gnome.Mahjongg.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" type="cached" width="128">org.gnome.Mahjongg.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.Mahjongg</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+ and CC-BY-SA-3.0</project_license>
  <name>GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">GNOME 上海麻將</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">GNOME 上海麻雀</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 麻将牌</name>
  <name lang="uk">Магджонґ GNOME</name>
  <name lang="tr">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="sv">GNOME Mahjong</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Gnomov mahjong</name>
  <name lang="sr">Гномов махјонг</name>
  <name lang="sl">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="sk">Madžong GNOME</name>
  <name lang="ru">Маджонг GNOME</name>
  <name lang="ro">Mahjongg GNOME</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="pt">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="pl">Madżong GNOME</name>
  <name lang="oc">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="nl">Gnome Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="nb">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="ms">Mahjongg GNOME</name>
  <name lang="lv">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="lt">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="ko">그놈 마작</name>
  <name lang="kk">GNOME Маджонг</name>
  <name lang="ja">GNOME 上海</name>
  <name lang="it">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="id">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="hu">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="hr">GNOME Mahjong</name>
  <name lang="he">מא־ג׳ונג מבית GNOME</name>
  <name lang="gl">Mahjongg de GNOME</name>
  <name lang="fur">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="fr">Mahjongg de GNOME</name>
  <name lang="fi">Gnomen Mahjong</name>
  <name lang="fa">ماهجونگ گنوم</name>
  <name lang="eu">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="es">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="eo">GNOME Maĝango</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="el">Ματζόνγκ</name>
  <name lang="dz">ཇི་ནོམ་ མཱ་ཇོང་།</name>
  <name lang="de">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="da">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="cs">Mahjongg GNOME</name>
  <name lang="ckb">گنۆم مەهجۆنگ</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="ca">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="bs">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="br">GNOME Mahjongg</name>
  <name lang="bg">Маджонг</name>
  <name lang="be">Маджонг GNOME</name>
  <summary>Match tiles and clear the board</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">匹配麻將牌並清空牌桌</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">匹配麻将牌清空版面</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Знайдіть однакові плитки і очистіть дошку</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Karoları eşleştir ve panoyu temizle</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Matcha brickor och töm brädet</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Pronađite parove pločica i očistite tablu</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Пронађите парове плочица и очистите таблу</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Poišči pare ploščic in počisti igralno ploščo.</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Spárujte kamene a vyčistite hraciu plochu</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Очистите доску от фишек, выбирая одинаковые</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Potrivește piese și curăță tabla</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Combine pedras e limpe o tabuleiro</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Junte peças iguais e limpe o tabuleiro</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Wyszukiwanie par kostek</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Fasètz correspondre de teules e voidatz lo platèu</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Vind dezelfde stenen en maak het bord leeg</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Merk like fliser og tøm brettet</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Padankan jubin dan kosongkan papan permainan</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Atrodi vienādus kauliņus un attīri galdiņu</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Raskite atitinkančius koklius ir išvalykite lentą</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">타일을 맞춰서 게임판을 비우십시오</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">Плиткаларды сәйкестендіріп, тақтаны тазалаңыз</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Abbina le tessere e ripulisci la tavola</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Mencocokkan kartu dan membersihkan papan</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Párosítsa a köveket és tisztítsa meg a táblát</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Uparite iste pločice i očistite ploču</summary>
  <summary lang="he">התאמת אריחים וריקון הלוח</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Emparelle pezas e limpe o taboleiro</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Cumbine lis tessaris e nete la taule</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Faites correspondre des tuiles et videz le plateau</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Sovita laatat ja tyhjennä pelialusta</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">خانه‌ها را جور کرده و تخته را پاک‌سازی کنید</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Parekatu lauzak eta garbitu taula</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Emparejar fichas iguales y limpiar el tablero</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Kongruu kahelojn kaj vakigu la tabulon</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Match tiles and clear the board</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Ταιριάξτε τα πλακίδια και καθαρίστε τον πίνακα</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Finden Sie übereinstimmende Kacheln und leeren Sie das Brett</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Find par af ens brikker og ryd brættet</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Najděte stejné kameny a vyčistěte tak herní desku</summary>
  <summary lang="ckb">کاشیەکان یەکخەو تەختەکە پاکەرەوە</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Emparella les fitxes i neteja el tauler</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Emparella les fitxes i neteja el tauler</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Uklopi pločice i obriši ploču</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Намерете съответстващите си плочки и изчистете дъската</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Вылучыце аднолькавыя косці і ачысціце дошку</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
   A solitaire version of the classic Eastern tile game. Tiles are stacked on
   the board at the start of the game. The goal is to remove all the tiles in
   as little time as possible. Select two matching tiles and they will disappear
   from the board, but you can only select a tile if there is an empty space to
   its left or right at the same level. Be careful: tiles that look alike
   may actually be slightly different.
  </p>
    <p>
   GNOME Mahjongg features a variety of starting layouts, some easy and some
   difficult. If you get stuck, you can ask for a hint, but this adds a large
   time penalty.
  </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Пасьянсавы варыянт класічнай усходняй гульні з касцямі. У пачатку гульні косці выкладваюцца на гульнявым полі. Задача гульні - як мага хутчэй прыбраць усе косці. Вы можаце прыбраць пару аднолькавых касцей. Косць можна выбраць, толькі калі на тым жа самым узроўні справа або злева нічога не ляжыць. Увага: падобныя косці ўсё-ткі могуць адрознівацца.</p>
    <p>Маджонг GNOME мае некалькі пачатковых выкладаў, ад простага да цяжкіх. Калі вы не ведаеце, што рабіць далей, можаце звярнуцца па падказку. Праўда, гэта дзеянне дадае істотны часавы штраф.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Версия на популярната азиатска игра за сам играч. В началото на играта всички плочки са подредени на дъската. Целта е за възможно най-малко време да махнете всички плочки. Изберете две плочки с еднакви фигури, за да ги махнете. Внимавайте — понякога плочките много си приличат, но са различни. Можете да махате само плочки, които са свободни — на същото ниво, отляво или отдясно, да няма друга плочка.</p>
    <p>Можете да избирате измежду много подредби — някои по-лесни, някои по-трудни. В краен случай може да поискате подсказка, но това води до наказание чрез завишаване на времето.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Pasijans verzija klasične istočne igre pločica. Pločice su naslagani na tabli na početku igree. Cilj je da uklonite sve pločice u što manje vremena moguće. Izaberite dvije odgovarajuće pločice i one će nestati sa table, ali možete da izaberete pločicu samo  ako postoji prazan prostor na lijevoj ili desnoj strani na istom nivou. Budite oprezni: pločice koje izgledaju podjednako može zapravo biti malo drugačija.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjongg ima niz polaznih rasporeda, neki su lakši a neki teži. Ako se zaglavite, možete da pitate za savjet, ali to dodaje veliku vremensku kaznu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Una versió d'un sol jugador del clàssic joc oriental de fitxes. Les fitxes estan apilades al tauler a l'inici del joc. L'objectiu és eliminar totes les fitxes en el menor temps possible. Seleccioneu dues fitxes que siguin iguals i desapareixeran del tauler, però només podeu seleccionar una fitxa si té un espai buit a la seva dreta o esquerra al mateix nivell. Aneu amb compte: algunes fitxes sembla que siguin iguals però en realitat no ho són.</p>
    <p>El GNOME Mahjongg inclou varietat de disposicions inicials, algunes de fàcils i d'altres de difícils. Si no podeu avançar, podeu demanar una pista, però us afegeix una sanció de temps.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca@valencia">
    <p>Una versió d'un sol jugador del clàssic joc oriental de fitxes. Les fitxes estan apilades al tauler a l'inici del joc. L'objectiu és eliminar totes les fitxes en el menor temps possible. Seleccioneu dues fitxes que siguen iguals i desapareixeran del tauler, però només podeu seleccionar una fitxa si té un espai buit a la seua dreta o esquerra al mateix nivell. Aneu amb compte: algunes fitxes pareix que siguen iguals però en realitat no ho són.</p>
    <p>El GNOME Mahjongg inclou varietat de disposicions inicials, algunes de fàcils i d'altres de difícils. Si no podeu avançar, podeu demanar una pista, però vos afig una sanció de temps.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ckb">
    <p>ماهیۆنگ لە گنۆم چەندین پابەندی جۆراوجۆری هەیە بۆئەوەی شێوەی تری پێ بدەیت. هەندێک ئاستی هەیە ئاسانە و هەندێکیشی ئاڵۆزە. هەرکاتێک گیر بوو، دەتوانی داوای یارمەتی بکەیت، بەڵام ئەوە بزانە کە کاتت زۆر بەفیڕۆ دەڕوا لە سزای ئەوە.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Solitérová verze klasické východní hry s kameny. Hrací kameny jsou na začátku hry navršeny na hrací desce. Cílem je všechny v co nejkratším čase odebrat. Když vyberete dva stejné kameny, tak z hrací desky zmizí. Vybírat můžete ale jen ty, které mají po své levé nebo pravé straně ve svojí vrstvě volné místo. A buďte všímaví: některé kameny vypadají podobně, ale jsou mezi nimi drobné rozdíly.</p>
    <p>Mahjongg GNOME obsahuje různé varianty počátečního rohložení kamenů, některé snadné, jiné obtížné. Když budete v koncích, můžete požádat o radu, ale k ní obdržíte také časovou penalizaci.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>En kabaleversion af det klassiske fjernøstlige spil med fliser. Fliserne stables på brættet ved spillets begyndelse. Målet er at fjerne alle fliserne på så kort tid som muligt. Vælg to ens felter og de vil forsvinde fra brættet. Men du kan kun vælge en flise, hvis der er tom plads på dens venstre eller højre side i samme højde. Vær forsigtig: Fliser som ser ens ud kan godt være en smule forskellige.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjongg har et udvalg af startarrangementer, hvoraf nogle er nemme og andre svære. Hvis du sidder fast, kan du bede om et tip - men dette medfører en stor straf på tid.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Eine Solospielvariante des klassischen Kachelspiels aus Asien. Die Kacheln sind zu Beginn des Spiels auf dem Brett in Stapeln ausgelegt. Ziel des Spiels ist es, in möglichst kurzer Zeit alle Kacheln zu entfernen. Sobald zwei gleiche Kacheln ausgewählt werden, verschwinden sie vom Spielfeld. Aber vorsicht, eine Kachel kann nur gewählt werden, wenn unmittelbar daneben ein freies Feld ist. Erschwerend kommt hinzu, dass einige Kacheln sich sehr ähnlich sehen.</p>
    <p>Gnome Mahjongg bietet eine Vielzahl an verschiedenen Ausgangspositionen. Einige davon sehr leicht, andere eher schwierig. Kommen Sie einmal nicht weiter, können Sie sich helfen lassen. Dafür gibt es dann allerdings eine größere Zeitstrafe.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Μια έκδοση πασιέντζας του κλασικού ανατολίτικου παιχνιδιού πλακιδίων. Τα πλακίδια στοιβάζονται στον πίνακα στην αρχή του παιχνιδιού. Ο σκοπός είναι να αφαιρεθούν όλα τα πλακίδια όσο το δυνατό πιο γρήγορα. Επιλέξτε δύο πλακίδια που ταιριάζουν και θα εξαφανιστούν από τον πίνακα, αλλά μπορείτε να επιλέξετε μόνο ένα πλακίδιο αν υπάρχει κενός χώρος στα αριστερά ή δεξιά του στο ίδιο επίπεδο. Προσοχή: τα πλακίδια που φαίνονται όμοια μπορεί στην πραγματικότητα να είναι λίγο διαφορετικά.</p>
    <p>Το GNOME Ματζόνγκ εμφανίζει μια ποικιλία αρχικών διατάξεων, κάποιες εύκολες και κάποιες δύσκολες. Αν κολλήσετε, μπορείτε να ζητήσετε μια υπόδειξη, αλλά αυτό προσθέτει μια ποινή μεγάλου χρόνου.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>A solitaire version of the classic Eastern tile game. Tiles are stacked on the board at the start of the game. The goal is to remove all the tiles in as little time as possible. Select two matching tiles and they will disappear from the board, but you can only select a tile if there is an empty space to its left or right at the same level. Be careful: tiles that look alike may actually be slightly different.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjongg features a variety of starting layouts, some easy and some difficult. If you get stuck, you can ask for a hint, but this adds a large time penalty.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p>Ermitluda versio de la klasika orienta kahela ludo. Kaheloj stakiĝas sur la tabulo je la komenco de la ludo. La celo estas forigo de ĉiuj kaheloj kiel eble plej rapide. Elektu du kongruajn kahelojn kaj ili foriĝos de la tabulo, sed vi nur povas elekti kahelon se ekzistas malplena spaco dekstren aŭ maldekstren samtempe. Atentu: kaheloj, kiuj ŝajne similas, povus iomete malsimili.</p>
    <p>GNOME Maĝango havas diversajn komencajn aranĝojn, kelkaj facilaj kaj kelkaj maldacilaj. Se vi ne scias kiel daŭrigi, vi povas demandi konsileton, sed tio aldonas grandan tempan punon.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Una versión del solitario Eastern. Las fichas se apilan en el tablero al principio del juego. El objetivo es quitar todas las fichas en el menor tiempo posible. Seleccione dos fichas iguales y desaparecerán del tablero, pero sólo puede seleccionar una ficha si tiene un espacio vacío a su izquierda o a su derecha en el mismo nivel. Tenga cuidado: hay fichas que parecen iguales pero que son ligeramente diferentes.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjongg tiene varias distribuciones iniciales, algunas fáciles y algunas difíciles. Si tiene problemas, puede pedir una pista, pero esto añade una penalización de tiempo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Ekialdeko bakarkako jokoaren bertsioa. Fitxak mahaigainean pilatzen dira jokoaren hasieran. Fitxa guztiak ahalik eta denbora laburrenean kentzea da helburua. Hautatu bat datozen bi fitxa eta mahaigainetik desagertuko dira. Baina soilik maila berean fitxaren ezkerrean edo eskuinean leku hutsa badago. Adi ibili: antzekoak diruditen fitxak desberdinak izan daitezkeelako.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjongg hasierako diseinu desberdinak ditu, batzuk errazak eta besteak zailak. Larri zaudenean, eskatu argibide bat (honek ordea zigor gisa denbora handiagotzen du).</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fa">
    <p>یک نگارش انفرادی از یک بازی کلاسیک شرقی. مهره‌ها در ابتدای بازی روی هم چیده شده‌اند. هدف این است که مهره‌ها را در کم‌ترین زمان ممکن حذف کنید. دو مهرهٔ منطبق با هم را گزیده تا از صفحه حذف شوند، ولی تنها می‌توانید مهره‌هایی را برگزینید که یک فضای خالی در سمت راست یا چپ آن در همان سطح وجود داشته باشد. مواضب باشید: مهره‌هایی که به نظر شبیه همند، ممکن است در واقع متفاوت باشند.</p>
    <p>ماهجونگ گنوم چیدمان‌های مختلفی را فراهم می‌کند، تعدادی ساده و تعدادی سخت. اگر گیر کردید، می‌توانید درخواست راهنمایی کنید، اما این کار یک جریمهٔ بزرگ زمانی خواهد داشت.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Pasianssiversio klassisesta aasialaisesta laattapelistä. Laatat pinotaan pelilaudalle pelin alkaessa. Tavoitteena on poistaa kaikki laatat mahdollisimman nopeasti. Valitse kaksi toisiaan vastaavaa laattaa, jolloin ne katoavat pelilaudalta. Voit valita laatan vain, jos laatan vasemmalla tai oikealla puolella on tilaa samalla tasolla. Ota huomioon, että toisiaan muistuttavat laatat saattavat olla kuitenkin hieman erilaisia.</p>
    <p>Gnomen Mahjong omaa lukuisia eri aloitusasetteluja, joista osa on helppoja ja toiset haastavia. Jos jäät jumiin, voit pyytää vinkkiä, mutta siitä saa aikasakon.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Une version solitaire du classique jeu de tuiles oriental. Les tuiles sont empilées sur le plateau au début de la partie. Le but est d’enlever toutes les tuiles en prenant le moins de temps possible. Lorsque deux tuiles qui se correspondent sont sélectionnées, elles disparaissent du plateau. Cependant, une tuile ne peut être sélectionnée que s’il y a un espace vide au même niveau à sa gauche ou à sa droite. Attention : des tuiles qui se ressemblent peuvent être en fait légèrement différentes.</p>
    <p>Mahjongg de GNOME comprend une variété de dispositions de départ, certaines faciles, d’autres plus difficiles. Si vous êtes bloqué, vous pouvez demander un indice mais vous recevez alors une pénalité de temps importante.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Une version dal classic zûc orientâl des tessaris. Al inizi dal zûc lis tessaris a son metudis in pile su la taule; l'obietîf al è di gjavâ dutis lis tessaris tal mancul timp pussibil. Selezion dôs tessaris che si cumbinin e chestis a sparissin de taule, ma tu puedis selezionâ une tessare dome se al è un spazi libar te sô çampe o diestre dal stes nivel. Sta atent: tessaris che a semein compagnis a podaressin jessi in realtât diferentis.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjongg al inclût une varietât di schemis iniziâi, cualchidun facil e altris dificii. Se tu restis blocât tu puedis domandâ un aiût, ma chest al zonte une penalitât al timp.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Unha versión do solitario Eastern. As fichas apílanse no taboleiro ao principio do xogo. O obxectivo é quitar todas as fichas no menor tempo posíbel. Seleccione dúas fichas iguais e desaparecerán do taboleiro, pero só pode seleccionar unha ficha se ten un espazo baleiro á súa esquerda ou a á súa dereita no mesmo nivel. Teña coidado: hai fichas que parecen iguais pero que son lixeiramente diferentes.</p>
    <p>Mahjongg de GNOME conta con varias disposicións de inicio, algunhas máis doadas e outras máis difíciles. Se se atasca pode solicitar axuda, pero isto engade unha penalización de tempo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>גרסה יחידנית של המשחק המזרחי הקלסי. האריחים מסודרים על הלוח בתחילת המשחק. מטרת המשחק היא להסיר את כל האריחים תוך כמה שפחות צעדים. ניתן לבחור בשני אריחים והם ייעלמו מהלוח, אך ניתן לבחור באריח רק אם יש מקום פנוי מימינו או משמאלו. אזהרה: אריחים דומים עשויים בפועל להיות שונים במקצת.</p>
    <p>מא־ג׳ונג מבית GNOME מציג מגוון של פריסות התחלה, חלקן פשוטות וחלקן מסובכות. אם נתקעת, ניתן לבקש רמז, אך פעולה זו תוסיף לך זמן ענישה.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Pasijans inačica klasične istočnjačke igre pločica. Pločice su smještene na ploči na početku igre. Cilj igre je ukloniti sve pločice čim prije je moguće. Odaberite dvije identične pločice i one će nestati s ploče, ali možete samo odabrati pločicu ako je prazan prostor lijevo ili desno na istoj razini. Budite oprezni: pločice koje izgledaju slično mogu biti malo drugačije.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjong obiluje različitim početnim rasporedima, neki su lakši a neki teži. Ako zapnete, možete pitati za sljedeći potez, ali to dodaje veliku kaznu u vremenu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A klasszikus keleti kőjáték digitális verziója. A kövek a táblára vannak helyezve a játék kezdetén. A cél az összes kő eltávolítása a lehető leggyorsabban. Válasszon ki két egyező követ, és azok eltűnnek a tábláról, de egy kő csak akkor választható ki, ha ugyanazon a szinten jobbra vagy balra van mellette egy üres hely. Legyen óvatos: a hasonlóan kinéző kövek valójában kissé eltérőek lehetnek.</p>
    <p>A GNOME Mahjongg számos kezdő elrendezést tartalmaz, némelyik könnyű, némelyik nehéz. Ha elakad, kérhet tippet, de ez nagy időbüntetéssel jár.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Versi soliter dari permainan kartu Timur klasik. Kartu ditumpuk pada papan di awal permainan. Sasarannya adalah untuk menyingkirkan semua kartu dalam waktu sesingkat-singkatnya. Pilihlah dua kartu yang cocok dan mereka akan menghilang dari papan, tapi Anda hanya dapat memilih suatu kartu bila ada ruang kosong di sebelah kiri atau kanan di tingkat yang sama. Berhati-hatilah: kartu yang nampaknya sama mungkin sebenarnya sedikit berbeda.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjongg memiliki tata letak awal yang bervariasi, beberapa mudah dan beberapa sulit. Bila Anda mengalami kebuntuan, Anda bisa meminta petunjuk, tapi ini menambahkan penalti waktu yang besar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Una versione del classico gioco orientale delle tessere. All'inizio del gioco le tessere sono impilate sulla tavola: l'obbiettivo è rimuovere tutte le tessere nel più breve tempo possibile. Seleziona due tessere corrispondenti e queste spariranno dalla tavola, ma puoi selezionare una tessera solo se c'è uno spazio libero a destra o a sinistra dello stesso livello. Fai attenzione: le tessere che sembrano simili potrebbero essere in realtà differenti.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjongg include una varietà di schemi iniziali, alcuni facili e altri difficili. Se rimani bloccato, puoi chiedere un aiuto, ma questo aggiunge una penalità al tempo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <p>Классикалық Шығыс мозаика ойынының солитер нұсқасы. Плиткалар ойын басталғанда тақтаға жиналады. Мақсаты – барлық қатарларды мүмкіндігінше аз уақытта жою. Екі сәйкес қатарды таңдамаңыз, олар тақтадан жоғалады, бірақ плитканы оның тек сол немесе оң жағында бірдей деңгейде бос орын болған кезде ғана таңдауға болады. Мұқият болыңыз: ұқсайтын плиткалар іс жүзінде сәл басқаша болуы мүмкін.</p>
    <p>GNOME Маджонгы ішінде көптеген бастау жаймалары бар, олардың кейбіреулері оңай, кейбіреулері қиын болады. Тұрып қалсаңыз, тұспал сұрай аласыз, бірақ ол үлкен уақыт күтуін қосады.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>고전적인 동양식 타일 게임의 혼자 하는 버전. 타일을 쌓은 상태로 게임을 시작합니다. 가능한한 적은 회수로 타일을 모두 제거하는 게 목표입니다. 맞는 타일 두 개를 선택하면 게임판에서 사라집니다. 하지만 같은 높이에 왼쪽 또는 오른쪽에 빈 공간이 있을 때만 타일을 선택할 수 있습니다. 조심하십시오: 똑같아 보이는 타일이 실제로는 약간 다를 수도 있습니다.</p>
    <p>그놈 마작에는 여러가지 퍼즐이 있습니다. 쉬운 퍼즐도 있고 어려운 퍼즐도 있습니다. 막힐 경우 힌트를 물어볼 수도 있지만, 그러면 시간이 줄어듭니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Klasikinio rytietiško koklių žaidimo soliterio versija. Žaidimo pradžioje kokliai yra sudėlioti lentoje. Tikslas yra kiek galima greičiau pašalinti visus koklius. Pasirinkus du vienodus koklius jie pradingsta iš lentos, bet galite pasirinkti koklį tik jei tame pačiame lygyje kairėje arba dešinėje yra tuščia vieta. Atsargiai: panašiai atrodantys kokliai gali iš tiesų šiek tiek skirtis.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjongg turi daug skirtingų išdėstymų, kai kurie paprasti, kiti sudėtingesni. Jei užstrigsite, galite prašyti patarimo, bet dėl to gausite didelę laiko baudą.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>Viena spēlētāja versija klasiskajai austrumu kauliņu spēlei. Spēles sākumā kauliņi ir salikti viens uz otra. Mērķis ir noņemt visus kauliņus pēc iespējas īsākā laikā. Izvēlies divus vienādus kauliņus un tie pazudīs no galdiņa, bet tos var izvēlēties tikai tad, ja pa labu vai kreisi no tā ir brīva vieta. Uzmanies — līdzīgi kauliņi var būt atšķirīgi.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjongg piedāvā dažādus sākuma izkārtojumus — daži ir viegli, bet citi ir grūti. Ja netiec uz priekšu, pajautā padomu, bet tas dod lielu laika sodu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Sebuah versi solitaire permainan jubin Timur klasik. Jubin-jubin ditindan dan disusun atas papan sebagai permulaan permainan. Matlamatnya adalah untuk membuang semua jubin dalam tempoh masa yang tersingkat. Dengan memilih dua jubin yang sepadan ia akan hilang dari atas papan, tetapi anda hanya boleh memilih satu jubin sekiranya ia tidak diapit di sebelah kiri atau kanan pada  aras yang sama. Hati-hati: a jubin nampak serupa tetapi sebenarnya sedikit berbeza.</p>
    <p>Mahjongg GNOME memfiturkan pelbagai bentangan permulaan, sesetengahnya mudah dan ada yang sukar. Jika anda tersangkut semasa bermain, anda boleh dapatkan pembayang, tetapi dengan penalti masa.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>En solitaire-versjon av det klassiske flisspillet fra østen. Flisene stables på brettet ved starten av spillet. Målet er å fjerne alle flisene på så liten tid som mulig. Velg to like fliser for å fjerne dem fra brettet, men du kan kun velge en flis hvis det er tomt på venstre eller høyre side på samme nivå. Vær nøye, fliser som ser like ut kan likevel ha små forskjeller.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjongg har en rekke forskjellige utforminger, noen enkle og noen vanskelige. Hvis du står fast kan du spørre om et hint, men dette gir deg en stor straff på tid.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Een patience-versie van het klassieke oosterse stenenspel. Stenen zijn opgestapeld op het bord aan het begin van het spel. Het doel is om alle stenen te verwijderen in zo min mogelijk tijd. Selecteer twee overeenkomende stenen en ze zullen van het bord verdwijnen, maar u kunt alleen een steen selecteren als er aan de linker- of rechterkant op hetzelfde niveau geen andere stenen zijn. Wees alert: stenen die op elkaar lijken kunnen eigenlijk lichtelijk verschillen.</p>
    <p>Gnome Mahjongg levert een variëteit aan borden, sommige makkelijk en andere moeilijk. Als u vastzit kunt u om een hint vragen, maar door dit te doen wordt er een tijdsstraf opgeteld.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>Una version solitària del classic jòc de teules oriental. Los teules son empilats sul platèu al començament de la partida. La tòca es de levar totes los teules en prenent lo mens de temps possible. Quand dos teules que se correspondon son seleccionats, desapareisson del platèu. Pasmens, un teule pòt pas èsser seleccionat que se i a un espaci void al meteis nivèl a son esquèrra o a sa dreita. Atencion : de teules que se semblan pòdon èsser en fait leugièrament diferentas.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjongg compren una varietat de disposicions de despart, certanas aisidas, d'autras mai dificilas. Se sètz blocat, podètz demandar un indici mas recevètz alara una penalitat de temps importanta.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Jednoosobowa wersja klasycznej gry dalekowschodniej. Kostki są ustawione na planszy na początku gry. Celem jest jak najszybsze usunięcie wszystkich kostek. Kostki znikają z planszy po wybraniu dwóch identycznych, ale można wybrać kostkę tylko, jeśli na tym samym poziomie nie ma innych kostek po prawej lub lewej stronie. Należy być ostrożnym: kostki, które wydają się identyczne, mogą się nieznacznie różnić.</p>
    <p>Madżong GNOME zawiera wiele plansz, niektóre łatwe, a niektóre trudne. W razie utknięcia można użyć podpowiedzi, ale dodaje to karę czasową.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Uma versão solitária do clássico jogo oriental de peças. As peças são empilhadas num tabuleiro antes de começar um jogo. O objetivo é remover todas as peças no mínimo de tempo possível. Selecione duas peças idênticas e elas desaparecerão do tabuleiro, mas só pode selecionar uma peça se tiver espaço à esquerda ou à direita desta, no mesmo patamar. Tenha atenção: as peças que parecem iguais por vezes apresentam pequenas diferenças.</p>
    <p>O GNOME Mahjongg mostra uma variedade de disposições, algumas fáceis e algumas difíceis. Se ficar bloqueado pode pedir uma dica, mas isso adicionará uma grande penalização de tempo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Uma versão do jogo de paciência do clássico jogo oriental de pedras. As pedras são empilhadas em um tabuleiro no começo do jogo. O objetivo é remover todas as pedras no menor espaço de tempo possível. Selecione duas pedras correspondentes e elas vão desaparecer do tabuleiro, mas você pode selecionar apenas uma pedra, se houver um espaço vazio à sua esquerda ou direita no mesmo nível. Tenha cuidado: pedras parecidas podem, na verdade, ser levemente diferentes.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjongg possui uma variedade de layouts de início, alguns fáceis e alguns difíceis. Se você ficar sem saída, você pode pedir uma dica, mas isso adicionar uma grande penalidade de tempo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>O versiune solitară a clasicului joc estic cu piese. Piesele sunt stivuite pe tablă la începutul jocului. Scopul este de a elimina toate piesele în cel mai scurt timp posibil. Selectați două piese care se potrivesc și ele vor dispărea de pe tablă, dar puteți selecta o piesă numai dacă există un spațiu liber la stânga sau la dreapta acesteia pe același nivel. Fiți atent: piesele care arată la fel ar putea fi de fapt puțin diferite.</p>
    <p>Mahjongg GNOME vine cu o varietate de aranjamente de început, unele simple iar altele complicate. Dacă v-ați blocat, puteți cere un indiciu, dar asta va adăuga o mare penalizare de timp.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Солитер классической азиатской игры. В начале игры фишки расположены поверх друг друга на игровом столе. Цель игры — убрать все фишки, затратив на это как можно меньше времени. Чтобы убрать фишки, найдите и выделите две одинаковые фишки, и они исчезнут с игрового стола. Можно выбирать только те фишки, которые расположены на одном и том же уровне и у которых свободна левая или правая грань. Будьте внимательны: некоторые фишки немного похожи друг на друга, но на самом деле являются разными.</p>
    <p>В маджонге GNOME используются различные раскладки фишек, некоторые раскладки проще, некоторые сложнее. Если вы затрудняетесь сделать ход, вы можете воспользоваться подсказкой, но в этом случае будет начислено штрафное время.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Solitér verzia klasickej hry s kameňmi Eastern. Na začiatku hry sú kamene poukladané na hracej ploche. Cieľom je odstrániť všetky kamene v čo najkratšom čase. Výberom dvoch rovnakých kameňov ich odstránite z hracej plochy, ale vybrať sa dajú len kamene, ktoré nie sú obklopené zľava a ani sprava inými kameňmi na rovnakej úrovni. Buďte opatrní, aj kamene, ktoré vyzerajú podobne sa môžu v skutočnosti trocha líšiť.</p>
    <p>Hra Madžong GNOME ponúka viaceré počiatočné rozloženia, ľahké a aj náročné. Ak si neviete poradiť, môžete požiadať o radu, ale za časovú penalizáciu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Igra Mahjongg je znana vzhodnjaška igra. Ploščice so na začetku igre postavljene na plošči. Cilj igre je čim hitreje poiskati in počistiti pare. Z izborom dveh enakih ploščic se ti izbrišeta, izbrati pa jih je mogoče le, če sta obe na isti globinski ravni in na levi ali na desni nista v stiku z drugo ploščico. Opozorilo: nekatere ploščice so si sila podobne ...</p>
    <p>Igra GNOME Mahjongg omogoča izbor različnih postavitev ploščic. Nekatere postavitve so enostavne, druge zelo zahtevne. Igra omogoča prikaz namigov, ki pa se kaznujejo s časovnim pribitkom.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Усамљеничко издање класичне Источњачке игре са плочицама. Плочице су нагомилане на табли на почетку игре. Ваш задатак је да уклоните све плочице у што краћем времену. Изаберите две подударне плочице и оне ће нестати са табле, али можете изабрати плочицу само ако је простор на истом нивоу са њене леве или десне стране слободан. Будите пажљиви: плочице које сличе једна другој могу заправо бити незнатно различите.</p>
    <p>Гномов Махјонг се одликује великим избором почетних распореда, неки су лаки а неки тешки. Ако се којим случајем заглавите, можете потражити савет, али то вас кажњава додавањем времена.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Usamljeničko izdanje klasične Istočnjačke igre sa pločicama. Pločice su nagomilane na tabli na početku igre. Vaš zadatak je da uklonite sve pločice u što kraćem vremenu. Izaberite dve podudarne pločice i one će nestati sa table, ali možete izabrati pločicu samo ako je prostor na istom nivou sa njene leve ili desne strane slobodan. Budite pažljivi: pločice koje sliče jedna drugoj mogu zapravo biti neznatno različite.</p>
    <p>Gnomov Mahjong se odlikuje velikim izborom početnih rasporeda, neki su laki a neki teški. Ako se kojim slučajem zaglavite, možete potražiti savet, ali to vas kažnjava dodavanjem vremena.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>En patiensversion av det klassiska österländska brickspelet. Brickor är staplade på brädet i början av spelet. Målet är att ta bort alla brickor på så lite tid som möjligt. Välj två matchande brickor så försvinner de från brädet, men du kan endast välja en bricka om det finns ett tomrum till vänster eller höger om brickan på samma nivå. Var uppmärksam: brickor som liknar varandra kan ändå skilja sig åt något.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjong har ett antal startlayouter, några enkla och några svåra. Om du fastnar kan du be om ett tips, men detta ger en stort tidstillägg.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Klasik Doğu karo oyununun solitaire sürümü. Oyunun başında karolar tahta üzerinde istiflenir. Hedef mümkün olan en kısa sürede tüm karoları kaldırmaktır. İki eşleşen karo seçin ve onlar panodan silinsin, fakat eğer aynı seviyede solunda veya sağında boş alan varsa yalnızca bir karo seçebilirsiniz. Dikkatli olun: birbirine benzeyen karolar azıcık farklı olabilir.</p>
    <p>GNOME Mahjongg, çeşitli başlangıç düzenlerine sahiptir, bazıları kolay ve bazıları zordur. Eğer sıkışırsanız bir ipucu isteyebilirsiniz, ancak bu büyük bir zaman cezası ekler.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Солітер версія класичної азійської гри. На початку гри плитки розташовано поверх одна одної на гральному столі. Мета гри — прибрати усі плитки, витративши на це як найменше часу. Щоб прибрати плитки, знайдіть і вберіть дві однакові плитки, й вони зникнуть з ігрового стола. Можна вибирати лише ті плитки, які розташовано на одному й тому ж рівні й у яких вільна ліва або права сторона. Будьте уважні: деякі плитки трохи схожі одна на одну, але насправді є різними.</p>
    <p>У маджонґу GNOME використовуються різні початкові розташування плиток, деякі розташування простіші, деякі складніші. Якщо ви не можете вирішити який хід зробити, можете скористатися підказкою, але у цьому випадку буде нараховано штрафний час.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>一款经典的中国麻将牌游戏。游戏开始时麻将牌摞在牌桌上。游戏的目标是以最快的速度移除所有的牌。选择花色相同的两张牌，它们就会从牌桌上消失，但只有在这张牌左侧或右侧是空的才能选中它。留意有些花色很像但并不一样。</p>
    <p>GNOME 麻将牌有好多种开局，有些容易，有些困难。如果困住了，您可以寻求提示，但会受到时间上的严重惩罚。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_HK">
    <p>傳統東方麻雀遊戲的啤牌版本。遊戲開始時麻雀牌都堆疊在棋盤上。目標是儘可能在最短時間內移除所有的麻雀牌。選擇兩個相同的麻雀牌，它們就會從棋盤上消失，但你只能選擇在同一層中左右有空位的麻雀牌。注意：看起來很像的麻雀牌可能實際上還是會有一點差別。</p>
    <p>GNOME 上海麻雀有多種起始的配置，有些簡單有些困難。如果你遇到難題，可以要求提示，但這樣會加上大量的時間。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>傳統東方麻將遊戲的紙牌版本。遊戲開始時麻將牌都堆疊在棋盤上。目標是儘可能在最短時間內移除所有的麻將牌。選擇兩個相同的麻將牌，它們就會從棋盤上消失，但您只能選擇在同一層中左右有空位的麻將牌。注意：看起來很像的麻將牌可能實際上還是會有一點差別。</p>
    <p>GNOME 上海麻將有多種起始的配置，有些簡單有些困難。如果您遇到難題，可以要求提示，但這樣會加上大量的時間。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot height="524" width="972" type="default">
      <image>https://people.gnome.org/~mcatanzaro/gnome-mahjongg.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <!-- should be kept in versionning inverted order -->
    <release urgency="medium" version="3.38.3" type="stable" date="2020-11-01" />
    <!-- release version="3.35.91" date="2020-02-15" type="development" urgency="low"/ -->
  </releases>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.Mahjongg.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Mahjongg</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-mahjongg/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <url type="help">https://help.gnome.org/users/gnome-mahjongg/stable/</url>
  <update_contact>mcatanzaro_at_gnome.org</update_contact>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <developer_name>The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">GNOME 專案</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 项目</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Проєкт GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">GNOME Projesi</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Гном пројекат</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Proiectul GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Het Gnome-project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ms">Projek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lv">GNOME projekts</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">GNOME projektas</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">그놈 프로젝트</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="kk">GNOME жобасы</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Il progetto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Proyek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">מיזם GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">O Proxecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fur">Il progjet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Le projet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Gnome-projekti</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fa">پروژهٔ گنوم</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">GNOME proiektua</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">El Proyecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">La GNOME-projekto</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Το έργο GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Das GNOME-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>UserDocs</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-mahjongg</translation>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>