<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>gnome.tali</pkgname>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">org.gnome.Tali.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">org.gnome.Tali.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.Tali</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Tali</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">骰子遊戲</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">骰子遊戲</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">掷骰子</name>
  <name lang="xh">i-Tali</name>
  <name lang="wa">Tali</name>
  <name lang="vi">Tali</name>
  <name lang="uk">Кістяний покер</name>
  <name lang="ug">Tali</name>
  <name lang="tr">Tali</name>
  <name lang="th">Tali</name>
  <name lang="te">తాలి</name>
  <name lang="ta">தலி</name>
  <name lang="sv">Tali</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Jamb</name>
  <name lang="sr">Јамб</name>
  <name lang="sq">Tali</name>
  <name lang="sl">Tali</name>
  <name lang="sk">Tali</name>
  <name lang="si">දාදුකැට</name>
  <name lang="ru">Тали</name>
  <name lang="ro">Tali</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Tali</name>
  <name lang="pt">Tali</name>
  <name lang="pl">Kości</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਟੇਲੀ</name>
  <name lang="or">ଟାଲି</name>
  <name lang="oc">Tali</name>
  <name lang="nn">Tali</name>
  <name lang="nl">Tali</name>
  <name lang="ne">टाली</name>
  <name lang="nb">Tali</name>
  <name lang="ms">Tali</name>
  <name lang="mr">टाली</name>
  <name lang="mn">Тали</name>
  <name lang="ml">ടാലി</name>
  <name lang="mk">Tali</name>
  <name lang="mai">ताली</name>
  <name lang="lv">Tali</name>
  <name lang="lt">Tali</name>
  <name lang="ko">탈리</name>
  <name lang="kn">ಟಾಲಿ</name>
  <name lang="km">Tali</name>
  <name lang="kk">Тали</name>
  <name lang="ja">Tali</name>
  <name lang="it">Tali</name>
  <name lang="is">Tali</name>
  <name lang="id">Tali</name>
  <name lang="hu">Tali</name>
  <name lang="hr">Jamb</name>
  <name lang="hi">ताली</name>
  <name lang="he">טאלי</name>
  <name lang="gu">તાલી</name>
  <name lang="gl">Tali</name>
  <name lang="ga">Tali</name>
  <name lang="fur">Tali</name>
  <name lang="fr">Tali</name>
  <name lang="fi">Tali</name>
  <name lang="fa">تالی</name>
  <name lang="eu">Tali</name>
  <name lang="et">Tali</name>
  <name lang="es">Tali</name>
  <name lang="eo">Talio</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Tali</name>
  <name lang="en_CA">Tali</name>
  <name lang="el">Τάλι</name>
  <name lang="dz">ཊ་ལི།</name>
  <name lang="de">Tali</name>
  <name lang="da">Yatzy</name>
  <name lang="cy">Tali</name>
  <name lang="cs">Tali</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">Tali</name>
  <name lang="ca">Tali</name>
  <name lang="bs">Tali</name>
  <name lang="br">Tali</name>
  <name lang="bn_IN">টালী</name>
  <name lang="bn">টালী</name>
  <name lang="bg">Генерал</name>
  <name lang="be">Tali</name>
  <name lang="az">Tali</name>
  <name lang="ast">Tali</name>
  <name lang="as">Tali</name>
  <name lang="ar">تالي</name>
  <name lang="af">Tali</name>
  <summary>Roll dice and score points</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">擲骰子與積分</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">掷骰子得分</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Киньте кубики і заробіть бали</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Zar atın ve puan kazanın</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Rulla tärningar och få poäng</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Bacite kockice i zaradite poene</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Баците коцкице и зарадите поене</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Vrzi kocke in zbiraj točke</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Hádžte kockami a zbierajte body</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Бросайте кости и набирайте очки</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Aruncă zarurile și câștigă puncte</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Lançar dados e marcar pontos</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Atire os dados e ganhe pontos</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Rzucanie kośćmi, aby zdobywać punkty</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Getatz los dats e recoltatz de punts</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Rol dobbelstenen en scoor punten</summary>
  <summary lang="ne">पासा हान्नुहोस् र प्राप्ताङ्क अङ्क</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Trill terningene og få poeng</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Lempar dadu dan skor mata</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Izmet kauliņu un iegūsti punktus</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Ridenkite kauliuką ir rinkite taškus</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">주사위를 굴려 점수를 얻으세요</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">Ойын тасын домалату және ұпай жинау</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Lancia i dadi e fai punti</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Lempar dadu dan dapatkan nilai</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Dobjon a kockával és szerezzen pontokat</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Bacajte kocke i sakupljajte bodove</summary>
  <summary lang="he">מטילים קוביות וזוכים בנקודות</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Tirar o dado e acumular puntos</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Tire un dât e fâs ponts</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Lancez les dés et récoltez des points</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Heitä noppaa ja ansaitse pisteitä</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">تاس بندازید و امتیاز بگیرید</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Tiratu dadoak eta lortu puntuak</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Tirar el dado y acumular puntos</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Roll dice and score points</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Ρίξτε τα ζάρια και κερδίστε πόντους</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Rollen Sie die Würfel und erzielen Sie Punkte</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Kast terninger og scor point</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Vrhněte kostky a získejte za to body</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Tireu els daus i aconseguiu punts</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Tireu els daus i aconseguiu punts</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Zavrti kocku i ostvari poene</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Хвърлете заровете и отбелязвайте точки</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Кідай косці і набірай ачкі</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      A variation on poker with dice and less money, this game is a family classic.
      Throw the dice three times in a row, holding back the ones you like, in order
      to make the best possible hand. You can also play a lesser-known variant with
      colored dice.
    </p>
    <p>
      Play between one and five opponents at three difficulty levels.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="as">
    <p>ডাইচ আৰু কম পইচাৰ সৈতে প'কাৰ খেলৰ এটা ভিন্ন ৰূপ, এই খেল জনপ্ৰিয়। ডাইচক তিনিবাৰ পেলাওক, আপোনাৰ পছন্দৰবোৰ ধৰি থওক, যাতে সম্ভবত উত্তম হাত নিৰ্মাণ কৰিব পাৰি। আপুনি এটা ৰঙীন ডাইচৰ সৈতে এটা কম-জ্ঞাত অপৰও খেলিব পাৰিব।</p>
    <p>তিনিটা সমস্যা স্তৰত এজনৰ পৰা পাঁচজন লৈকে প্ৰতিদন্দীৰ সৈতে খেলক।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Варыяцыя покера з касцямі і меншай колькасцю грошай, класічная сямейная гульня. Кідайце косці тры разы запар, пакідаючы тыя, што вам падабаюцца, з мэтай набраць найлепшы збор. Таксама паспрабуйце менш распаўсюджаны варыянт з каляровымі касцямі.</p>
    <p>Гуляйце з адным ці пяццю праціўнікамі на трох узроўнях цяжкасці.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Игра за цялото семейство — играе се без пари, а прилича на покер. Хвърлете заровете последователно, до три пъти, като задържате или не колкото решите от тях. Целта е да направите най-добрата комбинация. Може да играете и вариант с цветни зарове.</p>
    <p>Игра с един до пет опоненти от три различни трудности.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Tip pokera sa kockicama i manje novca, ova igra je klasićna porodična. Bacate kockice tri puta zaredom, zardžavajući onu koja vam odgovara, u cilju da napravite najbolji mogući potez. Također možete igrati i manje poznatu varijantu sa obojenim kockicama.</p>
    <p>Igrajte sa jednim ili pet protivnika sa tri težine.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Una variant del pòquer amb daus i menys diners, és un joc clàssic de família. Llenceu el dau tres vegades seguides, conservant els que vulgueu, per tal de fer la millor mà possible. També es pot jugar una variant menys coneguda amb daus de colors.</p>
    <p>Jugueu entre un i cinc oponents amb tres nivells de dificultat.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca@valencia">
    <p>Una variant del pòquer amb daus i menys diners, és un joc clàssic de família. Llenceu el dau tres vegades seguides, conservant els que vulgueu, per tal de fer la millor mà possible. També es pot jugar una variant menys coneguda amb daus de colors.</p>
    <p>Jugueu entre un i cinc oponents amb tres nivells de dificultat.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Variace na poker, akorát s kostkami a bez peněz v podobě klasické rodinné hry. Házíte kostkami třikrát po sobě, libovolné kostky můžete vrátit mezi vrhané a snažíte se získat co nejlepší „karty“. Můžete hrát také méně známou variantu s barevnými kostkami.</p>
    <p>Hrajte s jedním až pěti protivníky ve třech úrovních obtížnosti.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>En variant af poker med terninger og færre penge. Dette spil er en familieklassiker. Kast terningerne tre gange i træk, idet du holder dem tilbage du vil beholde, for at få den bedst mulige hånd. Du kan også spille en mindre kendt variant med farvede terninger.</p>
    <p>Spil med fra en til fem modstandere på tre sværhedsgrader.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Eine Variante des Poker mit Würfeln und weniger Geld. Würfeln Sie drei Mal hintereinander und behalten Sie die Würfel, die Ihnen zusagen, um die besten Zahlen zu behalten. Sie können ebenfalls eine weniger bekannte Variante mit farbigen Würfeln spielen.</p>
    <p>Spielen Sie gegen bis zu fünf Gegner auf drei unterschiedlichen Schwierigkeitsstufen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Μια παραλλαγή του πόκερ με ζάρια και λιγότερα χρήματα, αυτό το παιχνίδι είναι κλασικό οικογενειακό. Ρίξτε τη ζαριά τρεις φορές στη σειρά, κρατώντας αυτές που θέλετε, για να κάνετε τις καλύτερες δυνατές. Μπορείτε επίσης να παίξετε μια λιγότερο γνωστή παραλλαγή με χρωματιστά ζάρια.</p>
    <p>Παίξτε μεταξύ ενός και πέντε αντιπάλων σε τρία επίπεδα δυσκολίας.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>A variation on poker with dice and less money, this game is a family classic. Throw the dice three times in a row, holding back the ones you like, in order to make the best possible hand. You can also play a lesser-known variant with coloured dice.</p>
    <p>Play between one and five opponents at three difficulty levels.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Una variante del póker con dados y menos dinero, este juego es un clásico familia. Lance los dados tres veces y conserve los que quiere para conseguir la mejor mano posible. También puede jugar una variante menos conocida, con dados de colores.</p>
    <p>Juegue contra 1-5 oponentes y en tres niveles de dificultad.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Pokerraren aldaera bat, dadoekin eta diru gutxiagorekin. Jaurti dadoa hiru aldiz aldiko, nahi dituzunak gorde esku hobeagoa edukitzeko. Hain ezaguna ez den aldaera batera ere joka dezakezu: koloreztatutako dadoekin.</p>
    <p>Jokatu aurkari bat edo bosten aurka zailtasuneko hiru mailatan.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fa">
    <p>گونه‌ای از پوکر با تاس و با پول کمتر، این بازی، یک بازی کلاسیک خانوادگی است. یک تاس را سه بار پشت سر هم بیاندازید، آنهایی که دوست دارید را نگه دارید، تا اینکه بهترین دست ممکن را داشته باشید. شما همچنین می‌توانید یک گونه کمتر شناخته شده، با تاس رنگی را بازی کنید.</p>
    <p>بین یک تا پنج حریف و در سه سطح مختلف بازی کنید.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Muunnelma pokerista nopilla ja vähemmällä rahalla. Heitä noppaa kolme kertaa putkeen, pidä haluamasi nopat, yritä tehdä paras mahdollinen käsi. Voit pelata myös vähemmän tunnettua muunnelmaa väritetyillä nopilla.</p>
    <p>Pelaa yhdestä viiteen vastustajaa vastaan kolmella eri vaikeustasolla.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Un genre de poker avec des dés et moins d’argent, ce jeu est un classique familial. Lancez les dés trois fois d’affilée, en conservant ceux qui vous plaisent, pour constituer la meilleure main possible. Vous pouvez aussi jouer à une variante moins connue avec des dés colorés.</p>
    <p>Vous pouvez jouer contre un à cinq adversaires, avec trois niveaux de difficulté.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Une variant dal poker cun dâts e mancul bêçs, un classic zûc par fameis. Tire il dât par trê voltis e ten chei che ti plasin, in mût di vê la man miôr. Tu puedis ancje zuiâ a une variant mancul cognossude cun dâts colorâts.</p>
    <p>Zuie cuintri un o cinc aversaris su trê diviers nivei di dificoltât.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Unha variación no poker con dado e menos diñeiro, este xogo é un clásico familiar. Lance o dado tres veces, mantendo os que queira para facer a mellor man posíbel. Tamén pode xogar unha variante menos coñecida con un dado de cores.</p>
    <p>Xogar entre un ou máis opoñentes en tres niveis de dificultade.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>עיבוד מחודש על פוקר עם קוביות ועם פחות כסף, המשחק הזה הוא קלסיקה משפחתית. עליך להטיל את הקוביות שלוש פעמים ברצף ולשמור את ההטלות המועדפות עליך כדי לייצור את היד הטובה ביותר. ניתן לשחק בגרסה הפחות מוכרת עם קוביות בצבעים.</p>
    <p>אפשר לשחק משחקן בודד ועד חמישה בשלוש דרגות קושי.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Varijanta pokera s kockama i manje novaca, ova igra je obiteljski klasik. Bacajte kocku tri puta za redom, zadržavajući kocku koja vam najviše odgovara kako bi postigli najbolji mogući rezultat. Možete isto tako igrati i manje poznatu varijantu s obojenim kockama.</p>
    <p>Igrajte protiv dva do pet protivnika na tri razine težine.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A póker kockákkal és kevesebb pénzzel játszható változata, igazi családi klasszikus. Dobjon kockával egymás után háromszor, és a legjobb leosztás eléréséhez tartsa vissza, amelyiket kedveli. Játszhat egy kevésbé ismert változatot is színes kockákkal.</p>
    <p>Játsszon egy és öt közti számú ellenféllel, három nehézségi szinten.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Suatu variasi dari poker dengan dadu dan lebih sedikit uang, permainan ini adalah klasik untuk keluarga. Lempar dadu tiga kali berturut-turut, pertahankan yang Anda sukai, untuk membuat pegangan yang paling baik. Anda juga dapat memainkan varian yang kurang dikenal dengan dadu berwarna.</p>
    <p>Bermainlah melawan satu sampai lima lawan pada tiga tingkat kesulitan.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Una variante del poker con dadi e meno soldi, un classico gioco per famiglie. Lancia i dadi per tre volte e tieni quelli che ti piacciono in modo da avere la mano migliore. Puoi anche giocare a una variante meno nota con dadi colorati.</p>
    <p>Gioca contro uno o cinque avversari su tre diversi livelli di difficoltà.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>포커의 변종. 주사위를 사용하고 포커보다 적은 돈을 사용합니다. 이 게임은 아주 전통적인 게임입니다. 주사위를 세 번 연속으로 던져서 그 중에 마음에 드는 패를 선택합니다. 색깔 있는 주사위로 덜 알려진 변형 게임을 플레이할 수도 있습니다.</p>
    <p>세 가지 종류의 난이도로 하나에서 다섯을 상대로 플레이합니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Pokerio variantas su kauliukais ir mažiau pinigų, tai yra klasikinis šeimos žaidimas. Meskite kauliuką tris kartus iš eilės, pasilikdamas mėgiamus, siekiant pasidaryti geriausią įmanomą ranką. Taip pat galite žaisti mažiau žinomą spalvotų kauliukų žaidimą.</p>
    <p>Žaiskite su nuo vieno iki penkių priešininkų trim skirtingais lygiais.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>Pokera variants ar kauliņiem un mazāk naudas, šī ir klasiska ģimenes spēle. Met kauliņu trīs reizes pēc kārtas, pieturot tos, kurus vēlies, lai iegūtu labāko iespējamo kombināciju. Vari spēlēt arī mazāk pazīstamo variantu ar krāsainiem kauliņiem.</p>
    <p>Spēlē ar no viena līdz pieciem pretiniekiem tīs grūtības līmeņos.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Sebuah variasi poker yang diganti dengan dadu dan tiada duit sebenar terlibat, permainan ini adalah klasik keluarga. Lempar dadu sebanyak tiga kali, tahan yang anda mahu, untuk mendapatkan padanan yang terbaik. Anda juga boleh bermain varian kurang-dikenali dengan dadu berwarna.</p>
    <p>Main dengan seorang atau lima orang pihak lawan pada tiga aras kesukaran.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>En variasjon av poker med terninger og mindre penger. Dette spillet er en familieklassiker. Kast terningene tre ganger på rad, og ta vare på de du ønsker å beholde for å få best mulig resultat. Du kan også spille en mindre kjent variant med farger på terningene.</p>
    <p>Spill mot en til fem motstandere på tre vanskelighetsnivåer.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ne">
    <p>पोकर र कम पैसा सङ्ग पोकर एक भिन्नता, यो खेल एक पारिवारिक क्लासिक हो। पाईलोमा तीन पटक फ्याँक्नुहोस्, तपाईलाई मनपर्ने सम्भव बनाउनका लागि तपाईहरूलाई मनपर्छ। तपाईं रङ्गीन पासाको साथ कम ज्ञात संस्करण पनि खेल्न सक्नुहुन्छ।.</p>
    <p>तीन कठिनाइ स्तरहरूमा एक र पाँच विरोधीहरूको बीचमा खेल्नुहोस्।.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Dit spel is een familieklassieker: een variatie op poker met dobbelstenen en minder geld. Gooi de dobbelstenen drie keer achter elkaar, waarna u de dobbelstenen pakt die u goed vindt, om de best mogelijke hand te krijgen. U kunt ook een minder bekende variant spelen met gekleurde dobbelstenen.</p>
    <p>Speel tegen een tot vijf tegenstanders op drie moeilijkheidsniveaus.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>Un genre de poker amb de dats e mens d'argent, aqueste jòc es un classic familial. Getatz los dats tres còps de suita, en conservant los que vos agradan, per constituir la melhora man possibla. Podètz tanben jogar a una varianta mens coneguda amb des dats colorats.</p>
    <p>Podètz jogar contra un a cinc adversaris, amb tres nivèls de dificultat.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Klasyczna gra rodzinna, rodzaj pokera z kośćmi i mniejszymi pieniędzmi. Należy rzucić kośćmi trzy razy z rzędu, zatrzymując wybrane rzuty, aby mieć jak najlepsze rozdanie. Można także zagrać w mniej znaną odmianę z kolorowymi kośćmi.</p>
    <p>Można grać z od jednego do pięciu przeciwników na trzech poziomach trudności.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Sendo uma variante do poker com dados e menos dinheiro, este jogo é um clássico familiar. Lance os dados três vezes seguidas, retendo aqueles que lhe agradam, de forma a conseguir constituir a melhor mão possível. Pode também jogar uma variante menos conhecida com dados coloridos.</p>
    <p>Jogue com entre um a cinco adversários com três níveis de dificuldade.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Uma variação de pôquer com dados e menos dinheiro, este jogo é um clássico da família. Jogue os dados três vezes em uma rodada, guardando o que você quiser, de forma a fazer a melhor mão possível. Você também pode jogar uma variante menos conhecida com dados coloridos.</p>
    <p>Jogue com entre um e cinco oponentes em três níveis de dificuldade.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>O versiune de poker cu zaruri și bani puțini, acest joc este clasic pentru familii. Aruncați zarurile de trei ori la rând, păstrând rezultatele care vă plac, pentru a avea cel mai bun rezultat. Puteți juca, de asemenea, o variantă mai puțin cunoscută cu zaruri colorate.</p>
    <p>Joacă cu între unul și cinci adversari la trei nivele de dificultate.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Вариация игры в покер с костями. Выкидываете кости три раз подряд, откладывая после броска выгодные цифры. Вы также можете сыграть в менее известный вариант с цветными костями.</p>
    <p>Играйте с оппонентами (от одного до пяти) на трёх уровнях сложности.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Druh pokru, ktorý sa hrá s kockami a bez peňazí. Ide o klasickú rodinnú hru. Hoďte kockou trikrát za sebou a vyberte si pokus s najlepšou hodnotou na ruke. Tiež si môžete zahrať menej známu variantu s farebnou kockou.</p>
    <p>Hrajte proti jednému alebo až piatim protivníkom s troma úrovňami náročnosti.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Igra Tali je različica pokra, ki se igra s kockami. Kocke se meče trikrat zapored, pri tem pa igralec ohrani tiste vrednosti, ki jih želi, ponovno meče pa tiste, ki ne omogočajo najboljšega rezultata. Igro je mogoče igrati tudi z barvnimi kockami.</p>
    <p>Igro je mogoče igrati z do pet nasprotniki na treh različnih ravneh težavnosti.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Варијација покера са коцкицама и мање новца, ова игра је класична породична. Баците коцкице три пута за редом, задржавајући оне које вам највише одговарају, да бисте начинили најбоље могуће бацање. Можете такође да играте мање познату варијанту са обојеним коцкицама</p>
    <p>Играјте између једног и пет противника на три нивоа тежине.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Varijacija pokera sa kockicama i manje novca, ova igra je klasična porodična. Bacite kockice tri puta za redom, zadržavajući one koje vam najviše odgovaraju, da biste načinili najbolje moguće bacanje. Možete takođe da igrate manje poznatu varijantu sa obojenim kockicama</p>
    <p>Igrajte između jednog i pet protivnika na tri nivoa težine.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>En variant av poker med tärning och mindre pengar, det här spelet är en familjeklassiker. Kasta tärningarna tre gånger, behåll de du vill ha kvar efter varje gång och skapa bästa möjliga hand. Du kan också spela en mindre känd variant med färgade tärningar.</p>
    <p>Spela mot en till fem motståndare på tre svårighetsnivåer.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Zar ve daha az parayla bir poker çeşidi, bu oyun bir aile klasiğidir. Zarı üç kez üst üste atın, mümkün olan en iyi eli yapmak için istediklerinizi tutun. Renkli zarlı daha az bilinen bir çeşidini de oynayabilirsiniz.</p>
    <p>Birle beş arasında rakiple üç zorluk düzeyinde oynayın.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Варіант покеру з костями та з грошима, ця гра — класично для сім'ї. Кидайте кості три рази в ряд, забравши найкращі, щоб набрати найкращу руку. Можете грати менш відомий варіант з кольоровими костями.</p>
    <p>Грайте проти від одного до п'яти суперників, у три різні рівні складності.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>一种用骰子和零钱玩的扑克游戏，家中常备。掷一行骰子三次，留下自己想要的点，使自己的花色尽量好。还可以玩一种不太常见的彩色骰子。</p>
    <p>和一到五个对手玩，有三种难度级别。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_HK">
    <p>類似撲克啤牌遊戲，但改用骰子，而且不需要用錢，這個遊戲是家庭傳統遊戲。丟骰子三次，保留一個你想要的，以便將有利的留在自己手中。你也可以玩較少人知道有顏色的骰子的版本。</p>
    <p>與一到五位對手玩三種難度的遊戲。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>類似撲克紙牌遊戲，但改用骰子，而且不需要用錢，這個遊戲是家庭傳統遊戲。丟骰子三次，保留一個您想要的，以便將有利的留在自己手中。您也可以玩較少人知道有顏色的骰子的版本。</p>
    <p>與一到五位對手玩三種難度的遊戲。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot width="972" height="561" type="default">
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/tali/-/raw/master/data/screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="40.7" type="stable" date="2022-04-23">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release, with the following improvements since 40.6:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2022-03-19" type="stable" version="40.6">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release, with the following improvements since 40.5:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Update screenshot hosting</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release type="stable" version="40.5" date="2022-01-30">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release, with the following improvements since 40.3:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix build with meson-0.61</li>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release type="stable" version="40.4" date="2021-10-30">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release, with the following improvements since 40.3:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release type="stable" version="40.3" date="2021-09-18">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release, with the following improvements since 40.2:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="40.2" date="2021-08-15" type="stable">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release, with the following improvements since 40.1:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="40.1" date="2021-05-14" type="stable">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release, with the following improvements since 40.0:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release type="stable" date="2021-03-20" version="40.0">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release, with the following notable improvements
          since 3.38:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.38.3" date="2021-01-09" type="stable">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release, with the following improvements since 3.38.2:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release type="stable" version="3.38.2" date="2020-11-21">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release, with the following improvements since 3.38.0:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-09-14" type="stable" version="3.38.0">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release, with the following notable improvements
          since 3.36:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Scores support changed to use libgnome-games-support</li>
          <li>New application icon</li>
          <li>Help updates</li>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release type="development" date="2020-09-06" version="3.37.92">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.37 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-08-22" type="development" version="3.37.91">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.37 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.37.90" date="2020-08-08" type="development">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.37 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.37.3" type="development" date="2020-07-04">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.37 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>New application icon</li>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-04-26" type="development" version="3.37.1">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.37 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Scores support changed to use libgnome-games-support</li>
          <li>Various code modernization</li>
          <li>Snap package updated to use gnome-3-34 extension </li>
          <li>Help updates</li>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release type="stable" version="3.36.1" date="2020-03-28">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release, with the following improvements since 3.36.0:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.36.0" date="2020-03-07" type="stable">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release, with the following notable improvements
          since 3.32:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix Ctrl+Q keyboard shortcut for Quit</li>
          <li>Help updates</li>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.35.91" type="development" date="2020-02-15">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.35 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release type="development" date="2020-02-01" version="3.35.90">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.35 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Help updates</li>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release type="development" version="3.35.3" date="2020-01-04">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.35 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix Ctrl+Q keyboard shortcut for Quit</li>
          <li>Help updates</li>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.32.1" date="2019-08-08" />
  </releases>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.Tali.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Tali</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/tali/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://wiki.gnome.org/TranslationProject</url>
  <url type="help">https://help.gnome.org/users/tali/stable/</url>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <developer_name>The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">GNOME 計畫</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 项目</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Проект GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">GNOME Projesi</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr@latin">Gnomov projekat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Гномов пројекат</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Проект GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Proiectul GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">O projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="oc">Lo projècte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Het Gnome-project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ne">जिनोम परियोजना</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb">GNOME prosjektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ms">Projek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lv">GNOME projekts</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">GNOME projektas</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">그놈 프로젝트</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="kk">GNOME жобасы</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Il progetto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Projek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">מיזם GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">O Proxecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fur">Il progjet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Le projet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Gnome-projekti</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fa">پروژهٔ گنوم</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">GNOME proiektua</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">El proyecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">La GNOME-projekto</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Το έργο GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Das GNOME-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca@valencia">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="bg">Проектът GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="be">Праект GNOME</developer_name>
  <provides>
    <id>tali.desktop</id>
  </provides>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>HighContrast</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>UserDocs</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <translation type="gettext">tali</translation>
</component>