<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>gnome.gnome-characters</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.Characters.desktop</launchable>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">org.gnome.Characters.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" type="cached" width="128">org.gnome.Characters.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.Characters.desktop</id>
  <name>Characters</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">字元</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">字符</name>
  <name lang="uk">Символи</name>
  <name lang="tr">Karakterler</name>
  <name lang="tg">Аломатҳо</name>
  <name lang="ta">எழுத்துக்கள்</name>
  <name lang="sv">Tecken</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Tablica znakova</name>
  <name lang="sr">Таблица знакова</name>
  <name lang="sl">Znaki</name>
  <name lang="sk">Znaky</name>
  <name lang="sat">ᱪᱤᱱᱦᱟᱹ ᱠᱚ</name>
  <name lang="ru">Символы</name>
  <name lang="ro">Caractere</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Caracteres</name>
  <name lang="pt">Caracteres</name>
  <name lang="pl">Znaki</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਅੱਖਰ</name>
  <name lang="oc">Caractèrs</name>
  <name lang="nl">Tekens en symbolen</name>
  <name lang="ne">वर्ण</name>
  <name lang="nb">Tegn</name>
  <name lang="ms">Aksara</name>
  <name lang="ml">ക്യാരക്റ്റേഴ്സ്</name>
  <name lang="lv">Rakstzīmes</name>
  <name lang="lt">Simboliai</name>
  <name lang="ln">Minkomá</name>
  <name lang="ko">문자 도구</name>
  <name lang="kk">Таңбалар</name>
  <name lang="ja">文字</name>
  <name lang="it">Caratteri</name>
  <name lang="is">Stafir</name>
  <name lang="id">Karakter</name>
  <name lang="hu">Karakterek</name>
  <name lang="hr">Znakovi</name>
  <name lang="he">תווים</name>
  <name lang="gu">અક્ષરો</name>
  <name lang="gl">Caracteres</name>
  <name lang="gd">Caractaran</name>
  <name lang="fy">Characters</name>
  <name lang="fur">Caratars</name>
  <name lang="fr">Caractères</name>
  <name lang="fi">Merkit</name>
  <name lang="fa">نویسه‌ها</name>
  <name lang="eu">Karaktereak</name>
  <name lang="es">Caracteres</name>
  <name lang="eo">Signoj</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Characters</name>
  <name lang="el">Χαρακτήρες</name>
  <name lang="de">Zeichen</name>
  <name lang="da">Tegn</name>
  <name lang="cs">Znaky</name>
  <name lang="ckb">نووسەکان</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">Caràcters</name>
  <name lang="ca">Caràcters</name>
  <name lang="bg">Знаци</name>
  <name lang="be">Знакі</name>
  <name lang="ar">المحارف</name>
  <name lang="af">Karakters</name>
  <name lang="ab">Асимволқәа</name>
  <summary>Character map application</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">字元對應表應用程式</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">字符映射应用程序</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Програма символів</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Karakter eşlem uygulaması</summary>
  <summary lang="ta">எழுத்து வரைபட பயன்பாடு</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Teckentabellprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Program tablice znakova</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Програм таблице знакова</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Program za prikaz znakov pisav</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Aplikácia mapa znakov</summary>
  <summary lang="sat">ᱪᱤᱱᱦᱟᱹ ᱱᱟᱠᱷᱟ ᱮᱯᱞᱤᱠᱮᱥᱚᱱ</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Приложение карты символов</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Aplicație cu tabel de caractere</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Aplicativo de mapa de caracteres</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Aplicação Mapa de Caracteres</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Tablica znaków</summary>
  <summary lang="pa">ਅੱਖਰ ਖਾਕਾ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Aplicacion de la taula de caractèrs</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">De toepassing Tekens en symbolen</summary>
  <summary lang="ne">अक्षर मानचित्र अनुप्रयोग</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Program for tegnkart</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Aplikasi peta aksara</summary>
  <summary lang="ml">അക്ഷരങ്ങളുടെ വഴികാട്ടി</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Rakstzīmju tabulu lietotne</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Simbolių žemėlapio programa</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">문자 표 프로그램</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">Таңбалар картасы қолданбасы</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">文字マップアプリケーション</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Applicazione caratteri</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Stafatöfluforrit</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Aplikasi peta karakter</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Karaktertérkép alkalmazás</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Aplikacija za umetanje znakova</summary>
  <summary lang="he">יישום מפת תווים</summary>
  <summary lang="gu">અક્ષરનો નકશો એપલીકા</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Aplicación de mapa de caracteres</summary>
  <summary lang="gd">Aplacaid mapa charactaran</summary>
  <summary lang="fy">Karakter tabel applikaasje</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Aplicazion des mapis caratars</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Application de la table de caractères</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Merkkikarttasovellus</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">برنامهٔ نقشهٔ نویسه‌ها</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Karaktere-maparen aplikazioa</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Aplicación de mapa de caracteres</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Signa programo</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Character map application</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Εφαρμογή χάρτη χαρακτήρων</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Zeichentabelle-Anwendung</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Tegnoversigtsprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Aplikace s mapou znaků</summary>
  <summary lang="ckb">داوانامەی خشتەی نووسەکان</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Aplicació per mostrar caràcters</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Aplicació per a mostrar caràcters</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Програма с таблици на знаците</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Праграма з адмысловымі знакамі</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">تطبيق خريطة المحارف</summary>
  <summary lang="af">Karakterkaart toepassing</summary>
  <summary lang="ab">Асимволқәа рыхсаала аҧшьы</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>BSD-3-Clause AND GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>
      Characters is a simple utility application to find and insert unusual characters.  It allows you to quickly find the character you are looking for by searching for keywords.
    </p>
    <p>
      You can also browse characters by categories, such as Punctuation, Pictures, etc.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ab">
    <p>Асимволқәа-ари имариоу ҧшьуп иалукааша асимволқәа рыҧшаареи аҭагалареи рзыУи ишәнаҭоит алшара ишәҭаху асимвол иаарццакны аҧшаара ихадоу ажәақәа рыла</p>
    <p>Насгьы асимволқәа шәрышьҭаларц шәылшоит хкыла,иаҳҳәап, апунктуациа адыргақәа, асахьақәа.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="af">
    <p>Karakters is 'n eenvoudige nutstoepassing om ongewone karakters te vind en in te voeg. Dit laat u toe om vinnig karakter te vind deur met sleutelwoorde te soek.</p>
    <p>U kan ook deur karakter-kategorieë blaai, soos leestekens, prente, ens.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>«محارف» تطبيق بسيط للبحث عن المحارف غير المألوفة. يسمح لك التّطبيق بالبحث عن المحرف الّذي تريده بالبحث عن الكلمات المفتاحية.</p>
    <p>يمكنك تصفّح المحارف حسب فئاتها، كعلامات الترقيم و الصّور وغيرها.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Знакі - гэта простая праграма, якая дазваляе шукаць і ўстаўляць незвычайныя знакі. Вы можаце хутка знайсці патрэбны вам знак па ключавых словах.</p>
    <p>Таксама можна аглядаць знакі па катэгорыях, такіх як пунктуацыя, выявы і інш.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>„Знаци“ е лесна за ползване програма за намирането и вмъкването на по-редки знаци. Тя дава възможност бързо да намерите знак като го търсите с ключови думи.</p>
    <p>Може да разглеждате знаците и по категории като пунктуация, картинки и др.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Caràcters és una aplicació per a cercar i inserir caràcters inusuals. Us permet trobar ràpidament els caràcters que esteu cercant usant paraules clau.</p>
    <p>També podeu navegar els caràcters per categories, com ara puntuació, imatges, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca@valencia">
    <p>Caràcters és una aplicació per buscar i inserir caràcters inusuals. Vos permet trobar ràpidament els caràcters que esteu cercant usant paraules clau.</p>
    <p>També podeu navegar els caràcters per categories, com ara puntuació, imatges, etc. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ckb">
    <p>نووسەکان بریتین لە داوانامە بۆ دۆزینەوە و دانانی نووسەی نائاسایی. ڕێگەت دەدات بە خێرایی ئەو نووسانە بدۆزیتەوە کە بۆی دەگەڕێیت ئەویش بەبەکارهێنانی کلیلەووشە.</p>
    <p>دەتوانی بنواڕیتە نووسەکان بە پێی پۆلەکان، وەک خاڵبەندی، وێنە،هیتر.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Znaky je jednoduchá pomocná aplikace pro vyhledávání a vkládání méně běžných znaků. Znak, který hledáte, můžete rychle najít podle klíčových slov.</p>
    <p>Znaky můžete také procházet podle kategorií, jako například „interpunkce“, „obrázky“ atd.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Tegn er et simpelt hjælpeværktøj til at finde og indsætte usædvanlige tegn. Det giver dig mulighed for hurtigt at finde tegn, du leder efter, ved at søge efter nøgleord.</p>
    <p>Du kan også gennemse tegn efter kategorier såsom tegnsætning, billeder osv.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Zeichen ist ein einfaches Hilfsprogramm zum Auffinden und Einsetzen von selten verwendeten Zeichen. Sie können schnell das gesuchte Zeichen finden, indem Sie nach Schlüsselwörtern suchen.</p>
    <p>Sie können ebenfalls nach Kategorie suchen, wie z.B. nach Zeichensetzung oder Bildern.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Η εφαρμογή «Χαρακτήρες» είναι μια απλή βοηθητική εφαρμογή εύρεσης και εισαγωγής σπάνιων χαρακτήρων. Σας επιτρέπει να βρείτε γρήγορα τον χαρακτήρα που ψάχνετε αναζητώντας λέξεις κλειδιά.</p>
    <p>Μπορείτε επίσης να περιηγηθείτε στους χαρακτήρες κατά κατηγορίες, όπως στίξη, εικόνες κ.λπ.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Characters is a simple utility application to find and insert unusual characters. It allows you to quickly find the character you are looking for by searching for keywords.</p>
    <p>You can also browse characters by categories, such as Punctuation, Pictures, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p>Signoj estas simpla utila aplikaĵo por trovi kaj enmeti nekutimajn signojn. Ĝi permesas al vi rapide trovi la signon kiun vi serĉas per serĉi ŝlosilvortojn.</p>
    <p>Vi ankaŭ povas foliumi signojn laŭ kategorioj, kiel Interpunkcio, Bildoj, ktp.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Caracteres es una sencilla aplicación para buscar e insertar caracteres poco habituales. Le permite buscar rápidamente el carácter que está buscando usando palabras clave.</p>
    <p>Puede examinar los caracteres por categorías, tales como Puntuación, Imágenes, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Karaktereak aplikazio xume bat da ohikoak ez diren karaktereak bilatu eta txertatzeko. Gako-hitzen arabera bilatzea nahi duzun karakterea bizkor aurkitzen du.</p>
    <p>Kategorien arabera ere araka ditzakezu karaktereak. Hala nola, puntuazioa, irudiak eta abar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fa">
    <p>نویسه‌ها ابزاری ساده برای یافتن و درج نویسه‌های غیرمعمول است. این ابزار به شما امکان یافتن سریع نویسه‌ای که به دنبالش هستید را با جست‌وجو برای کلیدواژگان می‌دهد.</p>
    <p>همچنین می‌توانید نویسه‌ها را بر اساس دسته‌بندی‌هایی چون نقطه‌گذاری، نگاره‌ها و… بیابید.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Merkit on yksinkertainen sovellus, jonka avulla on mahdollista etsiä ja syöttää epätavallisia merkkejä. Voit etsiä merkkejä käyttäen hakusanoja.</p>
    <p>Voit myös selata merkkejä luokkien perusteella, esimerkiksi välimerkkejä, kuvia jne.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Caractères est un utilitaire pour chercher et insérer des caractères inhabituels. Il vous permet de trouver rapidement le caractère que vous cherchez par le biais de mots-clés.</p>
    <p>Vous pouvez aussi naviguer dans les caractères par catégories, comme par Ponctuation, Images, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Caratars al è un sempliç program par la ricercje e l'inseriment di caratars insolits. Al permet di cirî di corse dai caratars a mieç di une ricercje par peraulis clâf.</p>
    <p>Al è pussibil ancje esplorâ i caratars par categorie come puntuazions, figuris, ecc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fy">
    <p>Charakters is in maklik te brûken applikaasje foar it fynen en ynfieren fan ôfwikende karakters. It stelt jo yn steat fluch it karakter te fynen wer om sykje troch in oantal trefwurden yn te fieren.</p>
    <p>Jo kin ek per kategory troch karakters blêdzje, lykas Punktuaasje, Foto's, ensfh.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gd">
    <p>’S e goireas simplidh a th’ ann an Caractaran gus caractaran sònraichte a lorg ’s a chur ann. Leigidh e leat an caractar a tha thu ag iarraidh a lorg gu luath le taic faclan-luirg.</p>
    <p>’S urrainn dhut na caractaran a bhrabhsadh a-rèir roinn-seòrsa cuideachd, can puingeachadh, dealbhan is msaa.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Caracteres é unha utilidade sinxela para buscar e inserir caracteres non normais. Permítelle atopar de forma rápida o carácter que está buscando por etiquetas.</p>
    <p>Tamén pode explorar caracteres por categorías, como Puntuación, Imaxes, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gu">
    <p>અક્ષરો ઓ શોધવા અને અસામાન્ય અક્ષરો દાખલ કરવા માટે એક સરળ ઉપયોગીતા એપ્લિકેશન છે. તે તમને ઝડપથી તમારા કીવર્ડ્સ માટે અક્ષરને શોધવા માટે પરવાનગી આપે છે.</p>
    <p>તમે વિરામચિહ્ન, ચિત્રો, વગેરે દ્વારા પણ અક્ષરો બ્રાઉઝ કરી શકો છો.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>תווים זהו יישום שירות פשוט למציאה ולהכנסת תווים בלתי רגילים. הוא מאפשר לך למצאו במהירות תווים שהנך מחפש באמצעות חיפוש מילות מפתח.</p>
    <p>כמו כן ניתן לדפדף בתווים באמצעות קטגוריות, כמו סימני פיסוק, תמונות וכו׳.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Znakovi je mala aplikacija pomagala za pronalazak i umetanje neuobičajenih znakova. Omogućuje vam brz pronalazak znaka kojeg tražite pretragom po ključnoj riječi.</p>
    <p>Isto tako možete pregledavati znakove po kategorijama, poput interpunkcija, slika, itd.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Karakterek egy egyszerű segédprogram alkalmazás szokatlan karakterek kereséséhez és beszúrásához. Lehetővé teszi a keresett karakter gyors megtalálását kulcsszavakra való kereséssel.</p>
    <p>Böngészhet a karakterek között kategóriák szerint is, úgymint központozás, képek, stb.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Karakter adalah sebuah utilitas sederhana untuk mencari dan menyisipkan karakter-karakter tak umum. Ini memungkinkan Anda mencari secara cepat karakter yang Anda inginkan dengan mencari berdasarkan kata-kata kunci.</p>
    <p>Anda juga dapat meramban karakter-karakter menurut kategori, seperti Tanda Baca, Gambar, dsb.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>Stafataflan Characters er einfalt nytjatól til að finna og setja inn óvenjuleg staftákn. Fljótlegt er að finna táknið sem þú leitar að með því að setja inn stikkorð.</p>
    <p>Þú getur skoðað staftákn eftir flokkum, eins og Myndir, Greinamerki o.s.frv.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Caratteri è un semplice programma per la ricerca e l'inserimento di caratteri insoliti. Consente di cercare velocemente dei caratteri attraverso una ricerca per parole chiave.</p>
    <p>È anche possibile esplorare il caratteri per categorie come punteggiatura, immagini, ecc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>Characters は珍しい文字を探して挿入するためのシンプルなユーティリティです。キーワード検索により、素早く文字を発見できます。</p>
    <p>また、句読点記号や絵文字のようなカテゴリー別に閲覧することもできます。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <p>Таңбалар - бұл сирек кездесетін таңбаларды табу және кірістіру үшін арналған қолданба. Оның көмегімен сіз кілт сөздер көмегімен керек таңбаларды жылдам таба аласыз.</p>
    <p>Сонымен бірге, сіз таңбаларды санаттар бойынша шола аласыз, мыс. емле таңбалары, суреттер және т.б.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>문자 도구는 자주 사용하지 않는 문자를 찾아 입력하는 단순한 유틸리티 프로그램입니다. 찾아볼 문자를 단어로 빨리 찾아볼 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p>구두기호, 그림 등의 분류 방식으로 문자를 찾아볼 수 있습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ln">
    <p>Minkoma ézali ntoma mpona koluka mpe bakisa minkoma ya momeseno tê. Ezo sunga yo mpona kokuta na lombangu monkoma ozali koluka na nzéla ya liloba-mamá.</p>
    <p>Okoki mpe koluka minkoma na katégoli, lokola na bilembo bya bokomi, bilili, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Simboliai yra paprasta programa simbolių suradimui ir įterpimui. Ji leidžia greitai rasti pageidaujamą simbolį ieškant raktinių žodžių.</p>
    <p>Taip pat galite ieškoti simbolių pagal kategorijas, tokias kaip skyrybos ženklai, paveikslėliai ir kt.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>Rakstzīmes ir vienkārša utilītprogramma, lai atrastu un ievietotu neparastas rakstzīmes. Tā ļauj ātri atrast vajadzīgās rakstzīmes, meklējot atslēgvārdus.</p>
    <p>Rakstzīmes varat pārlūkot pēc kategorijām, piemēram, interpunkcija un attēli.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ml">
    <p>ക്യാരക്ടര്‍ എന്നത് ലളിതമായി ഉപയോഗിക്കാവുന്ന അപ്ലിക്കേഷന്‍ ആണ്.ഇത് അപൂര്‍വ്വമായ ക്യാരക്ടറെ കണ്ടെത്തുകയും കൂട്ടിച്ചേര്‍ക്കുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു.നിങ്ങള്‍ നല്‍കുന്ന സൂചകപദങ്ങളെ വേഗത്തില്‍ കണ്ടെത്തുന്നതിന് ഇത് അനുവദിക്കുന്നു.</p>
    <p>ചിത്രങ്ങള്‍ , ചിഹ്നങ്ങള്‍ മുതലായവ വിഭാഗങ്ങളായി ക്രമത്തില്‍ നിങ്ങളെ തിരയാം.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Aksara merupakan sebuah aplikasi utiliti ringkas yang dapat mencari dan menyisip aksara. Ia membolehkan anda cari aksara dengan pantas hanya dengan menggelintar kata kunci.</p>
    <p>Anda juga boleh melayari aksara mengikut kategori, seperti Tanda Baca, Gambar, dll.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Tegn er et enkelt verktøy for å finne og sette inn uvanlige tegn. Det lar deg finne tegn du leter etter raskt ved å søke etter nøkkelord.</p>
    <p>Du kan også bla gjennom tegn ved bruk av kategorier som tegnsetting, bilder, osv.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ne">
    <p>क्यारेक्टरस् असामान्य वर्णहरू फेला पार्न र सम्मिलित गर्न सरल उपयोगिक अनुप्रयोग हो। यसले तपाईँलाई चाँडै वर्णहरू खोज्ने र पत्ता लगाउने अनुमति दिन्छ।.</p>
    <p>तपाइँ पनि वर्ग द्वारा वर्णहरू ब्राउज गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ, जस्तै विराम चिन्ह, चित्रहरू आदि।.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Tekens en symbolen is een eenvoudig hulpmiddel om bijzondere tekens te zoeken en in te voegen. U kunt het door u gezochte teken snel vinden door middel van trefwoorden.</p>
    <p>U kunt ook tekens zoeken per categorie, zoals interpunctie, afbeeldingen, enz.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>Caractèrs es un utilitari per cercar e inserir de caractèrs inabituals. Vos permet de trobar rapidament lo caractèr que cercatz pel biais de mots-claus.</p>
    <p>Tanben podètz navegar dins los caractèrs per categorias, coma per Ponctuacion, Imatges, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pa">
    <p>ਕਰੈਕਟਰ (ਅੱਖਰ) ਅਸਧਾਰਨ ਅੱਖਰ ਲੱਭਣ ਤੇ ਪਾਉਣ ਵਾਲੀ ਸਰਲ ਸਹੂਲਤ ਵਾਲੀ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਹੈ। ਇਹ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਖਾਸ ਢੰਗ ਰਾਹੀਂ ਲੱਭ ਕੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਖਰ ਲੱਭਣ ਦੀ ਇਜਾਜ਼ਤ ਦਿੰਦੀ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p>ਤੁਸੀਂ ਵਰਗ ਜਿਵੇਂ ਕਿ ਵਿਰਾਮ-ਚਿੰਨ੍ਹ, ਤਸਵੀਰਾਂ ਰਾਹੀਂ ਵੀ ਅੱਖਰਾਂ ਦੀ ਝਲਕ ਵੇਖ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Tablica znaków to proste narzędzie do wyszukiwania i wstawiania znaków specjalnych. Umożliwia ono szybkie znajdowanie znaków dzięki słowom kluczowym.</p>
    <p>Można także przeglądać znaki według kategorii, takich jak interpunkcja, obrazki itp.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Caracteres é um utilitário simples para localizar e inserir caracteres pouco habituais. Permite-lhe encontrar rapidamente o carácter que procura, procurando por palavras chave.</p>
    <p>Também pode procurar por categorias, tais como pontuação, imagens, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>O aplicativo Caracteres é um utilitário simples para localizar e inserir caracteres incomuns. Ele permite que você localize de forma rápida o caractere desejado ao pesquisar por palavras-chaves.</p>
    <p>Você também pode navegar entre caracteres através de categorias, como pontuação, imagens, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Caractere este o aplicație simplă pentru găsirea și introducerea caracterelor rare. Ea vă permite să găsiți rapid caracterele pe care le doriți prin căutarea după cuvinte cheie.</p>
    <p>Puteți de asemenea să navigați prin caractere după categorii, precum punctuație, poze, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Символы — это простое приложение, для поиска и вставки необычных символов. Оно позволяет быстро находить нужный символ по ключевым словам.</p>
    <p>Также можно просматривать символы по категориям, таким как знаки пунктуации, картинки и т.д.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sat">
    <p>ᱪᱤᱱᱦᱟᱹᱯ ᱠᱚ ᱫᱚ ᱠᱷᱟᱹᱞᱤ ᱢᱤᱫᱴᱟᱹᱝ ᱥᱟᱫᱨᱚᱬ ᱭᱱᱤᱴᱭ ᱮᱯᱞᱤᱠᱮᱥᱚᱱ ᱠᱟᱱᱟ ᱡᱟᱦᱟᱸ ᱛᱮ ᱟᱢ ᱡᱟᱦᱱᱟᱜ ᱥᱮᱸᱫᱽᱨᱟ ᱟᱨ ᱮᱴᱟᱜ ᱞᱮᱠᱷᱟ ᱪᱤᱱᱦᱟᱹ ᱠᱚ ᱮᱢ ᱪᱷᱚ ᱫᱟᱲᱮᱭᱟᱜᱼᱟ ᱯᱮ ᱾ ᱱᱚᱶᱟ ᱛᱮ ᱡᱟᱦᱱᱟᱜ ᱜᱮ ᱪᱤᱱᱦᱟᱹ ᱞᱚᱜᱚᱱ ᱜᱮ ᱯᱟᱱᱛᱮ ᱜᱟᱱᱚᱜᱼᱟ ᱾</p>
    <p>ᱟᱢ ᱫᱚ ᱛᱷᱚᱠ ᱠᱚ ᱞᱮᱠᱷᱟ, ᱡᱮᱞᱠᱟ ᱪᱤᱠᱷᱱᱟᱹ, ᱪᱤᱛᱟᱹᱨ ᱠᱚ, ᱮᱴᱟᱜ ᱾</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Znaky je jednoduchá užitočná aplikácia na nájdenie a vloženie neobvyklých znakov. Umožňuje vám rýchlo nájsť znak, ktorý môžete vyhľadať pomocou kľúčových slov.</p>
    <p>Môžete tiež prehliadať znaky podľa kategórií, ako sú napríklad Znaky, Obrázky, atď.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Program Znaki je enostaven program za iskanje in vstavljanje neobičajnih znakov v besedilo. Omogoča hitro iskanje s ključnimi opisnimi besedami.</p>
    <p>Kategorije, kot so Znaki, Ločila, Sličice in podobno, je mogoče tudi prebrskati.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Знаковник је једноставно помагало за налажење и уметање необичних знакова. Он вам омогућава да лако нађете знак који тражите уносом кључних речи.</p>
    <p>Можете да листате знакове по категоријама као што су Интерпункције, Слике и друго.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Znakovnik je jednostavno pomagalo za nalaženje i umetanje neobičnih znakova. On vam omogućava da lako nađete znak koji tražite unosom ključnih reči.</p>
    <p>Možete da listate znakove po kategorijama kao što su Interpunkcije, Slike i drugo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Tecken är ett enkelt nyttoprogram för att söka och infoga ovanliga tecken. Det låter dig snabbt hitta tecknet du söker genom att söka efter nyckelord.</p>
    <p>Du kan också bläddra igenom tecken efter kategorier som skiljetecken, bilder o.s.v.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Karakterler, alışılmadık karakterleri bulmak ve eklemek için yardımcı yalın bir uygulamadır. Anahtar sözcükler arayarak karakteri hızlıca bulmanızı sağlar.</p>
    <p>Ayrıca karakterlere kategorileri ile göz atabilirsiniz, örneğin Noktalama, Resimler vb.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Символи — простенька програм для пошуку та вставлення незвичайних символів. Він дозволяє швидко знайти символ за допомогою ключових слів.</p>
    <p>Ви також можете переглянути символи через категорії, як-от Пунктуація, Малюнки тощо.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>字符 是一个简单的查找并插入特殊字符的实用程序。它可以让你通过通过搜索关键字快速找到你正在寻找的字符。</p>
    <p>你也可以按照目录浏览字符，比如 标点、图片等。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>《字元》是方便查找不常用字元並插入的簡單公用程式。透過關鍵字您就能快速尋找想要使用的字元。</p>
    <p>您可以根據分類來瀏覽字元，例如：標點符號、圖片…等。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-characters/raw/main/data/screenshots/screenshot1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-characters/raw/main/data/screenshots/screenshot2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.gnome.org/app/org.gnome.Characters/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-characters/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.gnome.org/donate</url>
  <update_contact>dueno_at_src.gnome.org</update_contact>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>HighContrast</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>SearchProvider</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <translation type="gettext">org.gnome.Characters</translation>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="42.0" date="2022-03-19">
      <p>Characters 42.0 comes plenty of changes</p>
      <ul>
        <li>Port to GTK 4 / libadwaita</li>
        <li>Proper dark theme support</li>
        <li>Fix various search provider related issues</li>
        <li>Search provider now displays the character on the search results</li>
        <li>Translations updates</li>
      </ul>
    </release>
    <release version="41.0" date="2021-09-21">
      <p>Characters 41 comes with a fix so that the close button shows on the sidebar at mobile sizes.</p>
      <p>Characters 41 also comes with updated translations for the following locales:</p>
      <ul>
        <li>Belarusian</li>
        <li>Chinese (Taiwan)</li>
        <li>Danish</li>
        <li>Dutch</li>
        <li>English (United Kingdom)</li>
        <li>Greek, Modern (1453-)</li>
        <li>Hebrew</li>
        <li>Korean</li>
        <li>Nepali</li>
        <li>Occitan (post 1500)</li>
        <li>Russian</li>
        <li>Tamil</li>
        <li>Western Frisian</li>
      </ul>
    </release>
    <release version="40.0" date="2021-03-20">
      <p>Characters has received a visual upgrade, and is now able to be used across mobile and desktop form factors.</p>
      <p>Characters 40 also comes with updated translations for the following locales:</p>
      <ul>
        <li>Bangla (India)</li>
        <li>Basque</li>
        <li>Bokmål, Norwegian</li>
        <li>Catalan</li>
        <li>Chinese (China)</li>
        <li>Chinese (Taiwan)</li>
        <li>Croatian</li>
        <li>Czech</li>
        <li>Danish</li>
        <li>Dutch</li>
        <li>English (United Kingdom)</li>
        <li>Esperanto</li>
        <li>Finnish</li>
        <li>French</li>
        <li>Friulian</li>
        <li>Galician</li>
        <li>German</li>
        <li>Greek, Modern (1453-)</li>
        <li>Hebrew</li>
        <li>Hungarian</li>
        <li>Indonesian</li>
        <li>Italian</li>
        <li>Japanese</li>
        <li>Kazakh</li>
        <li>Korean</li>
        <li>Latvian</li>
        <li>Lithuanian</li>
        <li>Panjabi</li>
        <li>Persian</li>
        <li>Polish</li>
        <li>Portuguese</li>
        <li>Portuguese (Brazil)</li>
        <li>Romanian</li>
        <li>Serbian</li>
        <li>Slovak</li>
        <li>Slovenian</li>
        <li>Spanish</li>
        <li>Swedish</li>
        <li>Turkish</li>
        <li>Ukrainian</li>
      </ul>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-04-08" version="3.32.1" />
  </releases>
</component>