<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <description>
    <p>
      A simple application to access and organize your e-books on
      GNOME. It is meant to be a simple and elegant replacement for using a
      file manager to deal with e-books.
    </p>
    <p>It lets you:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>View recent e-books</li>
      <li>Search through e-books</li>
      <li>View e-books (ePubs and comics) fullscreen</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="af">
    <p>'n Eenvoudige toepassing om e-boeke in GNOME te vertoon en organiseer. Dit is ontwikkel as 'n elegante plaasvervanger vir die gebruik van 'n lêerbestuurder om met e-boeke te werk.</p>
    <p>Dit stel jou in staat om:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Na onlangse e-boeke te kyk</li>
      <li>Deur e-boeke te soek</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>تطبيق بسيط للوصول إلى الكتب الرقمية و تنظيمها و مشاركتها في جنوم. صُمم ليكون بديلا بسيطًا و رائعًا عن مدير الملفات للتعامل مع الكتب الرقمية.</p>
    <p>يتيح لك:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>عرض الكتب الرقمية الحديثة</li>
      <li>البحث قي الكتب الرقمية</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="as">
    <p>ই আপোনাক অনুমতি দিয়ে:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Простая праграма для чытання і упарадкавання электронных кніг для GNOME. Яна распрацавана ў якасці простай і зручнай замены файлавага кіраўніка для працы з электроннымі кнігамі.</p>
    <p>Праграма дазваляе:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Праглядзець нядаўнія электронныя кнігі</li>
      <li>Шукаць у электронных кнігах</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Опростено приложение за достъп, организиране и споделяне на е-книгите в GNOME. Предназначено е да бъде олекотен и елегантен заместник на файловия мениджър при работа с е-документи.</p>
    <p>Чрез него можете да:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Скорошни е-книги</li>
      <li>Търсене в e-книгите</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bn_IN">
    <p>অাপনাকে অনুমতি দেয়:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Jednostavan program za pristup i organizacijuvaših elektronskih knjiga na GNOME.Namijenjeno je da bude jednostavna i elegantna zamjena za korištenje upravitelja datoteka za rad sa elektronskim knjigama.</p>
    <p>To vam omogućuje :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Pogledaj nedavne elektronske knjige</li>
      <li>Traži kroz elektronske knjige</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Un programa simple per a accedir i organitzar els llibres electrònics al GNOME. Està pensat per a ser un substitut simple i elegant d'un gestor de fitxers per als llibres electrònics.</p>
    <p>Us permet:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Visualitza els llibres electrònics recents</li>
      <li>Cerqueu als llibres</li>
      <li>Visualitzeu els llibres electrònics (ePubs i còmics) a pantalla completa</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca@valencia">
    <p>Un programa simple per accedir i organitzar els llibres electrònics al GNOME. Està pensat per a ser un substitut simple i elegant d'un gestor de fitxers per als llibres electrònics.</p>
    <p>Vos permet:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Visualitza els llibres electrònics recents</li>
      <li>Cerqueu als llibres</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ckb">
    <ul>
      <li>دووا پەرتوکە ئەلکترۆنییەکان پیشا بدە</li>
      <li>بگەڕێ بەناو پەرتوکە ئەلکترۆنییەکان</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Jednoduchá aplikace, kterou můžete používat pro přístup ke svým elektronickým knihám v GNOME a jejich roztřídění. Je zamýšlena jako snadná a elegantní náhrada za používání správce souborů k zacházení s e-knihami.</p>
    <p>Můžete v ní dělat následující věci:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Zobrazit si nedávné e-knihy</li>
      <li>Vyhledávat v e-knihách</li>
      <li>Zobrazte si e-knihy (ePub a komiksy) přes celou obrazovku</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Et simpelt program til at tilgå og organisere dine e-bøger i GNOME. Det er påtænkt at være en simpel og elegant erstatning for at bruge et filhåndteringsprogram til at håndtere e-bøger.</p>
    <p>Den lader dig:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Vis seneste e-bøger</li>
      <li>Søge gennem e-bøger</li>
      <li>Vis e-bøger (ePub'er og tegneserier) i fuldskærm</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Eine einfache Anwendung, um Ihre E-Bücher in GNOME zu betrachten und zu organisieren. Mit dieser Anwendung soll ein einfacher und eleganter Ersatz für eine Dateiverwaltung bereitgestellt werden, um mit E-Büchern zu arbeiten.</p>
    <p>Sie ermöglicht Ihnen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Kürzlich verwendete E-Bücher anzuzeigen</li>
      <li>In E-Büchern zu suchen</li>
      <li>E-Bücher (EPUB und Comics) im Vollbildmodus anzuzeigen</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Μια απλή εφαρμογή για να έχετε πρόσβαση, να οργανώσετε τα ηλεκτρονικά σας βιβλία στο GNOME. Προορίζεται να είναι απλή και κομψή με σκοπό να αντικαταστήσει την διαχείριση των ηλεκτρονικών σας βιβλίων από τον διαχειριστή αρχείων.</p>
    <p>Σας επιτρέπει να:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Προβολή πρόσφατων ηλεκτρονικών βιβλίων</li>
      <li>Αναζητήσετε σε ηλεκτρονικά βιβλία</li>
      <li>Δείτε ηλεκτρονικά βιβλία (PDF και κόμικ) σε πλήρη οθόνη</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>A simple application to access and organise your e-books on GNOME. It is meant to be a simple and elegant replacement for using a file manager to deal with e-books.</p>
    <p>It lets you:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>View recent e-books</li>
      <li>Search through e-books</li>
      <li>View e-books (ePubs and comics) fullscreen</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p>Simpla aplikaĵo por aliri kaj organizi viajn bitlibrojn ene de GNOME. Ĝi celas esti simpla kaj eleganta anstataŭigo de dosierfoliumilo, rilate al dokumentojn.</p>
    <p>Ĝi permesas al vi:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Rigardi freŝdatajn bitlibrojn</li>
      <li>Serĉi tra dokumentoj</li>
      <li>Montri bitlibrojn (ePub-ojn kaj komiksojn) tutekrane</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Una sencilla aplicación para acceder y organizar sus libros electrónicos en GNOME. Está pensada para ser un reemplazo sencillo elegante del uso de un gestor de archivos para gestionar sus libros electrónicos.</p>
    <p>Le permite:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ver los libros recientes</li>
      <li>Buscar en los libros electrónicos</li>
      <li>Ver libros electrónicos (epub y cómics) a pantalla completa</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>See võimaldab sul:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Zure liburu elektronikoa GNOMEn atzitu eta antolatzeko aplikazio xume bat: hau da, liburu elektronikoekin aritzeko fitxategi-kudeatzaile baten ordezko xume eta dotore bat.</p>
    <p>Honakoak eskaintzen dizkizu:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ikusi azken liburu elek.</li>
      <li>Bilatu liburu elektronikoen artean</li>
      <li>Ikusi liburu elektronikoak (EPUBak eta komikiak) pantaila osoan</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fa">
    <p>برنامه‌ای ساده برای دسترسی و مدیریت کتاب‌های الکترونیک در گنوم. این برنامه سعی دارد جایگزینی ساده و کارا برای استفاده از مدیر پرونده به منظور تعامل با کتاب‌های الکترونیک باشد.</p>
    <p>این برنامه می‌گذارد:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>کتاب‌های الکترونیک اخیر را ببینید</li>
      <li>در میان کتاب‌ّای الکترونیک جست‌وجو کنید</li>
      <li>نمایش تمام‌صفحهٔ کتاب‌های الکترونیک (ای‌پاب‌ها و کمیک‌ها)</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Yksinkertainen Gnome-sovellus kirjojen käyttöä, organisointia ja jakamista varten. Sen on tarkoitus korvata tiedostonhallinta kirjoihin liittyvässä käytössä. Saumattoman pilvi-integraation tarjoaa Gnomen verkkotilit.</p>
    <p>Sen avulla voit:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Katsella viimeisimpiä kirjoja</li>
      <li>Etsiä kirjojen sisällöstä</li>
      <li>Katsele sähköisiä kirjoja (ePubeja ja sarjakuvia) koko näytön tilassa</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Une application simple pour accéder à vos livres numériques et les organiser dans GNOME. Son but est d’être une alternative simple et élégante à l’utilisation d’un gestionnaire de fichiers pour traiter les livres numériques.</p>
    <p>Elle vous permet de :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Consulter les dernières parutions</li>
      <li>Chercher parmi votre bibliothèque</li>
      <li>Lire des livres numériques (ePub et bandes dessinées) en plein écran</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Une semplice aplicazion par acedi, organizâ e condividi su GNOME i propris e-book. E je pensade par jessi une alternative semplice e elegant a un file manager te gjestion dai documents.</p>
    <p>A permet di:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Viodi e-book resints</li>
      <li>Cirî tai e-book</li>
      <li>Viôt a plen visôr i e-book (ePubs e fumets)</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ga">
    <p>Ligeann sé duit:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Amharc ar r-leabhair le déanaí</li>
      <li>Cuardaigh r-leabhair</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Unha aplicación doada para acceder, organizar e compartir os seus documentos en GNOME. Está pensado para que sexa unha alternativa simple e elegante ao uso do explorador de ficheiros para xestionar os seus libros dixitais.</p>
    <p>Permítelle:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ver os libros dixitais recentes</li>
      <li>Buscar entre os libros dixitais</li>
      <li>Ver os libros dixitais (ePubs e bandas deseñadas) a pantalla completa</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>יישום פשוט לגישה ולארגון הספרים האלקטרוניים שלך על GNOME. היישום משמש חלופה פשוטה ואלגנטית למנהל קבצים לצורך טיפול בספרים אלקטרוניים.</p>
    <p>היישום מאפשר לך:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>הצגת הספרים האלקטרוניים האחרונים</li>
      <li>חיפוש מבעד לספרים אלקטרוניים</li>
      <li>צפייה בספרים אלקטרוניים (ePubs וקומיקס) במסך מלא</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="hi">
    <p>आपको करने देता है:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Jednostavna aplikacija za pristup i organizaciju vaših e-knjiga na GNOMU. Namjena aplikacije je da bude jednostavna i elegantna zamjena za rukovanje e-knjigama u upravitelju datoteka.</p>
    <p>Omogućuje vam:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Pregled nedavnih e-knjiga</li>
      <li>Pretragu e-knjiga</li>
      <li>Pregled e-knjiga (ePubs i stripova) u cijelom zaslonu</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>Egyszerű alkalmazás e-könyvek eléréséhez és rendszerezéséhez GNOME alatt. A fájlkezelő e-könyvek kezelésére való használatának egyszerű és elegáns helyettesítésére tervezték.</p>
    <p>Lehetővé teszi:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Legutóbbi e-könyvek megtekintése</li>
      <li>Keresés az e-könyvekben</li>
      <li>E-könyvek (ePub-ok és képregények) megtekintése teljes képernyőn</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Aplikasi sederhana untuk mengakses dan mengelola buku-el Anda pada GNOME. Ini dimaksudkan sebagai pengganti yang sederhana dan elegan dari manajer berkas untuk berurusan dengan buku-el.</p>
    <p>Ini memungkinkan Anda:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Tilik buku-el baru-baru ini</li>
      <li>Cari di antara buku-el</li>
      <li>Lihat buku-el (ePub dan komik) dalam layar penuh</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>Einfalt forrit til að skoða og skipuleggja rafbækurnar þínar í GNOME. Það er hugsað til þess að vera einföld og hreinleg leið til að sýsla með rafbækur í gegnum skráastjóra.</p>
    <p>Gerir þér kleift að:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Skoða nýlegar rafbækur</li>
      <li>Leita í rafbókum</li>
      <li>Skoða rafbækur (ePub og Comic) á heilskjá</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Una semplice applicazione per accedere, organizzare e condividere su GNOME i propri e-book. È pensata per essere un'alternativa semplice ed elegante all'utilizzo di un file manager nella gestione dei documenti.</p>
    <p>Permette di:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Visualizzare e-book recenti</li>
      <li>Cercare tra gli e-book</li>
      <li>Visualizzare e-book (ePub e fumetti) a schermo intero</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>GNOME 上で電子書籍を楽しんだり、管理できるシンプルなアプリケーションです。シンプルさとエレガントさを特長としており、電子書籍を楽しむためにファイルマネージャーを使う必要はありません。</p>
    <p>機能:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>最近読んだ電子書籍の表示</li>
      <li>電子書籍の検索</li>
      <li>電子書籍 (EPUB および Comic Book) のフルスクリーン表示</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <p>GNOME ішінде электрондық кітаптарыңызға қатынау және оларды реттеу үшін арналған қарапайым қолданба. Ол эл. кітаптармен жұмысы үшін файлдар басқарушысын алмастыратын қарапайым әрі элегантты шешім ретінде ұсынылады.</p>
    <p>Мүмкіндіктері:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Соңғы эл. кітаптарды қарау</li>
      <li>Эл. кітаптар ішінен іздеу</li>
      <li>Эл. кітаптарды (ePub және комикстер) толық экранда қарау</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="kn">
    <p>ಇದು ನಿಮಗೆ:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>그놈에서 전자책을 살펴보고 관리하는 간단한 프로그램입니다. 전자책을 다루려 파일 관리자를 사용할 때 간단하고 매력적인 대안 프로그램임을 의미합니다.</p>
    <p>이 프로그램에는 다음 기능이 있습니다:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>최근 전자책 보기</li>
      <li>전자책 검색</li>
      <li>최대 화면으로 전자책(전자책과 만화) 보기</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ln">
    <p>Esaleli ya mpamba pona koyingela na ba buku nimeriki na yo mpe koyangela  na GNOME. Ntina na ye ezali kozala boponi ya mpamba mpe ya kitoko na bosaleli moyangeli ya ba kasa pona kosala ba buku nimeriki.</p>
    <p>Ezo sunga yo pona:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Tala ba buku nimeriki ya suka</li>
      <li>Luka nakati ya bibilyotèque</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Paprasta programa GNOME aplinkai el. knygų pasiekimui. Ji siekia būti paprastu ir elegantišku failų tvarkytuvės pakaitalu darbui su el. knygomis.</p>
    <p>Ji jums leidžia:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Rodyti nesenai naudotas el. knygas</li>
      <li>Ieškokite el. knygose</li>
      <li>Rodyti el. knygas (ePub ir komiksus) visame ekrane</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>Vienkārša lietotne e-grāmatu piekļūšanai, organizēšanai un koplietošanai GNOME vidē. Tā ir paredzēta kā datņu pārvaldnieka aizvietotājs darbam ar e-grāmatām.</p>
    <p>Tās jums ļauj:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Skatīt nesenās e-grāmatas</li>
      <li>Meklēt e-grāmatās</li>
      <li>Skatīt e-grāmatas (ePub un komiksus) pilnekrāna režīmā</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ml">
    <p>ഗ്നോമിൽ നിങ്ങളുടെ ഇ-പുസ്തകങ്ങൾ അടുക്കിവെക്കാനും വായിക്കാനുമുള്ള ലളിതമായ പ്രയോഗം. ഫയൽ മാനേജർ ഉപയോഗിച്ചുഇ-പുസ്തകങ്ങൾ കൈകാര്യം ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് പകരമായി ലളിതവും മനോഹരവുമായ ഈ പ്രയോഗം  ഉപയോഗിക്കാം.</p>
    <p>ഇത് നിങ്ങള്‍ക്ക് വേണ്ടി:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>പുതിയ ഇ-ബുക്കുകള്‍ കാണാം</li>
      <li>ഇ-ബുക്കുകളിലൂടെയുളള തിരച്ചില്‍</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="mr">
    <p>तुम्हाला खालील पुरवेल:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Sebuah aplikasi ringka yang boleh mencapai dan mengurus ebuku anda di dalam GNOME. Ia pengganti yang ringkas tetapi elegan berbanding menggunakan ebuku dengan pengurus fail.</p>
    <p>Ia membolehkan anda;</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Lihat ebuku baru-baru ini</li>
      <li>Gelintar menyeluruhi ebuku</li>
      <li>Lihat ebuku (ePub dan komik) dalam skrin penuh</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Et enkelt program for å aksessere, organisere dine e-bøker i GNOME. Ment å være en enkel og elegant erstatning for å håndtere e-bøker med en filhåndterer.</p>
    <p>Det lar deg:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Vis nylige e-bøker</li>
      <li>Søk i e-bøker</li>
      <li>Vis e-bøker (ePubs og tegneserier) i fullskjerm</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Een eenvoudige toepassing om uw documenten op Gnome te beheren. Het is bedoeld als eenvoudige en elegante vervanging van een bestandsbeheerprogramma om met e-boeken te werken.</p>
    <p>U kunt hiermee:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Recente e-boeken bekijken</li>
      <li>E-boeken doorzoeken</li>
      <li>E-boeken (ePubs en strips) in volledig scherm bekijken</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>Una aplicacion simpla per accedir a vòstres libres numerics e los organizar dins GNOME. Sa tòca es d'èsser una alternativa simpla e eleganta a l'utilizacion d'un gestionari de fichièrs per tractar los libres numerics.</p>
    <p>Vos permet de :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Consultar las darrièras parucions</li>
      <li>Cercar demest vòstra bibliotèca</li>
      <li>Legir de libres numerics (ePub e bendas dessenhadas) en ecran complet</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="or">
    <p>ଏହା ଆପଣଙ୍କୁ ଅନୁମତି ଦେଇଥାଏ:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pa">
    <p>ਗਨੋਮ ਵਿੱਚ ਤੁਹਾਡੀਆਂ ਈ-ਬੁੱਕਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਵਰਤਣ ਤੇ ਉਹਨਾਂ ਦਾ ਪਰਬੰਧ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਸੌਖੀ ਜੇਹੀ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਈ-ਬੁੱਕਾਂ ਦਾ ਪਰਬੰਧ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਫਾਇਲ ਮੈਨੇਜਰ ਨੂੰ ਸੌਖਾ ਤੇ ਸਧਾਰਨ ਰੂਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਤਿਆਰ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p>ਇਹ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਲਈ ਹੈ:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>ਤਾਜ਼ਾ ਈ-ਕਿਤਾਬਾਂ ਵੇਖੋ</li>
      <li>ਈ-ਬੁੱਕਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਲੱਭੋ</li>
      <li>ਈ-ਬੁੱਕਾਂ (ePub ਅਤੇ ਹਾਸਰਸ ਕਿਤਾਬਾਂ) ਨੂੰ ਪੂਰੀ ਸਕਰੀਨ ਉੱਤੇ ਵੇਖੋ</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Prosty program umożliwiający czytanie i organizowanie e-booków w środowisku GNOME. Został on zaprojektowany jako prosty i elegancki interfejs do zarządzania e-bookami, zastępujący w tym celu menedżer plików.</p>
    <p>Program umożliwia:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Przeglądanie ostatnio używanych e-booków</li>
      <li>Przeszukiwanie e-booków</li>
      <li>Wyświetlanie e-booków (plików ePub i komiksów) w trybie pełnoekranowym</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Uma aplicação simples para aceder, organizar e partilhar livros eletrónicos no GNOME. Tem por objetivo ser uma forma simples e elegante de substituir a utilização de um gestor de ficheiros para gerir livros eletrónicos.</p>
    <p>Permite</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ver livros recentes</li>
      <li>Procurar livros</li>
      <li>Ver livros (PDF e banda desenhada) em ecrã completo</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Um aplicativo simples para acessar, organizar e compartilhar seus e-books no GNOME. Ele foi feito para servir como uma substituição simples e elegante de gerenciador de arquivos para lidar com e-books.</p>
    <p>Ele permite que você:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ver e-books recentes</li>
      <li>Pesquise através de e-books</li>
      <li>Veja e-books (ePubs e revistas) em tela cheia</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>O simplă aplicație care vă permite să vă accesați cărțile electronice în GNOME. Este conceput pentru a fi un înlocuitor simplu și elegant al managerului de fișiere pentru a gestiona cărți electronice.</p>
    <p>Vă permite:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Vizualizează cărțile electronice recente</li>
      <li>Căutați prin cărțile electronice</li>
      <li>Vizualizează cărți electronice (publicații electronice și benzi desenate) pe tot ecranul</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Простое приложение для управления электронными книгами в GNOME. Это приложение предоставляет простую и элегантную замену файловому менеджеру при работе с электронными книгами.</p>
    <p>Позволяет:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Открывать последние электронные книги</li>
      <li>Выполнять поиск по электронными книгам</li>
      <li>Просматривать электронные книги (ePubs и комиксы) в полноэкранном режиме</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Jednoduchá aplikácia prostredia GNOME na prístup k vašim elektronickým knihám a ich organizáciu. Cieľom tejto aplikácie je jednoducho a elegantne nahradiť správcu súborov ako prehliadač e-kníh.</p>
    <p>Umožňuje vám:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Zobraziť nedávne e-knihy</li>
      <li>Vyhľadávať v e-knihách</li>
      <li>Prehliadať e-knihy (ePuby a komiksy) v režime na celú obrazovku</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Enostaven program za dostop in urejanje elektronskih knjig za namizje GNOME. Zamišljen je kot enostavno orodje, ki naj bi nadomestilo uporabo upravljalnika datotek.</p>
    <p>Omogoča:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Pregled elektronskih knjig</li>
      <li>Iskanje po besedilu v elektronskih knjigah</li>
      <li>Prikaz elektronskih virov (ePub in Stripi) v celozaslonskem načinu</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Једноставан програм за приступ и сређивање електронских књига на Гному. Замишљен је да буде једноставна и пригодна замена управника датотека за рад са електронским књигама.</p>
    <p>Омогућава вам да:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Погледате скорашње е-књиге</li>
      <li>Претражујете е-књиге</li>
      <li>Прегледате е-књиге (еПуб или стрипове) преко целог екрана</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Jednostavan program za pristup i sređivanje elektronskih knjiga na Gnomu. Zamišljen je da bude jednostavna i prigodna zamena upravnika datoteka za rad sa elektronskim knjigama.</p>
    <p>Omogućava vam da:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Pogledate skorašnje e-knjige</li>
      <li>Pretražujete e-knjige</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Ett enkelt program för att komma åt och organisera dina e-böcker i GNOME. Det är avsett att vara en enkel och elegant ersättare för att hantera e-böcker med en filhanterare.</p>
    <p>Det låter dig:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Visa senaste e-böcker</li>
      <li>Söka genom e-böcker</li>
      <li>Visa e-böcker (ePub och serier) i helskärmsläge</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ta">
    <p>இதைக் கொண்டு நீங்கள் செய்யக்கூடியவை:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="te">
    <p>ఇది మిమ్మల్ని:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="th">
    <p>โปรแกรมอย่างง่ายสำหรับเข้าถึงและจัดระเบียบอีบุ๊กของคุณใน GNOME เป็นโปรแกรมเรียบหรูที่ใช้แทนโปรแกรมจัดการแฟ้มในการจัดการกับอีบุ๊ก</p>
    <p>ช่วยให้คุณ:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>ดูอีบุ๊กล่าสุด</li>
      <li>ค้นอีบุ๊ก</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>GNOME üzerinde belgelerinize erişmek, onları düzenlemek için basit bir uygulama. E-kitaplarınızı düzenlemek için dosya yöneticisinin yerini alabilecek basit ve şık bir çözüm olarak geliştirildi.</p>
    <p>Şunları yapmanıza olanak tanır:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Yakın zamanda kullanılan e-kitapları görüntülemek</li>
      <li>E-kitaplarda arama yapmak</li>
      <li>E-kitapları (PDF ve çizgi roman) tam ekranda görüntülemek</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Проста програма, щоб доступитись, упорядкувати ваші електронні книги в GNOME. Тобто це проста і витончена заміна файлового менеджера для роботи з електронними книгами.</p>
    <p>Програма дозволяє:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Переглянути нещодавні книги</li>
      <li>Шукати в книгах</li>
      <li>Переглядати книги (ePubs або комікси) в повному екранні</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="vi">
    <p>Đây là ứng dụng đơn giản để truy cập, tổ chức sách điện tử của bạn trên môi trường GNOME. Điều đó có nghĩa là nó phù hợp để thay thế cho bộ quản lý tập tin khi dùng với sách điện tử.</p>
    <p>Nó giúp bạn:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Sách điện tử bạn mới dùng</li>
      <li>Tìm trong sách điện tử</li>
      <li>Hiển thị sách điện tử (ePubs và truyện tranh) ở chế độ toàn màn hình</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>GNOME 下一款可访问、管理您的电子书的简洁应用。它的目标是成为一款替代文件管理器来处理电子书的优雅工具。</p>
    <p>它允许您：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>查看最近的电子书</li>
      <li>从电子书中搜索</li>
      <li>全屏查看电子书（ePub 和漫画）</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_HK">
    <p>它讓你可以：</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>簡單的應用程式，讓您可以在 GNOME 中存取與管理您的電子書。它希望能成為以檔案管理程式處理電子書的簡單優雅替代方案。</p>
    <p>它讓您可以：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>檢視最近使用的電子書</li>
      <li>搜尋電子書</li>
      <li>以全螢幕檢視（ePub 與漫畫）電子書</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>gnome.gnome-books</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.Books.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" height="64" type="cached">org.gnome.Books.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" width="128" type="cached">org.gnome.Books.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.Books.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Books</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">書籍</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">图书</name>
  <name lang="vi">Sách</name>
  <name lang="uk">Книги</name>
  <name lang="tr">Kitaplar</name>
  <name lang="th">หนังสือ</name>
  <name lang="sv">Böcker</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Knjige</name>
  <name lang="sr">Књиге</name>
  <name lang="sl">Knjige</name>
  <name lang="sk">Knihy</name>
  <name lang="ru">Книги</name>
  <name lang="ro">Cărți</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Livros</name>
  <name lang="pt">Livros</name>
  <name lang="pl">Książki</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਕਿਤਾਬਾਂ</name>
  <name lang="oc">Libres</name>
  <name lang="nl">Boeken</name>
  <name lang="ne">किताबहरू</name>
  <name lang="nb">Bøker</name>
  <name lang="ms">Buku</name>
  <name lang="ml">പുസ്തകങ്ങള്‍</name>
  <name lang="lt">Knygos</name>
  <name lang="lv">Grāmatas</name>
  <name lang="ln">Buku</name>
  <name lang="ko">책</name>
  <name lang="kk">Кітаптар</name>
  <name lang="ja">ブック</name>
  <name lang="it">Libri</name>
  <name lang="is">Rafbækur</name>
  <name lang="id">Buku</name>
  <name lang="hu">Könyvek</name>
  <name lang="hr">Knjige</name>
  <name lang="he">ספרים</name>
  <name lang="gl">Libros</name>
  <name lang="ga">Leabhair</name>
  <name lang="fur">Libris</name>
  <name lang="fr">Livres</name>
  <name lang="fi">Kirjat</name>
  <name lang="fa">کتاب‌ها</name>
  <name lang="eu">Liburuak</name>
  <name lang="es">Libros</name>
  <name lang="eo">Libroj</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Books</name>
  <name lang="el">Βιβλία</name>
  <name lang="de">Bücher</name>
  <name lang="da">Bøger</name>
  <name lang="cs">Knihy</name>
  <name lang="ckb">Books</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">Llibres</name>
  <name lang="ca">Llibres</name>
  <name lang="bs">Knjige</name>
  <name lang="bg">Книги</name>
  <name lang="be">Кнігі</name>
  <name lang="ar">الكتب</name>
  <name lang="af">Boeke</name>
  <summary>An e-book manager application for GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">GNOME 的電子書管理員應用程式</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">GNOME 下的一款电子书管理应用程序</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Ứng dụng quản lý sách điện tử dành cho môi trường GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Організатор електронних книг для GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">GNOME için e-kitap yönetici uygulaması</summary>
  <summary lang="th">โปรแกรมจัดการอีบุ๊กสำหรับ GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Ett program för hantering av e-böcker för GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Gnomov program za upravljanje elektronskim knjigama</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Гномов програм за управљање електронским књигама</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Program za upravljanje z elektronskimi knjigami za namizje GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Aplikácia na správu elektronických kníh pre GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Приложение для управления электронными книгами в GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Un manager de cărți electronice pentru GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Um aplicativo para gerenciamento de e-book para o GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Uma aplicação de gestão de livros eletrónicos para o GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Program do zarządzania e-bookami dla środowiska GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਲਈ ਈ-ਬੁੱਕ ਮੈਨੇਜਰ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਹੈ</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Una aplicacion de gestion dels libres numerics per GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Een Gnome-toepassing voor e-boekbeheer</summary>
  <summary lang="ne">जिनोमको लागि ई-किताब प्रबन्धक अनुप्रयोग</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Et program for å håndtere e-bøker for GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Sebuah aplikasi pengurus ebuku untuk GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ml">ഗ്നോമിന് വേണ്ടിയുളള ഡോക്യുമെന്റ് മാനേജര്‍ പ്രയോഗം</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">El. knygų tvarkymo programa GNOME aplinkai</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">E-grāmatu pārvaldības lietotne GNOME vidē</summary>
  <summary lang="ln">Esaleli ya koyangela ba buku nimeriki pona GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">그놈용 전자책 관리 프로그램</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">GNOME үшін электрондық кітаптарды басқару қолданбасы</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">GNOME の電子書籍管理アプリケーション</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Una applicazione GNOME per gestire e-book</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Rafbókaforrit fyrir GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Aplikasi manajer buku-el bagi GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Egy e-könyv kezelő alkalmazás a GNOME-hoz</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Aplikacija upravitelja e-knjiga za GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="he">יישום לניהול ספרים אלקטרוניים עבור GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Unha aplicación para xestionar libros dixitais para GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ga">Feidhmchlár bhainisteoireacht r-leabhar do GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Une aplicazion GNOME par ministrâ e-book</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Une application de gestion des livres numériques pour GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Kirjojen hallintasovellus Gnomelle</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">یک برنامهٔ مدیریت کتاب‌های الکترونیک برای گنوم</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Liburu elektronikoak kudeatzeko GNOMEren aplikazio bat</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Una aplicación para gestionar libros electrónicos para GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Bitlibra mastrum-aplikaĵo por GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">An e-book manager application for GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Εφαρμογή διαχείρισης ηλεκτρονικών βιβλίων του GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Eine Anwendung zur E-Bücher-Verwaltung für GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Et program til håndtering af e-bøger i GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Aplikace pro správu elektronických knih v GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ckb">ڕێکخەری پەرتووکی ئەلکترۆنی بۆ گنۆم</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Una aplicació per gestionar llibres electrònics al GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Una aplicació per a gestionar llibres electrònics al GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Program upravljitelj elektronskim knjigama za GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Програма за управление на е-книги в GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Праграма кіравання электроннымі кнігамі для GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">تطبيق إدارة الكتب الرقمية لجنوم</summary>
  <summary lang="af">'n E-boekbestuurder vir GNOME</summary>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>AppMenu</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-books/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">http://www.gnome.org/friends</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Books</url>
  <url type="translate">https://wiki.gnome.org/TranslationProject</url>
  <developer_name>The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">GNOME 專案</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 项目</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="vi">Dự án GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Проєкт GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">GNOME Projesi</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr@latin">Gnomov projekat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Гномов пројекат</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Проект GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Proiectul GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਪਰੋਜੈੱਕਟ</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="oc">Lo projècte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Het Gnome-project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb">GNOME prosjektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ms">Projek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ml">ഗ്നോം പ്രൊജക്റ്റ്</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">GNOME projektas</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lv">GNOME projekts</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">그놈 프로젝트</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="kk">GNOME жобасы</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">GNOME プロジェクト</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Il progetto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="is">GNOME verkefnið</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Proyek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">מיזם GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">O Proxecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fur">Il progjet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Le projet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Gnome-projekti</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fa">پروژهٔ گنوم</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">GNOME proiektua</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">El Proyecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">La GNOME-projekto</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Το έργο GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Das GNOME-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ckb">پرۆژەی گنۆم</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca@valencia">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="bg">Проектът GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ar">مشروع جنوم</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="af">Die GNOME Projek</developer_name>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-books/raw/master/data/screenshots/gnome-books-1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-books/raw/master/data/screenshots/gnome-books-2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-books/raw/master/data/screenshots/gnome-books-3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <update_contact>hadess_at_gnome.org</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-books</translation>
  <releases>
    <release date="2021-03-24" version="40.0">
      <description>
        <p>
          We are proud to announce Books 40.0 as the latest stable version.
        </p>
        <p>
          This new version uses an embedded version of Tracker 3 as its book
          indexer.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-09-06" version="3.34.0">
      <description>
        <p>
          We are proud to announce Books 3.34.0 as the latest stable version.
        </p>
        <p>
          This new version has a new application icon, fixes some CBR files not
          appearing, and looks when the content view is empty.
        </p>
        <p>
          The ePub view can now be zoomed, its night mode works better, and
          the files can be opened in Foliate and Bookworm.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-03-08" version="3.32.0">
      <description>
        <p>
          We are proud to announce Books 3.32.0 as the latest stable version.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-desecration">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-slavery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-worship">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-homosexuality">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-prostitution">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-adultery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-appearance">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>