<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>gnome.gnome-boxes</pkgname>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">org.gnome.Boxes.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" width="128" type="cached">org.gnome.Boxes.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.Boxes.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.1+</project_license>
  <name>Boxes</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">機櫃</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">機櫃</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">盒子</name>
  <name lang="vi">Máy</name>
  <name lang="uk">Коробки</name>
  <name lang="ug">قۇتىلار</name>
  <name lang="tr">Kutular</name>
  <name lang="th">กล่อง</name>
  <name lang="tg">Қуттиҳо</name>
  <name lang="te">పెట్టెలు</name>
  <name lang="ta">பெட்டிகள்</name>
  <name lang="sv">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Kutije</name>
  <name lang="sr">Кутије</name>
  <name lang="sk">Boxy</name>
  <name lang="sl">Škatle</name>
  <name lang="ru">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="ro">Cutii</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="pt">Caixas</name>
  <name lang="pl">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਬਾਕਸ</name>
  <name lang="or">ବାକ୍ସଗୁଡ଼ିକ</name>
  <name lang="oc">Maquinas</name>
  <name lang="nl">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="ne">बाकसहरू</name>
  <name lang="nb">Bokser</name>
  <name lang="ms">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="mr">बॉक्सेस</name>
  <name lang="ml">പെട്ടികള്‍</name>
  <name lang="lv">Kastes</name>
  <name lang="lt">Dėžės</name>
  <name lang="ko">박스</name>
  <name lang="kn">ಬಾಕ್ಸಸ್‌</name>
  <name lang="km">ប្រអប់</name>
  <name lang="kk">Бокстар</name>
  <name lang="ja">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="it">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="id">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="hu">Gépek</name>
  <name lang="hr">Boksevi</name>
  <name lang="hi">बक्सा</name>
  <name lang="he">קופסאות</name>
  <name lang="gu">બોક્સ</name>
  <name lang="gl">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="ga">Boscaí</name>
  <name lang="fur">Scjatulis</name>
  <name lang="fr">Machines</name>
  <name lang="fi">Boksit</name>
  <name lang="fa">جعبه‌ها</name>
  <name lang="eu">Makinak</name>
  <name lang="et">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="es">Cajas</name>
  <name lang="eo">Skatolaro</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="el">Πλαίσια</name>
  <name lang="de">Boxen</name>
  <name lang="da">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="cs">Boxy</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">Màquines</name>
  <name lang="ca">Màquines</name>
  <name lang="bs">Okviri</name>
  <name lang="bn_IN">বাক্স</name>
  <name lang="bg">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="be">Boxes</name>
  <name lang="as">বাকচসমূহ</name>
  <name lang="ar">«صناديق»</name>
  <name lang="af">Bokse</name>
  <summary>Virtualization made simple</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">虛擬化變得簡單</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">让虚拟化管理变得更轻松</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Ảo hóa trở nên đơn giản</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Проста віртуалізація</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Sanallaştırma kolaylaştırıldı</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Virtualisering på ett enkelt sätt</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Виртуелизација учињена једноставнијом</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Zjednodušuje virtualizáciu</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Enostavnost virtualizacije</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Виртуализация стала проще</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Virtualizare simplificată</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Virtualização simplificada</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Virtualização tornada simples</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Prosta wirtualizacja</summary>
  <summary lang="pa">ਵਰਚੁਲਾਈਜ਼ੇਸ਼ਨ ਸਰਲ ਬਣਾਈ</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">La virtualizacion facilament</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Virtualisatie eenvoudig gemaakt</summary>
  <summary lang="ne">अवास्तविकरण सरल बनाइयो</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Virtualisering gjort enkelt</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Saprotama virtualizācija</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Paprasta virtualizacija</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">가상화 기능을 쉽게 활용하게 해줍니다</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">Виртуализация енді оңай</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Virtualizzazione semplificata</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Virtualisasi menjadi sederhana</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Virtualizáció egyszerűen</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Virtualizaciju čini jednostavnijom</summary>
  <summary lang="he">וירטואליזציה בקלות</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Fai a virtualización doada</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Virtualizazion rindude semplice</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">La virtualisation rendue simple</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Helpoksi tehtyä virtualisointia</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">مجازی‌سازی ساده شده</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Birtualizazioa modu errazean</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Virtualización sencilla</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Virtualisation made simple</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Η εικονικοποίηση έγινε εύκολη</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Virtualisierung einfach gemacht</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Virtualisering gjort enkelt</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Virtualizovat se dá jednoduše</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">La virtualització feta simple</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Лесна виртуализация</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Select an operating system and let Boxes download and install it for you
      in a virtual machine.
    </p>
    <p lang="zh_CN">选择一款操作系统，并让盒子为您下载并在虚拟机中安装。</p>
    <p lang="uk">Виберіть операційну систему і надайте «Коробкам» змогу отримати і встановити її у віртуальній машині.</p>
    <p lang="tr">İşletim sistemi seçin ve bırakın Kutular sizin için indirip sanal makineye kursun.</p>
    <p lang="sv">Välj ett operativsystem och låt Boxes hämta och installera det åt dig i en virtuell maskin.</p>
    <p lang="sr">Изаберите оперативни систем и дозволите Кутијама да га преузму и инсталирају за вас, унутар виртуелне машине.</p>
    <p lang="sk">Vyberte operačný systém a nechajte ho prevziať a nainštalovať aplikáciou Boxy vo virtuálnom počítači.</p>
    <p lang="sl">Izberite operacijski sistem in prepustite programu, da prejme in namesti navidezno napravo.</p>
    <p lang="ru">Выберите операционную систему и позвольте Boxes загрузить и установить ее для вас на виртуальной машине.</p>
    <p lang="pt_BR">Selecione um sistema operacional e deixe o Boxes baixar e instalá-lo para você em uma máquina virtual.</p>
    <p lang="pt">Selecione um sistema operativo e deixe o Caixas descarregá-lo e instalá-lo para si numa máquina virtual.</p>
    <p lang="pl">Wybierz system operacyjny, a Boxes pobierze i zainstaluje go za Ciebie w maszynie wirtualnej.</p>
    <p lang="lt">Pasirinkite operacinę sistemą ir leiskite Dėžėms ją atsisiųsti ir įdiegta virtualioje mašinoje.</p>
    <p lang="ko">가상 머신에 다운로드하고 설치할 운영체제를 선택하십시오.</p>
    <p lang="kk">Операциялық жүйені таңдап, Бокстар үшін оны жүктеп, виртуалды машинаға орнатуға рұқсат етіңіз.</p>
    <p lang="it">Selezionare un sistema operativo e consentire a Boxes di scaricarlo e installarlo automaticamente in una macchina virtuale.</p>
    <p lang="id">Pilih sistem operasi dan biarkan Boxes mengunduh dan memasangnya untuk Anda di mesin virtual.</p>
    <p lang="hu">Válasszon egy operációs rendszert, és hagyja, hogy a Gépek letöltse és telepítse Önnek egy virtuális gépre.</p>
    <p lang="hr">Odaberite operativni sustav i prepustite Boksevima da preuzmu i instaliraju virtualni stroj umjesto vas.</p>
    <p lang="he">נא לבחור מערכת הפעלה כדי לאפשר לקופסאות להוריד ולהתקין אותה עבורך במכונה וירטואלית.</p>
    <p lang="gl">Seleccione un sistema operativo e déixelle a Caixas descargar e instalalo nunha máquina virtual.</p>
    <p lang="fur">Selezione un sisteme operatîf e lasse a Scjatulis il compit di discjamâlu e instalâlu intune machine virtuâl.</p>
    <p lang="fr">Sélectionnez un système d’exploitation et laissez Machines le télécharger et l’installer pour vous dans une machine virtuelle.</p>
    <p lang="fi">Valitse käyttöjärjestelmä ja anna Boksien ladata ja asentaa se sinulle virtuaalikoneeseen.</p>
    <p lang="fa">سیستم‌عاملی گزیده و بگذارید جعبه‌ها برایتان بارگیری و در دستگاهی مجازی نصبش کند.</p>
    <p lang="eu">Hautatu sistema eragile bat eta utzi Makinak aplikazioari hura deskargatzen eta makina birtual batean instalatzen.</p>
    <p lang="es">Seleccione un sistema operativo y deje que Cajas lo descargue e instale en una máquina virtual.</p>
    <p lang="en_GB">Select an operating system and let Boxes download and install it for you in a virtual machine.</p>
    <p lang="de">Wählen Sie ein Betriebssystem. Boxen wird es herunterladen und in einer virtuellen Maschine installieren.</p>
    <p lang="da">Vælg et styresystem og lad Boxes hente og installere det for dig på en virtuel maskine.</p>
    <p lang="cs">Vyberte operační systém a nechte Boxy jej stáhnout a nainstalovat do virtuálního počítače.</p>
    <p lang="ca">Seleccioneu un sistema operatiu i deixeu que Màquines el descarregui i l'instal·li en una màquina virtual.</p>
    <p lang="bg">Изберете операционна система — Boxes ще я изтегли и инсталира във виртуална машина.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p lang="zh_CN">特性：</p>
    <p lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p lang="tr">Özellikler:</p>
    <p lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p lang="sr">Могућности:</p>
    <p lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p lang="ru">Особенности:</p>
    <p lang="pt_BR">Recursos:</p>
    <p lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p lang="pl">Funkcje:</p>
    <p lang="lt">Savybės:</p>
    <p lang="ko">특징:</p>
    <p lang="kk">Мүмкіндіктері:</p>
    <p lang="it">Caratteristiche:</p>
    <p lang="id">Fitur:</p>
    <p lang="hu">Funkciók:</p>
    <p lang="hr">Značajke:</p>
    <p lang="he">יכולות:</p>
    <p lang="gl">Características:</p>
    <p lang="fur">Carateristichis:</p>
    <p lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p lang="fi">Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <p lang="fa">ویژگی‌ها:</p>
    <p lang="eu">Eginbideak:</p>
    <p lang="es">Características:</p>
    <p lang="en_GB">Features:</p>
    <p lang="de">Funktionsmerkmale:</p>
    <p lang="da">Funktioner:</p>
    <p lang="cs">Funkce:</p>
    <p lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p lang="bg">Възможности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Download freely available operating systems.</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">下载免费可用的操作系统。</li>
      <li lang="uk">Отримання вільно доступних операційних систем.</li>
      <li lang="tr">Serbestçe edinilebilen işletim sistemlerini indirin.</li>
      <li lang="sv">Hämta fritt tillgängliga operativsystem.</li>
      <li lang="sr">Преузми слободно доступних оперативних система.</li>
      <li lang="sk">Prevzatie voľne dostupných operačných systémov.</li>
      <li lang="sl">Prejem prosto dostopnega operacijskega sistema.</li>
      <li lang="ru">Загружайте свободно распространяемые операционные системы.</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Baixar sistemas operacionais livremente disponíveis.</li>
      <li lang="pt">Transferir sistemas operativos disponíveis gratuitamente.</li>
      <li lang="pl">Pobieranie wolno dostępnych systemów operacyjnych.</li>
      <li lang="lt">Atsisiunčia laisvai prieinamas operacines sistemas.</li>
      <li lang="ko">가용 운영 체제를 자유롭게 다운로드할 수 있습니다.</li>
      <li lang="kk">Еркін қолжетімді операциялық жүйелерді жүктеп алу.</li>
      <li lang="it">Scarica i sistemi operativi disponibili gratuitamente.</li>
      <li lang="id">Unduh sistem operasi yang tersedia secara bebas.</li>
      <li lang="hu">Szabadon elérhető operációs rendszerek letöltése.</li>
      <li lang="hr">Preuzmite besplatno dostupne operativne sustave.</li>
      <li lang="he">הורדה של מערכת הפעלות שזמינות באופן חופשי.</li>
      <li lang="gl">Descargar gratuitamente sistemas operativos dispoñíbeis.</li>
      <li lang="fur">Discjame i sistemis operatîfs disponibii in maniere gratuite.</li>
      <li lang="fr">Téléchargement en toute liberté de systèmes d’exploitation disponibles.</li>
      <li lang="fi">Lataa vapaasti saatavilla olevia käyttöjärjestelmiä.</li>
      <li lang="fa">بارگیری سیستم‌عامل‌های آزادانه در دسترس.</li>
      <li lang="eu">Deskargatu libre eskuragarri dauden sistema eragileak.</li>
      <li lang="es">Descargar sistemas operativos disponibles libremente.</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Download freely available operating systems.</li>
      <li lang="de">Ein frei verfügbares Betriebssystem herunterladen.</li>
      <li lang="da">Hent frit tilgængelige styresystemer.</li>
      <li lang="cs">Stažení volně dostupných operačních systémů.</li>
      <li lang="ca">Descarregueu sistemes operatius disponibles gratuïtament.</li>
      <li lang="bg">Изтегляне на достъпните операционни системи:</li>
      <li>Automatically install CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red
      Hat Enterprise Linux, and Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">自动安装 CentOS Stream、Debian、Fedora、微软 Windows、OpenSUSE、红帽 Enterprise Linux 和 Ubuntu。</li>
      <li lang="uk">Автоматичне встановлення CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux та Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="tr">CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux ve Ubuntu’yu kendiliğinden kurun.</li>
      <li lang="sv">Installera automatiskt CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux och Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="sr">Самостално инсталирање система Центос Стрим, Дебијан, Федора, Мајкрософт Виндоус, Опен-суса, Ред Хет Ентерпрајз Линукс и Убунту.</li>
      <li lang="sk">Automatická inštalácia systémov CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux, a Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="sl">Samodejna namestitev sistemov CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux in Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="ru">Автоматически устанавливайте CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, openSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux и Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Instalar automaticamente CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux e Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="pt">Instala automaticamente o CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux e Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="pl">Automatyczne instalowanie systemów CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux i Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="lt">Automatiškai įdiegia CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux bei Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="ko">CentOS 스트림, 데비안, 페도라, 마이크로소프트 윈도우, 오픈수세, 레드햇 엔터프라이즈 리눅스, 우분투를 자동으로 설치합니다.</li>
      <li lang="kk">CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux және Ubuntu жүйелерін автоматты түрде орнату.</li>
      <li lang="it">Installa automaticamente CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux e Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="id">Secara otomatis memasang CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, openSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux, dan Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="hu">CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux és Ubuntu automatikus telepítése.</li>
      <li lang="hr">Automatski instaliraj CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux, i Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="he">התקנה אוטומטית של CentOS Stream, דביאן, פדורה, Microsoft Windows,‏ OpenSUSE,‏ Red Hat Enterprise Linux ואובונטו.</li>
      <li lang="gl">Instalar automaticamente CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux e Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="fur">Instale in automatic CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux e Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="fr">Installation automatique de CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux, et Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="fi">Asenna automaattisesti CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux ja Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="fa">نصب خودکار جریان سنت‌او‌اس، دبیان، فدورا، ویندوز مایکروسافت، ردهت و اوبونتو.</li>
      <li lang="eu">Instalatu automatikoki CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux eta Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="es">Instalar automáticamente CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux, y Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Automatically install CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux, and Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="de">CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux und Ubuntu automatisch installieren.</li>
      <li lang="da">Installér automatisk CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux og Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="cs">Automatická instalace systémů CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux a Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="ca">Instal·leu automàticament CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux i Ubuntu.</li>
      <li lang="bg">Автоматично инсталиране на CentOS Stream, Debian, Fedora, Microsoft Windows, OpenSUSE, Red Hat Enterprise Linux и Ubuntu.</li>
      <li>Create virtual machines from operating system images with a couple of clicks.</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">从操作系统镜像创建虚拟机，仅需点击几次鼠标。</li>
      <li lang="uk">Створення віртуальних машин з образів операційних систем у декілька клацань кнопкою миші.</li>
      <li lang="tr">Birkaç tıkla işletim sistemi kalıplarından sanal makineler oluşturun.</li>
      <li lang="sv">Skapa virtuella maskiner från operativsystemsavbilder med några klick.</li>
      <li lang="sr">Стварање виртуелних машина из слика оперативних система у само пар кликова.</li>
      <li lang="sk">Vytvorenie virtuálnych počítačov z obrazov operačných systémov pomocou niekoľkých kliknutí.</li>
      <li lang="sl">Ustvarjanje navideznih naprav z odtisi operacijskih sistemov v nekaj korakih.</li>
      <li lang="ru">Создавайте виртуальные машины из образов операционной системы несколькими щелчками мыши.</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Criar máquinas virtuais a partir de imagens do sistema operacional com poucos cliques.</li>
      <li lang="pt">Crie máquinas virtuais a partir de imagens do sistema operativo com alguns cliques.</li>
      <li lang="pl">Tworzenie maszyn wirtualnych z obrazów systemów operacyjnych za pomocą paru kliknięć.</li>
      <li lang="lt">Sukuria virtualias mašinas iš operacinių sistemų atvaizdžių vos keliais paspaudimais.</li>
      <li lang="ko">몇 번의 마우스 단추 누름 동작으로 운영체제 이미지로 가상 머신을 만듭니다.</li>
      <li lang="kk">Бір-екі шерту арқылы операциялық жүйе бейнелерінен виртуалды машиналарды жасау.</li>
      <li lang="it">Crea macchine virtuali da immagini del sistema operativo in un paio di clic.</li>
      <li lang="id">Buat mesin virtual dari citra sistem operasi dengan beberapa klik.</li>
      <li lang="hu">Virtuális gépek létrehozása az operációs rendszer lemezképekből néhány kattintással.</li>
      <li lang="hr">Stvorite virtualni stroj iz slika operativnih sustava u samo nekoliko klikova.</li>
      <li lang="he">יצירה של מכונות וירטואליות מדמויות של מערכות הפעלה במספר לחיצות.</li>
      <li lang="gl">Crear máquinas virtuais desde imaxes de sistema operativo con só un par de clics.</li>
      <li lang="fur">Cree machinis virtuâls partint di imagjins di sistemis operatîfs cuntun pâr di clics.</li>
      <li lang="fr">Création de machines virtuelles à partir d’images de systèmes d’exploitation en quelques clics.</li>
      <li lang="fi">Luo virtuaalikoneita käyttöjärjestelmien levykuvista muutamalla napsautuksella.</li>
      <li lang="fa">ایجاد دستگاه‌های مجازی از تصویرهای سیستم‌عامل با چند کلیک.</li>
      <li lang="eu">Sortu makina birtualak sistema eragileen irudiak erabilita, klik pare bat eginda.</li>
      <li lang="es">Crear máquinas virtuales a partir de imágenes de sistemas operativos con unas pocas pulsaciones de ratón.</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Create virtual machines from operating system images with a couple of clicks.</li>
      <li lang="de">Aus Betriebssystem-Abbildern in wenigen Klicks virtuelle Maschinen erstellen.</li>
      <li lang="da">Opret virtuelle maskiner fra styresystemaftryk med nogle få klik.</li>
      <li lang="cs">Vytváření virtuálních strojů z obrazů operačních systémů na pár kliknutí.</li>
      <li lang="ca">Creeu màquines virtuals a partir d'imatges de sistema operatiu amb un parell de clics.</li>
      <li lang="bg">Създаване на виртуални машини от изображения на операционни системи с няколко действия с мишката.</li>
      <li>Limit the resources (memory and storage) your virtual machines consume from your system.</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">限制您的虚拟机所消耗的系统资源（内存和存储）。</li>
      <li lang="uk">Обмеження ресурсів (пам'яті і місця на диску), які віртуальні машини споживають у вашій системі.</li>
      <li lang="tr">Sanal makinelerinizin sisteminizden tükettiği kaynakları (bellek ve biriktirme) kısıtlayın.</li>
      <li lang="sv">Begränsa resurserna (minne och lagring) som dina virtuella maskiner förbrukar på ditt system.</li>
      <li lang="sr">Ограничавање колико ресурса (меморије и складишта) ваше виртуелне машине троше на вашем систему.</li>
      <li lang="sk">Obmedzenie prostriedkov (pamäte a úložiska), ktoré spotrebujú vaše virtuálne počítače z vášho systému.</li>
      <li lang="sl">Omejitev virov (pomnilnik in shramba) za nameščene navidezne naprave.</li>
      <li lang="ru">Ограничивайте ресурсы (память и хранилище), которые ваши виртуальные машины потребляют из вашей системы.</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Limitar os recursos (memória e armazenamento) que suas máquinas virtuais consomem de seu sistema.</li>
      <li lang="pt">Limite os recursos (memória e armazenamento) que as suas máquinas virtuais consomem a partir do seu sistema.</li>
      <li lang="pl">Ograniczanie zasobów (pamięci i dysków) komputera używanych przez maszyny wirtualne.</li>
      <li lang="lt">Riboja virtualių mašinų naudojamus jūsų kompiuterio išteklius (atmintį bei saugyklą).</li>
      <li lang="ko">가상 머신의 시스템 점유 자원(메모리 및 저장 용량)을 제한합니다.</li>
      <li lang="kk">Виртуалды машиналардың жүйеңізден тұтынатын ресурстарын (жады мен сақтауыш) шектеу.</li>
      <li lang="it">Limita le risorse (memoria e archiviazione) utilizzate dalle macchine virtuali dal sistema.</li>
      <li lang="id">Batasi sumber daya (memori dan penyimpanan) yang dikonsumsi mesin virtual Anda dari sistem Anda.</li>
      <li lang="hu">Az erőforrások (memória és tárhely) korlátozása, amelyet a virtuális gépei elvehetnek a rendszerétől.</li>
      <li lang="hr">Ograničite resurse (memoriju i pohranu) koje virtualni stroj koristi s vašeg računala.</li>
      <li lang="he">הגבלת המשאבים (זיכרון ואחסון) שהמכונות הווירטואליות שלך צורכות מהמערכת שלך.</li>
      <li lang="gl">Limite os recursos (memoria e almacenamento) que consumen as máquinas virtuais do seu sistema.</li>
      <li lang="fur">Limite lis risorsis (memorie e archiviazion) che lis tôs machinis virtuâls a consumin dal to sisteme.</li>
      <li lang="fr">Limitation des ressources (mémoire et stockage) que vos machines virtuelles consomment sur votre ordinateur.</li>
      <li lang="fi">Rajoita resursseja (muisti ja tallennustila), joita virtuaalikoneet voivat järjestelmältä käyttää.</li>
      <li lang="fa">محدود کردن منابع مصرفی (حافظه و ذخیره‌سازی) دستگاه مجازیتان از سامانه.</li>
      <li lang="eu">Mugatu zure makina birtualek zure sistematik kontsumitzen dituzten baliabideak (memoria eta biltegiratzea).</li>
      <li lang="es">Limitar los recursos (memoria y almacenamiento) que consumen sus máquinas virtuales de su sistema.</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Limit the resources (memory and storage) your virtual machines consume from your system.</li>
      <li lang="de">Schränken Sie die Ressourcen (Arbeitsspeicher und Speicher) ein, die virtuelle Maschinen auf Ihrem Rechner belegen.</li>
      <li lang="da">Begræns ressourcerne (hukommelse og lager) dine virtuelle maskiner bruger på dit system.</li>
      <li lang="cs">Omezení prostředků (paměť a úložiště), které virtuální stroje čerpají ze systému.</li>
      <li lang="ca">Limiteu els recursos del vostre sistema (memòria i emmagatzematge) que consumeix la vostra màquina virtual.</li>
      <li lang="bg">Ограничаване на ресурсите (памет и място за съхранение), които виртуалните машини ползват от системата.</li>
      <li>Take snapshots of virtual machines to restore to previous states.</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">对虚拟机进行快照以便方便地恢复先前的状态。</li>
      <li lang="uk">Створення знімків віртуальних машин для відновлення їхніх попередніх станів.</li>
      <li lang="tr">Önceki durumlara döndürmek için sanal makinelerin anlık görüntülerini alın.</li>
      <li lang="sv">Ta ögonblicksbilder av virtuella maskiner för att återställa till tidigare tillstånd.</li>
      <li lang="sr">Стварање снимака виртуелних машина за враћање на претходна стања.</li>
      <li lang="sk">Vytvorenie snímkov virtuálnych počítačov na obnovenie predchádzajúcich stavov.</li>
      <li lang="sl">Priprava posnetkov stanja navidezne naprave za obnovitev v predhodno stanje.</li>
      <li lang="ru">Делайте моментальные снимки виртуальных машин для восстановления предыдущих состояний.</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Criar capturas das máquinas virtuais para armazenar os estados anteriores.</li>
      <li lang="pt">Efetua imagens do sistema de máquinas virtuais para restaurar a estados anteriores.</li>
      <li lang="pl">Wykonywanie migawek maszyn wirtualnej do przywracania poprzednich stanów.</li>
      <li lang="lt">Padaro virtualių mašinų momentines kopijas jų ankstesnėms būsenoms atkurti.</li>
      <li lang="ko">가상 머신을 이전 상태로 되돌릴 스냅샷을 저장합니다.</li>
      <li lang="kk">Алдыңғы қалып-күйге қалпына келтіру үшін виртуалды машиналардың снапшоттарын жасау.</li>
      <li lang="it">Cattura istantanee delle macchine virtuali per ripristinare gli stati precedenti.</li>
      <li lang="id">Ambil snapshot dari mesin virtual untuk mengembalikan ke keadaan sebelumnya.</li>
      <li lang="hu">Pillanatképek készítése a virtuális gépekről az előző állapotok visszaállításához.</li>
      <li lang="hr">Stvorite snimke sustava virtualnih strojeva kako bi mogli vraćati na prijašnje stanje.</li>
      <li lang="he">לכידת תמונת המצב של המכונות הווירטואליות כדי לשחזר למצבים קודמים.</li>
      <li lang="gl">Tome instantáneas da súas máquinas virtuais para restaurar estados anteriores.</li>
      <li lang="fur">Fâs istantaniis di machinis virtuâls par ripristinâ ai stâts precedents.</li>
      <li lang="fr">Création d’instantanés de machines virtuelles pour les restaurer à des états antérieurs.</li>
      <li lang="fi">Ota tilannevedoksia virtuaalikoneista palataksesi aiempiin tilanteisiin.</li>
      <li lang="fa">گرفتن تصویرهای لحظه‌ای از دستگاه‌های مجازی برای بازگردانی به وضعیت‌های پیشین.</li>
      <li lang="eu">Egin makina birtualen bat-batekoak, lehenagoko egoeretara leheneratzeko.</li>
      <li lang="es">Hacer instantáneas de sus máquinas virtuales para recuperar estados anteriores.</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Take snapshots of virtual machines to restore to previous states.</li>
      <li lang="de">Schnappschüsse einer virtuellen Maschine erstellen, um auf vorherige Zustände zurückzufallen.</li>
      <li lang="da">Tag øjebliksbilleder af virtuelle maskiner for at gendanne til en tidligere tilstand.</li>
      <li lang="cs">Vytváření záloh virtuálních strojů pro obnovení předchozích stavů.</li>
      <li lang="ca">Feu una instantània de la vostra màquina virtual per a poder restaurar-la en qualsevol moment a un estat previ.</li>
      <li lang="bg">Снимки на състоянието на виртуалните машини, към които може да се връщате.</li>
      <li>Redirect USB devices from your physical machine into virtual machines.</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">将您的物理机器的 USB 设备重定向至虚拟机中。</li>
      <li lang="uk">Переспрямовування пристроїв USB з вашої фізичної машини до віртуальних машин.</li>
      <li lang="tr">USB aygıtlarını fiziksel makinenizden sanal makinelere yönlendirin.</li>
      <li lang="sv">Omdirigera USB-enheter från din fysiska maskin till virtuella maskiner.</li>
      <li lang="sr">Преусмеравање УСБ уређаја са ваше физичке машине у виртуелне машине.</li>
      <li lang="sk">Presmerovanie USB zariadení z vášho fyzického počítača do virtuálnych počítačov.</li>
      <li lang="sl">Preusmeritev naprav USB iz fizične na navidezne naprave.</li>
      <li lang="ru">Перенаправляйте USB-устройства с физической машины на виртуальные машины.</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Redirecionar dispositivos USB de sua máquina física para máquinas virtuais.</li>
      <li lang="pt">Redirecione dispositivos USB da sua máquina física para máquinas virtuais.</li>
      <li lang="pl">Przekierowywanie urządzeń USB z komputera do maszyn wirtualnych.</li>
      <li lang="lt">Nukreipia jūsų fizinio kompiuterio USB įrenginius į virtualias mašimas.</li>
      <li lang="ko">USB 장치의 입력 동작을 가상 머신으로 전달합니다.</li>
      <li lang="kk">USB құрылғыларын физикалық машинадан виртуалды машиналарға қайта бағыттау.</li>
      <li lang="it">Reindirizzamento dei dispositivi USB del proprio computer verso le macchine virtuali.</li>
      <li lang="id">Alihkan perangkat USB dari mesin fisik Anda ke mesin virtual.</li>
      <li lang="hu">USB eszközök átirányítása a fizikai gépről a virtuális gépekre.</li>
      <li lang="hr">Preusmjerite USB uređaje s vašeg fizičkog računala u virtualne strojeve.</li>
      <li lang="he">הפניית התקני USB מהמכונה הפיזית שלך למכונות וירטואליות.</li>
      <li lang="gl">Redirixa dispositivos USB desde súa máquina física ás máquinas virtuais.</li>
      <li lang="fur">Indrece i dispositîfs USB de to machine fisiche tes machinis virtuâls.</li>
      <li lang="fr">Redirection des périphériques USB de votre machine physique vers les machines virtuelles.</li>
      <li lang="fi">Uudelleenohjaa USB-laitteet fyysiseltä tietokoneelta virtuaalikoneille.</li>
      <li lang="fa">هدایت مستقیم افزاره‌های یو‌اس‌بی از دستگاه فیزیکیتان به دستگاه‌های مجازی.</li>
      <li lang="eu">Berbideratu USB gailuak zure makina fisikotik makina birtualetara.</li>
      <li lang="es">Redireccionar dispositivos USB de su máquina física a máquinas virtuales.</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Redirect USB devices from your physical machine into virtual machines.</li>
      <li lang="de">Leiten Sie USB-Geräte von Ihrem physischen Rechner in virtuelle Maschinen um.</li>
      <li lang="da">Omdirigér USB-enheder fra din fysiske maskine til virtuelle maskiner.</li>
      <li lang="cs">Přesměrování zařízení USB z fyzického stroje do virtuálního.</li>
      <li lang="ca">Redirigeix dispositius USB de la vostra màquina física a la màquina virtual.</li>
      <li lang="bg">Пренасочване на устройствата по USB от физическата към виртуалните машини.</li>
      <li>3D acceleration for some of the supported operating systems.</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">为某些支持的操作系统启用 3D 加速。</li>
      <li lang="uk">Прискорення просторової графіки для деяких із підтримуваних операційних систем.</li>
      <li lang="tr">Desteklenen bazı işletim sistemleri için 3B hızlandırma.</li>
      <li lang="sv">3D-acceleration för några av de operativsystem som stöds.</li>
      <li lang="sr">3Д убрзање за неке од подржаних оперативних система.</li>
      <li lang="sk">3D akcelerácia pre niektoré podporované operačné systémy.</li>
      <li lang="sl">Podpora za 3D pospeševanje nekaterih podprtih operacijskih sistemov.</li>
      <li lang="ru">3D-ускорение для некоторых поддерживаемых операционных систем.</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Aceleração 3D para alguns dos sistemas operacionais suportados.</li>
      <li lang="pt">Aceleração 3D para alguns dos sistemas operativos suportados.</li>
      <li lang="pl">Przyspieszenie 3D w części obsługiwanych systemów operacyjnych.</li>
      <li lang="lt">3D spartinimas kaikuriose palaikomose operacinėse sistemose.</li>
      <li lang="ko">일부 운영체제에서 3D 가속 기능을 지원합니다.</li>
      <li lang="kk">Кейбір қолдау көрсетілетін операциялық жүйелер үшін 3D үдетуі.</li>
      <li lang="it">Accelerazione 3D per alcuni dei sistemi operativi supportati.</li>
      <li lang="id">Akselerasi 3D untuk beberapa sistem operasi yang didukung.</li>
      <li lang="hu">3D gyorsítás néhány támogatott operációs rendszernél.</li>
      <li lang="hr">3D ubrzanje za određene podržane operativne sustave.</li>
      <li lang="he">האצה תלת־ממדית לחלק ממערכות ההפעלה הנתמכות.</li>
      <li lang="gl">Aceleración 3D para algúns dos sistemas operativos compatíbeis.</li>
      <li lang="fur">Acelerazion 3D par cualchi sisteme operatîf supuartât.</li>
      <li lang="fr">Accélération 3D pour certains des systèmes d’exploitation pris en charge.</li>
      <li lang="fi">3D-kiihdytys joillekin tuetuista käyttöjärjestelmistä.</li>
      <li lang="fa">شتاب‌دهی سه‌بعدی برای برخی سیستم‌عامل‌های پیشتیبانی شده.</li>
      <li lang="eu">3D azelerazioa sistema eragile batzuetarako.</li>
      <li lang="es">Aceleración 3D para algunos de los sistemas operativos soportados.</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">3D acceleration for some of the supported operating systems.</li>
      <li lang="de">3D-Beschleunigung für einige der unterstützten Betriebssysteme.</li>
      <li lang="da">3D-acceleration for nogle af de understøttede styresystemer.</li>
      <li lang="cs">3D akcelerace pro některé z podporovaných operačních systémů.</li>
      <li lang="ca">Acceleració 3D per a alguns dels sistemes operatius suportats.</li>
      <li lang="bg">Тримерно ускорение за някои от поддържаните операционни системи.</li>
      <li>Automatically resize virtual machines displays to the window size.</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">自动将虚拟机的显示大小调整为适合窗口大小。</li>
      <li lang="uk">Автоматичне зміна розмірів дисплеїв віртуальних машин до розмірів вікна.</li>
      <li lang="tr">Sanal makine ekranlarını pencere boyutuna kendiliğinden boyutlandır.</li>
      <li lang="sv">Ändra automatiskt storlek på virtuella maskiners skärmar till fönsterstorleken.</li>
      <li lang="sr">Самостално сразмеравање екрана виртуелних машина на величину прозора.</li>
      <li lang="sk">Automatická zmena veľkosti displejov virtuálnych počítačov podľa veľkosti okna.</li>
      <li lang="sl">Samodejno prilagajanje velikosti vmesnika navideznih naprav na velikost okna.</li>
      <li lang="ru">Автоматическое изменение размера дисплеев виртуальных машин в соответствии с размером окна.</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Redimensionar automaticamente telas de máquinas virtuais para o tamanho de janela.</li>
      <li lang="pt">Redimensionamento automático das máquinas virtuais para o tamanho da janela.</li>
      <li lang="pl">Automatyczne dopasowywanie ekranów maszyn wirtualnych do rozmiaru okna.</li>
      <li lang="lt">Automatiškai keičia virtualių mašinų vaizduoklius pagal lango dydį.</li>
      <li lang="ko">가상 머신 화면을 창 크기에 맞춰 자동으로 조정합니다.</li>
      <li lang="kk">Виртуалды машиналар экрандарын терезе өлшеміне автоматты түрде өзгерту.</li>
      <li lang="it">Ridimensionare automaticamente gli schermi delle macchine virtuali in base alle dimensioni della finestra.</li>
      <li lang="id">Secara otomatis mengubah ukuran layar mesin virtual ke ukuran jendela.</li>
      <li lang="hu">Virtuális gépek kijelzőinek automatikus átméretezése az ablak méretére.</li>
      <li lang="hr">Automatska promjena veličine zaslona virtualnih strojeva na veličinu prozora.</li>
      <li lang="he">שינוי אוטומטי של תצוגות המכונות הווירטואליות לגודל החלון.</li>
      <li lang="gl">Redimensionar as pantallas das máquinas virtuais automaticamente ao tamaño da xanela.</li>
      <li lang="fur">Ridimensione in automatic i schermis des machinis virtuâls ae dimension dal barcon.</li>
      <li lang="fr">Redimensionnement automatique des écrans des machines virtuelles ajusté à la taille de la fenêtre.</li>
      <li lang="fi">Muuta virtuaalikoneiden näyttöjen koko automaattisesti ikkunan kokoon.</li>
      <li lang="fa">تغییر خودکار اندازهٔ نمایشگر دستگاه‌های مجازی به اندازهٔ پنجره.</li>
      <li lang="eu">Automatikoki aldatu makina birtualen bistaratzeen tamaina leihoaren tamainara egokitzeko.</li>
      <li lang="es">Redimensionar automáticamente la pantalla de las máquinas virtuales al tamaño de la ventana.</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Automatically resize virtual machines displays to the window size.</li>
      <li lang="de">Die Anzeigengröße virtueller Maschinen automatisch an die Fenstergröße anpassen.</li>
      <li lang="da">Ændr automatisk størrelse på virtuelle maskiners skærme til vinduesstørrelsen.</li>
      <li lang="cs">Automatické přizpůsobení velikosti displeje virtuálních strojů podle velikosti okna.</li>
      <li lang="ca">La pantalla de la màquina virtual s'adapta automàticament a la mida de la finestra.</li>
      <li lang="bg">Автоматично преоразмеряване на екраните на виртуалните машини спрямо прозореца на визуализация.</li>
      <li>Share clipboard between your system and virtual machines.</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">在您的系统和虚拟机之间共享剪贴板。</li>
      <li lang="uk">Спільне використання буфера обміну даними вашою операційною системою і віртуальними машинами.</li>
      <li lang="tr">Sisteminiz ve sanal makineler arasında panoyu paylaşın.</li>
      <li lang="sv">Dela urklipp mellan ditt system och virtuella maskiner.</li>
      <li lang="sr">Подели оставу вашег система и виртуелних машина.</li>
      <li lang="sk">Zdieľanie schránky medzi vaším systémom a virtuálnymi počítačmi.</li>
      <li lang="sl">Souporaba odložišča med sistemom in navideznimi napravami.</li>
      <li lang="ru">Обменивайтесь буфером обмена между вашей системой и виртуальными машинами.</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Compartilhar área de transferência de seu sistema e sua máquinas virtuais.</li>
      <li lang="pt">Partilhar área de transferência entre o seu sistema e máquinas virtuais.</li>
      <li lang="pl">Udostępnianie schowka między komputerem a maszynami wirtualnymi.</li>
      <li lang="lt">Bendrina iškarpinę tarp jūsų sistemos ir virtualios mašinos.</li>
      <li lang="ko">시스템과 가상 머신의 클립보드를 공유합니다.</li>
      <li lang="kk">Жүйе мен виртуалды машиналар арасында алмасу буферін ортақ пайдалану.</li>
      <li lang="it">Condividi gli appunti tra il sistema e le macchine virtuali.</li>
      <li lang="id">Bagikan papan klip antara sistem Anda dan mesin virtual.</li>
      <li lang="hu">Vágólap megosztása a rendszere és a virtuális gépek között.</li>
      <li lang="hr">Dijelite međuspremnik između vašeg računala i virtualnih strojeva.</li>
      <li lang="he">שיתוף לוח הגזירים בין המערכת שלך והמכונות הווירטואליות.</li>
      <li lang="gl">Compartir o portapapeis entre o seu sistema e as máquinas virtuais</li>
      <li lang="fur">Condivît lis notis tra il sisteme e lis machinis virtuâls.</li>
      <li lang="fr">Presse-papiers partagé entre votre ordinateur et les machines virtuelles.</li>
      <li lang="fi">Jaa leikepöytä järjestelmän ja virtuaalikoneiden välillä.</li>
      <li lang="fa">هم‌رسانی تخته‌گیره بین دستگاه‌های مجازی و سامانه‌تان.</li>
      <li lang="eu">Partekatu arbela sistemaren eta makina birtualen artean.</li>
      <li lang="es">Compartir el portapapeles entre su sistema y las máquinas virtuales.</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Share clipboard between your system and virtual machines.</li>
      <li lang="de">Die Zwischenablage mit Ihrem System und der virtuellen Maschine gemeinsam verwenden.</li>
      <li lang="da">Del udklipsholderen mellem dit system og dine virtuelle maskiner.</li>
      <li lang="cs">Sdílení schránky mezi systémem a virtuálními strojem.</li>
      <li lang="ca">Compartiu el porta-retalls entre el vostre sistema i la màquina virtual.</li>
      <li lang="bg">Споделяне на буфера за обмен между физическата и виртуалните машини.</li>
      <li>Share files to virtual machines by dropping them from your file manager into the Boxes window.</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">只需从您的文件管理器中拖曳文件至盒子窗口即可将文件共享给虚拟机。</li>
      <li lang="uk">Надання файлів віртуальним машинам скиданням їх з вікна вашої програми для керування файлами до вікна «Коробок».</li>
      <li lang="tr">Dosyaları, dosya yöneticinizden Kutular penceresine bırakarak paylaşın.</li>
      <li lang="sv">Dela filer till virtuella maskiner genom att släppa dem från din filhanterare till Boxes-fönstret.</li>
      <li lang="sr">Дељење датотека ка виртуелним машинама једноставним превлачењем из вашег управника датотека на прозор Кутија.</li>
      <li lang="sk">Sprístupnenie súborov virtuálnym počítačom ich pustením do okna aplikácie Boxy z vášho správcu súborov.</li>
      <li lang="sl">Souporaba datotek z navideznimi napravami z enostavnim potegom iz upravljalnika datotek v okno Škatel.</li>
      <li lang="ru">Предоставляйте виртуальным машинам общий доступ к файлам, сбросив их из файлового менеджера в окно Boxes.</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Compartilhar arquivos com máquinas virtuais arrastando e soltando-os a partir de seu gerenciador de arquivos para a janela do Boxes.</li>
      <li lang="pt">Partilhe ficheiros em máquinas virtuais, ao larga-los do seu gestor de ficheiros para a janela do Caixas.</li>
      <li lang="pl">Udostępnianie plików maszynom wirtualnym przez przeciąganie ich z menedżera plików do okna programu Boxes.</li>
      <li lang="lt">Bendrina failus su virtualiomis mašinomis juos nutempiant iš jūsų failų tvarkyklės į Dėžių langą.</li>
      <li lang="ko">파일 관리자에서 박스 창으로 파일을 끌어다 놓아 가상머신과 파일을 공유합니다.</li>
      <li lang="kk">Файл менеджерінен Бокстар терезесіне тастау арқылы виртуалды машиналармен файлдармен бөлісу.</li>
      <li lang="it">Condividi i file rilasciandoli dal gestore di file nelle finestre delle macchine virtuali.</li>
      <li lang="id">Bagikan berkas ke mesin virtual dengan menjatuhkannya dari pengelola berkas Anda ke jendela Boxes.</li>
      <li lang="hu">Fájlok megosztása a virtuális gépek számára a fájlkezelőjéből a Gépek ablakára történő ejtésükkel.</li>
      <li lang="hr">Dijelite datoteke s virtualnim strojevima povlačenjem i ispuštanjem iz vašeg preglednika datoteka u prozor Bokseva.</li>
      <li lang="he">שיתוף קבצים למכונות וירטואליות על ידי גרירתם ממנהל הקבצים שלך לחלון של קופסאות.</li>
      <li lang="gl">Compartir ficheiros coas máquinas virtuais soltándoos desde o seu sistema de ficheiros na xanela de Caixas.</li>
      <li lang="fur">Condivît i files cu lis machinis virtuâls molant i files dal to gjestôr di files al barcon di Scjatulis.</li>
      <li lang="fr">Partage de fichiers sur les machines virtuelles en les déposant depuis votre gestionnaire de fichiers dans la fenêtre de Machines.</li>
      <li lang="fi">Jaa tiedostoja virtuaalikoneille pudottamalla tiedostot tiedostohallinnasta Boksit-ikkunaan.</li>
      <li lang="fa">هم‌رسانی پرونده با دستگاه‌های مجازی با رها کردنشان از مدیر پرونده‌تان به پنجرهٔ جعبه‌ها.</li>
      <li lang="eu">Partekatu fitxategiak makina birtualekin haiek zure fitxategi-kudeatzailetik Makinak leihora eramanda.</li>
      <li lang="es">Compartir archivos con máquinas virtuales arrastrándolos desde su gestor de archivos a la ventana de Cajas.</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Share files to virtual machines by dropping them from your file manager into the Boxes window.</li>
      <li lang="de">Teilen Sie Dateien mit virtuellen Maschinen, indem Sie diese von der Dateiverwaltung in das »Boxen«-Fenster ziehen.</li>
      <li lang="da">Del filer med virtuelle maskiner ved at trække dem fra din filhåndtering og slippe dem i Boxes-vinduet.</li>
      <li lang="cs">Sdílení souborů s virtuálními stroji jejich přetažením ze správce souborů do okna Boxů.</li>
      <li lang="ca">Compartiu fitxers a la màquina virtual arrossegant-los des del vostre gestor de fitxers fins a la finestra del Màquines.</li>
      <li lang="bg">Споделяне на файлове с виртуалните машини чрез завлачването им от програма за управление на файлове към прозореца на Boxes.</li>
      <li>Setup Shared Folders between your system and virtual machines.</li>
      <li lang="zh_CN">设置在您的系统和虚拟机之间共享的目录。</li>
      <li lang="uk">Налаштовування спільних тек для вашої операційної системи та віртуальних машин.</li>
      <li lang="tr">Sisteminiz ve sanal makineler arasında Paylaşılan Klasörler kurun.</li>
      <li lang="sv">Konfigurera delade mappar mellan ditt system och virtuella maskiner.</li>
      <li lang="sr">Подешавање дељених фасцикли између вашег система и виртуелних машина.</li>
      <li lang="sk">Nastavenie sprístupnených priečinkov medzi vaším systémom a virtuálnymi počítačmi.</li>
      <li lang="sl">Nastavitev map souporabe med sistemom in navideznimi napravami.</li>
      <li lang="ru">Настраивайте общие папки между вашей системой и виртуальными машинами.</li>
      <li lang="pt_BR">Configurar pastas compartilhadas entre seu sistema e máquinas virtuais.</li>
      <li lang="pt">Configuração de Pastas Partilhadas entre o seu sistema e máquinas virtuais.</li>
      <li lang="pl">Konfiguracja udostępnianych katalogów między komputerem a maszynami wirtualnymi.</li>
      <li lang="lt">Nustato bendrinamus aplankus tarp jūsų sistemos ir virtualių mašinų.</li>
      <li lang="ko">시스템과 가상 머신이 공유할 폴더를 설정합니다.</li>
      <li lang="kk">Жүйеңіз бен виртуалды машиналар арасында ортақ бумаларды баптау.</li>
      <li lang="it">Configura le cartelle condivise tra il sistema e le macchine virtuali.</li>
      <li lang="id">Siapkan Folder Bersama antara sistem dan mesin virtual Anda.</li>
      <li lang="hu">Megosztott mappák beállítása a rendszere és a virtuális gépek között.</li>
      <li lang="hr">Postavljanje dijeljenih mapa između vašeg računala i virtualnih strojeva.</li>
      <li lang="he">הגדרת תיקיות משותפות בין המערכת והמכונות הווירטואליות שלך.</li>
      <li lang="gl">Configurar Cartafoles compartidos entre o seu sistema e as máquinas virtuais.</li>
      <li lang="fur">Configure cartelis condividudis tra il sisteme e lis machinis virtuâls.</li>
      <li lang="fr">Configuration des dossiers partagés entre votre ordinateur et les machines virtuelles.</li>
      <li lang="fi">Aseta jaettuja kansioita järjestelmän ja virtuaalikoneiden välille.</li>
      <li lang="fa">برپایی شاخه‌های هم‌رسانده بین دستگاه‌های مجازی و سامانه‌تان.</li>
      <li lang="eu">Konfiguratu zure sistemak eta makina birtualek partekatzen dituzten karpetak.</li>
      <li lang="es">Configurar carpetas compartidas entre su sistema y las máquinas virtuales.</li>
      <li lang="en_GB">Setup Shared Folders between your system and virtual machines.</li>
      <li lang="de">Gemeinsame Ordner zwischen Ihrem System und der virtuellen Maschine einrichten.</li>
      <li lang="da">Opret delte mapper mellem dit system og dine virtuelle maskiner.</li>
      <li lang="cs">Nastavení sdílené složky mezi vaším systémem a virtuálními stroji.</li>
      <li lang="ca">Configureu carpetes compartides entre el vostre sistema i la màquina virtual.</li>
      <li lang="bg">Настройване на споделени папки между физическата и виртуалните машини.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-boxes-logos/-/raw/master/screenshots/gnome-42/01-icon-view.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-boxes-logos/-/raw/master/screenshots/gnome-42/02-display-view.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-boxes-logos/-/raw/master/screenshots/gnome-42/03-preferences-dialog.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-boxes-logos/-/raw/master/screenshots/gnome-42/04-vm-creation-assistant.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="42.3" date="2022-07-07" />
    <release date="2022-07-01" version="42.2" />
    <release date="2022-05-30" version="42.1" />
    <release version="42.0" date="2022-03-18">
      <p>GNOME Boxes 42.0 is the result of six months of bugfixes, performance improvements, and feature development including:</p>
      <ul>
        <li>New virtual machine preferences dialog simplifying resource tweaking, debugging, device and snapshot management</li>
        <li>Various user experience improvements in the virtual machine creation assistant</li>
        <li>Allow for enabling UEFI for operating systems known to support it</li>
        <li>Improvements in the icon and list view for managing your virtual machine collection</li>
        <li>Updated translations</li>
      </ul>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>AppMenu</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>HighContrast</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>SearchProvider</kudo>
    <kudo>UserDocs</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <provides>
    <binary>gnome-boxes</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.Boxes.desktop</launchable>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <developer_name>The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">GNOME 專案</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 项目</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="vi">Dự án GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Проєкт GNOME </developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">GNOME Projesi</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Гном пројекат</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Проект GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Proiectul GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਪਰੋਜੈਕਟ</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="oc">Lo projècte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Het Gnome-project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ne">जिनोम परियोजना</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb">GNOME prosjektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ms">Projek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lv">GNOME projekts</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">GNOME projektas</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">그놈 프로젝트</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="kk">GNOME жобасы</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Il progetto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Proyek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">מיזם GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">O proxecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fur">Il progjet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Le projet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Gnome-projekti</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fa">پروژهٔ گنوم</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">GNOME proiektua</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">El Proyecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">La GNOME Projekto</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Το έργο GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Das GNOME-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="bg">Проектът GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="af">Die GNOME-projek</developer_name>
  <update_contact>felipeborges_at_gnome.org</update_contact>
  <url type="homepage">https://gnomeboxes.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-boxes/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">http://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <url type="help">https://help.gnome.org/users/gnome-boxes/stable/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://wiki.gnome.org/TranslationProject</url>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-boxes</translation>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <custom>
    <value key="GnomeSoftware::key-colors">[(143, 124, 209)]</value>
  </custom>
</component>