<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>gnome.gnome-screenshot</pkgname>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">org.gnome.Screenshot.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">org.gnome.Screenshot.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.Screenshot.desktop</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.Screenshot.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Screenshot</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">螢幕擷圖</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">螢幕擷圖</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">截图</name>
  <name lang="xh">Umfanekiso weskrini</name>
  <name lang="vi">Chụp màn hình</name>
  <name lang="uk">Знімок екрана</name>
  <name lang="ug">ئېكران كۆرۈنۈشى</name>
  <name lang="tr">Ekran Görüntüsü</name>
  <name lang="th">จับภาพหน้าจอ</name>
  <name lang="tg">Сурати экран</name>
  <name lang="te">తెరపట్టు</name>
  <name lang="ta">ஸ்கிரீன்ஷாட்</name>
  <name lang="sv">Skärmbild</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Snimač ekrana</name>
  <name lang="sr">Снимач екрана</name>
  <name lang="sl">Zaslonska slika</name>
  <name lang="sk">Snímka obrazovky</name>
  <name lang="ru">Снимок экрана</name>
  <name lang="ro">Captură de ecran</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Captura de tela</name>
  <name lang="pt">Captura de ecrã</name>
  <name lang="pl">Zrzut ekranu</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਸਕਰੀਨ-ਸ਼ਾਟ</name>
  <name lang="or">ଆଶୁଚିତ୍ର</name>
  <name lang="oc">Captura d'ecran</name>
  <name lang="nl">Schermafdruk</name>
  <name lang="ne">स्क्रिनसट</name>
  <name lang="nb">Skjermbilde</name>
  <name lang="ms">Tangkap layar</name>
  <name lang="mr">स्क्रीनशॉट</name>
  <name lang="ml">സ്ക്രീന്‍ഷോട്ട്</name>
  <name lang="lv">Ekrānattēls</name>
  <name lang="lt">Nuotrauka</name>
  <name lang="ko">스크린샷</name>
  <name lang="kn">ತೆರೆಚಿತ್ರ</name>
  <name lang="km">រូបថតអេក្រង់</name>
  <name lang="kk">Скриншот</name>
  <name lang="ja">スクリーンショット</name>
  <name lang="it">Schermata</name>
  <name lang="is">Skjámynd</name>
  <name lang="id">Cuplikan layar</name>
  <name lang="hu">Képernyőkép</name>
  <name lang="hr">Slikanje zaslona</name>
  <name lang="hi">स्क्रीनशॉट</name>
  <name lang="he">צילום מסך</name>
  <name lang="gu">સ્ક્રીનશોટ</name>
  <name lang="gl">Captura de pantalla</name>
  <name lang="gd">Glacadh-sgrìn</name>
  <name lang="ga">Gabháil Scáileáin</name>
  <name lang="fur">Cature de schermade</name>
  <name lang="fr">Capture d’écran</name>
  <name lang="fi">Kuvakaappaus</name>
  <name lang="fa">نماگرفت</name>
  <name lang="eu">Pantaila-argazkia</name>
  <name lang="et">Ekraanipilt</name>
  <name lang="es">Captura de pantalla</name>
  <name lang="eo">Ekrankopio</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Screenshot</name>
  <name lang="el">Στιγμιότυπο οθόνης</name>
  <name lang="de">Bildschirmfoto</name>
  <name lang="da">Skærmbillede</name>
  <name lang="cs">Snímek obrazovky</name>
  <name lang="crh">Ekran-körüntisi</name>
  <name lang="ckb">وێنەی شاشە</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">Captura</name>
  <name lang="ca">Captura</name>
  <name lang="bs">Snimak ekrana</name>
  <name lang="bn_IN">স্ক্রিন-শট</name>
  <name lang="bg">Снимка на екрана</name>
  <name lang="be">Экранны здымак</name>
  <name lang="ast">Captura pantalla</name>
  <name lang="as">স্ক্ৰিনশ্বট</name>
  <name lang="ar">لقطة الشاشة</name>
  <name lang="an">Captura de pantalla</name>
  <name lang="af">Skermskoot</name>
  <summary>Save images of your screen or individual windows</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">將整個桌面或獨立的視窗儲存為影片</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_HK">將整個桌面或獨立的視窗儲存為影片</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">将您的屏幕或单个窗口保存为图像</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Ghi lại ảnh của cả màn hình hay chỉ từng cửa sổ riêng biệt</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Зберегти зображення екрана або окремого вікна</summary>
  <summary lang="ug">بۇ ئېكران ياكى مەلۇم بىر كۆزنەكنى سۈرەت قىلىپ ساقلايدىغان پروگراممىدۇر</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Masaüstünüzün veya pencerelerinizin görüntülerini kaydedin</summary>
  <summary lang="th">บันทึกภาพของหน้าจอหรือหน้าต่างที่กำหนด</summary>
  <summary lang="tg">Тасвирҳои экранҳои худ ё равзанаҳои мушаххасро захира кунед</summary>
  <summary lang="te">మీ తెర లేదా వ్యక్తిగత కిటికీల యొక్క బొమ్మలను భద్రపరుచుకోండి</summary>
  <summary lang="ta">உங்கள் பணிமேடையின்  அல்லது தனித்தனி சாளரங்களின் படங்களை சேமிக்கவும்</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Spara bilder av din skärm eller individuella fönster</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Sačuvajte slike vašeg ekrana ili pojedinačnih prozora</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Сачувајте слике вашег екрана или појединачних прозора</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Zajemanje slik zaslona ali posameznih oken</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Ukladá obrázky vašej obrazovky alebo jednotlivých okien</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Сохранить изображение с экрана или отдельных окон</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Salvează imagini ale ecranului sau ale unor ferestre individuale</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Salve imagens da sua tela ou de janelas individuais</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Grave imagens do seu ecrã ou de janelas individuais</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Zapisywanie obrazów pulpitu lub poszczególnych okien</summary>
  <summary lang="pa">ਆਪਣੀ ਸਕਰੀਨ ਜਾਂ ਅੱਡ-ਅੱਡ ਵਿੰਡੋਜ਼ ਦੇ ਚਿੱਤਰ ਸੰਭਾਲੋ</summary>
  <summary lang="or">ଆପଣଙ୍କ ପରଦା କିମ୍ବା ବ୍ଯକ୍ତିଗତ ୱିଣ୍ଡୋର ପ୍ରତିଛବିକୁ ସଂରକ୍ଷଣ କରନ୍ତୁ</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Enregistra los imatges de vòstre ecran o de vòstras fenèstras individualas</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Afbeeldingen van uw bureaublad of vensters maken</summary>
  <summary lang="ne">तपाईंको पर्दा वा व्यक्तिगत सन्झ्यालको छविहरू बचत गर्नुहोस्</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Lagre bilder av innholdet på skjermen eller i individuelle vinduer</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Simpan imej skrin atau tetingkap individu anda</summary>
  <summary lang="mr">पडद्याचे किंवा परस्पर पटलांची प्रतिमा साठवा</summary>
  <summary lang="ml">നിങ്ങളുടെ സ്ക്രീനിന്റെ അല്ലെങ്കില്‍ ഓരോ ജാലകങ്ങളുടെ ചിത്രങ്ങള്‍ സൂക്ഷിക്കുക</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Saglabā darbvirsmas vai logu attēlus</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Įrašyti jūsų darbalaukio ar atskirų langų nuotraukas</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">화면이나 개별 창의 이미지를 저장합니다</summary>
  <summary lang="kn">ನಿಮ್ಮ ತೆರೆಯನ್ನು ಅಥವ ಪ್ರತ್ಯೇಕ ಕಿಟಕಿಗಳ ಚಿತ್ರಗಳನ್ನು ಉಳಿಸಿ</summary>
  <summary lang="km">រក្សាទុករូបភាពនៃអេក្រង់របស់អ្នក ឬវីនដូនីមួយៗ</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">Толық экран немесе бөлек терезелер скриншоттарын сақтау</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">画面またはウィンドウの画像を保存します</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Salva immagini dello schermo o di singole finestre</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Vista myndir af skjáborðinu þínu eða af einstökum gluggum</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Menyimpan gambar layar atau jendela tertentu</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">A képernyő vagy egyedi ablakok képeinek mentése</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Spremite slike vašeg zaslona ili određenih prozora</summary>
  <summary lang="hi">अपने स्क्रीन या निजी विंडो के चित्र को सहेजें</summary>
  <summary lang="he">שמירת תמונות של שולחן העבודה או של חלונות בנפרד</summary>
  <summary lang="gu">તમારા સ્ક્રીન અથવા વ્યક્તિગત વિન્ડોના ચિત્રો સંગ્રહો</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Gardar imaxes da súa pantalla ou de xanelas individuais</summary>
  <summary lang="gd">Sàbhail dealbhan dhen sgrìn agad no de dh’uinneagan fa leth</summary>
  <summary lang="ga">Sábháil íomhánna do scáileáin nó fhuinneog aonair</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Salve imagjins dal to visôr o di ugnui barcons</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Enregistrer les images de votre écran ou de vos fenêtres individuelles</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Tallenna kuvia työpöydästä tai yksittäisistä ikkunoista</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">ذخیرهٔ تصویرها از صفحه‌تان یا پنجره‌های تکی</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Gorde mahaigainaren edo banakako leihoen irudiak</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Ekraanist või üksikutest akendest pildi salvestamine</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Guarde imágenes de su pantalla o de ventanas individuales</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Konservi bildojn de via ekrano aŭ de unuopaj fenestroj</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Save images of your screen or individual windows</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Αποθηκεύστε στιγμιότυπα της οθόνης σας ή ξεχωριστά παράθυρα</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Bildschirmfotos Ihres Bildschirms oder einzelner Fenster speichern</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Gem billeder af din skærm eller individuelle vinduer</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Uložit obrázky pracovní plochy nebo konkrétních oken</summary>
  <summary lang="crh">Ekranıñız ya da ferdiy pencereleriñizniñ suretlerini saqla</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Guarda imatges de la pantalla o de finestres individuals</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Deseu imatges de la pantalla o de finestres individuals</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Sačuvajte slike vašeg ekrana ili pojedinačnih prozora</summary>
  <summary lang="bn_IN">পর্দা অথবা স্বতন্ত্র উইন্ডোর ছবি সংরক্ষণ করুন</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Запазване на снимки на екрана или индивидуални прозорци</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Захаванне здымкаў экрана ці асобных вокнаў</summary>
  <summary lang="as">আপোনাৰ পৰ্দা অথবা স্বতন্ত্ৰ উইন্ডোসমূহৰ ছবি সংৰক্ষণ কৰক</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">احفظ صور لشاشتك أو للنوافذ المنفردة</summary>
  <summary lang="an">Alce imachens d'a suya pantalla u de finestras individuals</summary>
  <summary lang="af">Stoor beelde van die skerm of individuele vensters</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Screenshot is a simple utility that lets you take pictures of your computer screen.
      Screenshots can be of your whole screen, any specific application, or a selected
      rectangular area.
      You can also copy the captured screenshot directly into the GNOME clipboard and
      paste it into other applications.
    </p>
    <p>
      Screenshot allows you to take screenshots even when it’s not open: just
      press the PrtSc button on your keyboard, and a snapshot of your whole screen will
      be saved to your Pictures folder.
      Hold Alt while pressing PrtSc and you will get a screenshot of only the currently
      selected window.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>La captura de pantalla és una utilitat senzilla que us permet fer fotos de la pantalla de l'ordinador. Les captures de pantalla poden ser de tota la pantalla, de qualsevol aplicació específica o d'una àrea rectangular seleccionada. També podeu copiar la captura de pantalla capturada directament al porta-retalls del GNOME i enganxar-la a altres aplicacions.</p>
    <p>La captura de pantalla us permet fer captures de pantalla fins i tot quan no està oberta: només heu de prémer el botó PrtSc del teclat i es desarà una instantània de tota la pantalla a la carpeta Imatges. Manteniu premuda Alt mentre premeu PrtSc i obtindreu una captura de pantalla de la finestra seleccionada.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fa">
    <p>نماگرفت، ابزاری ساده است که می‌گذارد از صفحهٔ رایانه‌تان عکس بگیرید. نماگرفت‌ها می‌توانند از تمام صفحه‌تان، برنامه‌ای خاص یا ناحیه‌ای گزیده باشند. همچنین می‌توانید نماگرفت را مستقیماً در تخته‌گیرهٔ گنوم رونویسی و در برنامه‌های دیگر بچسبانید.</p>
    <p>نماگرفت می‌گذارد حتا هنگام بسته بودنش، از صفحه عکس بگیرید: تنها دکمهٔ نماگرفت را روی صفحه‌کلیدتان فشرده و تصویری از تمام صفحه‌تان در شاخهٔ تصاویر ذخیره می‌شود. هنگام فشردننماگرفت، دگرساز را گرفته تا تنها از پنجرهٔ گزیده عکس بگیرید.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Cature de schermade al è un sempliç program che al permet di scatâ imagjins dal visôr dal computer. Lis imagjins caturadis a puedin jessi di dut il visôr, une specifiche aplicazion o une aree retangolâr selezionade. Al è pussibil ancje copiâ la schermade apene caturade intes notis e incolâle in altris aplicazions.</p>
    <p>Cature de schermade al permet di caturâ imagjins ancje cuant che la aplicazion no je in esecuzion: frache il tast Stamp (o PrtScr) par salvâ une istantanie dal visôr che e vignarà salvade te cartele Imagjins. Tignint fracât il tast Alt adun cun Stamp tu varâs une schermade nome dal barcon atualmentri selezionât.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>‫GNOME צילום מסך הוא כלי פשוט שמאפשר לך לצלם את צג המחשב שלך. ניתן לצלם את המסך כולו, יישום מסוים או סתם אזור מלבני. אפשר גם להעתיק את הצילום ישירות ללוח הגזירים של GNOME ולהדביק ביישומים אחרים.</p>
    <p>‏צילום מסך מאפשר לך לצלם את המסך גם כאשר אינו פתוח: כל שעליך לעשות הוא ללחוץ על מקש ה־PrtSc במקלדת שלך, ותמונה של כל המסך שלך תישמר בתיקיית התמונות שלך. לחיצה על Alt בזמן לחיצה על PrtSc תביא לצילום החלון הנוכחי בלבד.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Slikanje zaslona je jednostavan alat koji vam omogućuje uslikavanje zaslona vašeg računala. Uslikati možete cijeli zaslon, određenu apliakciju ili odabrano područje zaslona. Možete i kopirati sliku zaslona izravno u GNOME međuspremnik i zalijepiti ju u neku drugu aplikaciju.</p>
    <p>Slikanje zaslona omogućuje vam uslikavanje čak i ako nije otvoren. Jednostavno pritisnite PrtSc tipku na vašoj tipkovnici i snimak vašeg cijelog zaslona će bit spremljen u vašu mapu Slika. Držite pritisnutim Alt dok pritiskate PrtSc i dobiti ćete snimku trenutno odabranog prozora.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>Captura d'ecran es un utilitari per vos permetre de prene de capturas d'ecran aisidament. Aquelas capturas pòdon concernir vòstre ecran entièr, una aplicacion en particular o una zòna que definissètz. Podètz tanben copiar la captura dirèctament dins lo quichapapiers de GNOME e la pegar dins una autra aplicacion.</p>
    <p>Captura d'ecran vos permet de prene de capturas d'ecran quitament se es pas aviada : quichatz simplament sul boton Impr. ecran sus vòstre clavièr e l'integralitat de vòstre ecran serà salvat al vòstre dorsièr Imatges. Mantenètz la tòca Alt en meteis temps que Impr. ecran e sola la fenèstra en cors serà enregistrada.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>A Captura de ecrã é uma aplicação utilitária simples que permite tirar fotografias do ecrã do computador. As capturas podem ser do ecrã inteiro, de uma aplicação específica ou de uma área retangular selecionada por si. Também pode enviar a captura para a área de transferência do GNOME e colá-la noutras aplicações.</p>
    <p>A Captura de ecrã pode ser usada mesmo quando não está aberta: basta premir a tecla PrtSc e uma fotografia do ecrã inteiro será gravada na pasta Imagens. Manter a tecla Alt premida e premir PrtSc para obter uma fotografia da janela atualmente selecionada.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Skärmbild är ett enkelt verktyg som låter dig ta bilder av din datorskärm. Skärmbilder kan täcka hela din skärm, ett specifikt program eller en vald rektangulär yta. Du kan även kopiera den infångade skärmbilden direkt till GNOME:s urklipp och klistra in den i andra program.</p>
    <p>Skärmbild låter dig ta skärmbilder även när det inte är öppet: tryck bara på PrtSc-knappen på ditt tangentbord så kommer en skärmbild av hela din skärm att sparas till din mapp Bilder. Om du håller ner Alt medan du trycker på PrtSc så kommer du att få en skärmbild av det för närvarande valda fönstret.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>«Знімок» — простенька програмка, що дозволяє робити знімки з вашого екрана. Знімки можуть бути всього екрана, вказаної програми або квадратної ділянки. Ви можете також копіювати та захоплювати знімки напряму в буфер обміну GNOME і вставляти в інші програми.</p>
    <p>«Знімок» надає змогу робити знімки, навіть якщо він не відритий: просто натисніть клавішу PrtSc на вашій клавіатурі й знімок усього екрана буде збережено у теці «Картинки». Утримуйте Alt і натисніть PrtSc, щоб одержати знімок тільки вибраного вікна.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="vi">
    <p>Chụp màn hình là một tiện ích đơn giản để giúp bạn chụp ảnh từ màn hình của máy tính. Chụp có thể là toàn màn hình, bất kỳ ứng dụng cụ thể, hay có thể chọn một vùng hình chữ nhật. Bạn còn có thể chép ảnh chụp trực tiếp vào clipboard của GNOME và dán nó vào ứng dụng khác.</p>
    <p>Chụp màn hình cho phép bạn chụp màn hình ngay cả khi nó không được mở: chỉ cần bấm phím PrtSc trên bàn phím, và một bản chụp toàn bộ màn hình sẽ được lưu vào thư mục dành để lưu "Ảnh". Giữ phím Alt trong khi ấn PrtSc và bạn sẽ chụp cửa sổ hiện đang được kích hoạt.</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-screenshot</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-screenshot/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">http://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-screenshot/-/raw/master/data/screenshots/gnome-screenshot-3.38-1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-screenshot/-/raw/master/data/screenshots/gnome-screenshot-3.38-2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <releases>
    <release urgency="medium" date="2021-11-13" version="41.0" type="stable">
      <description>
        <p>Drop support for non-unique mode in headless instance</p>
        <p>metainfo: Align app name with .desktop name</p>
        <p>Translation updates</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="40.0" type="stable" urgency="medium" date="2021-03-20">
      <description>
        <p>Move sound effects to gnome-shell</p>
        <p>Focus the filename entry by default</p>
        <p>Remember delay for area screenshots</p>
        <p>Remove compulsory_for_desktop</p>
        <p>metainfo: add a launchable tag</p>
        <p>Translation updates</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-09-10" type="stable" urgency="medium" version="3.38.0">
      <description>
        <p>Changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Completely redesign the UI</li>
          <li>Port to libhandy</li>
          <li>Allow taking area screenshots with timeout</li>
          <li>Deprecate --include-border and --remove-border options</li>
          <li>Deprecate --border-effect option</li>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release urgency="medium" version="3.36.0" type="stable" date="2020-03-10">
      <description>
        <p>Translation updates.</p>
        <p lang="ckb">نوێکارییەکانی وەرگێڕان.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <update_contact>ebassi@gnome.org</update_contact>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-screenshot</translation>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0" />
</component>