<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>gnome-keysign</pkgname>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">org.gnome.Keysign.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" height="128" width="128">org.gnome.Keysign.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.Keysign</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Keysign</name>
  <summary>OpenPGP Keysigning helper</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      GNOME Keysign allows signing OpenPGP keys comfortably and securely
      via the local network or Bluetooth.
    </p>
    <p>
      It can scan another key's barcode and transfer the key securely,
      allowing for casual two-party key signing sessions.
      It follows best practises by sending the encrypted signatures
      to the UIDs of a key using the Email client the user configured
      to use.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>
Umí číst čárový kód jiného klíče a klíče bezpečně přenášet, což se hodí pro dvoustranné podepisování klíčů. Drží se osvědčené praxe posílání šifrovaných podpisů do UID klíče pomocí e-mailového klienta, kterého pro daný účel uživatel nastavil.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>
      GNOME Nøgleunderskriver gør det muligt at underskrive OpenPGP-nøgler
      komfortabelt og sikkert via det lokale netværk eller Bluetooth.
    </p>
    <p>
      Den kan skanne andre nøglers stregkode og overføre nøglen sikkert,
      hvilket giver afslappede nøgleunderskrivningssessioner mellem to parter.
      Den følger bedste praksisser ved at sende de krypterede underskrifter
      til UID'erne af en nøgle med den e-mailklient brugeren har
      konfigureret.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>
      Das Programm scannt den Barcode eines anderen Schlüssels und überträgt
      den Schlüssel sicher, was spontane Signierpartys zu zweit ermöglicht. Es hält
      sich dabei an die übliche Vorgehensweise. So schickt es die verschlüsselten
      Signaturen als E-Mail-Anhang an die Benutzerkennungen des Schlüssels unter
      Benutzung des E-Mail-Clients, den der Benutzer schon eingerichtet hat.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es_ES">
    <p>
      GNOME-Keysign permite firmar llaves OpenPGP de manera cómoda y segura
      a través de la red local o Bluetooth.
    </p>
    <p>
      Puede escanear el código de barra de otra llave y transferirla
      de manera segura, permitiendo sesiones casuales bipartitas de firma de llave.
      Siga buenas prácticas al enviar las firmas cifradas a los UID
      de una llave usando el cliente de correo configurado por
      el usuario.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>
      Il peut lire le code-barre d’une autre clé et transférer la clé
      de façon sûre, permettant des sessions de signature de clés bipartites.
      Il suit les bonnes pratiques en envoyant les signatures chiffrées aux
      identifiants UID d’une clé avec le client de messagerie configuré par
      l’utilisateur.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>
      Al pues scansionâ un codiç a sbaris di une altre clâf e trasferî la 
      clâf in sigurece, permetint a dôs personis di fâ sessions casuâls di firme des clâfs.
      Al seguìs il miôr costum di inviâ lis firmis cifradis
      al UIDs di une clâf doprant il client E-mail che l'utent al à configurât
      di doprâ.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>
      A GNOME Kulcsaláíró lehetővé teszi, hogy OpenPGP kulcsokat írjon
      alá kényelmesen és biztonságosan a helyi hálózaton vagy
      Bluetoothon keresztül.
    </p>
    <p>
      Képes leolvasni egy másik kulcs vonalkódját, és biztonságosan
      átküldeni a kulcsot, így egyszerű kétszereplős kulcsaláírást
      biztosít. Követi a legjobb gyakorlatokat azáltal, hogy a
      felhasználó által beállított levelezőprogramot használja a
      kulcs UID-jaihoz tartozó titkosított aláírások elküldéséhez.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>
      GNOME-Keysign memungkinkan penandatanganan kunci OpenPGP dengan nyaman dan aman
      melalui jaringan lokal atau Bluetooth.
    </p>
    <p>
      Ini dapat memindai kode kunci lain dan mentransfer kunci secara aman, 
      memungkinkan sesi penandatanganan dua-pihak kasual.
      Ini mengikuti praktik terbaik dengan mengirimkan tanda tangan terenkripsi
      ke UID kunci menggunakan klien Surel yang dikonfigurasi pengguna
      untuk digunakan.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>
      GNOME-Keysign permette di firmare chiavi OpenPGP in modo semplice e sicuro
      utilizzando la rete locale o il Bluetooth.
    </p>
    <p>
      È possibile leggere il codice a barre di un altro e trasferire la chiave
      in modo sicuro, permettendo a due persone di effettuare una sessione di
      firma delle chiavi.
      Segue le linee guida inviando le firme cifrate agli UID della chiave
      utilizzando il client email configurato dall'utente.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>
      Gnome Keysign laat u eenvoudig en veilig OpenPGP-sleutels ondertekenen
      via het lokale netwerk of Bluetooth.
    </p>
    <p>
      Het kan de barcode van een andere sleutel scannen en de sleutel veilig overdragen,
      wat informele sleutelondertekeningssessies tussen twee partijen mogelijk maakt.
      Het verzendt de versleutelde ondertekeningen naar de UID’s van een sleutel
      met de door de gebruiker ingestelde e-mailcliënt.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>
      GNOME Keysign umożliwia wygodne i bezpieczne podpisywanie kluczy
      OpenPGP przez sieć lokalną lub Bluetooth.
    </p>
    <p>
      Można zeskanować kod kreskowy innego klucza i bezpiecznie go
      przesłać, co umożliwia przeprowadzanie nieformalnych sesji
      podpisywania kluczy przez dwie osoby.
      Program używa sprawdzonych zasad, wysyłając zaszyfrowane podpisy
      do UID klucza za pomocą klienta poczty skonfigurowanego przez
      użytkownika.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>
      GNOME Keysign permite assinar chaves OpenPGP de forma
      confortável e segura por meio da rede local ou do Bluetooth.
    </p>
    <p>
      Ele pode escanear o código de barras de outra tecla e
      transferir a chave com segurança, permitindo sessões
      informais de sinalização de duas partes.
      Ele segue as práticas recomendadas enviando as assinaturas
      criptografadas para os UIDs de uma chave usando o cliente
      de e-mail que o usuário configurou para usar.
    </p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.Keysign.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image height="529" width="646">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Keysign?action=AttachFile&amp;do=get&amp;target=send.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image width="646" height="529">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Keysign?action=AttachFile&amp;do=get&amp;target=receive.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Keysign</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/gnome-keysign/gnome-keysign/issues</url>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.2.0" date="2019-10-23">
      <description>
        <p>
         * Fix error stemming from removing the crashing gpgme detection
         * build: Unvendorise babel-glade python module
         * change email message to facilitate usage of certifications
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-09-13" version="1.1.1">
      <description>
        <p>
         * Allow to drag and drop an email or its attachment into the app
         * show options to save produced certification as a file
         * Added a tooltip to the Internet button
         * Change logo to a wax seal
         * select usable private keys for signing, only
         * made appdata file validate under stricter requirements
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-01-21" version="1.0.1">
      <description>
        <p>
         * fixed up appdata
         * Cater for newer wormhole close() semantics
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2019-01-08">
      <description>
        <p>
         * Run with python3 from the desktop file
         * Removed monkeysign support
         * Stop installing gks-qrcode
         * Increased Python2 support in the tests
         * Fixed stopping wormhole discovery
         * Ship a new icon for the app
         * Removed gpgmh wrapper module
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-08-30" version="0.9.9">
      <description>
        <p>Transfer keys via the Internet through Magic Wormhole</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-07-04" version="0.9.8">
      <description>
        <p>Check for Bluetooth in a separate thread, detect powered off Bluetooth device, do not show offline keys</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-05-17" version="0.9.7.2">
      <description>
        <p>Made Appdata go into right places</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-10-03" version="0.9.5">
      <description>
        <p>Add Bluetooth support</p>
        <p>Default to gpgme</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <update_contact>tobiasmue@gnome.org</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-keysign</translation>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>