<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <description>
    <p>
      Sound Recorder provides a simple and modern interface that provides a
      straight-forward way to record and play audio.
      It allows you to do basic editing, and create voice memos.
    </p>
    <p>
      Sound Recorder automatically handles the saving process so that you
      do not need to worry about accidentally discarding the previous recording.
    </p>
    <p>Supported audio formats:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 and MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="af">
    <p>Klankopnemer verskaf 'n moderne koppelvlak en bied 'n eenvoudige manier om klank op te neem en terug te speel. Verder laat dit basiese redigeering toe en stel jou instaat om klanknotas te neem.</p>
    <p>Klankopnemer hanteer die stoor van opnames outomaties sodat jy nie daaroor hoef te bekommer nie.</p>
    <p>Ondersteunde klankformate:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 and MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="an">
    <p>A Gravadora de sons proporciona una interficie sencilla y moderna que ofreix una traza facil de gravar y reproducir sons. Permite fer una edición basica y creyar notas de voz.</p>
    <p>A Gravadora de sons chestiona automaticament o proceso d'alzau, por o que no ha de preocupar-se que a gravación se pierda accidentalment.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>مسجل الصوت يقدم لك واجهة سهلة وحديثة توفر لك </p>
    <p>مسجل الصوت يقوم تلقائياً بحفظ التسجيلات لذلك لا داعي للقلق إذا لم تحفظ التسيجل السابق .</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="as">
    <p>শব্দ ৰেকৰ্ডাৰে এটা সাধাৰণ আৰু আধুনিক আন্তঃপৃষ্ঠ প্ৰদান কৰে যি অডিঅ' ৰেকৰ্ড কৰাৰ আৰু বজোৱাৰ এটা প্ৰত্যক্ষ পদ্ধতি প্ৰদান কৰে। ই আপোনাক মৌলিক সম্পাদন কৰাৰ, আৰু ভয়েচ মেমোসমূহ সৃষ্টি কৰাৰ অনুমতি দিয়ে।</p>
    <p>শব্দ ৰেকৰ্ডাৰে সংৰক্ষণ প্ৰক্ৰিয়াক স্বচালিতভাৱে নিয়ন্ত্ৰণ কৰে যাতে আপুনি আগৰ ৰেকৰ্ডিং ভুলতে বাদ দিয়াৰ বিষয়ে ভাৱিব নালাগে।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Гукавы рэгістратар мае просты і сучасны інтэрфэйс які дае простую магчымасць запісваць і прайграваць гукі. Ён дазваляе вам рабіць базавыя рэдагаванні і ствараць галасавыя памяткі.</p>
    <p>Гукавы рэгістратар аўтаматычна рэгулюе захаваны працэс і вам не трэба хвалявацца што знікне папярэдні запіс.</p>
    <p>Падтрымліваемыя фарматы аўдыя:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 і MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Snimač zvuka pruža jednostavno i moderno korisničko sučelje koje omogućavadirektno snimanje i slušanje zvuka. Dopušta osnovno uređivanje, i kreiranje glasovnih podsjetnika.</p>
    <p>Snimač zvuka automatski rukuje spašavanjem tako da nema potrebe da brinete o odbacivanju prethodnog snimanja.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>L'Enregistrador de so proporciona una interfície simple i moderna que permet enregistrar i reproduir àudios. Us permet fer edicions bàsiques i crear notes de veu.</p>
    <p>L'Enregistrador de so gestiona automàticament el procés de desament de manera que no us heu de preocupar si heu suprimit accidentalment algun enregistrament.</p>
    <p>Formats d'àudio admesos:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 i MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca@valencia">
    <p>L'gravadora de so proporciona una interfície simple i moderna que permet gravar i reproduir àudios. Vos permet fer edicions bàsiques a més a més de crear notes de veu.</p>
    <p>L'gravadora de so gestiona automàticament el procés de guardat de manera que no vos hàgeu de preocupar de suprimir accidentalment algun gravació	 anterior.</p>
    <p>Formats d'àudio admesos:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 and MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ckb">
    <p>جۆرە دەنگی پشتگیریکراو:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 and MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Nahrávání zvuku poskytuje jednoduché a moderní rozhraní, ve kterém můžete přímočarou cestou nahrávat a přehrávat zvuk. Umožňuje základní úpravy a vytváření zvukových poznámek.</p>
    <p>Automaticky se stará o ukládání, takže nemusíte mít obavu, že si nedopatřením zrušíte předchozí nahrávku.</p>
    <p>Podporované zvukové formáty:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 a MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Lydoptager har en simpel og moderne brugerflade, som giver en enkel måde at optage og afspille lyd. Den giver dig mulighed for at lave basal redigering og oprette lyd-memo'er.</p>
    <p>Lydoptager gemmer automatisk, så du ikke behøver være bange for at komme til at slette den tidligere optagelse ved et uheld.</p>
    <p>Understøttede lydformater:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 og MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Der Tonaufzeichner stellt eine einfache und moderne Schnittstelle zur Verfügung, welche das Aufzeichnen und Abspielen von Tönen etc. ermöglicht. Grundlegende Bearbeitungsfunktionen und das Aufzeichnen von Gesprächsnotizen werden unterstützt.</p>
    <p>Der Tonaufzeichner handhabt den Speicherungsprozess automatisch, so dass man sich keine Sorgen machen muss, vorherige Aufzeichnungen zu verlieren.</p>
    <p>Unterstützte Tonformate:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 und MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Η ´Εγγραφή ήχου είναι μια απλή και σύγχρονη διεπαφή που παρέχει έναν εύκολο τρόπο εγγραφής και αναπαραγωγής ήχου. Σας επιτρέπει να κάνετε βασική επεξεργασία και δημιουργία φωνητικών υπενθυμίσεων.</p>
    <p>Η Εγγραφή ήχου χειρίζεται αυτόματα τη διαδικασία αποθήκευσης, έτσι ώστε να μην χρειάζεται να ανησυχείτε για κατά λάθος απόρριψη προηγούμενης εγγραφής.</p>
    <p>Υποστηριζόμενες μορφές ήχου:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 και MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Sound Recorder provides a simple and modern interface that provides a straight-forward way to record and play audio. It allows you to do basic editing, and create voice memos.</p>
    <p>Sound Recorder automatically handles the saving process so that you do not need to worry about accidentally discarding the previous recording.</p>
    <p>Supported audio formats:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 and MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p>Sonregistrilo provizas simplan kaj modernan fasadon kiu donas rektan vojon por registri kaj ludi sonon. Ĝi permesas al vi fari bazan redaktadon kaj krei voĉo-notojn.</p>
    <p>Sonregistrilo aŭtomate traktas la konservo-procezon por ke vi ne maltrankviliĝu pri akcidenta forĵeto de la antaŭa registraĵo.</p>
    <p>Subtenataj sonaj formoj:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 kaj MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>La Grabadora de sonidos proporciona una interfaz sencilla y moderna que ofrece una manera fácil de grabar y reproducir sonidos. Permite hacer una edición básica y crear notas de voz.</p>
    <p>La Grabadora de sonidos gestiona automáticamente el proceso de guardado, por lo que no tiene que preocuparse de que la grabación se pierda accidentalmente.</p>
    <p>Formatos de sonido soportados:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 y MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Soinu-grabatzaileak interfaze xume eta modernoa eskaintzen du audioa grabatzeko eta erreproduzitzeko zuzeneko moduarekin. Oinarrizko edizioa baimentzen du, baita ahotsezko zirkularrak sortzea ere.</p>
    <p>Soinu grabatzaileak automatikoki gordetzeko prozesua kudeatzen duenez, ez duzu kezkatu beharrik aurreko grabazioa ezuste batean baztertuz gero.</p>
    <p>Onartutako audio-formatuak:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 eta MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fa">
    <p>ضبط صوت یک واسط ساده و مدرن را برای ضبط و پخش آسان صدا فراهم می‌کند. همچنین به شما اجازهٔ ویرایش ساده و ساخت یادداشت‌های صوتی را می‌دهد.</p>
    <p>ضبط صوت به صورت خودکار روند ذخیره را انجام می‌دهد تا شما نگران دورانداختن اتفاقی پرونده پیشین نباشید.</p>
    <p>قالب‌های صوتی پشتیبانی شده:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>وربیس اوگ، اپوس، فلک، ام‌پی‌تری و موو</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Ääninauhuri tarjoaa pelkistetyn ja nykyaikaisen käyttöliittymän, jonka avulla äänen tallentaminen ja toistaminen käy ketterästi. Sovelluksen avulla voit tehdä pieniä muokkauksia ja nauhoittaa äänimuistioita.</p>
    <p>Ääninauhuri käsittelee tallennuksen automaattisesti, joten et vahingossakaan hävitä aiempaa nauhoitustasi.</p>
    <p>Tuetut äänimuodot:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 ja MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>L’Enregistreur de son présente une interface simple et moderne fournissant un moyen direct d’enregistrer et de lire du contenu audio. Il permet de modifier le son de manière basique et de créer des mémos vocaux.</p>
    <p>L’Enregistreur de son gère automatiquement le processus d’enregistrement sur disque, ce qui évite de devoir se soucier d’une perte accidentelle d’un enregistrement sonore précédent.</p>
    <p>Formats audio pris en charge :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 et MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Regjistradôr di suns e je une semplice e moderne interface che a furnìs un mût trasparent e clâr di regjistrâ e riprodusi audio. E permet di fâ modifichis basilârs e di creâ pro memorie vocâi.</p>
    <p>Regjistradôr di sun al ministre in maniere automatiche il procès di salvament cussì che no si à di vê pôre di vê scartât cence volê la regjistrazion precedent.</p>
    <p>Formâts audio supuartâts:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 e MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>A gravadora de son fornece unha interface moderna e simple para levar a cabo gravacións e reproducións de son rápidas. Tamén permite a edición básica e a creación de recordatorios de voz.</p>
    <p>A gravadora de son xestiona automaticamente o proceso de gardado polo que non terá que preocuparse sobre o rexeite accidental de gravacións anteriores.</p>
    <p>Formatos de son admitidos:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 e MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>רשמקול מספק ממשק פשוט וחדיש המספק דרך פשוטה להקלטת ולהאזנה לשמע. הוא מאפשר לך עריכה בסיסית ויצירת תזכירים קוליים.</p>
    <p>רשמקול מטפל באופן אוטומטי בתהליך השמירה כך שלא נדרש לדאוג על השלכה בטעות של הקלטה קודמת.</p>
    <p>Supported audio formats:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 and MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Snimatelj zvuka omogućuje jednostavno i moderno sučelje koje omogućuje ravnomjerno snimanje i reprodukciju zvuka. Omogućuje vam osnovno uređivanje i stvaranje video bilješka.</p>
    <p>Snimatelj zvuka automatski rukuje procesom spremanja stoga se ne morate brinuti o slučajnom gubitku prijašnjih nespremljenih snimaka.</p>
    <p>Podržani zvučni formati:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 i MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Hangrögzítő egy egyszerű és modern felületet biztosít, amely egyszerű utat nyújt a hang rögzítéséhez és lejátszásához. Lehetővé teszi az alap szerkesztések elvégzését és hangfeljegyzések létrehozását.</p>
    <p>A Hangrögzítő automatikusan kezeli a mentési folyamatot, ezért nem kell aggódnia a korábbi felvétel véletlen eldobása miatt.</p>
    <p>Támogatott hangformátumok:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 és MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Perekam Suara menyediakan antar muka yang modern dan sederhana yang memberi cara singkat untuk merekam dan memutar audio. Itu memungkinkan Anda melakukan penyuntingan dasar dan membuat memo suara.</p>
    <p>Perekam Suara secara otomatis menangani proses penyimpanan sehingga Anda tak perlu khawatir secara tak sengaja membuang rekaman sebelumnya.</p>
    <p>Format audio yang didukung:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3, dan MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>Studd hljóðsnið:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 og MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Il Registratore di suoni è una semplice e moderna interfaccia che fornisce un trasparente e chiaro modo per registrare e riprodurre audio. Consente di fare modifiche basilari e di creare memo vocali.</p>
    <p>Il Registratore di suoni gestisce automaticamente il processo di salvataggio così che non c'è da preoccuparsi di aver scartato accidentalmente la registrazione precedente.</p>
    <p>Formati audio supportati:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 e MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>サウンドレコーダーはシンプルでモダンなインターフェースを備えており、音声の録音、再生を直感的に行うことができます。また、基本的な音声編集やボイスメモの作成もできます。</p>
    <p>サウンドレコーダーは自動的に保存処理を行います。録音データをうっかり破棄してしまう心配はもうありません。</p>
    <p>サポートしている音声フォーマット:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis、Opus、FLAC、MP3、MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <p>Дыбыстарды жазу қолданбасы аудионы жазу және ойнатуға арналған жеңіл, заманауи әрі түсінікті интерфейсті ұсынады. Ол қарапайым түзетуді, әрі дыбыстық жазбаларды жасауды мүмкін етеді.</p>
    <p>Дыбыстарды жазу қолданбасы сақтауды өзі орындайды, сол себептен, жасалған дыбыстық жазбалар жоғала ма деп уайымдау керек емес.</p>
    <p>Қолдауы бар аудио пішімдері:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 және MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>녹음기의 인터페이스는 간단하면서 현대적이고, 직관적으로 오디오를 녹음하고 재생할 수 있습니다. 간단한 편집을 할 수도 있고, 음성 메모를 만들 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p>녹음기는 저장을 자동으로 처리하므로 이전 녹음을 실수로 잃어버릴 걱정을 하지 않아도 됩니다.</p>
    <p>지원하는 오디오 형식:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3, MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Garso įrašymas suteikia paprastą ir modernią sąsają, kuri leidžia paprastai įrašyti bei groti garsą. Ji leidžia atlikti bazinį redagavimą bei sukurti garso įrašus.</p>
    <p>Garso įrašymas automatiškai apdoroja įrašymo procesą, tad nereikia rūpintis, kad netyčia neišmestumėt ankstesnio įrašo.</p>
    <p>Palaikomi garso formatai:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 ir MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>Skaņas ierakstītājs sniedz vienkāršu un modernu saskarni, kas vienkārši ļauj ierakstīt un atskaņot audio. Tas ļauj veikt vienkāršu rediģēšanu un veidot balss piezīmes.</p>
    <p>Skaņas ierakstītājs automātiski nodrošina saglabāšanas procesu, lai jums nevajadzētu uztraukties par nejaušu iepriekšējo ierakstu nesaglabāšanu.</p>
    <p>Atbalstītie audio formāti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 un MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="mjw">
    <p>Sound Recorder aseh rai nei, lasi nangli rai tene det pu tameh matha nangne, athe aseh kenep rai nei.</p>
    <p>Audio formats support an:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 and MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ml">
    <p>സൗണ്ട് റെക്കോർഡർ ശബ്ദങ്ങൾ ശേഖരിക്കാനും കേൾക്കുവാനും ഒരു എളുപ്പവും നവീനവുമായ സമ്പർക്കമുഖം നൽകുന്നു. അത് ശബ്ദ മെമ്മോകൾ നിർമ്മിക്കാനും തിരുത്തലുകൾ വരുത്തുവാനും അനുവദിക്കുന്നു.</p>
    <p>ഫയലുകളുടെ സംരക്ഷണം സൗണ്ട് റെക്കോർഡർ സ്വയം ചെയ്യുന്നതിനാൽ നേരത്തെയുള്ള ശേഖരങ്ങൾ അറിയാതെ നഷ്ടമാകുമെന്ന് താങ്കൾ ഭയപ്പെടേണ്ടതില്ല.</p>
    <p>പിന്തുണയ്ക്കുന്ന ശബ്ദരീതികൾ:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 കൂടാതെ MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Perakam Bunyi menyediakan satu antara muka ringkas dan modern yang mana cara merakam dan main audio yang tidak berbelit. Ia membolehkan anda buat penyuntingan asas, dan hasilkan memo bersuara.</p>
    <p>Perakam Bunyi secara automatik mengendalikan proses penyimpanan supaya anda tidak perlu risau sekiranya terbuang rakaman terdahulu yang ada.</p>
    <p>Format audio disokong:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 dan MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Lydopptaker har et enkelt og moderne grensesnitt som lar deg ta opp og spille av lyd på en enkel måte. Programmet lar deg gjøre grunnleggende redigering og opptak av notater med lyd.</p>
    <p>Lydopptaker håndterer lagringsprosessen automatisk slik at du ikke trenger å bekymre deg om overskriving av forrige opptak ved en feiltakelse.</p>
    <p>Støttede lydformater:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 og MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ne">
    <p>ध्वनि रिकर्डरले सरल र आधुनिक इन्टरफेस प्रदान गर्दछ जसले अडियो र रेकर्ड गर्न र सीधा निर्देशन प्रदान गर्दछ। यसले तपाईंलाई आधारभूत सम्पादन गर्न अनुमति दिन्छ, र आवाज मेमोहरू सिर्जना गर्दछ।.</p>
    <p>ध्वनि रेकर्डरले स्वचालित रूपमा बचत प्रक्रियालाई ह्यान्डल गर्दछ ताकि तपाइँ अघिल्लो रेकर्डिङलाई गलत तरिकाले खारेज गर्ने बारे चिन्ता गर्नुपर्दैन।</p>
    <p>समर्थित ध्वनि ढाँचाहरू:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 र MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Geluidsrecorder biedt een eenvoudige en moderne interface waarmee u audio kunt opnemen en afspelen. Het laat elementair bewerken van de audio en het maken van stem-memo’s toe.</p>
    <p>Geluidsrecorder zorgt automatisch voor het opslagproces, zodat u zich geen zorgen hoeft te maken over het per ongeluk verwijderen van de vorige opname.</p>
    <p>Ondersteunde audioformaten:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 en MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>L'Enregistrador de son presenta una interfàcia simpla e modèrna que provesís un mejan dirècte d'enregistrar e de legir de contengut àudio. Permet de modificar lo son d'un biais basic e de crear de memòs vocals.</p>
    <p>L'Enregistrador de son gerís automaticament lo processus d'enregistrament sus disc, aquò evita de se dever tracassar d'una pèrda accidentala d'un enregistrament sonòr precedent.</p>
    <p>Formats àudio preses en cargar :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 e MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pa">
    <p>ਸਾਊਂਡ ਰਿਕਾਰਡ ਇੱਕ ਸਧਾਰਨ ਤੇ ਆਧੁਨਿਕ ਇੰਟਰਫੇਸ ਦਿੰਦਾ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ ਆਡੀਓ ਰਿਕਾਰਡ ਅਤੇ ਚਲਾਈ ਜਾ ਸਕਦੀ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਕੁਝ ਮੁੱਢਲੀ ਐਡੀਟਿੰਗ ਤੇ ਆਵਾਜ਼ੀ ਮੀਮੋ ਬਣਾਉਣ ਦੀ ਸਹੂਲਤ ਵੀ ਮਿਲਦੀ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p>ਸਾਊਂਡ ਰਿਕਾਰਡ ਆਪਣੇ-ਆਪ ਹੀ ਸੰਭਾਲਣ ਦੀ ਕਾਰਵਾਈ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਕਰਕੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਗਲਤੀ ਨਾਲ ਵੀ ਪਿਛਲੀ ਰਿਕਾਰਡ ਗੁਆਉਣ ਦਾ ਫ਼ਿਕਰ ਨਹੀਂ ਕਰਨਾ ਪੈਂਦਾ ਹੈ।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Program do nagrywania dźwięku dostarcza prosty i nowoczesny interfejs, umożliwiający nagrywanie i odtwarzanie dźwięku w prosty sposób. Można także przeprowadzać podstawową edycję i tworzyć notatki głosowe.</p>
    <p>Program do nagrywania dźwięku automatycznie zajmuje się procesem zapisywania, więc nie ma obawy utraty poprzednich nagrań.</p>
    <p>Obsługiwane formaty dźwięku:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 i MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Gravador de som fornece um ambiente simples e moderno e uma forma avançada de gravar e reproduzir áudio. Permite-lhe fazer edição básica e criar memorandos de voz.</p>
    <p>O Gravador de som gere automaticamente o processo de gravação para que não necessite de se preocupar com acidentes com gravações anteriores.</p>
    <p>Formatos de áudio suportados:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 e MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>O Gravador de som possui uma interface simples e moderna que oferece uma forma expressa de gravar e reproduzir áudio. Ele lhe permite realizar edição básica e criar memorandos de voz.</p>
    <p>O Gravador de som lida automaticamente com o processo de salvamento, desta forma você não precisa ficar com receio de descartar acidentalmente a gravação anterior.</p>
    <p>Formatos de áudio com suporte:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 e MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Înregistrator de sunet pune la dispoziție o interfață simplă și modernă ce oferă o cale simplă de a înregistra și reda clipuri audio. Vă permite să efectuați editări de bază și să creeați memorii vocale.</p>
    <p>Înregistrator de sunet se ocupă automat de procesul de salvare astfel încât nu trebuie să vă faceți griji despre ștergerea accidentală a înregistrărilor precedente.</p>
    <p>Formate audio suportate:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 și MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Диктофон предоставляет простой, современный и дружелюбный интерфейс для записи и воспроизведения звука, в приложении имеются базовые функции для редактирования записей и создания голосовых заметок.</p>
    <p>Диктофон автоматически выполняет сохранение, поэтому вам не нужно беспокоиться о том, что вы можете случайно перезаписать предыдущую запись.</p>
    <p>Поддерживаемые аудиоформаты:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 и MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Program Nahrávanie zvuku poskytuje jednoduché a moderné rozhranie, ktoré umožňuje priamy spôsob nahrávania a prehrávania zvuku. Umožňuje vám vykonávať základné úpravy a vytvárať hlasové poznámky.</p>
    <p>Program Nahrávanie zvuku automaticky riadi proces ukladania, takže sa nemusíte báť, ak omylom odstránite predošlú nahrávku.</p>
    <p>Podporované formáty zvuku:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 a MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Snemalnik zvoka je enostaven in sodoben program, ki omogoča hitro snemanje in predvajanje zvoka. Omogoča enostavnejše urejanje in ustvarjanje zvočnih opomnikov.</p>
    <p>Snemalnik zvoka samodejno upravlja shranjevanje, zato ni treba skrbeti, da bi posnetek izgubili.</p>
    <p>Podprti zvočni zapisi:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 in MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Снимач звука обезбеђује једноставно и савремено сучеље које обезбеђује непосредан начин за снимање и пуштање звука. Допушта вам да обавите основно уређивање, и да направите гласовне белешке.</p>
    <p>Снимач звука самостално рукује процесом чувања тако да не морате да се бринете о случајном брисању претходног снимка.</p>
    <p>Подржани звучни записи:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Огг Ворбис, Опус, ФЛАЦ, МП3 и МОВ</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Snimač zvuka obezbeđuje jednostavno i savremeno sučelje koje obezbeđuje neposredan način za snimanje i puštanje zvuka. Dopušta vam da obavite osnovno uređivanje, i da napravite glasovne beleške.</p>
    <p>Snimač zvuka samostalno rukuje procesom čuvanja tako da ne morate da se brinete o slučajnom brisanju prethodnog snimka.</p>
    <p>Podržani zvučni zapisi:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 i MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Ljudinspelaren tillhandahåller ett enkelt och modernt gränssnitt som erbjuder ett enkelt sätt att spela in och spela upp ljud. Det låter dig göra grundläggande redigering och skapa röstmeddelanden.</p>
    <p>Ljudinspelaren hanterar automatiskt sparande så du behöver inte oroa dig för att av misstag kasta bort den föregående inspelningen.</p>
    <p>Ljudformat som stöds:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 och MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Ses Kaydedicisi, ses kaydetmeniz ve oynatmanız için kolay bir yol sunan sade ve çağdaş bir arayüz sağlar. Temel düzenlemeler yapmanıza ve sesli notlar oluşturmanıza olanak tanır.</p>
    <p>Ses Kaydedicisi, kaydetme sürecini kendi kendine yönetir; böylece, bir önceki kaydı yanlışlıkla silmekten korkmanıza gerek kalmaz.</p>
    <p>Desteklenen ses biçimleri:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 ve MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Записувач звуку надає простий і новітній інтерфейс для записування й програвання звуку. Це дозволяє робити базове редагування і створювати звукові примітки.</p>
    <p>Записувач звуку автоматично записує, тому не варто переживати за випадково відкинуті попередні записи.</p>
    <p>Підтримувані звукові формати:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 і MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="vi">
    <p>Ứng dụng thu âm đưa ra một giao diện đơn giản và hiện đại cái mà đưa ra cách dễ dàng để mà ghi âm và phát lại. Nó cho phép bạn thực hiện các thao tác sửa cơ bản, và tạo ghi chú bằng giọng nói.</p>
    <p>Úng dụng thu âm tự động xử lý quá trình ghi lại do đó bạn không cần phải lo lắng về các tai nạn loại bỏ bản ghi trước đó.</p>
    <p>Các định dạng âm thanh được hỗ trợ:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, MP3 và MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>录音机提供了简单并且现代的交互界面以便用户直观地录制和播放音频。您可用它进行一些基本的音频编辑，还可以制作音频备忘录。</p>
    <p>录音机会自动进行保存，所以您不用担心不小心丢失以前的录音。</p>
    <p>支持的音频格式：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis、Opus、FLAC、MP3 和 MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>錄音機提供簡易且現代的介面，讓使用者可以直覺的錄音、播放。它有基本的編輯功能，也能建立錄音備忘錄。</p>
    <p>錄音機會自動處理儲存過程，因此您無需擔憂意外丟失先前的錄製項目。</p>
    <p>支援的音訊格式：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ogg Vorbis、Opus、FLAC、MP3 和 MOV</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>gnome.gnome-sound-recorder</pkgname>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">org.gnome.SoundRecorder.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">org.gnome.SoundRecorder.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.SoundRecorder.desktop</id>
  <name>Sound Recorder</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">錄音機</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">錄音機</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">录音机</name>
  <name lang="vi">Thu âm</name>
  <name lang="uk">Записувач звуку</name>
  <name lang="tr">Ses Kaydedici</name>
  <name lang="tg">Сабткунандаи овоз</name>
  <name lang="te">శబ్ద నమోదకం</name>
  <name lang="sv">Ljudinspelare</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Snimač zvuka</name>
  <name lang="sr">Снимач звука</name>
  <name lang="sl">Snemalnik zvoka</name>
  <name lang="sk">Nahrávanie zvuku</name>
  <name lang="ru">Диктофон</name>
  <name lang="ro">Înregistrator de sunet</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Gravador de som</name>
  <name lang="pt">Gravador de som</name>
  <name lang="pl">Nagrywanie</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਸਾਊਂਡ ਰਿਕਾਰਡ</name>
  <name lang="oc">Enregistrador de son</name>
  <name lang="nl">Geluidsrecorder</name>
  <name lang="ne">ध्वनि रेकर्डर</name>
  <name lang="nb">Lydopptaker</name>
  <name lang="ms">Perakam Bunyi</name>
  <name lang="ml">സൗണ്ട് റെക്കോർഡർ</name>
  <name lang="mjw">Sound Recorder</name>
  <name lang="lv">Skaņu ierakstītājs</name>
  <name lang="lt">Garso įrašymas</name>
  <name lang="ko">녹음기</name>
  <name lang="kk">Дыбыстарды жазу қолданбасы</name>
  <name lang="ja">サウンドレコーダー</name>
  <name lang="it">Registratore di suoni</name>
  <name lang="is">Hljóðupptaka</name>
  <name lang="id">Perekam Suara</name>
  <name lang="hu">Hangrögzítő</name>
  <name lang="hr">Snimatelj zvuka</name>
  <name lang="he">רשמקול</name>
  <name lang="gl">Gravadora de son</name>
  <name lang="fur">Regjistradôr di suns</name>
  <name lang="fr">Enregistreur de son</name>
  <name lang="fi">Ääninauhuri</name>
  <name lang="fa">ضبط صوت</name>
  <name lang="eu">Soinu grabatzailea</name>
  <name lang="es">Grabadora de sonidos</name>
  <name lang="eo">Sonregistrilo</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Sound Recorder</name>
  <name lang="el">Εγγραφή ήχου</name>
  <name lang="de">Tonaufzeichner</name>
  <name lang="da">Lydoptagelse</name>
  <name lang="cs">Nahrávání zvuku</name>
  <name lang="ckb">تۆرمارکەری دەنگ</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">Enregistradora de so</name>
  <name lang="ca">Enregistrador de so</name>
  <name lang="bs">Snimač zvuka</name>
  <name lang="be">Гукавы рэгістратар</name>
  <name lang="as">শব্দ ৰেকৰ্ডাৰ</name>
  <name lang="an">Gravadora de sons</name>
  <name lang="ar">مُسجل الأصوات</name>
  <name lang="af">Klankopnemer</name>
  <summary>A simple, modern sound recorder for GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">簡易且現代的 GNOME 錄音機</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">用于 GNOME 的一个简单、现代的录音机</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Một ứng dụng thu âm đơn giản mà hiện đại dành cho môi trường GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Простий, новітній записувач звуку для GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">GNOME için sade, çağdaş bir ses kaydedici</summary>
  <summary lang="tg">Сабткунандаи овози осон ва ҳозиразамон барои GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">En enkel, modern ljudinspelare för GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Jednostavan, savremen snimač zvuka za Gnom</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Једноставан, савремен снимач звука за Гном</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Snemalnik zvoka za GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Jednoduché, moderné nahrávanie zvuku pre prostredie GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Простое, современное приложения для записи звука в GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Un înregistrator de sunet simplu și modern, pentru GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Um gravador de som moderno e simples para o GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Um simples e moderno gravador de som para o GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Prosty, nowoczesny program do nagrywania dźwięku dla GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਲਈ ਸਧਾਰਨ, ਆਧੁਨਿਕ ਸਾਊਂਡ ਰਿਕਾਰਡਰ</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Un enregistrador de son simple e modèrne per GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Een eenvoudige, moderne geluidsrecorder voor Gnome</summary>
  <summary lang="ne">जिनोमकाको लागि सरल, आधुनिक ध्वनि रेकर्डर</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">En enkel, moderne lydopptaker for GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Sebuah perakam bunyi yang ringkas dan modern untuk GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ml">ഗ്നോമിനു വേണ്ടിയുള്ള ഒരു ലളിതവും നവീനവുമായ ശബ്ദലേഖിനി</summary>
  <summary lang="mjw">Isi joike, nonlom akai phan sound recorder GNOME aphan.</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Vienkāršs, mūsdienīgs skaņas ierakstītājs GNOME videi</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Paprasta garso įrašymo programa GNOME aplinkai</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">간단하면서 현대적인 그놈 데스크톱 녹음기</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">GNOME үшін жеңіл әрі заманауи дыбыстарды жазу қолданбасы</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">シンプルでモダンな GNOME のサウンドレコーダー</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Un semplice e moderno registratore di suoni per GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Einföld hljóðupptaka fyrir GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Suatu perekam suara modern yang sederhana bagi GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Egy egyszerű, modern hangrögzítő a GNOME-hoz</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Jednostavan, moderan snimatelj zvuka za GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="he">רשמקול פשוט וחדיש עבור GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Unha gravadora de son moderna e sinxela para GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Un sempliç, moderni regjistradôr di suns par GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Un enregistreur de son simple et moderne pour GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Yksinkertainen ja nykyaikainen ääninauhuri Gnomelle</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">یک ضبط صوت مدرن و ساده برای گنوم</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">GNOMEren interfaze xume eta modernoa duen soinu-grabatzailea</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Una grabadora de sonidos sencilla y moderna para GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Simpla, moderna sonregistrilo por GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">A simple, modern sound recorder for GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Ένας απλός, σύγχρονος εγγραφέας ήχου για το GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Ein einfacher, moderner Tonaufzeichner für GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="da">En simpel, moderne lydoptager til GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Jednoduchá a moderní aplikace pro nahrávání zvuku v GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ckb">سادە، پێشکەوتوو بۆ تۆماری دەنگ لە گنۆم</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Un gravadora de so simple i modern pel GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Un enregistrador de so simple i modern pel GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Jednostavan i moderan snimač zvuka za GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Просты, сучасны гукавы рэгістратар для GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="as">GNOME ৰ বাবে এটা সাধাৰণ, আধুনিক শব্দ ৰেকৰ্ডাৰ</summary>
  <summary lang="an">Una gravadora de sons sencilla y moderna ta GNOME</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">مسجل أصوات بسيط و حديث لجنوم</summary>
  <summary lang="af">'n Eenvoudige, moderne klankopnemer vir GNOME</summary>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-sound-recorder/raw/master/data/resources/screenshots/screenshot1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-sound-recorder/raw/master/data/resources/screenshots/screenshot2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0" />
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-03-19" version="42.0">
      <description>
        <p>42.0 is out!</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Port to GTK4 / libadwaita</li>
          <li>Proper dark theme support</li>
          <li>Translations updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="40.0" date="2021-03-23" />
    <release version="3.38.1" date="2021-01-25">
      <description>
        <p>Bugfix release</p>
        <ul>
          <li>
            Translation updates
          </li>
          <li>
            Fix export dialog for recordings disappears shortly after opening
          </li>
          <li>
            Fix not able to use space bar in recording name input
          </li>
          <li>
            Fix recording is lost when using space bar in name input
          </li>
          <li>
            Fix ui becomes unusable and recording is lost after stopping a record
          </li>
          <li>
            Remove m4a option since using it results in unusable recordings
          </li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.38.0" date="2020-09-18">
      <description>
        <p>An overall update of Sound Recorder's design</p>
        <ul>
          <li>
            The possibility to seek backward/forward while playing a recording
          </li>
          <li>
            Recordings now always display the associated wave
          </li>
          <li>
            The possiblity to export a recording
          </li>
          <li>
            Code cleanup and translations updates
          </li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-09-10" version="3.34.0">
      <description>
        <p>Translations updates</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.SoundRecorder.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/SoundRecorder</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-sound-recorder/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://wiki.gnome.org/TranslationProject</url>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <developer_name>The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">GNOME 專案</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 项目</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="vi">Dự án GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Проєкт GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">GNOME Projesi</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Гном пројекат</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Проект GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Proiectul GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="oc">Lo projècte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Het Gnome-project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb">GNOME prosjektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ms">Projek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="mjw">GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lv">GNOME projekts</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">GNOME projektas</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">그놈 프로젝트</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="kk">GNOME жобасы</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Il progetto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="is">GNOME verkefnið</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Proyek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">מיזם GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">O Proxecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fur">Il progjet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Le projet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Gnome-projekti</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fa">پروژهٔ گنوم</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">GNOME proiektua</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">El Proyecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">La GNOME Projekto</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Το έργο GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Das GNOME-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <update_contact>meg387_at_gmail.com</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">org.gnome.SoundRecorder</translation>
  <custom>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">workstation</value>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">mobile</value>
  </custom>
</component>