<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>gnome.gnome-maps</pkgname>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">org.gnome.Maps.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">org.gnome.Maps.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.Maps.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>Maps</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">地圖</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">地圖</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">地图</name>
  <name lang="vi">Bản đồ</name>
  <name lang="uk">Карти</name>
  <name lang="tr">Haritalar</name>
  <name lang="tg">Харитаҳо</name>
  <name lang="te">పటాలు</name>
  <name lang="ta">வரைபடங்கள்</name>
  <name lang="sv">Kartor</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Karte</name>
  <name lang="sr">Карте</name>
  <name lang="sl">Zemljevidi</name>
  <name lang="sk">Mapy</name>
  <name lang="ro">Hărți</name>
  <name lang="ru">Карты</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Mapas</name>
  <name lang="pt">Mapas</name>
  <name lang="pl">Mapy</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਨਕਸ਼ਾ</name>
  <name lang="oc">Mapas</name>
  <name lang="nl">Kaarten</name>
  <name lang="ne">मानचित्र</name>
  <name lang="nb">Kart</name>
  <name lang="ms">Peta</name>
  <name lang="ml">ഭൂപടങ്ങള്‍</name>
  <name lang="mjw">Maps</name>
  <name lang="lv">Kartes</name>
  <name lang="lt">Žemėlapiai</name>
  <name lang="ko">지도</name>
  <name lang="kn">ಮ್ಯಾಪ್ಸ್</name>
  <name lang="kk">Карталар</name>
  <name lang="ja">地図</name>
  <name lang="it">Mappe</name>
  <name lang="is">Landakort</name>
  <name lang="id">Peta</name>
  <name lang="hu">Térképek</name>
  <name lang="hr">Karte</name>
  <name lang="hi">नक्शे</name>
  <name lang="he">מפות</name>
  <name lang="gl">Mapas</name>
  <name lang="gd">Mapaichean</name>
  <name lang="ga">Léarscáileanna</name>
  <name lang="fur">Mapis</name>
  <name lang="fr">Cartes</name>
  <name lang="fi">Kartat</name>
  <name lang="fa">نقشه‌ها</name>
  <name lang="eu">Mapak</name>
  <name lang="et">Kaardid</name>
  <name lang="es">Mapas</name>
  <name lang="eo">Mapoj</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Maps</name>
  <name lang="el">Χάρτες</name>
  <name lang="de">Karten</name>
  <name lang="da">Kort</name>
  <name lang="cs">Mapy</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">Mapes</name>
  <name lang="ca">Mapes</name>
  <name lang="bs">Karte</name>
  <name lang="bg">Карти</name>
  <name lang="as">মানচিত্ৰ</name>
  <name lang="ar">الخرائط</name>
  <name lang="an">Mapas</name>
  <name lang="af">Padkaart</name>
  <summary>Find places around the world</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">尋找世界上各個地方</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">寻找世界各地的地点</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Tìm các địa điểm trên khắp thế giới</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Знаходити місця по світу</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Dünya genelindeki yerleri bul</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Hitta platser i världen</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Nađite mesta širom sveta</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Нађите места широм света</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Iskanje mesta po svetu</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Vyhľadáva miesta po celom svete</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Găsește locații din întreaga lume</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Поиск местоположений по всему миру</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Encontre lugares ao redor do mundo</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Encontre locais em todo o mundo</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Wyszukiwanie miejsc na świecie</summary>
  <summary lang="pa">ਸੰਸਾਰ ਭਰ ਵਿੱਚ ਥਾਵਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਲੱਭੋ</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Recèrca d'emplaçaments a l'entorn del monde</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Vind plaatsen de wereld rond</summary>
  <summary lang="ne">विश्वभरका स्थानहरू फेला पार्नुहोस्</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Se på steder over hele verden</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Cari tempat-tempat di sekitar dunia</summary>
  <summary lang="ml">ലോകമെമ്പാടുമുള്ള സ്ഥലങ്ങൾ കണ്ടെത്തുക</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Atrodi vietas visā pasaulē</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Rasti vietas aplink pasaulį</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">전세계의 장소를 찾아봅니다</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">Дүниежүзілік орындарды табу</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Trova luoghi in giro per il mondo</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Finndu staði út um allan heim</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Temukan tempat di seluruh dunia</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Helyek keresése a világ minden pontján</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Potražite mjesta diljem svijeta</summary>
  <summary lang="he">מציאת מקומות מסביב לעולם</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Busque lugares por todo o mundo</summary>
  <summary lang="gd">Lorg àitichean air feadh an t-saoghail</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Cjate puescj tor atôr pal mont</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Recherche d’emplacements autour du monde</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Löydä sijainteja ympäri maailman</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">یافتن مکان‌ها در هر جایی از جهان</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Bilatu lekuak munduan zehar</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Encuentre lugares por todo el mundo</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Trovi lokojn tra la mondo</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Find places around the world</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Βρείτε μέρη από όλο τον κόσμο</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Orte in der ganzen Welt finden</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Find steder i hele verden</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Vyhledávejte místa na celém světě</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Troba llocs arreu del món</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Trobeu llocs arreu del món</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Търсене на места по света</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">جِد الأماكن حول العالم</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Maps gives you quick access to maps all across the world. It allows you
      to quickly find the place you’re looking for by searching for a city or
      street, or locate a place to meet a friend.
    </p>
    <p>
      Maps uses the collaborative OpenStreetMap database, made by hundreds of
      thousands of people across the globe.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="af">
    <p>Padkaart gee vinnige toegang tot padkaarte van regoor die wêreld. Dit laat mens toe om vinnig 'n gewenste plek te vind deur te soek vir 'n stad of 'n straat, of om 'n ontmoetingspunt op te spoor.</p>
    <p>Padkaart gebruik die gesamentlike OpenStreetMap-databasis, geskep deur honderde duisende mense regoor die wêreld.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="an">
    <p>Mapas te ofreix un acceso rapido a mapas de tot o mundo. Te permite trobar puestos rapidament mirando por ciudat u por carrera, u mirar un puesto ta trobar-te con un amigo.</p>
    <p>Os mapas fan servir a base de datos colaborativa OpenStreetMap, feita por cients de mils de personas de tot o mundo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>يمكّنك تطبيق الخرائط من مطالعة خرائط العالم أجمع، فهو يمكّنك من العثور على ما تريد بالبحث عن مدينة أو اسم شارع أو مكان ستجمتع فيه مع صديقك.</p>
    <p>يستخدم تطبيق الخراط قاعدة بيانات «خريطة الشارع المفتوحة» التعاونية، والتي شارك فيها آلاف الأشخاص حول العالم.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="as">
    <p>মানচিত্ৰই আপোনাক বিশ্বৰ সকলো মানচিত্ৰলৈ এটা দ্ৰুত অভিগম প্ৰদান কৰে। ই আপোনাক এটা নগৰ অথবা বাটৰ বাবে সন্ধান কৰি আপুনি বিচৰা স্থান দ্ৰুতভাৱে সন্ধান কৰাৰ অনুমতি দিয়ে, অথবা এজন বন্ধুক লগ ধৰিবলৈ এটা স্থান অৱস্থিত কৰাৰ সুবিধা দিয়ে।</p>
    <p>মানচিত্ৰই সংযোগি OpenStreetMap ডাটাবেইচ ব্যৱহাৰ কৰে, যাক বিশ্বৰ বিভিন্ন প্ৰান্তৰ লোকে সৃষ্টি কৰিছে।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>„Картите“ ви дават бърз достъп до места и карти по целия свят. Те ви позволяват бързо да намерите мястото, което търсите, независимо дали е град, улица или място на уречена срещал.</p>
    <p>Картите използват базите от данни на OpenStreetMap. Те са събрани от стотици хиляди хора от целия свят.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Karte vam daju brz pristup kartama cijelog svijeta.Omogućava vam da brzo nađete mjesto koje tražite , tražeći grad ili ulicu , ili da pronađe mjesto da sretnete priajtelja.</p>
    <p>Karte koriste kolaboraticnu OpenStreetMap bazu podataka, napravljenu od strane stotinu hiljada ljudi širom svijeta.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El Mapes us dona un accés ràpid a mapes d'arreu del món. Us permet trobar ràpidament el lloc que esteu cercant tant si és una ciutat com un carrer, o ubicar un lloc per a trobar-vos amb una amistat.</p>
    <p>El Mapes empra la base de dades col·laborativa de l'OpenStreetMap, creada per centenars de milers de persones d'arreu del món.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca@valencia">
    <p>El Mapes vos dóna un accés ràpid a mapes d'arreu del món. Vos permet trobar ràpidament el lloc que esteu cercant tant si és una ciutat com un carrer, o ubicar un lloc per trobar-vos amb una amistat.</p>
    <p>El Mapes empra la base de dades col·laborativa de l'OpenStreetMap, creat per centenars de milers de persones d'arreu del món.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Aplikace Mapy poskytuje rychlý přístup k mapám celého světa. Díky ní můžete rychle najít místo, které hledáte, ať už podle názvu města nebo ulice, nebo určit místo pro setkání s přáteli.</p>
    <p>Mapy využívají databázi OpenStreetMap, která vzniká díky spolupráci stovek tisíců lidí z celého světa.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Kort giver dig hurtig adgang til kort over hele verden. Det giver dig mulighed for hurtigt at finde stedet du leder efter ved at søge efter en by eller gade, eller et sted hvor du kan mødes med en ven.</p>
    <p>Kort bruger den kollaborative OpenStreetMap-database, skabt af flere hundrede tusinde mennesker over hele verden.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>»Karten« gibt Ihnen einen schnellen Zugang zu Karten aus der ganzen Welt. Es erlaubt Ihnen, Orte schnell zu finden, indem Sie eine Stadt oder eine Straße suchen, oder einen Ort zu finden, um einen Freund zu treffen.</p>
    <p>»Karten« nutzt die gemeinschaftliche OpenStreetMap-Datenbank, die von hunderttausenden Menschen aus der ganzen Welt erstellt worden ist.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Η εφαρμογή Χάρτες, σας παρέχει μια γρήγορη πρόσβαση σε χάρτες από όλο τον κόσμο. Σας επιτρέπει να βρείτε γρήγορα μια τοποθεσία αναζητώντας είτε μια πόλη είτε μια οδό, ή μπορείτε να εντοπίσετε μια τοποθεσία για να συναντήσετε ένα φίλο.</p>
    <p>Η εφαρμογή Χάρτες, χρησιμοποιεί την βάση δεδομένων OpenStreetMap, που έχει φτιαχτεί από χιλιάδες άτομα σε όλο τον κόσμο.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Maps gives you quick access to maps all across the world. It allows you to quickly find the place you’re looking for by searching for a city or street, or locate a place to meet a friend.</p>
    <p>Maps uses the collaborative OpenStreetMap database, made by hundreds of thousands of people across the globe.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p>Mapoj donas al vi rapidan aliron al mapoj de la tuta mondo. Ĝi ebligas vin rapide trovi la lokon, kiun vi serĉas, serĉante urbon aŭ straton, aŭ trovi lokon por renkonti amikon.</p>
    <p>Mapoj uzas la kunlaboran datumbazon OpenStreetMap, farita de centoj da miloj da personoj tra la tuta mondo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Mapas le ofrece un acceso rápido a mapas de todo el mundo. Le permite encontrar lugares rápidamente buscando por ciudad o por calle, o buscar un lugar para encontrarse con un amigo.</p>
    <p>Mapas usa la base de datos colaborativa OpenStreetMap, hecha por cientos de miles de personas de todo el mundo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Kaardid kasutavad ühistööna valminud OpenStreetMap andmebaasi, millele on kaasa aidanud tuhanded inimesed üle maailma.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Mapek mundu osoan zeharreko mapetarako atzipen azkarra eskaintzen dizu. Bilatzen ari zaren lekua modu azkar batean aurkitzen lagunduko dizu kalearen edo herriaren izena bilatuz, edo bilatu leku bat lagunekin aurkitzeko.</p>
    <p>Mapak auzolanean eraikitako OpenStreetMap datu-basea darabil, mundu osoan zehar ehun eta milaka pertsonen artean sortutakoa</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fa">
    <p>نقشه‌ها دسترسی سریعی به نقشه‌ها در تمام جهان را می‌دهد. این برنامه می‌گذارد با جست‌وجو برای یک شهر یا خیابان، مکانی را که به دنبالشید یافته یا مکانی را برای قرار مشخّص کنید.</p>
    <p>نقشه‌ها از پایگاه دادهٔ مشارکتی OpenStreetMap استفاده می‌کند که به دست صدها هزار نفر در سراسر جهان درست شده است.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Kartat mahdollistaa maailmanlaajuisen karttatiedon käytön nopeasti. Voit paikallistaa haluamasi paikan etsimällä vaikkapa kaupunkia tai katua.</p>
    <p>Kartat hyödyntää tuhansien ihmisten yhdessä luomaa OpenStreetMap-tietokantaa.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>L’application Cartes vous donne un accès rapide à des cartes du monde entier. Elle permet de trouver rapidement un emplacement en recherchant par ville ou par rue, ou de situer un endroit de rencontre avec un ami.</p>
    <p>Les cartes utilisent la base de données collaborative OpenStreetMap, à laquelle contribuent des centaines de milliers de personnes dans le monde entier.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Mapis ti da un acès veloç a lis mapis ator pal mont. Ti permet di cjatâ di corse il puest che ti interesse cirint citât o vie, o cirî un puest dulà cjatâsi cuntun ami.</p>
    <p>Mapis al dopre il database colaboratîf OpenStreetMap, fat da centenârs di miârs di personis ator pal mont.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gd">
    <p>Bheir Mapaichean dhut inntrigeadh luath dha mhapaichean air feadh an t-saoghail. Leigidh e leat àite a lorg gu luath a-rèir baile no sràide no an t-àite a lorg far a bheil thu airson tachairt ri caraid.</p>
    <p>Cleachdaidh Mapaichean stòr-dàta OpenStreetMap co-obrachail a chaidh a chruthachadh leis na mìltean mòra de dhaoine o fheadh an t-saoghail.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Mapas dálle acceso a mapas de todo o mundo. Permítelle buscar de forma rápida o lugar que está buscando por cidade ou rúa, ou localizar un lugar para encontrarse con un amigo.</p>
    <p>Mapa usa a base de datos colaborativa de OpenStreetMap, feita por centos de persoas por todo o mundo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>מפות נותן לך גישה מהירה למפות על פני כל העולם. הוא מאפשר לך למצוא במהירות את המקום שאתה מחפש באמצעות חיפוש עיר או רחוב, או לאתר מקום לפגישת חבר.</p>
    <p>מפות משתמש במסד הנתונים השיתופי OpenStreetMap, שנוצר על ידי מאות אלפי אנשים על פני כדור הארץ.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hi">
    <p>नक्शे आपको सभी दुनिया भर में नक्शे के लिए त्वरित पहुँच देता है. दोस्त से मिलने के लिए एक जगह का पता लगाने के लिए, या जल्दी से एक शहर या सड़क के लिए खोजकर आप ढूंढ रहे जगह आपको बताती है.</p>
    <p>नक्शे दुनिया भर में हजारों, सैकड़ों लोगों के द्वारा बनाई सहयोगी OpenStreetMap डेटाबेस का उपयोग करता है.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Karte vam daju brz pristup kartama diljem svijeta. Omogućuje vam da brzo pronađete mjesto koje tražite pretragom gradova ili ulica, ili lociranje mjesta za sastanak s prijateljem.</p>
    <p>Karte koriste suradničku OpenStreetMap bazu podataka, načinjenu od strane stotine tisuća ljudi diljem svijeta.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Térképek gyors hozzáférést ad térképekhez az egész világról. Lehetővé teszi egy keresett hely gyors megtalálását település vagy utca keresésével, vagy találni egy helyet, ahol ismerőseivel találkozhat.</p>
    <p>A Térképek az együttműködésen alapuló OpenStreetMap adatbázist használja, amelyet több százezer ember készít a világ minden részén.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Peta memberi Anda akses cepat ke peta di seluruh penjuru dunia. Ini memungkinkan Anda secara cepat menemukan tempat yang Anda cari dengan mencari suatu kota atau jalan, atau menemukan tempat untuk bertemu dengan teman.</p>
    <p>Peta memakai basis data kolaboratif OpenStreetMap, yang dibuat oleh ratusan ribu orang di seluruh dunia.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>Landakortaforritið gefur aðgang að landakortum hvaðanæva úr heiminum. Það hjálpar þér að finna staði, til dæmis með því að leita að götu eða bæ, nú eða með því að skoða kort til að finna góðan stað til að hitta vinina.</p>
    <p>Landakortaforritið notar OpenStreetMap gagnagrunninn, sem er samvinnuverkefni hundruða þúsunda manna víðsvegar um heiminn.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Mappe fornisce un rapido accesso alla cartografia mondiale. Consente di trovare velocemente i luoghi utilizzando la ricerca per città o per indirizzo e di trovare i luoghi in cui incontrare i propri amici.</p>
    <p>Mappe usa il database OpenStreetMap creato dalla collaborazione di centinaia di migliaia di persone da ogni parte del mondo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>世界中あらゆる場所の地図に簡単にアクセスできます。都市や住所を検索して、お探しの場所をさっと見つけられ、待ち合わせ場所もすぐに特定できます。</p>
    <p>この地図アプリは、OpenStreetMap データベースを利用しています。このデータベースは、世界中の膨大な人々が協力して作成しています。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <p>Карталар қолданбасы сізге дүниежүзі карталарына жылдам қатынауды мүмкін қылады. Оның көмегімен керек болған орынды оның орналасқан қаласын не көшесін енгізу арқылы табуға, немесе доспен кездесу үшін орынды табуға болады.</p>
    <p>Карталар қолданбасы қауымдастық ұсынатын OpenStreetMap дерекқорын қолданады, оны дүниежүзінің әр жеріндегі мыңдаған адамдар жасайды.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>지도로 전 세계 모든 지도에 빠르게 접근할 수 있습니다. 도시, 거리, 친구를 만날 여러분이 찾는 장소를 빠르게 찾을 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p>지도는 전세계 수많은 사람이 함께 만든 OpenStreenMap 데이터베이스를 사용합니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Žemėlapiai leidžia jums lengvai pasiekti pasaulio žemėlapius. Ši programa leidžia greitai rasti ieškomą vietą naudojant paiešką pagal miestą ar gatvę bei rasti vietą susitikimui su draugu.</p>
    <p>Žemėlapiai naudoja OpenStreetMap duomenų bazę, kurią sukūrė tūkstančiai žmonių iš viso pasaulio.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>Kartes dod iespēju ātri piekļūt kartēm visā pasaulē. Tās ļauj ātri atrast  kādu vietu, meklējot pilsētu vai ielu, vai atrast vietu, kur sastapt draugus.</p>
    <p>Kartes izmanto kolektīvi veidoto OpenStreetMap datubāzi, ko veidojuši tūkstošiem cilvēku visā pasaulē.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ml">
    <p>ഭൂപടങ്ങള്‍ താങ്കള്‍ക്കു ലോകത്തിലെ എല്ലായിടത്തെയും ഭൂപടങ്ങളിലേക്കു പ്രവേശനം നല്‍കുന്നു. ഇത് താങ്കള്‍ അന്വേഷിക്കുന്ന സ്ഥലം നഗരമോ തെരുവൊ തിരയുന്നതിലൂടെ പെട്ടന്നു തന്നെ കണ്ടുപിടിക്കാന്‍ അല്ലെങ്കില്‍ സുഹൃത്തിനെ കാണുവാന്‍ ഒരു സ്ഥലം കണ്ടുപിടിക്കാന്‍ സഹായിക്കുന്നു.</p>
    <p>ഭൂപടങ്ങള്‍ സഹകരണപരമായ OpenStreetMap ന്റെ ശേഖരിച്ചു് വചിട്ടുള്ള വിവരങ്ങളും വസ്തുതകളും ഉപയോഗിക്കുന്നുണ്ട്, ലോകത്തിലെ എല്ലായിടത്തിലേയും നൂറുകണക്കിനു ആളുകള്‍ ചേര്‍ന്നുണ്ടക്കിയതാണത്.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Peta memudahkan capaian pada peta di serata dunia. Ia membolehkan anda cari tempat yang dikehendaki dengan pantas iaitu menggelintar sebuah bandar atau jalan, atau ketahui lokasi untuk bertemu dengan rakan.</p>
    <p>Peta menggunakan pangkalan data OpenStreetMap yang terhasil secara kolaboratif oleh beratus-ratus individu di serata  dunia.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Kart gir deg rask tilgang til kart for hele verden. Det lar deg raskt finne stedet du leter etter ved å søke etter en by eller en gate, eller finne et sted å møte en venn.</p>
    <p>Kart bruker OpenStreetMap-databasen som er laget av hundretusener av mennesker fra hele verden.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Kaarten geeft u snelle toegang tot kaarten over de hele wereld. U kunt snel de plaats waarnaar u op zoek bent vinden door te zoeken naar een stad of de straat, of de plek opzoeken om een vriend te ontmoeten.</p>
    <p>Kaarten gebruikt de gemeenschappelijk opgebouwde OpenStreetMap-database, gemaakt door honderdduizenden mensen over de hele wereld.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>L'aplicacion Mapas vos dona un accès rapid a de mapas del monde entièr. Permet de trobar rapidament un emplaçament en recercant per vila o per carrièra, o de situar un endreit de recontre amb un amic.</p>
    <p>Las mapas utilizan la basa de donadas collaborativa OpenStreetMap, a la quala contribuisson de centenats de milierats de personas dins lo monde entièr.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pa">
    <p>ਨਕਸ਼ਾ (ਮੈਪਸ) ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਸੰਸਾਰ ਭਰ ਦੇ ਨਕਸ਼ੇ ਉਪਲੱਬਧ ਕਰਵਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇਹ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਤੁਰੰਤ ਸ਼ਹਿਰ ਜਾਂ ਸੜਕਾਂ ਦੇ ਨਾਂ ਰਾਹੀਂ ਥਾਂ ਲੱਭਣ ਲਈ ਜਾਂ ਮਿੱਤਰ ਨੂੰ ਮਿਲਣ ਲਈ ਥਾਂ ਪੱਕਾ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਮੱਦਦ ਕਰਦੀ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p>ਨਕਸ਼ਾ (ਮੈਪਸ) ਸਾਂਝਾ OpenStreetMap ਡਾਟਾਬੇਸ ਵਰਤਦਾ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨੂੰ ਸੰਸਾਰ ਭਰ ਦੇ ਲੱਖਾਂ-ਕਰੋੜਾਂ ਲੋਕਾਂ ਵਲੋਂ ਤਿਆਰ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Mapy zapewniają szybki dostęp do map całego świata oraz umożliwiają szybkie wyszukiwanie miejsc według miast i ulic. Pomogą również ustalić miejsce spotkania z przyjaciółmi.</p>
    <p>Mapy udostępniane są przez projekt OpenStreetMap, który jest tworzony przez setki tysięcy ludzi z całego świata.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Mapas dá-lhe acesso a mapas de todo o mundo. Permite que encontre rapidamente o local que procura, procurando por uma cidade ou rua, ou localizando um sítio para um encontro com um amigo.</p>
    <p>A aplicação Mapas utiliza a base de dados colaborativa OpenStreetMap, feita por centenas de milhares de pessoas por todo o globo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Mapas oferece a você acesso rápido a mapas ao redor de todo o mundo. Permite que você localize rapidamente o local que deseja encontrar através da pesquisa por uma cidade ou rua e a encontrar um local para encontrar um amigo(a).</p>
    <p>Mapas usa o banco de dados colaborativo do OpenStreetMap, com contribuições de centenas de milhares de pessoas ao redor do planeta.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Hărți vă oferă acces rapid la hărți din întreaga lume. Vă permite să găsiți rapid locul pe care îl căutați, să căutați un oraș sau o stradă sau să localizați un loc unde să întâlniți un prieten.</p>
    <p>Hărți colaborează cu OpenStreetMap folosind o întreagă bază de date, realizată de sute de mii de oameni de pe întregul pământ.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Приложение «Карты» позволяет получить быстрый доступ к картам по всему миру, находить места в городах, на улицах или указывать места для встречи с друзьями.</p>
    <p>Карты используют базу данных OpenStreetMap, созданную сотнями тысяч людей по всеми миру.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Aplikácia Mapy vám poskytuje rýchly prístup k mapám celého sveta. Umožňuje vám rýchlo nájsť miesto, ktoré hľadáte zadaním vyhľadávanej obce alebo ulice, prípadne zistiť polohu, kde sa máte stretnúť s priateľom.</p>
    <p>Aplikácia Mapy používa databázu projektu OpenStreetMap, na ktorej spolupracujú stovky tisícov ľudí z celého sveta.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Program omogoča hiter dostop do zemljevidov sveta. Omogoča hitro iskanje mest in ulic, različnih javnih prostorov, ki jih je nujno treba obiskati, ali mesta zmenka s prijatelji.</p>
    <p>Program uporablja podatkovno zbirko OpenStreetMap, ki jo ustvarja več sto tisoč posameznikov na vseh koncih sveta.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Гномове Карте вам дају брз приступ картама широм света. Омогућава вам да брзо и лако пронађете место које тражите тражећи град или улицу, или да одредите место за сусрет са пријатељима.</p>
    <p>Овај програм користи заједничку базу података „OpenStreetMap“, коју стварају стотине хиљада људи широм света.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Gnomove Karte vam daju brz pristup kartama širom sveta. Omogućava vam da brzo i lako pronađete mesto koje tražite tražeći grad ili ulicu, ili da odredite mesto za susret sa prijateljima.</p>
    <p>Ovaj program koristi zajedničku bazu podataka „OpenStreetMap“, koju stvaraju stotine hiljada ljudi širom sveta.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Kartor ger dig snabb tillgång till kartor över hela världen. Det låter dig hitta platsen du letar efter genom att söka efter en stad eller gata eller finna ett ställe att möta en vän på.</p>
    <p>Kartor använder kartdatabasen OpenStreetMap, skapad genom samarbete av flera hundratusentals personer över hela världen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="te">
    <p>పటాలు మీకు ప్రపంచవ్యాప్తంగా ఉన్న పటాలకు శీఘ్రంగా ప్రాప్యతను కల్పిస్తుంది. ఒక నగరం లేదా వీధి, లేదా ఒక స్నేహితుడు కలుసుకునే ప్రదేశాన్ని ప్రవేశపెట్టి వెదకడం ద్వారా మీరు వెతుకుతున్న ప్రదేశాన్ని త్వరగా కనుగొనడంలో సహకరిస్తుంది.</p>
    <p>పటాలు ప్రపంచవ్యాప్తంగా వేలమంది వ్యక్తుల సహకారంతో తయారుచేయబడిన ఓపెన్‌స్ట్రీట్‌మ్యాప్ డేటాబేసును వినియోగిస్తుంది.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tg">
    <p>Харитаҳо барои шумо ба тамоми ҳаритаҳои ҷаҳон имкони дастраси зуд медиҳад. Ин барнома ба шумо инчунин имкон медиҳад, ки тавонед шаҳр ё кӯчаи мехостагиро ёфт кунед ё барои бо дӯстон фохӯрдан маконро муайян кунед.</p>
    <p>Харитаҳо пойгоҳи иттилоотии OpenStreetMap-ро, ки бо миллионҳо одам аз тамоми ҷаҳон ташкил шудааст, истифода мебарад.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Haritalar, dünya çapındaki haritalara hızla erişmenizi sağlar. Şehir ya da sokak araması yoluyla aramakta olduğunuz yeri hızla bulmanızı veya arkadaşınızla buluşacağınız yeri belirlemenizi sağlar.</p>
    <p>Haritalar, küresel çapta yüzbinlerce insanca hazırlanan OpenStreetMap ile ortak veri tabanını kullanır.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Карти надають швидкий доступ до карт по всьому світу. Вони дозволяють швидко знайти місце, яке ви шукаєте, через пошук міста, вулиці, ба визначити місце для зустрічі з друзями.</p>
    <p>Карти використовують колективну базу даних OpenStreetMap, яку роблять тисячі осіб по всій планеті.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="vi">
    <p>Maps giúp bạn truy cập bản đồ trên toàn thế giới. Nó cho phép bạn nhanh chóng tìm đến chỗ mà bạn đang tìm bằng cách tìm thành phố hay đường, hoặc vị trí địa điểm để gặp mặt bạn bè.</p>
    <p>Maps dùng cơ sở dữ liệu OpenStreetMap cộng tác, được tạo bởi hàng trăm ngàn người trên toàn cầu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>地图应用帮您快速访问世界各地的地图。允许您快速定位到城市、街道或约会地点。</p>
    <p>地图应用使用了 OpenStreetMap 数据库，该数据库由全球成千上万的人们协同制作。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_HK">
    <p>Maps 讓你可以快速存取世界上的地圖。它讓你快速的找到想找的位置，只要搜尋城市或街道，也可以定位要與朋友見面的場所。</p>
    <p>Maps 使用共同協作的 OpenStreetMap 資料庫，由全球各地難以計數的人們共同製作。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>《地圖》讓您可以快速存取世界上的地圖。它讓您快速的找到想找的位置，只要搜尋城市或街道，也可以定位要與朋友見面的場所。</p>
    <p>《地圖》使用共同協作的 OpenStreetMap 資料庫，由全球各地難以計數的人們共同製作。</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.Maps.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-maps/raw/HEAD/data/screenshots/maps-main.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-maps/raw/HEAD/data/screenshots/maps-route.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-maps/raw/HEAD/data/screenshots/maps-pinpoint.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-07-01" version="42.3">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix setting the correct month in the public transit time settings</li>
          <li>Fix crash on exit</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="42.2" date="2022-05-28">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix using Ukrainian address format for addresses in Ukraine</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="42.1" date="2022-04-22">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Update GWeather dependency to version 4</li>
          <li>Update the Resrobot public transit plugin to use the v2.1 API</li>
          <li>Don't optimize away keep left/right instructions for turn-by-turn routes</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="42.0" date="2022-03-19">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Allow paralell installation of development versions and stable releases</li>
          <li>Add support for the \"prefer dark style\" preference</li>
          <li>Add support for maps: URIs with search queries</li>
          <li>Use more fine-tuned initial zoom level for more place types</li>
          <li>Show u-turn icons in turn-by-turn routes</li>
          <li>Improve appdata metadata with updated screenshots</li>
          <li>Use the location portal when sandboxed</li>
          <li>Only use location bias when searching at high zoom to avoid problems in the Photon search engine</li>
          <li>Remember the state of showing the scale between runs</li>
          <li>Tidy up showing time labels in public transit itineraries by using tabular numbers</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2022-02-12" version="41.4">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-12-04" version="41.2">
      <ul>
        <li>Translation updates</li>
      </ul>
    </release>
    <release version="41.1" date="2021-10-30">
      <ul>
        <li>Translation updates</li>
      </ul>
    </release>
    <release version="41.0" date="2021-09-18">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Use new GNOME style icons for search results</li>
          <li>Show e-mail addresse for places when available</li>
          <li>Show take-away availability for restaurants and similar places</li>
          <li>Remove Facebook check-in support, as it's not supported by libgfbgraph anymore</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="40.4" date="2021-08-13">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Update donation and wiki web links in appdata</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="40.3" date="2021-07-09">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix regression when signing in for OSM editing</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-06-04" version="40.2">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix crashes when no aerial tile definition is available</li>
          <li>Fix cut-off text in place bubble in some translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="40.1" date="2021-05-01">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix a bug where unfavoring a place made it unselectable until after a restart</li>
          <li>Use country code attribute from GraphHopper/Photon geocode results to improve
accuracy of address formatting among others</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-03-20" version="40.0">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Redesigned place bubbles</li>
          <li>Adaptive UI for the place bubbles on small screens</li>
          <li>Show translated place names in user's language when available</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.38.4" date="2021-02-12">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix a bug resulting in writing a broken last view position on exit in some circumstances</li>
          <li>Fix a bug preventing wrapping around at the date line with dark tiles</li>
          <li>Fix a bug causing hanging in cases when dragging around route markers</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.38.3" date="2021-01-09">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix a bug where place details gets lost after searching again for the same place</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-11-21" version="3.38.2">
      <description>
        <ul>Translation updates</ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-10-07" version="3.38.1.1">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix a race-condition bug in search-as-you-type resulting in out-of-sync search results in some circumstances</li>
          <li>Fix updating missing details after editing a POI in OpenStreetMap</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-10-03" version="3.38.1">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Show error message in popover when a search request has failed</li>
          <li>Fix exception on shutdown when unregistering DBus</li>
          <li>Fix "no network" display to fit on smaller screens</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-09-12" version="3.38.0">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Initial adpative UI</li>
          <li>Added night mode</li>
          <li>Added support for hybrid aerial layer</li>
          <li>Public transit plugin for South Africa (GoMetro)</li>
          <li>Improved keyboard navigation in routing sidebar</li>
          <li>Make more use of localized number formatting</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-07-04" version="3.36.4">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix an issue where some search result gets the wrong level of name</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-04-25" version="3.36.2">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Don't reset query points when routing fails (e.g. no public transit provider is available) to allow switching mode with the same query</li>
          <li>Fix a bug not displaying tiles south of the equator when using --local command line option</li>
          <li>Allow entering DMS coordinates without comma between latitude and logitude parts</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-03-28" version="3.36.1">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Updated POI defintions for OpenStreetMap editing</li>
          <li>Fix link to sign up for an OpenStreetMap account</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.36.0" date="2020-03-07">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Initial support for public transit routing</li>
          <li>Re-arrange context menu. Move "export as image" to hamburger menu</li>
          <li>Avoid flickering the current location marker when changes</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-01-04" version="3.34.3">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added Malay translation</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.34.2" date="2019-11-23">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix generating Wikipedia URLs in some cases</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-10-07" version="3.34.1">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Update tile size to 512 px when using --local option</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-09-09" version="3.34.0">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Auto-complete "search-as-you-type"</li>
          <li>Revamped sharing dialog</li>
          <li>Support opening OpenStreetMap URLs</li>
          <li>Faster startup</li>
          <li>Remember map style last used when starting (street or aerial view)</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.32.2.1" date="2019-05-21">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix misaligned rendering of shape layers with the new map tiles</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.32.2" date="2019-05-06">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Remove some unnessesary instructions in turn-by-turn route searches</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.32.1" date="2019-03-31">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Updated Croatian translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-03-11" version="3.32.0">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Show live-updated thumbnails for the street/aerial layer switcher, instead of (outdated) hard-code thumbnails</li>
          <li>Move app menu to the headerbar</li>
          <li>Updated application icon</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <recommends>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
  <provides>
    <id>gnome-maps.desktop</id>
  </provides>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <developer_name>The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">GNOME 專案</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 项目</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="vi">Dự án GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Проєкт GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">GNOME Projesi</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Гномов пројекат</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Proiectul GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Проект GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਪਰੋਜੈਕਟ</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="oc">Lo projècte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Het Gnome-project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ne">जिनोम परियोजना</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb">GNOME prosjektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ms">Projek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="mjw">GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lv">GNOME projekts</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">GNOME projektas</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">그놈 프로젝트</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="kk">GNOME жобасы</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Il progetto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="is">GNOME verkefnið</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Proyek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">מיזם GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">O Proxecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fur">Il progjet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Le projet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Gnome-projekti</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fa">پروژهٔ گنوم</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">GNOME proiektua</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">El Proyecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">La projekto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Το έργο GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Das GNOME-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="bg">Проектът GNOME</developer_name>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Maps</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-maps/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.gnome.org/donate/</url>
  <update_contact>gnome-maps-list@gnome.org</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-maps</translation>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-desecration">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-slavery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-worship">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-homosexuality">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-prostitution">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-adultery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-appearance">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <custom>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">workstation</value>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">mobile</value>
  </custom>
</component>