<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>gnome.gnome-weather</pkgname>
  <icon width="64" type="cached" height="64">org.gnome.Weather.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" height="128" type="cached">org.gnome.Weather.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.Weather</id>
  <name>Weather</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">天氣</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">天氣</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">天气</name>
  <name lang="vi">Thời tiết</name>
  <name lang="uk">Погода</name>
  <name lang="tr">Hava Durumu</name>
  <name lang="th">รายงานอากาศ</name>
  <name lang="tg">Обу ҳаво</name>
  <name lang="te">వాతావరణం</name>
  <name lang="ta">வானிலை</name>
  <name lang="sv">Väder</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Vreme</name>
  <name lang="sr">Време</name>
  <name lang="sl">Vreme</name>
  <name lang="sk">Počasie</name>
  <name lang="ru">Погода</name>
  <name lang="ro">Vreme</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Meteorologia</name>
  <name lang="pt">Meteorologia</name>
  <name lang="pl">Pogoda</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਮੌਸਮ</name>
  <name lang="oc">Metèo</name>
  <name lang="nl">Weer</name>
  <name lang="ne">मौसम</name>
  <name lang="nb">Vær</name>
  <name lang="ms">Cuaca</name>
  <name lang="ml">കാലാവസ്ഥ</name>
  <name lang="mjw">Botor</name>
  <name lang="lv">Laikapstākļi</name>
  <name lang="lt">Orai</name>
  <name lang="ko">날씨</name>
  <name lang="kn">ಹವಾಮಾನ</name>
  <name lang="kk">Ауа райы</name>
  <name lang="ja">天気</name>
  <name lang="it">Meteo</name>
  <name lang="is">Veður</name>
  <name lang="id">Cuaca</name>
  <name lang="hu">Időjárás</name>
  <name lang="hr">Vrijeme</name>
  <name lang="he">מזג האוויר</name>
  <name lang="gl">Clima</name>
  <name lang="gd">Aimsir</name>
  <name lang="ga">Aimsir</name>
  <name lang="fy">Waar</name>
  <name lang="fur">Meteo</name>
  <name lang="fr">Météo</name>
  <name lang="fi">Sää</name>
  <name lang="fa">آب‌وهوا</name>
  <name lang="eu">Eguraldia</name>
  <name lang="et">Ilm</name>
  <name lang="es">Meteorología</name>
  <name lang="eo">Vetero</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Weather</name>
  <name lang="el">Καιρός</name>
  <name lang="de">Wetter</name>
  <name lang="da">Vejr</name>
  <name lang="cs">Počasí</name>
  <name lang="ckb">کەش و هەوا</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">Meteorologia</name>
  <name lang="ca">Meteorologia</name>
  <name lang="bs">Vrijeme</name>
  <name lang="bn_IN">আবহাওয়া</name>
  <name lang="bg">Прогноза</name>
  <name lang="be">Надвор'е</name>
  <name lang="as">বতৰ</name>
  <name lang="ar">الطقس</name>
  <name lang="an">Orache</name>
  <name lang="af">Weer</name>
  <name lang="ab">Амш зеиԥшроу</name>
  <summary>Show weather conditions and forecast</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">顯示天氣狀況與氣象預報</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_HK">顯示天氣狀況與氣象預報</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">显示天气状况和天气预报</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Xem tình hình thời tiết và dự báo</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Показувати погодні умови і прогноз</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Hava durumunu ve tahminleri göster</summary>
  <summary lang="th">แสดงสภาพอากาศและการพยากรณ์</summary>
  <summary lang="tg">Намоиш додани шароитҳо ва пешгӯии обу ҳаво</summary>
  <summary lang="te">వాతావరణ పరిస్థితులను, సూచినలను చూపించు</summary>
  <summary lang="ta">வானிலை நிலவரம் மற்றும் முன்கணிப்பை காட்டு</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Visar prognoser och väderförhållanden</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Prikažite vremenske prilike i prognozu</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Прикажите временске прилике и прогнозу</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Spremljanje trenutnih vremenskih razmer in napovedi</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Zobrazuje poveternostné podmienky a predpoveď počasia</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Показать погодные условия и прогноз</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Afișează prognoza și condițiile meteorologice</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Mostra condições meteorológicas e previsão do tempo</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Mostra as condições meteorológicas e previsões</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Wyświetlanie warunków pogodowych i prognozy</summary>
  <summary lang="pa">ਮੌਸਮ ਹਾਲਤ ਅਤੇ ਭਵਿੱਖਬਾਣੀ ਵੇਖੋ</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Aficha lo temps que fa e las previsions</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Weersomstandigheden en -verwachtingen tonen</summary>
  <summary lang="ne">हालको मौसम अवस्था अनुगमन गर्दछ, र पूर्वानुमान गर्दछ</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Vis værforhold og værmelding</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Tunjuk keadaan dan ramalan cuaca</summary>
  <summary lang="ml">കാലാവസ്ഥയുടെ നിഅയും പ്രവചനവും കാണിക്കുക</summary>
  <summary lang="mjw">Botor pen palodep birta</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Rādīt laikapstākļu prognozi</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Rodyti orų sąlygas ir prognozes</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">날씨와 일기 예보 보기</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">Ауа рай күйін және болжамын көрсету</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">天気の概況と予報を表示します</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Mostra condizioni e previsioni meteo</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Birta veðurslýsingar og veðurspár</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Tampilkan kondisi dan ramalan cuaca</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Időjárási viszonyok és előrejelzés megjelenítése</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Pogledajte vašu lokalnu vremensku prognozu</summary>
  <summary lang="he">הצגת תנאים ואת תחזית מזג האוויר</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Mostrar as condicións e predicións do tempo</summary>
  <summary lang="gd">Seall an aimsir an-dràsta agus ro-aithris</summary>
  <summary lang="ga">Taispeáin staid agus réamhaisnéis na haimsire</summary>
  <summary lang="fy">Waaromstannicheden en waarfoarsizzingen sjen litte</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Mostre condizions e previsions meteo</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Affiche le temps qu’il fait et les prévisions</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Näytä säätiedot ja -ennuste</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">نمایش وضعیت و پیش‌بینی آب‌وهوا</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Erakutsi eguraldiaren egoera eta iragarpena</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Ilmaolude ja ilmateate kuvamine</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Mostrar las condiciones meteorológicas y el pronóstico</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Montras veterajn statojn kaj prognozojn</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Show weather conditions and forecast</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Εμφάνιση συνθηκών καιρού και πρόβλεψης</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Wetterberichte und -vorhersagen anzeigen</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Vis vejrforhold og -udsigt</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Zobrazte si povětrnostní podmínky a předpověď počasí</summary>
  <summary lang="ckb">دۆخی کەش و هەوا پیشان بدە</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Mostra les condicions actuals i la predicció meteorològica</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Mostra les condicions actuals i la predicció meteorològica</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Prikaži vremenske uslove i prognozu</summary>
  <summary lang="bn_IN">আবহাওয়ার পরিস্থিতি এবং পূর্বাভাস দেখান</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Показване на метеорологичното време и прогноза</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Паказ прагнозаў і бягучага надвор'я</summary>
  <summary lang="as">বতৰৰ অৱস্থা আৰু পূৰ্বানুমান দেখুৱাওক</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">اعرض حالة الطقس و النشرة الجوية</summary>
  <summary lang="an">Amostrar as condicions meteorolochicas y o pronostico</summary>
  <summary lang="af">Wys weerstoestande en voorspellings</summary>
  <summary lang="ab">Шәахәаԥш амш зеиԥшроу, насгьы  уи аҽеиҭакшьа</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+ and CC-BY-3.0 and CC-BY-SA-3.0</project_license>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>HighContrast</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>SearchProvider</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <description>
    <p>
      A small application that allows you to monitor the current weather
      conditions for your city, or anywhere in the world.
    </p>
    <p>
      It provides access to detailed forecasts, up to 7 days, with hourly
      details for the current and next day, using various internet services.
    </p>
    <p>
      It also optionally integrates with the GNOME Shell, allowing you to see
      the current conditions of the most recently searched cities by just
      typing the name in the Activities Overview.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ab">
    <p>Идыум аҧшьы  амш зеиԥшроу агәаҭаразыШәықалақь, мамзар даҽа ҭыԥк аҟны.</p>
    <p>Насгьы иара ишәынаҭоит алшара амш зеиԥшрахо нҭкааны (7 мш рҟынӡа) аилкаараеиуеиԥшым аинтернет маҵзурақәа рҟны.</p>
    <p>Хықәкыла аԥшьы GNOME Shell иадцалоуп, уи ишәынаҭоит алшараизаамҭанытәиу аҭагылазаашьа ааигәа шәызшьҭаз ақалақьқәа рҟны агәаҭаралаԥшхагаратә режимла ақалақь ахьӡ анашәырбалак.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="af">
    <p>'n klein program waarmee jy die huidige weerstoestande vir jou stad, of enige plek ter wêreld, kan monitor.</p>
    <p>Dit bied toegang tot gedetailleerde voorspellings, tot 7 dae, met uurlikse besonderhede vir die huidige en volgende dag, deur gebruik te maak van verskeie internet dienste.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="an">
    <p>Una chicota aplicación que le permite monitorizar l'orache actual en a suya ciudat, u en qualsiquier puesto d'o mundo.</p>
    <p>Proporciona acceso a pronosticos actualizaus, dica 7 días, con detalles cada hora ta o día actual y o siguient, usando quantos servicios d'Internet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>تطبيق صغير يتيح لك مراقبة حالات الطقس الحالية لمدينتك أو أي مدينة تريدها في العالم.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="as">
    <p>এটা সৰু এপ্লিকেচন যি আপোনাক আপোনাৰ নগৰ, অথবা পৃথিৱীৰ যিকোনো ঠাইত বৰ্তমান বতৰ অৱস্থা পৰ্যবেক্ষণ কৰাৰ অনুমতি দিয়ে।</p>
    <p>ই বিভিন্ন ইন্টাৰনেট সেৱাসমূহ ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি বৰ্তমান আৰু পৰৱৰ্তী দিনৰ বাবে প্ৰতি ঘন্টা বিৱৰণসমূহৰ সৈতে, ৭ দিন লৈকে, বিৱৰিত আগজাননী প্ৰদান কৰে।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Маленькая праграма, якая дазваляе сачыць надвор'ем у вашым горадзе ці ў любым іншым месцы свету.</p>
    <p>Яна забяспечвае доступ да падрабязных прагнозаў (да сямі дзён) з пагадзіннай дэталізацыяй на сёння і заўтра.</p>
    <p>Можа інтэгравацца ў абалонку GNOME, што дазваляе глядзець надвор'е ў гарадах, якія вы нядаўна шукалі, проста напісаўшы назву аднаго з іх у меню Агляд дзейнасці.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Малка програма за наблюдение на текущото метеорологично време в града ви или някъде другаде по света.</p>
    <p>Има възможност за подробни прогнози — до седмица напред, с почасово състояние за текущия и следващия дни. Ползва различни източници по Интернет.</p>
    <p>Може да се интегрира и с обвивката на GNOME — GNOME Shell, което ви дава възможност да видите текущите метеорологични условия в скоро търсените градове като просто напишете името им в прегледа на дейностите.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bn_IN">
    <p>একটি ছোট অ্যাপ্লিকেশন যা আপনাকে আপনার শহর বা বিশ্বের যে কোনও জায়গায় বর্তমান আবহাওয়ার পরিস্থিতি পর্যবেক্ষণ করতে দেয়।</p>
    <p>এটি বিভিন্ন ইন্টারনেট পরিষেবা ব্যবহার করে বর্তমান এবং পরের দিনটির জন্য প্রতি ঘন্টার বিশদ বিশদ সহ ৭ দিন অবধি বিস্তারিত পূর্বাভাসের অ্যাক্সেস সরবরাহ করে।</p>
    <p>এটি ঐচ্ছিকভাবে জিনোম শেল এর সাথে সংহত করে, সক্রিয় ক্রিয়াকলাপের ওভারভিউতে নামটি টাইপ করে আপনাকে সর্বাধিক সন্ধান করা শহরগুলির বর্তমান অবস্থা দেখতে দেয়।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Mala aplikacija koja dopušta prikaz trenutnih vremenskih uslova za vaš grad, ili bilo gdje u svijetu.</p>
    <p>Omogućava pristup detaljnijoj vremenskoj prognozi, 7 dana unaprijed, sa detaljima po satu za trenutni i sljedeći dan, koristeći različite internet usluge.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Un programa petit que us permet fer un seguiment de les condicions meteorològiques actuals a la vostra ciutat o a qualsevol lloc del món.</p>
    <p>També podeu accedir a les previsions actualitzades de fins a 7 dies i per hores pel dia actual i l'endemà. Proporcionades per diversos serveis d'Internet.</p>
    <p>Opcionalment també es pot integrar amb el GNOME Shell de manera que vegeu les condicions actuals de les últimes ciutats que hàgiu cercat teclejant el seu nom al resum d'activitats.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca@valencia">
    <p>Un programa petit que vos permet fer un seguiment de les condicions meteorològiques actuals a la vostra ciutat o a qualsevol lloc del món.</p>
    <p>També podeu accedir a les previsions actualitzades de fins a 7 dies i per hores pel dia actual i l'endemà. Proporcionades per diversos serveis d'Internet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ckb">
    <p>نەرمەکاڵایەکی بچووک ڕێگەت دەکات چاودێری کەش و هەوای ئێستا بکەیت و بۆ ئەو شوینەی لێیت و هەموو جیهان.</p>
    <p>ڕێگەت دەدات بچیتە دۆخی کەش و هەوای زیاتر، بۆ ٧ رۆژ، لەگەڵ زانیاری بۆ هەموو کاژێرەکان  بۆ ئەم رۆژە و رۆژەکانی تر، بە بەکارهێنانی خزمەتگوزاری ئینتەرنێت.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Malá aplikace, díky které můžete sledovat aktuální povětrnostní podmínky ve svém městě nebo kdekoliv na světě.</p>
    <p>Díky využití několika internetových služeb poskytuje podrobnou předpověď až na 7 dní, pro dnešek a zítřek s detaily po hodinách.</p>
    <p>Umí se integrovat do prostředím GNOME Shell, takže si můžete zobrazit aktuální počasí v nedávno vyhledaných městech napsaním jejich názvu v přehledu činností.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Et lille program, som giver dig mulighed for at overvåge de nuværende vejrforhold i din by, eller hvor som helst i verden.</p>
    <p>Det tilbyder adgang til detaljerede vejrudsigter, op til syv dage, med detaljer hver time for i dag og i morgen ved at benytte forskellige internettjenester.</p>
    <p>Der er også valgfri integration med GNOME Shell, som tillader dig at se de nuværende forhold i de senest søgte byer, blot ved at indtaste byens navn i Aktivitets-oversigten.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Eine kleine Anwendung, welche es Ihnen erlaubt, das aktuelle Wetter für Ihre Stadt oder für einen beliebigen Ort auf der Welt zu betrachten.</p>
    <p>Bietet Zugang zu detaillierter Wettervorhersage über bis zu 7 Tage mit stündlichen Details für den laufenden und den folgenden Tag auf Basis mehrerer Internetdienste.</p>
    <p>Lässt sich auf Wunsch in die GNOME-Shell einbinden, so dass Sie sich über das aktuelle Wetter jeder eingegebenen Stadt informieren können, indem Sie den Ortsnamen in die Aktivitätenübersicht eingeben.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Μια μικρή εφαρμογή που σας επιτρέπει να παρακολουθείτε τις τρέχουσες καιρικές συνθήκες για την πόλη σας, ή για οποιαδήποτε άλλη τοποθεσία στον κόσμο.</p>
    <p>Παρέχει πρόσβαση σε λεπτομερείς προβλέψεις, έως και 7 ημέρες, με ωριαία στοιχεία για την τρέχουσα και την επόμενη μέρα, με τη χρήση διαφόρων υπηρεσιών διαδικτύου.</p>
    <p>Επίσης ενσωματώνεται προαιρετικά με το GNOME Shell, επιτρέποντάς σας να δείτε τις τρέχουσες συνθήκες της πόλης που αναζητήθηκε πρόσφατα απλά πληκτρολογώντας το όνομα στην επισκόπηση των Δραστηριοτήτων.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>A small application that allows you to monitor the current weather conditions for your city, or anywhere in the world.</p>
    <p>It provides access to detailed forecasts, up to 7 days, with hourly details for the current and next day, using various internet services.</p>
    <p>It also optionally integrates with the GNOME Shell, allowing you to see the current conditions of the most recently searched cities by just typing the name in the Activities Overview.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p>Eta aplikaĵo kiu permesas al vi observi la nunajn veterajn kondiĉojn de via urbo, aŭ ie ajn en la mondo.</p>
    <p>Disponigas la atingon je detalaj prognozoj, ĝis 7 tagoj, kun hora detalo por la nuna kaj sekvanta tago, pere de diversaj retaj serviloj.</p>
    <p>Ĝi ankaŭ laŭvole integras kun la GNOME Ŝelo, permesante al vi vidi la nunajn kondiĉojn de la plej freŝe serĉitaj urboj per nura tajpo de ties nomo en la Superrigardo de Agoj.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Una pequeña aplicación que le permite monitorizar el tiempo actual en su ciudad, o en cualquier lugar del mundo.</p>
    <p>Proporciona acceso a pronósticos actualizados, hasta 7 días, con detalles cada hora para el día actual y el siguiente, usando varios servicios de Internet.</p>
    <p>También se integra opcionalmente con GNOME Shell, permitiéndole ver las condiciones actuales de cualquier ciudad buscada recientemente simplemente escribiendo su nombre en la vista de Actividades.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Väike rakendus, mille abil saab jälgida praeguseid ilmaolusid sinu linnas või ükskõik kus maailmas.</p>
    <p>Erinevate internetiteenuste kaasabil saab rakendusega vaadata kuni 7 päeva ilmateateid koos igatunniste üksikasjadega praeguse ja järgmise päeva kohta.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Aplikazio txiki bat da, zure herriko edo munduko beste leku bateko uneko eguraldiaren berri ematen dizuna.</p>
    <p>Iragarpen xehatuak ikusteko aukera ematen du, 7 egun artekoak, ordukako xehetasunak ematen dituztenak uneko egunerako eta hurrengo egunerako, hainbat Interneteko zerbitzu erabiliz.</p>
    <p>Aukeran, GNOME Shell-ekin integratu daiteke, azken aldian bilatutako herrien uneko baldintzak ikusteko haien izena jardueren ikuspegian idatzita.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fa">
    <p>برنامه‌ای کوچک که می‌گذارد وضعیت آب‌وهوای کنونی شهرتان یا هر جای دیگری از جهان را بررسی کنید.</p>
    <p>با استفاده از خدمات اینترنتی مختلف، دسترسی به پیش‌بینی‌های دقیق را تا ۷ روز، با جزییات ساعتی برای امروز و فردا را فراهم می‌کند.</p>
    <p>همچنین به‌طور اختیاری با پوستهٔ گنوم یکپارچه شده، اجازهٔ دیدن وضعیت کنونی شهرهای جست‌وجو شدهٔ اخیر را تنها با نوشتن نام در نمای‌کلی فعّالیت‌ها را می‌دهد.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Pieni sovellus, joka mahdollistaa kotikaupunkisi tai minkä tahansa muun sijainnin säätietojen hakemisen.</p>
    <p>Se tarjoaa eri verkkopalveluita käyttäen yksityiskohtaisen ennusteen seuraavan viikon ajalle sekä tuntikohtaiset tiedot kuluvalle ja seuraavalle päivälle.</p>
    <p>Se myös valinnaisesti integroituu Gnome-työpöytään, jolloin viimeksi tarkasteltujen sijaintien säätiedot ovat nähtävissä yleisnäkymässä kirjoittamalla paikkakunnan nimen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Une petite application qui vous permet de surveiller les conditions météo dans votre ville ou n’importe où dans le monde.</p>
    <p>Elle permet d’accéder à des prévisions détaillées jusqu’à 7 jours, avec des détails horaires pour le jour actuel et le lendemain, en utilisant divers services internet.</p>
    <p>Elle peut également s’intégrer à GNOME Shell, permettant de voir les conditions actuelles de n’importe quelle ville configurée en tapant simplement le nom dans la vue d’ensemble des activités.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Une piçule aplicazion che a permet di tegnî di voli lis condizions meteo atuâi de tô citât, o cualsisei puest intal mont.</p>
    <p>Al furnìs acès a previsions in detai (fin a 7 dîs), cun detais oraris par vuê e pal prossim dì, doprant plui servizis internet.</p>
    <p>Volint ancje a si integre cun GNOME Shell, permetint di viodi lis condizions meteo atuâi des citâts plui cirudis di resint; al baste scrivi il lôr non inte Panoramiche Ativitâts.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fy">
    <p>In lytse applikaasje dy't de hjoeddeistiche waarsomstannicheden byhâld foar jo stêd, of earne oars op'e wrâld.</p>
    <p>It jout tagong ta in detaillearre waarfoarsizzing, oant 7 dagen foarút, mei in oerliks oersjoch far hjoerd en moarn, en makket gebrûk fan ferskate ynternet tsjinsten.</p>
    <p>Kin yntegrearre wurde yn GNOME Shell, wat de hjoeddeistiche waaromstannicheden fan de meast sochte stêden sichtber makket troch allinich mar harren namme yn it Activiteiten Oersjoch te typen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ga">
    <p>Feidhmchláirín a ligeann duit monatóireacht a dhéanamh ar aimsir reatha do cathrach, nó aimsir aon áite eile sa domhan.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gd">
    <p>Aplacaid bheag a leigeas leat sùil a chumail air staid na h-aimsire sa bhaile agad no àite sam bith air an t-saoghal.</p>
    <p>Bheir e dhut ro-aithris mionaideach suas gu 7 làithean le fiosrachadh airson gach uair airson an diugh ’s a-màireach le taic o chaochladh sheirbheisean eadar-lìn.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Un pequena aplicación que lle permitirá facer un seguimento das condicións meteorolóxicas actuais da súa cidade, ou calquera lugar do mundo.</p>
    <p>Fornece acceso a predicións detalladas ate 7 días, con información por hora do día actual e seguinte, usando varios servizos de internet.</p>
    <p>Tamén se integra con GNOME Shell o que lle permite ver as condicións meteorolóxicas actuais das cidades máis buscadas recentemente escribindo o seu nome na Vista de actividades.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>יישום קטן המאפשר לך לצפות בתנאי מזג האוויר הנוכחיים בעיר שלך או בכל מקום אחר בעולם.</p>
    <p>הוא מספק גישה לתחזיות מפורטות, עד לשבוע ימים, פרטים לפי שעה ליום הנוכחי ולזה שלאחריו, באמצעות שרתי אינטרנט שונים.</p>
    <p>ניתן לשלב אותו עם מעטפת GNOME, המאפשרת לך לראות את תנאי מזג האוויר של רוב הערים שחיפשת לאחרונה, בהקלדת שם בסקירת פעילויות.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Mala aplikacija koja vam omogućuje praćenje trenutne vremenske prognoze u vašem gradu, ili bilo gdje na svijetu.</p>
    <p>Omogućuje vam pristup opširnoj prognozi vremena, do 7dana, sa satnim pojedinostima za trenutni i sljedeći dan, koristeći razne internetske usluge.</p>
    <p>Isto tako se po izboru integrira s GNOME ljuskom, omogućujući vam pregled trenutne vremenske prognoze najčešće traženih gradova, jednostavno samo upisivanjem naziva grada u Aktivnosti pregledu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>Egy kicsi alkalmazás, amely lehető teszi a jelenlegi időjárási körülmények figyelését a településén vagy bárhol a világon.</p>
    <p>Részletes előrejelzésekhez biztosít hozzáférést 7 napos időtávra, valamint különféle internetes szolgáltatásokat felhasználva óránkénti részleteket nyújt az aktuális és a következő napra.</p>
    <p>Ezen felül opcionálisan beépül a GNOME parancsértelmezőbe, lehetővé téve a leggyakrabban keresett városok aktuális időjárásának megtekintését a név begépelésével a tevékenységek áttekintőjébe.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Aplikasi kecil yang memungkinkan Anda memantau kondisi cuaca saat ini untuk kota Anda, atau dimanapun di dunia.</p>
    <p>Ini memberikan akses ke ramalan cuaca terrinci, sampai dengan 7 hari, dengan rincian per jam bagi hari ini dan besok, memakai berbagai layanan internet.</p>
    <p>Ini secara opsional juga terintegrasi dengan GNOME Shell, memungkinkan Anda melihat kondisi saat ini dari kota yang baru-baru ini dicari hanya dengan mengetikkan namanya dalam Ringkasan Aktivitas.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>Lítið forrit til að fylgjast með veðurskilyrðum og spám fyrir ákveðinn stað, eða í heiminum öllum.</p>
    <p>Það veitir aðgang að nákvæmum veðurspám, allt upp í 7 daga fram í tímann, með upplýsingar á klukkustundar fresti fyrir næstu 2 daga; það styðst við ýmsar þjónustur á internetinu.</p>
    <p>Hægt er að fella það inn í GNOME Skelina, þannig að þú getur séð veðurskilyrði í þeim borgum sem síðast hefur verið leitað að með því einu að slá nafn þeirra inn í aðgerðayfirlitið.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Una semplice applicazione per controllare le condizioni meteorologiche della propria città o di qualsiasi altra località.</p>
    <p>Fornisce accesso a previsioni dettagliate (fino a sette giorni) con dettagli orari del giorno attuale e di quello successivo sfruttando molteplici servizi Internet.</p>
    <p>Può anche essere integrata, opzionalmente, con GNOME Shell, consentendo di visualizzare le condizioni correnti delle città visitate recentemente digitandone il nome nella panoramica «Attività».</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>あなたの街や、世界中の都市の現在の天候を確認することができる小さなアプリケーションです。</p>
    <p>さまざまなインターネットサービスを使用して詳細な天気予報を参照できます。週間天気予報や、当日と翌日の時間ごとの詳細な天気予報などが利用できます。</p>
    <p>GNOME Shell と統合することができ、アクティビティ画面で都市名を入力することで、よく調べる都市の現在の天候を参照することができます。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <p>Өз қалаңыз, немесе әлемнің басқа жерлері үшін ағымдағы ауа райы жағдайын көрсететін кішігірім қолданба.</p>
    <p>Ол интернеттің бірнеше көздері ұсынатын, 7 күнге дейін алға, ал ағымдағы және келесі күн үшін сағат бойынша ақпараты бар ауа райы болжамдарын қарауды мүмкін қылады.</p>
    <p>Сонымен қатар, оның GNOME Shell ішіне интеграциясы бар, белсенділік көрінісінде жақында ізделген қалалар үшін ауа райы болжамын көрсете алады, ол үшін қала атын енгізу керек.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>당신이 사는 도시를 비롯하여 전세계 모든 곳의 현재 날씨를 알게 해주는 작은 프로그램입니다.</p>
    <p>여러 인터넷 서비스에서 일주일까지의 자세한 일기 예보를 가져와 알려드리며, 오늘과 내일 날씨는 시간별로도 알 수 있게 해드립니다.</p>
    <p>그놈 쉘에서 선택적으로 통합되므로, 활동 개요에 도시명을 입력하면 가장 최근에 검색된 도시의 현재 상태를 볼 수 있게 해줍니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Maža programa, kuri jums leidžia stebėti orų sąlygas jūsų mieste arba bet kur pasaulyje.</p>
    <p>Ji leidžia matyti iki 7 dienų prognozę su valandų tikslumo informacija, teikiamą įvairių interneto tarnybų.</p>
    <p>Ji taip pat integruojasi su GNOME Shell, leisdama matyti orų sąlygas paskutiniuose ieškotuose miestuose tiesiog įvedant jų pavadinimus veiklų apžvalgoje.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>Maza lietotne, kas palīdz uzraudzīt pašreizējos laikapstākļus jūsu pilsētā vai jebkurā citā pasaules vietā.</p>
    <p>Tā sniedz piekļuvi detalizētām prognozēm līdz 7 dienām, ar detalizāciju līdz stundām aktuālajai un nākamajai dienai, ko sniedz dažādi interneta servisi.</p>
    <p>To var arī integrēt ar GNOME čaulu, ļaujot redzēt apstākļus nesen meklētajās pilsētās, ievadot to nosaukumus aktivitāšu pārskatā.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ml">
    <p>നിങ്ങളുടെ നഗരത്തിലെയോ, ലോകത്തെ മറ്റേതെങ്കിലും സ്ഥലത്തിന്റെയോ ഇപ്പോഴത്തെ കാലവസ്ഥയെ നിരീക്ഷിക്കാൻ സഹായിക്കുന്ന ഒരു ചെറിയ പ്രയോഗം.</p>
    <p>വ്യത്യസ്ത ഇന്റർനെറ്റ് സേവനങ്ങൾ ഉപയോഗിച്ച് ഇന്നത്തെയും നാളത്തെയും മണിക്കൂർ തോറുമുള്ള വിവരങ്ങളുൾപ്പടെ ഏഴു ദിവസത്തേക്കുള്ള സമഗ്രമായ പ്രവചനങ്ങൾ ലഭ്യമാക്കുന്നു.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Sebuah aplikasi kecil yang membolehkan anda pantau keadaan cuaca semasa bandar anda, atau mana-mana lokasi di seluruh dunia.</p>
    <p>Ia menyediakan capaian ramalan terperinci, sehingga 7 hari, dengan perincian setiap jam bagi hari ini dan hari esok, menggunakan pelbagai perkhidmatan internet yang ada.</p>
    <p>Ia juga disepadukan secara pilihan dengan Shell GNOME, membolehkan anda melihat keadaan semasa bandar digelintar baru-baru hanya menaip nama dalam Selayang Pandang Aktiviti.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Et lite program som lar deg overvåke værforholdene for din by eller hvor som helst i verden.</p>
    <p>Gir tilgang til detaljerte værmeldinger opp til syv dager med detaljer time for time for i dag og i morgen. Bruker forskjellige tjenester på internett.</p>
    <p>Integrerer også med GNOME skallet, og lar deg se tilstanden i de mest brukte byene ved å søke etter navnet i aktivitetsoversikten.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ne">
    <p>एउटा सानो अनुप्रयोगले तपाईंलाई तपाईंको शहर, वा संसारको कुनै पनि ठाउँमा मौसमको सर्त निगरानी गर्न अनुमति दिन्छ।</p>
    <p>यसले विभिन्न इन्टरनेट सेवाहरू प्रयोग गरी वर्तमान र अर्को दिनको लागि घटेको विवरणहरूको साथ, ७ दिनसम्म विस्तृत पूर्वानुमानहरूको पहुँच प्रदान गर्दछ।</p>
    <p>यो पनि वैकल्पिक रूपमा जिनोम शैलसँग एकीकृत हुन्छ, तपाईंलाई हालको खोजी सहरहरूको अवस्था र क्रियाकलाप अवलोकनमा यसको नाम टाइप गरेर हालको अवस्था हेर्न अनुमति दिन्छ।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Een kleine toepassing waarmee u de actuele weersomstandigheden kunt volgen in uw woonplaats, of waar ook ter wereld.</p>
    <p>U krijgt gedetailleerde weersverwachtingen, tot aan 7 dagen vooruit, met elk uur nieuwe informatie voor de huidige en volgende dag, geleverd door diverse internetdiensten.</p>
    <p>Het integreert ook desgewenst met de Gnome Shell en biedt u de mogelijkheid de huidige weersomstandigheden te zien van de meest recent gezochte steden door gewoon de naam in te geven in het activiteitenoverzicht.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>Una pichona aplicacion que vos permet de susvelhar las condicions metèo dins vòstra vila o ont que siá dins lo mond.</p>
    <p>Permet d'accedir a de previsions detalhadas fins a 7 jorns, amb de detalhs oraris pel jorn actual e l'endeman, en utilizant divèrses servicis Internet.</p>
    <p>Tanben, se pòt integrar a GNOME Shell, e permetre de veire las condicions actualas de quins vila configurada que siá en picant simplament son nom dins la vista d'ensemble de las activitats.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pa">
    <p>ਇੱਕ ਛੋਟੀ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ, ਜੋ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਸ਼ਹਿਰ ਜਾਂ ਸੰਸਾਰ ਵਿੱਚੋਂ ਹੋਰ ਥਾਵਾਂ ਲਈ ਮੌਜੂਦਾ ਮੌਸਮ ਦਾ ਧਿਆਨ ਰੱਖਣ ਲਈ ਸਹਾਇਕ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p>ਇਹ ਵੱਖ-ਵੱਖ ਇੰਟਰਨੈੱਟ ਸੇਵਾਵਾਂ ਦੀ ਵਰਤੋਂ ਕਰਕੇ 7 ਦਿਨਾਂ ਤੱਕ ਦੀ ਵੇਰਵੇ ਸਮੇਤ ਭਵਿੱਖਬਾਣੀ ਦਿੰਦੀ ਹੈ, ਇਸ ਤੋਂ ਇਲਾਵਾ ਅੱਜ ਅਤੇ ਭਲਕ ਲਈ ਘੰਟਿਆਂ ਦੇ ਮੁਤਾਬਕ ਵੇਰਵਾ ਵੀ ਮੌਜੂਦ ਰਹਿੰਦਾ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p>ਇਹ ਚੋਣਵੇਂ ਰੂਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਗਨੋਮ ਸ਼ੈੱਲ ਨਾਲ ਵੀ ਜੁੜਿਆ ਹੋਈ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਸਰਗਰਮੀ ਸੰਖੇਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਕਿਸੇ ਲੱਭੇ ਗਏ ਸ਼ਹਿਰਾਂ ਦਾ ਕੇਵਲ ਨਾਂ ਲਿਖ ਕੇ ਹੀ ਮੌਜੂਦਾ ਹਾਲਤ ਨੂੰ ਵੇਖਣ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Mały program umożliwiający monitorowanie obecnych warunków pogodowych w miejscu zamieszkania lub w dowolnym miejscu na świecie.</p>
    <p>Zapewnia dostęp do dokładnych prognoz na 7 dni ze szczegółami na każdą godzinę w dniu bieżącym oraz następnym, korzystając z różnych serwisów internetowych.</p>
    <p>Program można również zintegrować z powłoką GNOME, co umożliwia dostęp do obecnych warunków pogodowych w ostatnio wyszukiwanych miastach poprzez pisanie ich nazw na ekranie podglądu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Uma pequena aplicação que lhe permite monitorizar as condições atmosféricas atuais da sua cidade, ou qualquer outro local no mundo, e aceder a previsões atualizadas, até 7 dias, disponibilizadas por vários serviços na Internet.</p>
    <p>Fornece acesso a previsões detalhadas até 7 dias, com detalhes horários para o dia atual e seguinte, usando vários serviços da Internet.</p>
    <p>Também se integra, opcionalmente, com a shell do GNOME, permitindo-lhe ver as condições atuais das cidades mais recentemente procuradas, simplesmente digitando o seu nome na vista de atividades.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Um pequeno aplicativo que permite a você monitorar as atuais condições meteorológicas da sua cidade, ou qualquer lugar do mundo.</p>
    <p>Fornece acesso a previsões de tempo detalhadas, de até 7 dias, com detalhes de hora em hora para o dia atual e para o próximo, usando vários serviços da internet.</p>
    <p>Ele também integra-se, de forma opcional, com o GNOME Shell, permitindo que você veja as condições atuais das cidades mais pesquisadas recentemente, somente digitando o nome no Panorama de Atividades.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>O mică aplicație ce permite monitorizarea condițiilor meteorologice pentru orașul dumneavoastră, sau orice localitate din lume.</p>
    <p>Oferă acces la prognoze meteo detaliate, până la 7 zile, cu detalii orare pentru ziua în curs și următoarea, folosing diferite servicii online.</p>
    <p>De asemenea, opțional, se poate integra cu GNOME Shell, și vă permite să observați condițiile meteo curente pentru cele mai recente căutate orașe prin simpla introducere a numelero în căsuța de căutare din panorama Activități.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Небольшое приложение, которое позволяет отслеживать текущее состояние погоды для вашего города или любой точки мира.</p>
    <p>Оно также предоставляет доступ к подробному прогнозу погоды (до 7 дней) от различных Интернет-служб.</p>
    <p>Приложение также опционально интегрируется с GNOME Shell, позволяя вам видеть текущие условия в городах, в которых недавно проводился поиск, просто набрав название города в Обзорном режиме.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Malá aplikácia, ktorá vám umožňuje sledovať aktuálne počasie vo vašom meste, alebo kdekoľvek vo svete.</p>
    <p>Poskytuje prístup k podrobnej predpovedi až na 7 dní s hodinovými podrobnosťami pre aktuálny a nasledujúci deň prostredníctvom rozličných internetových služieb.</p>
    <p>Tiež je dostupná voliteľná integrácia so Shellom prostredia GNOME, ktorá vám umožní vidieť aktuálne podmienky naposledy hľadaných miest zadaním názvu v prehľade Aktivít.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Program, ki omogoča nadzor trenutnih vremenskih pogojev za izbrana mesta kjerkoli na svetu.</p>
    <p>Omogoča prikaz podrobne vremenske napovedi prek različnih spletnih mest do 7 dni, z urno razdelitvijo poteka za en dan naprej.</p>
    <p>Izbirno se program vključuje tudi v okolje Lupine GNOME in omogoča pregled trenutnega vremena v izbranih oziroma iskanih mestih z enostavnim vpisom imena v polje pregleda dejavnosti.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Програмче које вам омогућава да надгледате тренутне временске прилике за ваш град, или било где у свету.</p>
    <p>Обезбеђује приступ опширним временским прогнозама, до 7 дана, са једночасовним појединостима за текући и наредни дан, користећи разне интернет услуге.</p>
    <p>Такође се може објединити са Гномовом шкољком, омогућавајући вам да видите тренутне услове последњих тражених градова једноставним куцањем њихових имена у прегледу активности.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Programče koje vam omogućava da nadgledate trenutne vremenske prilike za vaš grad, ili bilo gde u svetu.</p>
    <p>Obezbeđuje pristup opširnim vremenskim prognozama, do 7 dana, sa jednočasovnim pojedinostima za tekući i naredni dan, koristeći razne internet usluge.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Ett litet program som låter dig hålla koll på aktuella väderförhållanden för din stad eller andra platser i världen.</p>
    <p>Det tillhandahåller detaljerade prognoser sju dagar framåt med detaljerad information per timme för aktuell och nästkommande dag, från diverse internettjänster.</p>
    <p>Det integrerar också valfritt med GNOME-skalet, vilket gör det möjligt för dig att se aktuella förhållanden för de senast eftersökta städerna genom att bara skriva namnet i Aktivitetsöversikten.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tg">
    <p>Обу ҳаво барномаи хурдест, ки барои назорати шароити обу ҳаво дар шаҳри шумо ё шаҳри дигари ҷаҳон имкон медиҳад.</p>
    <p>Тавассути ин барнома пешгӯии вазъи обу ҳавоии ботафсил дар 7 рӯз, як соат, рӯзи ҷорӣ ё навбатӣ тавассути хадамотҳои гуногуни интернетӣ дастрас мешавад.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="th">
    <p>โปรแกรมเล็กๆ ที่ช่วยคุณติดตามสภาพอากาศปัจจุบันของเมืองของคุณ หรือที่ใดๆ ในโลก</p>
    <p>คุณจะสามารถเข้าถึงข้อมูลพยากรณ์อากาศ 7 วันข้างหน้า พร้อมรายละเอียดเป็นรายชั่วโมงสำหรับวันปัจจุบันและวันถัดไป จากบริการต่างๆ หลายแหล่งในอินเทอร์เน็ต</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Şehrinizin ya da dünyadaki herhangi bir yerin anlık hava durumunu gözleyebileceğiniz ufak bir uygulama.</p>
    <p>Türlü internet hizmetleri kullanarak 7 güne dek ayrıntılı tahminlerle birlikte şimdiki ve sonraki gün için saatlik ayrıntılara erişmeyi sağlar.</p>
    <p>İsteğe bağlı olarak GNOME Kabuğu ile tümleşir, Etkinlikler Genel Görünümüne son aranan şehirlerin yalnızca adını girerek geçerli hava durumlarını görmenizi sağlar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Маленька програма, яка дозволяє стежити за поточними погодними умовами вашого міста або будь-де в світі.</p>
    <p>Програма надає доступ до детального прогнозу, до семи днів, з погодинними подробицями для поточного і наступного дня, використовуючи різні служби в інтернеті.</p>
    <p>Також необов'язково вбудовується в GNOME Shell, дозволяючи бачити поточні погодні умови найнедавніших міст. Достатньо ввести потрібного вам міста в огляді діяльності.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="vi">
    <p>Ứng dụng nhỏ cho phép bạn theo dõi điều kiện thời tiết hiện tại ở thành phố của bạn, hay bất kỳ nơi nào khác trên thế giới.</p>
    <p>Nó cung cấp dự báo thời tiết chi tiết đến bảy ngày, chi tiết đến từng giờ cho hôm nay và ngày kế tiếp, sử dụng các dịch vụ internet khác nhau.</p>
    <p>Nó cũng được tích hợp cùng Hệ vỏ GNOME, cho phép bạn xem tình hình hiện tại của các thành phố mới tìm bằng cách gõ tên vào "Tổng quan hoạt động".</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>一个允许你监视所在城市或世界各地的当前天气状况的小应用。</p>
    <p>它使用各种不同的网络服务，提供非常具体的 7 天的天气预报，包括当天和第二天的每个小时的具体天气。</p>
    <p>它也可选与 GNOME Shell 集成，允许你通过在活动概览中输入名字来查看最近搜索的城市的当前状况。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_HK">
    <p>一個小型應用程式，允許你監控你的城市或是世界中任一地區目前的天氣狀況。</p>
    <p>它提供了詳細的天氣預報，最多達 7 天，有每小時針對目前與明天的詳細資料，使用各種互聯網服務提供。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>一個小型應用程式，允許您監控您的城市或是世界中任一地區目前的天氣狀況。</p>
    <p>它提供了詳細的天氣預報，最多達 7 天，有每小時針對目前與明天的詳細資料，使用各種網際網路服務提供。</p>
    <p>它也可以選擇性與 GNOME Shell 整合，讓您在活動概覽中輸入名稱就可以搜尋最近尋找過的城市並查看它目前的天氣狀況。</p>
  </description>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-weather/raw/HEAD/misc/screenshots/hourly.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-weather/raw/HEAD/misc/screenshots/daily.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.Weather.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Weather</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-weather/issues</url>
  <update_contact>christopherdavis_at_gnome.org</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">org.gnome.Weather</translation>
  <provides>
    <id>org.gnome.Weather.Application.desktop</id>
    <id>org.gnome.Weather.desktop</id>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="42.0" date="2022-03-20">
      <description>
        <p>GNOME Weather 42 comes with a port to GTK4, a new thermometer widget, and support for GNOME's new dark style preference. It also comes with up-to-date translations for the following locales:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Abkhazian</li>
          <li>Basque</li>
          <li>Bokmål, Norwegian</li>
          <li>Bulgarian</li>
          <li>Catalan</li>
          <li>Chinese (China)</li>
          <li>Croatian</li>
          <li>Czech</li>
          <li>Danish</li>
          <li>Finnish</li>
          <li>French</li>
          <li>Friulian</li>
          <li>Galician</li>
          <li>German</li>
          <li>Hebrew</li>
          <li>Hungarian</li>
          <li>Icelandic</li>
          <li>Indonesian</li>
          <li>Italian</li>
          <li>Japanese</li>
          <li>Kazakh</li>
          <li>Korean</li>
          <li>Latvian</li>
          <li>Lithuanian</li>
          <li>Occitan</li>
          <li>Occitan (post 1500)</li>
          <li>Persian</li>
          <li>Polish</li>
          <li>Portuguese</li>
          <li>Portuguese (Brazil)</li>
          <li>Russian</li>
          <li>Serbian</li>
          <li>Slovak</li>
          <li>Slovenian</li>
          <li>Spanish</li>
          <li>Swedish</li>
          <li>Turkish</li>
          <li>Ukrainian</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-09-21" version="41.0">
      <description>
        <p>GNOME Weather 41 brings updated translations for the following locales:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Belarusian</li>
          <li>Croatian</li>
          <li>Danish</li>
          <li>Western Frisian</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-08-10" version="40.1">
      <description>
        <p>Forecast chart's rounded corners</p>
        <p>Better dark themes support</p>
        <p>Updated translations for the following locales:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Belarusian</li>
          <li>Chinese (China)</li>
          <li>Chinese (Taiwan)</li>
          <li>Czech</li>
          <li>English</li>
          <li>Galician</li>
          <li>Hebrew</li>
          <li>Greek</li>
          <li>Korean</li>
          <li>Nepali</li>
          <li>Occitan</li>
          <li>Slovak</li>
          <li>Vietnamese</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="40.0" date="2021-03-20">
      <description>
        <p>GNOME Weather 40 brings an exciting new redesign that works on both desktop and mobile form factors.</p>
        <p>Weather 40 also comes with updated translations for the following locales:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Bangla (India)</li>
          <li>Basque</li>
          <li>Bokmål, Norwegian</li>
          <li>Catalan</li>
          <li>Chinese (China)</li>
          <li>Chinese (Taiwan)</li>
          <li>Croatian</li>
          <li>Czech</li>
          <li>Danish</li>
          <li>Dutch</li>
          <li>English (United Kingdom)</li>
          <li>Esperanto</li>
          <li>Finnish</li>
          <li>French</li>
          <li>Friulian</li>
          <li>Galician</li>
          <li>German</li>
          <li>Greek, Modern (1453-)</li>
          <li>Hebrew</li>
          <li>HungarianIndonesian</li>
          <li>Italian</li>
          <li>Japanese</li>
          <li>Kazakh</li>
          <li>Korean</li>
          <li>Latvian</li>
          <li>Lithuanian</li>
          <li>Panjabi</li>
          <li>Persian</li>
          <li>Polish</li>
          <li>Portuguese</li>
          <li>Portuguese (Brazil)</li>
          <li>Romanian</li>
          <li>Serbian</li>
          <li>Slovak</li>
          <li>Slovenian</li>
          <li>Spanish</li>
          <li>Swedish</li>
          <li>Turkish</li>
          <li>Ukrainian</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.34.0" date="2019-09-24">
      <description>
        <p>GNOME Weather 3.34 includes bug fixes and general improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Export location information to GNOME Shell (Florian Müllner)</li>
          <li>Use weather station's time zone (Jim Mason)</li>
          <li>Allow enter key to show location (James Westman)</li>
          <li>Fix search provider (Florian Müllner)</li>
        </ul>
        <p>It also includes translation updates for the following locales:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Catalan</li>
          <li>Chinese (China)</li>
          <li>Danish</li>
          <li>Icelandic</li>
          <li>Karbi</li>
          <li>Korean</li>
          <li>Persian</li>
          <li>Tamil</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.32.0" date="2019-03-11" />
  </releases>
  <developer_name>The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">GNOME 專案</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 项目</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="vi">Dự án GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Проєкт GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">GNOME Projesi</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tg">Лоиҳаи GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Гном пројекат</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Проект GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Proiectul GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਪਰੋਜੈਕਟ</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="oc">Lo projècte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Het Gnome-project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ne">जिनोम परियोजना</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb">GNOME prosjektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ms">Projek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="mjw">GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lv">GNOME projekts</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">GNOME projektas</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">그놈 프로젝트</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="kk">GNOME жобасы</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Il progetto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="is">GNOME verkefnið</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Proyek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">מיזם GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">O Proxecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fy">It GNOME Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fur">Il progjet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Le projet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Gnome-projekti</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fa">پروژهٔ گنوم</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">GNOME proiektua</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="et">GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">El Proyecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">La Projekto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Το έργο GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Das GNOME-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ckb">پرۆژەی گنۆم</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="bn_IN">জিনোম প্রকল্প</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="bg">Проектът GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="be">Праект GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ab">Апроект GNOME.</developer_name>
  <url type="donation">http://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://wiki.gnome.org/TranslationProject</url>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="social-info">mild</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <custom>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">workstation</value>
    <value key="Purism::form_factor">mobile</value>
  </custom>
</component>