<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>gnome.hitori</pkgname>
  <icon height="64" width="64" type="cached">org.gnome.Hitori.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" width="128" type="cached">org.gnome.Hitori.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.Hitori</id>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA-3.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <!-- Translators: the name of the application as it appears in a software center -->
  <name>GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 数壹</name>
  <name lang="uk">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="tr">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="sv">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Gnom Hitori</name>
  <name lang="sr">Гном Хитори</name>
  <name lang="sl">Igra Hitori</name>
  <name lang="sk">Hitori prostredia GNOME</name>
  <name lang="ru">GNOME Хитори</name>
  <name lang="ro">Hitori GNOME</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="pt">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="pl">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="oc">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="nl">Gnome Hitori</name>
  <name lang="ne">जिनोम हिटोरि</name>
  <name lang="nb">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="ms">Hitori GNOME</name>
  <name lang="ml">ഗ്നോം ഹിറ്റോറി</name>
  <name lang="lt">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="lv">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="ko">그놈 히토리</name>
  <name lang="kk">GNOME Хитори ойыны</name>
  <name lang="ja">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="it">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="id">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="hu">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="hr">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="he">היטורי GNOME</name>
  <name lang="gl">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="fur">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="fr">Hitori de GNOME</name>
  <name lang="fi">Gnomen Hitori</name>
  <name lang="fa">گنوم هیتوری</name>
  <name lang="eu">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="es">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="eo">GNOME Hitorio</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="el">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="de">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="da">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="cs">Hitori GNOME</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="ca">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="bs">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="bg">Хитори</name>
  <name lang="be">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="as">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="ar">جنوم هيتوري</name>
  <name lang="an">GNOME Hitori</name>
  <name lang="ab">GNOME Хитори</name>
  <!-- Translators: the brief summary of the application as it appears in a software center. -->
  <summary>Play the Hitori puzzle game</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">遊玩 Hitori 解謎遊戲</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_HK">玩 Hitori 解謎遊戲</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">开玩益智游戏数壹</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Зіграти головоломка Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Chơi trò chơi giải đố Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Hitori bulmaca oyununu oynayın</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Spela pusselspelet Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Igrajte igru slagalica Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Играјте игру слагалица Хитори</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Igraj miselno igro Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Hrajte hru Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Игра-головоломка Хитори</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Joacă jocul de puzzle Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Jogue o quebra-cabeça Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Jogue os puzzles Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Gra logiczna Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="pa">ਹੀਟੋਰੀ ਬੁਝਾਰਤ ਖੇਡ ਖੇਡੋ</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Jogar al copacap Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Speel het Hitori-puzzelspel</summary>
  <summary lang="ne">हिटोरि खेल खेल्नुहोस्</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Spill det populære puslespillet Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Main permainan teka-teki Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="ml">ഹിറ്റോറി പസില്‍ കളിക്കുക</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Žaiskite Hitori galvosūkių žaidimą</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Spēlēt Hitori prāta spēli</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">히토리 퍼즐 게임을 플레이합니다</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">Хитори жұмбақ ойынын ойнату</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">Hitori (ひとりにしてくれ) をプレイします</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Gioca al rompicapo Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Mainkan permainan menyusun gambar Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Japán eredetű logikai játék a számokkal</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Igrajte Hitori igru slagalice</summary>
  <summary lang="he">לשחק במשחק החשיבה היטורי</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Xogue ao xogo de crebacabezas Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Zuie al berdei Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Jouer au casse-tête Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Pelaa Hitori-pulmapeliä</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">بازی پازلِ هیتوری را بازی کنید</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Jokatu Hitori puzzlera</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Jugar al juego de puzle Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Ludi la Hitori-puzlon</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Play the Hitori puzzle game</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Παίξτε το παιχνίδι παζλ Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Das Hitori-Puzzle spielen</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Spil opgavespillet Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Hrát logickou hru Hitori.</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Jugueu al trencaclosques Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Jugueu al trencaclosques Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Igraj Hitori logičku igru</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Абстрактна главоблъсканица с числа</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Гуляць у гульню Пазлы Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="as">Hitori সাঁথৰ খেল খেলক</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">العب لعبة أحجية هيتوري</summary>
  <summary lang="an">Chugar a o chuego de puzle Hitori</summary>
  <summary lang="ab">Ахәмарра-хыԥҽыга Хитори</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Hitori is a logic game similar to the popular game of Sudoku.</p>
    <p>
      You play the game against the clock, aiming to eliminate all the duplicate
      numbers in each row and column in the fastest time.
      Multiple sizes of game board are supported, and you can place markers on
      cells to help work out the solution.
      If you get stuck, the game can give you a hint.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ab">
    <p>Хитори- алогикатә хәмарроуп, зегьы бзиа ирбо ахәмарра судоку еиԥшуп</p>
    <p>Ахәмарра аамҭа ԥкуп. Ахәмарра хықәкыс иамоуп- иаарцҵакны хыԥхьаӡарала еиқәшәаз  ацәаҳәақәеи аиҵагылақәеи рықәгара. Ахәмарра иаднакылоит ахәмарратә ҭыԥ ашәагаақәа ԥыҭк.Шәара ишәылшоит иқәшәыргылалар ахыԥҽыга аҳасабразы ишәыцхраауа адыргақәа.Ишәзымдыруазар изаҟә шьаҿоу иҟаҵатәу, шәхы иашәархәар шәылшоит аҵаҳәара.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="an">
    <p>Hitori ye un chuego de lochica semellant a o Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Puede chugar contra o reloch, prebando d'eliminar totz os numeros duplicaus en cada ringlera y columna lo mas ascape posible. Se suportan quantas grandarias de tablero y puede colocar marcadors en as celdas ta aduyar-le a trobar a solución. Si tiene problemas, o chuego puede dar-le una pista.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>هيتوري لعبة منطق شبيهة باللّعبة الشّعبيّة سودوكو.</p>
    <p>ستلعب ضدّ الوقت محاولا إزالة كلّ الأرقام المتكرّرة في كلّ صفّ وعمود بأسرع ما يمكن. عدّة مقاسات للوحة مدعومة، ويمكنك وضع العلامات على الخلايا لمساعدتك في فكّ الأحجية. إن علقت يمكن للّعبة إعطائك تلميحا ما.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="as">
    <p>Hitori জনপ্ৰিয় খেল Sudoku ৰ সৈতে সদৃশ এটা যৌক্তিক খেল।</p>
    <p>আপুনি সময়ৰ বিপক্ষে এই খেলখন খেলে, য'ত আপুনি আটাইতকৈ কম সময়ত প্ৰতি শাৰী আৰু স্তম্ভত প্ৰতিলিপি সংখ্যা আতৰোৱাৰ চেষ্টা কৰে। খেল বৰ্ডৰ কেইবাটাও আকাৰ সমৰ্থিত, আৰু আপুনি সমাধানৰ বাবে কোষবোৰত চিহ্নক দিব পাৰে। যদি আপুনি ফচি যাব, খেলে আপোনাক সহায় কৰিব পাৰে।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Hitori гэта лагічная гульня падобная на папулярныя гульні Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Вы гуляеце ў гульню з абмежаваным часам, з мэтай ліквідаваць усе паўтараюцца лічбы ў кожным радку і слупку ў самы кароткі тэрмін. Падтрымліваюцца шматлікія памеры гульнявога поля, і вы можаце змясціць маркеры на клеткі, каб дапамагчы выпрацаваць рашэнне. Калі вы спыніцеся, гульня можа даць вам падказку.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Хитори е логическа игра подобна на Судоку</p>
    <p>Играете за по-малко време, целта да махнете повтарящите се числа във всеки ред и колона. Поддържат се много размери на дъската, а по нея може да поставяте маркери, за да си помагате за решението. Може да поискате подсказка, когато не може да продължите.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Hitori je logička igra slična popularnoj igri Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Igrate igru protiv sata, pokušavajući da eliminišete duple brojeve u svakom redu i koloni u najkraćem vremenskom roku. Više veličina table za igu je podržano, i možete postaviti oznake na poljima kako bi ste razmislili o rješenju. Ukoliko ne znaze šta dalje, igra će vam predložiti potez.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>L'Hitori és un joc de lògica similar al popular Sukodu.</p>
    <p>Jugueu contra rellotge, amb l'objectiu d'eliminar tots els nombres duplicats a cada fila i columna en el menor temps possible. Es pot jugar a taulers de diferent mida, i podeu posar els marcadors a les cel·les per ajudar-vos a trobar la solució. Si us quedeu bloquejat, el joc us pot donar una pista.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca@valencia">
    <p>El Hitori és un joc de lògica similar al popular Sukodu.</p>
    <p>Jugueu contra rellotge, amb l'objectiu d'eliminar tots els nombres duplicats a cada fila i columna en el menor temps possible. Es pot jugar a taulers de diferent mida, i podeu posar els marcadors a les celes per ajudar-vos a trobar la solució. Si vos quedeu bloquejat, el joc vos pot donar una pista.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Hitori je logická hra podobná populárnímu Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Hru hrajete na čas a cílem je co nejrychleji vyřadit všechna duplicitní čísla v každém řádku a sloupci. Je podporováno více velikostí hrací desky a při hledání řešení si můžete pomáhat umísťováním značek do políček. Když se zaseknete, umí vám hra nabídnout radu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Hitori er et spil om logik i stil med det populære spil Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Du spiller mod uret, mens du forsøger at eliminere alle de ens tal i hver række og kolonne på hurtigst mulig tid. Der understøttes flere brætstørrelser, og du kan placere markører på cellerne for at hjælpe med at finde løsningen. Hvis du sidder fast, kan du få et tip.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Hitori ist ein Logikspiel, ähnlich dem bekannten Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Sie spielen gegen die Uhr. Dabei versuchen Sie so schnell wie möglich so viele doppelte Zahlen wie möglich in einer Reihe oder Spalte zu entfernen. Unterschiedliche Spielfeldgrößen werden unterstützt, dabei können Sie Markierungen verwenden, die Ihnen bei der Lösung der Aufgabe helfen. Falls Sie mal nicht weiterkommen, kann Ihnen das Spiel einen Tipp geben.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το Hitori είναι ένα παιχνίδι λογικής παρόμοιο με το δημοφιλές παιχνίδι Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Παίζετε το παιχνίδι ενάντια στο ρολόι, προσπαθώντας να περιορίσετε όλους τους διπλότυπους αριθμούς σε κάθε γραμμή και στήλη στον ταχύτερο χρόνο. Υποστηρίζονται πολλαπλά μεγέθη ταμπλό παιχνιδιού, και μπορείτε να προσθέσετε δείκτες στα κελιά για να βοηθηθείτε με τη λύση. Αν κολλήσετε, το παιχνίδι μπορεί να σας δώσει και μια υπόδειξη.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Hitori is a logic game similar to the popular game of Sudoku.</p>
    <p>You play the game against the clock, aiming to eliminate all the duplicate numbers in each row and column in the fastest time. Multiple sizes of game board are supported, and you can place markers on cells to help work out the solution. If you get stuck, the game can give you a hint.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p>Hitorio estas logika ludo, simila al la populara ludo Sudoko.</p>
    <p>Vi ludas la ludon kontraŭ la horloĝo, celanta forigi ĉiujn oblajn nombroj en ĉiu vico kaj kolumno dum la plej rapida tempo. Multoblaj grandoj de luda tabulo estas subtenataj kaj vi povas meti signojn sur ĉelon por helpi trovi la solvon. Se vi akiras senmoviĝi, la ludo povas doni al vi sugeston.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Hitori es un juego de lógica similar al Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Puede jugar contra el reloj, intentando eliminar todos los números duplicados en cada fila y columna lo más rápido posible. Se soportan varios tamaños de tablero y puede colocar marcadores en las celdas para ayudarle a encontrar la solución. Si tiene problemas, el juego puede darle una pista.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Hitori logika motako joko bat da, Sudoku joko ospetsuaren antzekoa.</p>
    <p>Ordulariaren aurka jokatzen duzu, errenkada eta zutabe bakoitzean bikoiztutako zenbaki guztiak kentzen saiatuz ahalik eta azkarren. Hainbat tamainatako taulak daude, markatzaileak gelaxketan ezarri ditzakezu ebazpenean laguntzeko. Noraezean aurkitzen bazara, jokoak argibide bat eman dezake.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fa">
    <p>هیتوری یک بازی منطق است مشابه بازی معروف سودوکو.</p>
    <p>شما این بازی را در مقابل زمان انجام می‌دهید، با هدف اینکه در سریع‌ترین زمان ممکن تمام اعداد تکراری در هر ردیف و ستون را حذف کنید. اندازه‌های متفاوتی از تخته بازی پشتیبانی می‌شوند، و شما می‌توانید علامت‌هایی در خانه‌های جدول قرار دهید تا برای یافتن راه حل شما را کمک کنند. اگر گیر کردید، بازی می‌تواند شما را راهنمایی کند.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Hitori on sudokun kaltainen logiikkapeli.</p>
    <p>Pelaat kelloa vastaan, tavoitteenasi on hankkiutua eroon kaikista tuplanumeroista jokaisessa rivissä ja sarakkeessa mahdollisimman nopeasti. Peli tukee useita eri laudan kokoja, halutessasi voit asettaa merkkejä soluihin ratkaisun selvittämiseksi. Jos olet jumissa, peli voi antaa vihjeen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Hitori est un jeu de logique similaire au populaire jeu de Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Vous jouez contre la montre, l’objectif étant d’éliminer tous les nombres en double dans chaque ligne et colonne le plus rapidement possible. Plusieurs tailles de plateau sont proposées et vous pouvez placer des marqueurs sur des cases afin d’aider à trouver une solution. Si vous êtes bloqué, le jeu peut vous donner un indice.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Hitori al è un zûc di logjiche simil al Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Zuie cuintri il timp cirint di eliminâ ducj i numars duplicâts in ogni rie e colone. Aumente il numar di celis e tu puedis meti marcaduris par judâti te soluzion. Se tu ti impantanis il zûc al pues judâti.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Hitori é un xogo de lóxica similar ao popular xogo de Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Vostede xoga contra o reloxo co fin de eliminar todos os números duplicados en cada fila e columna no mellor tempo posíbel. Conta con taboleiros de xogo de varios tamaños e pode dispor marcadores nas celas que lle axuden a acadar unha solución. Se se atasca, o xogo daralle un consello.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>היטורי הוא משחק חשיבה פשוט הדומה למשחק הפופולרי סודוקו.</p>
    <p>ניתן לשחק נגד השעון, במטרה לחסל את כל המספרים הכפולים בכל שורה ועמודה בזמן הקצר ביותר. גדלים שונים של לוח המשחק נתמכים, וניתן למקם סמנים על תאים כדי לעזור להגיע לפתרון. אם נתקעת, ניתן לקבל רמז מהמשחק.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Hitori je logička igra slična popularnoj igri Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Igrate igru protiv vremena, s ciljem eliminacije svih duplih brojeva u svakom redku i stupcu u što mogućem kraćem vremenu. Više veličina igrače ploče je podržana a možete i smjestiti oznake na ćelije za pomoć pronalaska rješenja. Ako zapnete, igra vam može dati savjet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Hitori egy Sudokuhoz hasonló logikai játék.</p>
    <p>A játék időre megy, a cél minden sorban és oszlopban az összes többször szereplő szám eltüntetése. Több méretű játéktábla használható, a cellákra elhelyezett jelölők segítségével pedig könnyíthető a megoldás. Ha elakad, a játék tud tippet is adni.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Hitori adalah suatu permainan logika mirip permainan populer Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Anda bermain melawan jam, bertujuan mengeliminasi semua angka duplikat dalam setiap baris dan kolom secepat mungkin. Papan permainan dalam berbagai ukuran didukung, dan Anda dapat menempatkan penanda pada sel untuk membantu mencari solusi. Bila Anda menemui jalan buntu, permainan bisa memberi Anda petunjuk.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Hitori è un gioco di logica molto simile al Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Gioca control il tempo cercando di eliminare il più velocemente possibile tutti i numeri duplicati in ogni rica e colonna. Aumenta il numero delle celle e posiziona dei marcatori per aiutarti nella soluzione del puzzle: se ti blocchi, puoi anche chiedere un piccolo aiuto. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>Hitori (ひとりにしてくれ) は数独に似た論理ゲームです。</p>
    <p>できるだけ早く、各行と各列から重複した数字を取り除いてください。ゲーム盤の大きさは複数用意されており、パズルを解く補助としてマス目にマークを付けることもできます。行き詰まったときのためにヒントも用意されています。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <p>Хитори — әйгілі Судоку ойынына ұқсас логикалық ойыны.</p>
    <p>Ойынды сағатқа қарсы ойнайсыз, ең аз уақытта әр жол мен бағандағы барлық қайталанатын сандарды жою керек. Ойынның тақтаның бірнеше өлшеміне қолдауы бар және шешімді пысықтауға көмектесу үшін ұяшықтарға маркерлерді орналастыруға болады. Егер тұрып қалсаңыз, ойын тұспалды бере алады.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>히토리는 유명한 스도쿠와 비슷한 논리 게임입니다.</p>
    <p>가능한한 빨리 각 행과 열의 중복된 숫자를 제거하는 게임입니다. 여러가지 크기의 게임판 크기를 지원하고, 해법을 알아내는데 도움이 되도록 칸에 표시를 할 수도 있습니다. 막힐 경우, 게임에서 힌트를 줄 수도 있습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Hitori yra loginis žaidimas, panašus į populiarųjį Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Galite žaisti su laikrodžiu, siekdami pašalinti visus besidubliuojančius skaičius kiekvienoje eilutėje bei stulpelyje kiek galima greičiau. Palaikomi įvairūs lentos dydžiais, be to, galite langeliuose padėti žymiklius, kad būtų lengviau surasti sprendimą. Jei užstrigsite, žaidimas gali pateikti patarimą.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>Hitori ir loģikas spēle, kas ir līdzīga populārajai spēlei Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Jūs varat spēlēt šo spēli pret pulksteni, mēģinot likvidēt visus dublikāta skaitļus katrā rindā un kolonnā, visīsākajā laikā. Ir atbalstīti vairāki spēlēs galdiņa izmēri un uz šūnām varat novietot marķierus, lai palīdzētu atrast atrisinājumu. Ja iestrēgsiet, spēle jums var dot padomu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ml">
    <p>ജനപ്രിയമായ സുഡോക്കു പോലെ ബുദ്ധിപരമായ കളിയാണ് ഹിറ്റോറി.</p>
    <p>കഴിയുന്നത്ര വേഗത്തില്‍ ഓരോ വരിയിലെയും നിരയിലെയും ഡ്യൂപ്ലിക്കേറ്റ് സംഖ്യകള്‍ നീക്കം ചെയ്യുകയാണ് ലക്ഷ്യം. പ്രശ്നപരിഹാരത്തിനായി ഓരോ സെല്ലിലും അടയാളങ്ങള്‍ സ്ഥാപിക്കാവുന്നതാണ്. കളിയില്‍ തടസമുണ്ടായാല്‍ സൂചനകള്‍ ലഭ്യമാണ്.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Hitori ialah sebuah permainan logik seakan dengan permainan terkenal Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Anda bermain mengatasi jam, dengan matlamat untuk hapuskan semua nombor pendua dalam setiap baris dan lajur dan masa terpantas. Papan permainan dengan pelbagai saiz disokong, dan anda boleh letak penanda di atas sel untuk memudahkan penyelesaian. Jika anda tersangkut ketika bermain, anda boleh dapatkan satu pembayang.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Hitori er et logikkspill som ligner på det populære spillet Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Du spiller spillet mot klokken og målet er å eliminere alle dupliserte tall i hver rad og kolonne så fort som mulig. Du kan bruke flere størrelser på brettet, og du kan plassere markører på celler som hjelper med å løse problemet. Hvis du står fast kan spillet gi deg et hint.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Hitori is een logisch spel, vergelijkbaar met het populaire Sudoku.</p>
    <p>U speelt het spel tegen de klok en probeert alle dubbele nummers in elke rij en kolom zo snel mogelijk te elimineren. Meerdere groottes van het spelbord worden ondersteund, en u kunt aanduidingen plaatsen op cellen om die u kunnen helpen bij het zoeken naar de oplossing. Als u vast raakt te zitten, kan het spel een hint geven.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>Hitori es un jòc de logica similar al popular jòc de Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Jogatz contra la mòstra, l'objectiu es d'eliminar totes leo nombres en doble dins cada linha e colomna lo mai rapidament possible. Mantuna talha de platèu son prepausadas e podètz plaçar de marcadors sus de cellulas per fin d'ajudar a trobar una solucion. Se sètz blocat, lo jòc vos pòt donar un indici.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Hitori to gra logiczna, podobna do popularnej gry Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Należy jak najszybciej wyeliminować podwójne liczby w każdym wierszu i kolumnie przed upływem określonego czasu. Obsługiwane są różne rozmiary planszy, a na komórkach można umieszczać znaczniki ułatwiające znalezienie rozwiązania. Gra może wyświetlić podpowiedź w razie utknięcia.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Hitori é um jogo de lógica similar ao popular Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Joga-se a contrarrelógio, tentando eliminar todos os números duplicados em cada linha e coluna no mínimo de tempo. São suportados vários tamanhos de tabuleiro e pode colocar marcadores em células para o ajudar a descobrir a solução. Se ficar encravado, o jogo dá-lhe uma dica.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Hitori é um jogo de lógica parecido com o popular Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Você começa o jogo contra o relógio, com o objetivo de eliminar todos os números duplicados de cada linha e coluna no tempo mais rápido. Há suporte a vários tamanhos de tabuleiros de jogo, e você pode posicionar marcadores nas células para ajudar a resolver a solução. Se você ficar preso, o jogo poderá oferecer-lhe uma dica.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Hitori este un joc de logică similar cu jocul popular Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Jucați jocul contra-timp, țintind spre eliminarea tuturor numerelor duplicate pe fiecare linie și coloană în cel mai rapid timp. Sunt suportate dimensiuni multiple ale tablei de joc, și puteți să plasați marcaje pe celule pentru a ajuta în descoperirea soluției. Dacă vă blocați, jocul poate să ofere un indiciu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Хитори — логическая игра, похожая на популярную игру судоку.</p>
    <p>Игра идёт на время. Цель игры — убрать как можно быстрее все совпадающие числа в каждой строке и столбце. Игра поддерживает несколько размеров игрового поля. Вы можете устанавливать метки, которые помогают при решении головоломки. Если вы не знаете, какой сделать ход, вы можете воспользоваться подсказкой.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Hitori je logická hra podobná populárnej hre Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Cieľom hrania hry je eliminovať všetky zdvojené čísla v každom riadku a stĺpci v čo najkratšom čase. Je podporovaných viacero veľkostí hracej plochy a môžete si umiestniť značky na bunky a pomôcť si tak nájsť riešenie. Ak nebudete vedieť čo ďalej, hra vám môže poskytnúť radu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Hitori je logična igra, podobna igri Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Igra Hitori je tekmovanje s časom. Cilj igre je čim hitreje najti vsa podvojena števila v vsaki vrstici in stolpcu. Igro je mogoče igrati na več težavnostnih ravneh, program pa omogoča tudi označevanje celic za hitrejše reševanje. Podprti so tudi namigi za najtežje trenutke.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Хитори је логичка игра слична Судокуу.</p>
    <p>Ви играте игру против времена, с циљем да поништите све удвостручене бројеве у сваком реду и ступцу у што краћем временском року. Подржано је неколико величина играчке табле, а можете да постављате означаваче на пољима да вам помогну у проналажењу решења. Ако ли вам негде запне, игра може да вам дошапне савет.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Hitori je logička igra slična Sudokuu.</p>
    <p>Vi igrate igru protiv vremena, s ciljem da poništite sve udvostručene brojeve u svakom redu i stupcu u što kraćem vremenskom roku. Podržano je nekoliko veličina igračke table, a možete da postavljate označavače na poljima da vam pomognu u pronalaženju rešenja. Ako li vam negde zapne, igra može da vam došapne savet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Hitori är ett logikspel liknande det populära spelet Sudoku.</p>
    <p>Du spelar spelet mot klockan, med målet att eliminera alla upprepade nummer i varje rad och kolumn på snabbast möjliga tid. Spelbräden i flera storlekar stöds, och du kan placera markörer på celler som ett stöd för att finna lösningen. Om du kör fast kan spelet ge dig ett tips.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Hitori, gözde Sudoku oyununa benzer mantık oyunudur.</p>
    <p>Oyunu her satır ve sütunda yinelenen sayıları ortadan kaldırmak amacıyla zamana karşı oynarsınız. Oyun tahtasının çoklu boyutları desteklenir ve hücrelere çözümü bulmaya yardımcı işaretler koyabilirsiniz. Takıldığınız yerde oyun size ipucu verebilir.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Hitori — логічна гра схожа на популярну гру судоку.</p>
    <p>Грається проти годинника, з ціллю усунути всі подвійні числа в кожному рядку або стовпці якнайшвидше. Підтримується кілька розмірів ігрової дошки, можете залишати мітки на комірках, щоб легше знайти розв'язок. Якщо застрягнете, гра може дати підказку.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>数壹，是一款逻辑类益智游戏，类似数独。</p>
    <p>游戏中，你要以最快的速度，消除每行每列数字中所有重复项。游戏支持多种面板尺寸，可在方格里做标记。如果思路卡住了，还可获取提示。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_HK">
    <p>Hitori 是一種類似數獨的邏輯遨遊戲。</p>
    <p>你要在時限內完成遊戲，目標是在最短時間內清除每一欄、每一列中重複的數字。遊戲盤支援多種尺寸，你可以在格子裏放上標記來協助找出解答。如果你卡關了，遊戲可以給你提示。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>Hitori 是一種類似數獨的邏輯遨遊戲。</p>
    <p>您要在時限內完成遊戲，目標是在最短時間內清除每一欄、每一列中重複的數字。遊戲盤支援多種尺寸，您可以在格子裡放上標記來協助找出解答。如果您卡關了，遊戲可以給您提示。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot width="400" height="480" type="default">
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/hitori/-/raw/main/data/screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>hitori</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.Hitori.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Hitori</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/hitori/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <url type="help">https://help.gnome.org/users/hitori/stable/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://wiki.gnome.org/TranslationProject/LocalisationGuide</url>
  <update_contact>philip_at_tecnocode.co.uk</update_contact>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <developer_name>The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">GNOME 專案</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">GNOME 项目</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Проєкт GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">GNOME Projesi</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Гном пројекат</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Проект GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Proiectul GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">O Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="oc">Lo projècte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Het Gnome-project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ms">Projek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">GNOME projektas</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lv">GNOME projekts</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">그놈 프로젝트</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="kk">GNOME жобасы</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Il progetto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Proyek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">מיזם GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">O Proxecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fur">Il progjet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Le projet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Gnome-projekti</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fa">پروژهٔ گنوم</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">GNOME proiektua</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">El Proyecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Το έργο GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Das GNOME-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ab">Апроект GNOME</developer_name>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>AppMenu</kudo>
    <kudo>HighContrast</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>UserDocs</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <recommends>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">small</display_length>
  </requires>
  <translation type="gettext">hitori</translation>
  <releases>
    <release version="3.38.4" type="stable" date="2022-04-04">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Add initial support for playing the game with a keyboard.</li>
          <li>Translation updates.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.38.3" date="2021-09-17" type="stable">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Add metadata about hardware and display size requirements.</li>
          <li>Translation updates.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.38.2" date="2021-05-25" type="stable">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Add scalable icon.</li>
          <li>Fix app being listed as ‘proprietary’.</li>
          <li>Translation updates.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.38.1" date="2021-03-05" type="stable">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.38.0" date="2020-09-10" type="stable">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.37.1" date="2020-09-03" type="development">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-08-19" version="3.37.0" type="development">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Documentation updates.</li>
          <li>Translation updates.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release type="stable" version="3.36.0" date="2020-03-11">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>No changes; version bump only.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release type="development" version="3.35.0" date="2020-02-24">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Allow resizing the window smaller.</li>
          <li>Translation updates.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.34.0" date="2019-09-02" type="stable">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Translation updates.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.33.0" date="2019-08-22" type="development">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Remember window size and position.</li>
          <li>Support localised (non-Arabic) digits on the game board.</li>
          <li>Add keyboard shortcuts dialogue and improve keyboard shortcuts and mnemonics.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-08-22" version="3.32.0" type="stable" />
    <release date="2019-03-04" version="3.31.92" type="development" />
    <release date="2019-02-19" version="3.31.0" type="development" />
    <release type="stable" date="2017-10-02" version="3.22.4" />
    <release date="2017-04-30" version="3.22.3" type="stable" />
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-desecration">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-slavery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-worship">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-adultery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-appearance">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-homosexuality">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-prostitution">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>