<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <description>
    <p>
      GnuCash is a program for personal and small-business financial-accounting.
    </p>
    <p>
      Designed to be easy to use, yet powerful and flexible, GnuCash allows you to track bank accounts, stocks, income and expenses. As quick and intuitive to use as a checkbook register, it is based on professional accounting principles like double-entry
      accounting to ensure balanced books and accurate reports.
    </p>
    <p>With GnuCash you can (but are not limited to):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Keep track of your day to day personal income and expenses</li>
      <li>Manage your stock, bond and mutual fund accounts with ease</li>
      <li>Keep your small business' accounting up to date</li>
      <li>Create accurate reports and graphs from your financial data</li>
      <li>Set up scheduled transactions to avoid repeated data entry</li>
      <li>Exchange by CSV/FinTS(former HBCI) or import SWIFT-MT9xx/QIF/OFX data including Transaction Matching</li>
      <li>Perform financial calculations, such as a loan repayment</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>جنوكاش هو برنامج للمحاسبة الشخصية و الأعمال التجارية الصغيرة</p>
    <p>مصمم ليكون سهل الاستخدام، لكنه قوي ومرن، جنوكاش يسمح لك بتتبع الحسابات المصرفية والأسهم والإيرادات والمصروفات. وطريقة سريعة وبديهية لاستخدام دفتر الشيكات، لأنه يقوم على مبادئ المحاسبة المهنية مثل محاسبة القيد المزدوج لضمان الدفاتر المتوازنة والتقارير الدقيقة.</p>
    <p>مع جنوكاش يمكنك (ولكن لا تقتصر على):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>تعقب الدخل الشخصي يوما بعد يوم والنفقات الخاصة بك</li>
      <li>إدارة الأسهم والسندات وحسابات صناديق الاستثمار بسهولة</li>
      <li>تتبع المحاسبة الخاصة باعمالك التجارية و تحديثها يوميا</li>
      <li>إنشاء تقارير دقيقة و رسوم البيانية من البيانات المالية</li>
      <li>قم بإعداد المعاملات المجدولة لتجنب إدخال البيانات المتكررة</li>
      <li>تنفيذ العمليات الحسابية المالية، مثل سداد القروض</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="as">
    <p>GnuCash হল ব্যক্তিগত আৰু ক্ষুদ্ৰ-ব্যৱসায় বিত্তীয়-গণনাৰ এটা কাৰ্যসূচী.</p>
    <p>ব্যৱহাৰৰ সুবিধাৰ্থে আৰ্হি কৰিছে, এতিয়াও শক্তিশালী আৰু সংকুচিত-প্ৰসাৰিত, GnuCash য়ে আপোনাক বেংক একাউন্টবোৰ, ষ্টকবোৰ, আয় আৰু ব্যয়বোৰৰ হিচাপ ৰাখিবলৈ অনুমতি দিয়ে. এটা পৰীক্ষা বহীৰ পঞ্জীয়নৰ দৰে ব্যৱহাৰ কৰিবলৈ ক্ষিপ্ৰ আৰু সহজে বুজি পোৱা, এইটো পৰিমাণৰ কিতাপবোৰ আৰু সঠিক ৰিপোৰ্টবোৰ নিশ্চিত কৰিবলৈ দ্বিগুণ-প্ৰৱিষ্টি গণনাটোৰ দৰে দক্ষ গণনাৰ নীতিবোৰৰ ওপৰত আধাৰিত.</p>
    <p>GnuCash ৰ সৈতে আপুনি পাৰে (কিন্তু সীমিত কৰা নহয়):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>আপোনাৰ প্ৰত্যেক দিনৰ আয় আৰু ব্যয়বোৰৰ হিচাপ ৰাখক</li>
      <li>আৰামেৰে আপোনাৰ ষ্টক, বণ্ড আৰু মিচুৱেল পুঁজিৰ একাউন্টবোৰ পৰিচালনা কৰক</li>
      <li>আপোনাৰ ক্ষুদ্ৰ ব্যৱসায়ৰ হিচাবটো আপ টু ডেট কৰি ৰাখক</li>
      <li>আপোনাৰ বিত্তীয় ডাটাৰ পৰা সঠিক ৰিপোৰ্ট আৰু লেখবোৰ তৈয়াৰ কৰক</li>
      <li>ডাটা প্ৰৱিষ্টিৰ পুনৰাবৃত্তিটো আওকাণ কৰিবলৈ নিৰ্ধাৰিত লেনদেনবোৰ ছেট আপ কৰক</li>
      <li>ঋণ পুনৰ পৰিশোধৰ দৰে বিত্তীয় গণনাবোৰ সম্পাদন কৰক</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="brx">
    <p>GnuCash आ निजि आरो फिसा-फालांगि राङारि-एकाउन्टिंनि मोनसे प्रग्राम।</p>
    <p>गोरलैयै बाहायनो डिजाइन खालामनाय जायो, थेवबो गोहोगोरा आरो रुयदब, GnuCash आ नोंथांखौ अरायबो बेंक एकाउन्ट, स्टक, आय आरो खरसाखौ ट्रेक खालामनो गनायथि होयो। गोख्रै आरो हरखाब बुजिखांनाय महरै, आनजाद-बाक्सु रेजिस्टार महरै बाहायनो, बेयो फालांगियारि एकाउन्टिं खान्थियाव सोनारनाय जेरै-बेलेन्सगोनां बुक(बिजाब) आरो गेबें रिपर्टखौ रोखा खालामनो मोननै-हाबहोनाय एकाउन्टिं।</p>
    <p>GnuCashजों नोंथाङा हायो (नाथाय सिमागोनां नङा):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>नोंथांनि सानफ्रोमबोनि निजि आय आरो खरसानि हिसाबखौ दोन</li>
      <li>नोंथांनि स्टक, बन्ड आरो मिउसुआल फान्ड एकाउन्टखौ गोरलैयै मेनेज खालाम</li>
      <li>नोंथांनि फालांगिनि एताउन्टिंखौ गोदानै दोन</li>
      <li>गेबें रिपर्ट आरो ग्राफ्सखौ नोंथांनि राङारि डाटा निफ्राय सोरजि</li>
      <li>गलेगले डाटा हाबहोनायखौ नागारनो फारिलाइ खालामखानाय लेनदेनखौ सेट आप खालाम</li>
      <li>राङारि हिसाबखौ मावफुं, जेरै- लन सुख'फिननाय</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El GnuCash és un progrma per a comptabilitat financera personal o de petites empreses.</p>
    <p>Dissenyat per ser fàcil d'usar, però tot i així potent i flexible, el GnuCash us permet fer un seguiment de comptes bancaris, accions, ingressos i despeses. Tan ràpid i intuïtiu d'usar com un registre de xecs, està basat en principis comptables professionals com ara la comptabilitat per partida doble per assegurar llibres balancejats i informes exactes.</p>
    <p>Amb el GnuCash podeu (però no esteu limitats a):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Feu un seguiment del dia a dia dels vostres ingressos i despeses</li>
      <li>Gestioneu el vostres comptes de fons d'accions, obligacions o inversions amb facilitat</li>
      <li>Mantingueu la comptabilitat de la vostra petita empreas actualitzada</li>
      <li>Creeu informes i gràfiques exactes a partir de les vostres dades financeres</li>
      <li>Configura assentaments periòdics per evitar l'entrada de dades repetides</li>
      <li>Intercanvia per CSV/FinTS(abans HBCI) o importa les dades SWIFT-MT9xx/QIF/OFX incloent-hi la Concordància d'assentaments</li>
      <li>Feu càlculs financers, com ara l'amortització de préstecs</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>GnuCash er et program til finanshåndtering for personer og små virksomheder.</p>
    <p>Med GnuCash kan du (men er ikke begrænset til):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Holde styr på dine indtæger og udgifter</li>
      <li>Håndtere dine aktier, obligationer og investeringsbeviser</li>
      <li>Holde din bogføring for den mindre virksomhed opdateret</li>
      <li>Oprette præcise rapporter og grafer over dine financielle data</li>
      <li>Opsæt planlagte transaktioner for at undgå gentagelse af dataindtastning</li>
      <li>Udfør finansielle beregninger, såsom tilbagebetaling af lån</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>GnuCash ist ein Buchhaltungsprogramm für Privatpersonen und kleine Unternehmen.</p>
    <p>Entworfen, um einfach im Gebrauch zu sein, aber mächtig und flexibel, erlaubt GnuCash Ihnen den Überblick über Ihre Bankkonten wie Wertpapiere, Einkünfte wie Aufwendungen zu behalten. So intuitiv und schnell zu benutzen wie ein Scheckbuchregister basiert es auf professionellen Prinzipien wie der doppelten Buchführung um ausgeglichene Bücher und präzise Berichte zu gewährleisten.</p>
    <p>Mit GnuCash können Sie neben Anderem:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Die Übersicht über Ihre täglichen persönlichen Einnahmen und Ausgaben bewahren</li>
      <li>Mit Leichtigkeit Ihre Renten, Aktien und Fonds verwalten</li>
      <li>Ihre kleine Geschäftsbuchhaltung auf dem Laufenden halten</li>
      <li>Präzise Berichte und Grafiken Ihrer Finanzdaten erzeugen</li>
      <li>Terminierte Buchungen einrichten, um wiederholte Dateneingabe zu vermeiden</li>
      <li>Datenaustausch mittels CSV/FinTS(former HBCI) oder importiere SWIFT-MT9xx/QIF/OFX Daten, einschließlich Buchungsabgleich</li>
      <li>Finanzkalkulationen ausführen wie Kredit-Rückzahlung</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>GnuCash es un programa para la contabilidad financiera personal y pequeños negocios.</p>
    <p>Diseñado para ser fácil de emplear, pero potente y flexible, GnuCash permite rastrear cuentas bancarias, reservas, ingresos y gastos. Tan rápido e intuitivo para emplear como un registro de comprobación, está basado en los principios profesionales de contabilidad como apunte-doble para asegurar los balances de libros y boletines detallados.</p>
    <p>Con GnuCash puede (pero está liminato):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Conservar seguimiento diario de ingresos y gastos personales</li>
      <li>Gestiona sus cuentas de reservas, depósitos y fondos de inversión con facilidad</li>
      <li>Conserve su contabilidad de los pequeños negocios al día</li>
      <li>Crea boletines precisos y gráficas desde sus datos financieros</li>
      <li>Fije transacciones planificadas para evitar datos de asiento repetido</li>
      <li>Cambio por CSV/FinTS (formato HBCI) o importaciones de datos SWIFT-MT9xx/QIF/OFX incluyendo Transacciones Cotejadas</li>
      <li>Proporciona cálculos financieros, como una amortización de un préstamo</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fa">
    <p>گنوکش که برای سهولتِ استفاده در عین قدرت و انعطاف‌پذیری طراحی شده است، تو را قادر می‌سازد حساب‌های بانکی، سهام، درآمدها و هزینه‌هایت را پیگیری کنی. به همان سرعت و قابل درک بودنِ کاربردِ ثبت‌کننده دفترچه چک، برای اطمینان از دفترهای تراز و گزارش‌های دقیق بر پایه قواعد حسابداری حرفه‌ای از جمله حسابداری دوطرفه بنا شده است.</p>
    <p>با گنوکش می‌توانی (البته به آنها محدود نیستی):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>درآمد و هزینه‌های شخصی روزانه خود را پیگیری کنی</li>
      <li>سهام، اوراق قرضه و حساب‌های صندوق‌های سرمایه‌گذاری مشترک را به آسانی مدیریت کنی</li>
      <li>حسابداری کسب و کار کوچک خود را بروز نگه داری</li>
      <li>از داده‌های مالی خود گزارش‌ها و نمودارهای دقیق تهیه کنی</li>
      <li>برای رهایی از ورود داده تکراری تراکنش‌های زمانبندی‌شده تنظیم کنی</li>
      <li>محاسبات مالی از قبیل بازپرداخت وام انجام دهی</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>GnuCash on ohjelma henkilökohtaiseen ja pienyritysten kirjanpitoon.</p>
    <p>Helppokäyttöiseksi, mutta silti tehokkaaksi ja joustavaksi suunnitellun GnuCashin avulla voit seurata pankkitilejä, osakkeita, tuloja ja menoja. Käyttö on helppoa ja intuitiivista kuten ruutuvihkon käyttö. Silti GnuCash sisältää ammattimaisten omaksumia periaatteita kuten kahdenkertaisen kirjanpidon varmistaakseen tasapainossa olevat merkkaukset ja tarkat raportit.</p>
    <p>GnuCashin avulla voit (mutta et ole rajoittunut):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Pitää kirjaa päivittäisistä tuloista ja menoista</li>
      <li>Hallita osake-, bondi- ja rahastotilejä helposti</li>
      <li>Pitää pienyrityksesi kirjanpidon ajan tasalla</li>
      <li>Luoda tarkkoja raportteja ja kuvaajia taloustietoihisi pohjaten</li>
      <li>Asettaa aikataulutettuja siirtoja välttääksesi toistuvien tietojen kirjaamisen</li>
      <li>Vaihtaa tietoja CSV-/FinTS (entinen HBCI) -muodoissa tai tuoda SWIFT-MT9xx-/QIF-/OFX-tietoa sisältäen tapahtumien täsmäämisen</li>
      <li>Suorittaa talouteen liittyviä laskutoimituksia, kuten lainan takaisinmaksusuunnitelman</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>GnuCash est un programme pour la gestion de finances personnelles et de petites entreprises.</p>
    <p>Conçu pour être facile à utiliser, mais puissant et flexible, GnuCash vous permet de suivre les comptes bancaires, les actions, les revenus et les dépenses. Aussi rapide et intuitif à utiliser qu'un registre papier, il est basé sur des principes comptables professionnels comme la comptabilité en partie double pour garantir des livres équilibrés et des rapports précis.</p>
    <p>Avec GnuCash vous pouvez (entre autres) :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Suivre vos revenus et vos dépenses personnelles au jour le jour</li>
      <li>Gérer facilement vos actions, obligations et fonds communs de placement</li>
      <li>Garde les comptes de votre petite entreprise à jour</li>
      <li>Créer des rapports et des graphiques précis à partir de vos données financières</li>
      <li>Configurer des transactions récurrentes pour éviter de ré-entrer les mêmes données</li>
      <li>Échanger par CSV/FinTS (anciennement HBCI) ou importer des données SWIFT-MT9xx/QIF/OFX, y compris avec une correspondance des transactions</li>
      <li>Effectuer des calculs financiers, comme le remboursement d'un prêt</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>גנוקאש היא תכנת הנהלת חשבונות, לשימוש אישי ולעסקים קטנים.</p>
    <p>מיועדת להיות קלה לשימוש, אך עצמתית וגמישה, גנוקאש מאפשרת לעקוב אחר חשבונות בנק, ניירות־ערך, הכנסות והוצאות. היא מהירה ואינטואיטיבית לשימוש, בדומה לרישום בפנקס המחאות. היא מבוססת על עקרונות חשבונאיים מקצועיים כמו מערכת חשבונאות כפולה כדי להבטיח ספרים מאוזנים ודוחות מדויקים.</p>
    <p>עם גנוקאש ניתן גם (אך לא רק):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>מעקב יומי אחר הכנסות והוצאות אישיות</li>
      <li>ניהול מניות, אגרות חוב וקרנות נאמנות בקלות</li>
      <li>שמירה על עדכניות ספרי החשבונות בעסק קטן</li>
      <li>יצירת דוחות ותרשימים מדויקים מהנתונים הפיננסיים</li>
      <li>הגדרת תנועה מחזורית למניעת הזנות כפולות</li>
      <li>העברות חליפין על־ידי CSV/FinTS (לשעבר HBCI) או ייבוא נתונים מ SWIFT-MT9xx/QIF/OFX כולל התאמת תנועה</li>
      <li>ביצוע חישובים פיננסיים, כמו פרעון הלוואה</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="hi">
    <p>GnuCash व्यक्तिगत और लघु-व्यवसाय वित्तीय-लेखांकन के लिए एक प्रोग्राम है. </p>
    <p>उपयोग में आसान, फिर भी शक्तिशाली और लचीले रूप में तैयार किया गया GnuCash आपको बैंक खातों, शेयरों, आय और व्यय पर नजर रखने में सक्षम बनाता है. त्वरित और चेकबुक रजिस्टर के रूप में उपयोग के लिए सहज यह सुविधा दोहरी-प्रविष्टि लेखांकन जैसे पेशेवर लेखांकन सिद्धांतों पर आधारित है जो संतुलित लेखा-बही और सटीक रिपोर्ट तैयार करना सुनिश्चित करती है. </p>
    <p>GnuCash के साथ आप यह सब कर सकते हैं (लेकिन यहीं तक सीमित नहीं है):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>अपनी रोजमर्रा की व्यक्तिगत आय और व्यय पर नज़र रखें</li>
      <li>अपने शेयर, बांड और म्यूचुअल फंड खातों को सरलता से प्रबंधित करें</li>
      <li>अपने लघु व्यवसाय के लेखांकन को अप टू डेट रखें</li>
      <li>अपने वित्तीय डेटा से सटीक रिपोर्ट और ग्राफ बनाएं</li>
      <li>डेटा प्रविष्टि के दोहराव से बचने के लिए निर्धारित लेनदेन सेट करें</li>
      <li>ऋण अदायगी जैसी वित्तीय गणनाएं पूरी करें</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>GnuCash je računovodstveni program, namijenjen pojedincima i malim poduzećima.</p>
    <p>Osmišljen da bude jednostavan u upotrebi, istovremeno moćan i prilagodljiv, GnuCash ti omogućava praćenje bankovnih računa, dionica, prihoda i rashoda. GnuCash se zasniva na profesionalnim računovodstvenim načelima kao što je dvojno knjigovodstvo, te osigurava saldirane knjige i točne izvještaje.</p>
    <p>Mali isječak mogućnosti programa GnuCash:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Prati dnevne prihode i rashode</li>
      <li>Upravljaj kontima dionica, obveznica i investicijskih fondova s lakoćom</li>
      <li>Održi računovodstvo tvog malog poduzeća aktualnim</li>
      <li>Stvori točne izvještaje i dijagrame pomoću tvojih financijskih podataka</li>
      <li>Postavi terminirane transakcije i izbjegni višestruko unositi datume</li>
      <li>Razmijeni pomoću CSV/FinTS (prijašnji HBCI) ili uvezi SWIFT-MT9xx/QIF/OFX podatke, uključujući uspoređivanje transakcija</li>
      <li>Izradi financijske kalkulacije, kao što je otplaćivanje kredita</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>GnuCash adalah sebuah program akuntansi keuangan untuk personal dan usaha kecil.</p>
    <p>Didesain agar mudah digunakan, kaya fitur dan fleksibel, GnuCash memungkinkan Anda melacak akun bank, saham, pendapatan dan pengeluaran. Secepat dan seintuitif register buku cek, GnuCash dibuat berdasar prinsip-prinsip akuntansi profesional seperti akuntansi pencatatan-ganda untuk memastikan pembukuan yang seimbang dan laporan yang akurat.</p>
    <p>Dengan GnuCash Anda dapat (namun tidak terbatas):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Melacak pendapatan dan pengeluaran personal harian Anda</li>
      <li>Mengelola akun saham, obligasi, dan reksadana dengan mudah</li>
      <li>Menjaga akuntansi usaha kecil Anda tetap mutakhir</li>
      <li>Membuat laporan dan grafik yang akurat dari data keuangan Anda</li>
      <li>Mengatur transaksi terjadwal untuk menghindari entri data yang berulang</li>
      <li>Ganti dengan CSV/FinTS(former HBCI) atau impor data SWIFT-MT9xx/QIF/OFX termasuk Pencocokan Transaksi</li>
      <li>Melakukan perhitungan finansial, seperti angsuran pinjaman</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>GnuCash è un programma per la contabilità personale e delle piccole imprese.</p>
    <p>Progettato per essere di semplice utilizzo ma comunque potente e flessibile, GnuCash permette di tenere traccia dei conti bancari, delle azioni, delle entrate e delle uscite. Intuitivo nell'utilizzo come un libretto degli assegni, si basa sui principi fondamentali della contabilità per garantire il bilancio dei conti e l'accuratezza dei resoconti.</p>
    <p>Con GnuCash è possibile:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Tenere traccia quotidianamente delle entrate e delle uscite personali</li>
      <li>Gestire con facilità i tuoi conti per azioni, obbligazioni e fondi comuni</li>
      <li>Mantenere aggiornata la contabilità della tua piccola attività</li>
      <li>Creare dei resoconti e dei grafici accurati dai tuoi dati finanziari</li>
      <li>Impostare delle transazioni pianificate per evitare l'immissione ripetitiva di dati</li>
      <li>Scambiare tramite CSV / FinTS (ex HBCI) o importare i dati SWIFT-MT9xx/QIF/OFX incluso l'abbinamento delle transazioni</li>
      <li>Effettuare calcoli finanziari, quali quelli per il rimborso di un prestito</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="kn">
    <p>ಗ್ನುಕ್ಯಾಶ್ ಎನ್ನುವುದು ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಮತ್ತು ಸಣ್ಣ ಉದ್ಯಮದ ಹಣಕಾಸು-ಲೆಕ್ಕಪತ್ರಕ್ಕಾಗಿನ ಒಂದು ಪ್ರೊಗ್ರಾಮ್ ಆಗಿದೆ.</p>
    <p>ಬಳಕೆಗೆ ಸುಲಭವಾದ, ಆದರೆ ಅಷ್ಟೇ ಸಶಕ್ತ ಮತ್ತು ಸುಲಭವಾಗಿ ಹೊಂದಿಕೆಯಾಗುವಂತೆ ವಿನ್ಯಾಸಗೊಳಿಸಲಾದ ಗ್ನುಕ್ಯಾಶ್ ಬಳಸಿಕೊಂಡು ನೀವು ಬ್ಯಾಂಕ್ ಖಾತೆಗಳನ್ನು, ಸ್ಟಾಕ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು, ಆದಾಯ ಮತ್ತು ವೆಚ್ಚಗಳ ಮೇಲ್ವಿಚಾರಣೆ ನಡೆಸಲು ಅವಕಾಶವಿರುತ್ತದೆ. ಬ್ಯಾಲೆನ್ಸ್ ಆದ ಪುಸ್ತಕಗಳು ಮತ್ತು ನಿಖರವಾದ ವರದಿಗಳು ದೊರೆಯುವುದನ್ನು ಖಚಿತಪಡಿಸಿಕೊಳ್ಳಲು ಒಂದು ಚೆಕ್‌ಬುಕ್ ರಿಜಿಸ್ಟರ್‌ನಂತೆ ಚುರುಕಾಗಿ ಮತ್ತು ಸುಲಭವಾಗಿ ಬಳಸಬಹುದಾಗಿರುವ ಇದು ಡಬಲ್-ಎಂಟ್ರಿ ಅಕೌಂಟಿಂಗ್‌ನಂತರ ವೃತ್ತಿಪರ ಅಕೌಂಟಿಗ್ ನಿಯಮಗಳ ಮೇಲೆ ಆಧರಿತವಾಗಿರುತ್ತದೆ.</p>
    <p>ಗ್ನುಕ್ಯಾಶ್ ಬಳಸಿಕೊಂಡು ನೀವು (ಇಷ್ಟಕ್ಕೆ ಮಿತಿಯಾಗಿರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>ನಿಮ್ಮ ದೈನಂದಿನ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಆದಾಯ ಮತ್ತು ವೆಚ್ಚಗಳ ಜಾಡನ್ನು ಇರಿಸಿಕೊಳ್ಳಬಹುದು</li>
      <li>ನಿಮ್ಮ ಸ್ಟಾಕ್‌, ಬಾಂಡ್ ಮತ್ತು ಮ್ಯುಚವಲ್‌ ಫಂಡ್ ಖಾತೆಗಳನ್ನು ಸುಲಭವಾಗಿ ನೋಡಿಕೊಳ್ಳಬಹುದು</li>
      <li>ನಿಮ್ಮ ಸಣ್ಣ ಉದ್ಯಮದ ಹಣಕಾಸು ಲೆಕ್ಕಗಳನ್ನು ಅಪ್‌ ಟು ಡೇಟ್ ಆಗಿ ಇರಿಸಿಕೊಳ್ಳಬಹುದು</li>
      <li>ನಿಮ್ಮ ಹಣಕಾಸು ಮಾಹಿತಿಯಿಂದ ನಿಖರವಾದ ವರದಿಗಳು ಮತ್ತು ನಕ್ಷೆಗಳನ್ನು ರಚಿಸಬಹುದು</li>
      <li>ಪುನರಾವರ್ತಿತ ದತ್ತಾಂಶ ನಮೂದಿಸುವುದನ್ನು ತಪ್ಪಿಸಲು ಅನುಸೂಚಿತ ವ್ಯವಹಾರಗಳನ್ನು ಸಿದ್ಧಗೊಳಿಸಬಹುದು</li>
      <li>ಸಾಲ ಮರುಪಾವತಿಯಂತಹ ಹಣಕಾಸು ಲೆಕ್ಕಾಚಾರಗಳನ್ನು ನಿರ್ವಹಿಸಬಹುದು</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="kok">
    <p>GnuCash ही खाजगी आणि ल्हान-व्यवसाय अर्थिक खात्याखातीर कार्यावळ आसा.</p>
    <p>वापरपाक सोपे, तरीय शक्तिमान आणि लवचिक अशे तयार केल्ले, GnuCash तुमका बँक खाती, स्टॉक, उत्पन्न आणि खर्च हाचेर लक्ष दवरूंक दिता. चेकबुक नोंदवही म्हण वापरपाक ते सोपे आसा आणि डबल एंट्री अकौन्टिंगसारकिल्या व्यावसायिक अकौन्टिंग तत्त्वांचेर ते आदारित आसा जाकालागून समतोल हिशोब आणि अचूक अहवाल हांची खात्री मेळटा.</p>
    <p>GnuCash संयत तुमी (पुण मेरेन मर्यादित ना):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>दर दिसाच्या तुमच्या खाजगी कमाई आणि खर्चार ट्रॅक दवरात</li>
      <li>तुमची स्टॉक, बॉन्ड आणि म्यूच्यूअल फंड खात्यांचे सहज व्यवस्थापन करात.</li>
      <li>तुमच्या व्यवसायाचे खाते अप टू डेट दवरात</li>
      <li>तुमच्या अर्थिक डेटातल्यान अचूक अहवाल आणि ग्राफ्स तयार करात </li>
      <li>थारायिल्ले व्यवहार कसल्योय परत परत डेटा नोंदी टाळपाखातीर थारायात.</li>
      <li>अर्थिक मेजप करात, देखीक कर्जाची परत फेड</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="kok@latin">
    <p>GnuCash ek kariavoll khasgi ani lhan-ud'degachea vrutachea hixobachi</p>
    <p>Sompeponnim vaprunk ankhlea, torui bollixtt ani bagovpi, GnuCash bank khatim, santthe, zodd ani khorch topasunk porvangi dita. Rokddem ani somzupi vaprunk ek chekpustokachea nondpott'tte sarkhi, ti vevsaik hixobachea totvancher adarit asa zoxe porim doddttea nondnnechea hixob zulloilelim pustokam ani binchukiche vakeanchi khatri korunk</p>
    <p>GnuCasha vorvim tujean (punn hachea porian moriadit)</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Tujea dispott'ttea khasgi zodd ani khorchacho hixob dhor</li>
      <li>Tuje santthe, homipotram ani mutual nidhichim khatim sompeponnim hatall</li>
      <li>Tuje lhan vepari hixob aichea tarkhent dovor</li>
      <li>Binchukiche vake ani alekh tujea arthik mhaite pasun roch</li>
      <li>Tharavik vevhar bosoi portun portun mhaitechi nond tallunk</li>
      <li>Arthik gonnit kor zoxe porim ek rinnachem feddop koxem</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ks">
    <p>GnuCash छु अख परोगराम </p>
    <p>डिज़ायिन करनॊ आमुत युथ ईसतेमाल करुन आसान गछ़ॊ, तोतॊ गछ़ॊ ताकतवर तॊ लचकदार आसुन,GnuCash छु तोहयॊ ईजाज़त दिवान टरेक करनस मनज़ बेनक एकावुनट, सिटाक,ईनकम तॊ खरॊच</p>
    <p>GnuCashस सॊत हेकिव तोहयॊ ( मगर छॊ नॊ हदस मनज़):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>खयाल थॊयिव पननॊन दोह दॊश कॊन ज़ॊती आमदन तॊ खरचस</li>
      <li>पनॊन सिटाक, बानड तॊ मयूचवल फनड एकावनटन कॊरिव मनेज आसॊनी सान</li>
      <li>पनॊन सुमाल बिज़नस एकावनटिनग थॊयिव अप टु डेट</li>
      <li>बनॊयिव सही रिपोट तॊ गराफ पननॊ फायनानशल डाटा पयॊठ</li>
      <li>सेट अप कॊरिव शडूलॊड टरानज़ेकशन यक तरफ तरावनॊ बापत दोहरावनॊ आमॊच़ डाटा एनटरी</li>
      <li>पॊरफारम कॊरिव फायनानशल कलकुलेशनॊ, मसलन लोन रिपेमेनट</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>GnuCash ir personīgo un mazā biznesa finanšu pārvaldības programma.</p>
    <p>Izstrādāts, lai būtu viegli lietojams un tajā pat laikā jaudīgs un elastīgs, GnuCash ļauj jums saglabāt kontus, ieņēmumus, izdevumus un akcijas. Lai arī to var izmantot kā vienkāršu izdevumu uzskaiti, tas ir balstīts uz profesionāliem grāmatvedības principiem, kā divkāršais ieraksts, nodrošinot bilanci un precīzus pārskatus.</p>
    <p>Ar GnuCash jūs varat (un ne tikai):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Uzskaitīt jūsu ikdienas ieņēmumus un izdevumus</li>
      <li>Ērti pārvaldīt akcijas un vērtspapīrus</li>
      <li>Uzturiet savu mazo biznesu aktuālu</li>
      <li>Izveidot precīzus pārskatus un grafikus saviem finanšu datiem</li>
      <li>Iestatiet plānotos grāmatojumus, lai novērstu atkārtotu datu ievadi</li>
      <li>Veikt finanšu aprēķinus, piemēram, kredīta atmaksu</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="mai">
    <p>GnuCash व्यक्तिगत आओर लघु-व्यवसाय वित्तीय-लेखांकन कलेल एकटा प्रोग्राम अछि.</p>
    <p>उपयोग मे आसान, तइयो शक्तिशाली आओर लचीला तैआर कएल गेल GnuCash अहाँकेँ बैंक खाता, शेयर, आय आओर व्यय पर नजर राखए मे सक्षम बनाबैत अछि. त्वरित आओर चेकबुक रजिस्टर क रूपेँ उपयोग कलेल सहज ई सुविधा दोहरा-प्रविष्टि लेखांकन जहिना पेशेवर लेखांकन सिद्धांत पर आधारित अछि जे संतुलित लेखा-बही आओर सटीक रिपोर्ट तैआर कएनाइ सुनिश्चित करैत अछि.</p>
    <p>GnuCash क सँग अहाँ ई सब कए सकैत छी (मुदा एतय धरि सीमित नहि अछि):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>अपन रोजमर्रा क व्यक्तिगत आय आओर व्यय पर नज़र राखू</li>
      <li>अपन शेयर, बांड आओर म्यूचुअल फंड खाता केँ सरलता सँ प्रबंधित करू</li>
      <li>अपन लघु व्यवसाय क लेखांकन केँ अप टू डेट राखू</li>
      <li>अपन वित्तीय डेटा सँ सटीक रिपोर्ट आओर ग्राफ बनाबू</li>
      <li>डेटा प्रविष्टि क दोहराव सँ बचए कलेल निर्धारित लेनदेन सेट करू</li>
      <li>ऋण अदायगी जहिना वित्तीय गणना पूरा करू</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="mni">
    <p>GnuCash ꯑꯁꯤ ꯑꯁꯤ ꯃꯤ ꯃꯁꯥꯒꯤ ꯑꯣꯏꯕ ꯑꯃꯁꯨꯡ ꯑꯄꯤꯛꯄ ꯂꯂꯣꯟ-ꯏꯇꯤꯛꯀꯤ ꯁꯦꯜꯊꯨꯝ-ꯑꯦꯀꯥꯎꯟꯇꯤꯡꯒꯤ ꯄ꯭ꯔꯣꯒ꯭ꯔꯥꯝ ꯑꯃꯅꯤ ꯫</p>
    <p>ꯁꯤꯖꯤꯟꯅꯕꯗ ꯂꯥꯏꯅꯕ ꯗꯤꯖꯥꯏꯟ ꯇꯧꯕꯅꯤ, ꯍꯧꯖꯤꯛꯁꯨ ꯃꯄꯥꯡꯒꯜ ꯂꯩꯔꯤ ꯑꯃꯁꯨꯡ ꯐ꯭ꯂꯦꯛꯁꯤꯕꯜ ꯑꯣꯏꯔꯤ, GnuCash ꯅ ꯕꯦꯡꯛ ꯑꯦꯀꯥꯎꯟꯠꯁꯤꯡ, ꯁ꯭ꯇꯣꯛꯁꯤꯡ, ꯏꯀꯝ ꯑꯃꯁꯨ ꯆꯥꯗꯤꯡꯁꯤꯡ ꯇ꯭ꯔꯦꯛ ꯇꯧꯕ ꯌꯥꯍꯜꯂꯤ꯫ ꯆꯦꯛꯕꯨꯛ ꯔꯦꯖꯤꯁꯇꯔ ꯑꯃ ꯑꯣꯏꯅ ꯁꯤꯖꯤꯟꯅꯅꯕ ꯃꯁꯤ ꯌꯥꯝꯅ ꯊꯨꯕ ꯑꯃꯁꯨꯡ ꯈꯪꯅꯤꯡꯒꯟꯕ ꯑꯣꯏꯕꯅ ꯃꯁꯤ ꯈꯨꯗꯝ ꯑꯣꯏꯅ ꯕꯦꯂꯦꯟꯁ ꯕꯨꯛꯁꯤꯡ ꯑꯃꯁꯨꯡ ꯆꯞ-ꯆꯥꯕ ꯔꯤꯄꯣꯔꯠꯁꯤꯡ ꯄꯤꯅꯕ ꯗꯕꯜ-ꯑꯦꯟꯇ꯭ꯔꯤ ꯑꯦꯀꯥꯎꯟꯇꯤꯡ ꯑꯣꯏꯕ ꯄ꯭ꯔꯣꯐꯦꯁꯅꯦꯜ ꯑꯦꯀꯥꯎꯇꯤꯡ ꯄ꯭ꯔꯤꯟꯁꯤꯄꯜꯁꯤꯡꯗ ꯌꯨꯝꯐꯝ ꯑꯣꯏ꯫</p>
    <p>GnuCash ꯇꯧꯗꯨꯅ ꯑꯗꯣꯝꯅ ꯇꯧꯕ ꯉꯝꯒꯅꯤ (ꯑꯗꯨꯕꯨ ꯄꯪꯈꯩ ꯂꯩꯇꯦ):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>ꯑꯗꯣꯝꯒꯤ ꯅꯣꯡꯃ ꯃꯣꯡꯃꯒꯤ ꯅꯁꯥꯒꯤ ꯏꯟꯀꯝ ꯑꯃꯁꯨꯡ ꯆꯥꯗꯤꯡ ꯇ꯭ꯔꯦꯛ ꯇꯧꯕꯤꯌꯨ</li>
      <li>ꯑꯗꯣꯝꯒꯤ ꯁ꯭ꯇꯣꯛ, ꯕꯣꯟꯗ ꯑꯃꯁꯨꯡ ꯃꯤꯎꯆꯨꯌꯦꯜ ꯐꯟꯗ ꯑꯦꯀꯥꯎꯟꯠꯁꯤꯡ ꯂꯥꯏꯅ ꯁꯤꯜꯂꯥꯡꯎ</li>
      <li>ꯑꯗꯣꯝꯒꯤ ꯑꯄꯤꯛꯄ ꯂꯂꯣꯟ-ꯏꯇꯤꯛꯀꯤ ꯑꯦꯀꯥꯎꯟꯇꯤꯡ ꯑꯞ ꯇꯨ ꯗꯦꯠ ꯑꯣꯏꯅ ꯊꯝꯕꯤꯌꯨ</li>
      <li>ꯑꯗꯣꯝꯒꯤ ꯐꯥꯏꯅꯥꯟꯁꯤꯌꯦꯜ ꯗꯥꯇꯥꯗꯒꯤ ꯆꯞ ꯆꯥꯕ ꯔꯤꯄꯣꯔꯠ ꯑꯃꯁꯨꯡ ꯒ꯭ꯔꯥꯐꯁꯤꯡ ꯁꯦꯝꯒꯠꯂꯣ</li>
      <li>ꯗꯥꯇꯥ ꯍꯟꯖꯤꯟꯅ ꯆꯪꯁꯤꯟꯗꯅꯕ ꯁꯦꯗꯤꯎꯜ ꯇꯧꯔꯕ ꯇ꯭ꯔꯥꯟꯁꯦꯛꯁꯟꯁꯤꯡ ꯁꯦꯠ ꯑꯞ ꯇꯧꯔꯣ</li>
      <li>ꯁꯦꯜ-ꯊꯨꯝ ꯄꯥꯕ ꯄꯥꯡꯊꯣꯛꯎ ꯈꯨꯗꯝ ꯑꯣꯏꯅ ꯂꯣꯟ ꯁꯤꯡꯒꯠꯄ</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="mni@bengali">
    <p>GnuCash অসি মীওই অমগী অমসুং অপীকপা-ব্যুজিনেস ফাইনান্সিএল-একাউন্তিংগী প্রোগ্রাম অমনি।</p>
    <p>সিজিন্নবদা লায়বা, অদুবু অকনবা ওইবা অমসুং হোংদোক-হোংজিন য়াবা মওংদা সেম্লবা, GnuCashনা নহাকপু বেঙ্ক একাউন্তসিং, স্তোকসিং, ইনকম অমসুং চাদিংসিং ত্রেক তৌবা য়াহল্লি। য়াংনা অমসুং খুদক্তা পাংথোকপা ঙম্বা মরম্না চেকবুক রেজিস্তর অমগুম্না সিজিন্নবা য়ারবা, মসিনা বেলেন্স ওইরবা বুকসিং অমসুং চপ চাবা রিপোর্তসিং ফংহন্নবগীদমক মসি সিনফমগী ওইবা একাউন্তিং প্রিন্সিপলসিং হায়বদি দবল-এন্ত্রি একাউন্তিংগুম্বদা য়ুম্ফম ওইবনি।</p>
    <p>GnuCashগা লোয়ননা নহাক্না ঙমগনি (অদুবু অকক্নবা মওংদা নত্তে):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>নহাক্কী নুমিৎ খুদিংগী ওইবা নসাগী ইনকম অমসুং চাদিংসিং ত্রেক তৌ</li>
      <li>নহাক্কী স্তোক, বোন্দ অমসুং ম্যুচুএল ফন্দ একাউন্তসিং লায়না মেনেজ তৌ</li>
      <li>নহাক্কী অপীকপা ব্যুজিনেসকী একাউন্ত সেম্বদু অপ তু দেত ওইহল্লু</li>
      <li>নহাক্কী ফাইনান্সিএল দেতাদগী চপ চাবা রিপোর্তসিং অমসুং গ্রাফসিং সেম্মু</li>
      <li>দেতা এন্ত্রি হঞ্জিন্না তৌদনবগীদমক সেদ্যুল লেপ্লবা ত্রাঞ্জেক্সনসিং সেত অপ তৌ</li>
      <li>লোন রিপেএমেন্ত অমগুম্বা, ফাইনান্সিএল কেল্ক্যুলেসনসিং পাংথোকউ</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="mr">
    <p>GnuCash हा वैयक्तिक व लघु-उद्योग आर्थिक-लेखांकनासाठी प्रोग्रॅम आहे.</p>
    <p>वापरण्यास अतिशय सोपे, तरीही प्रभावी व लवचिक अशा पद्धतीने रचना करण्यात आलेल्या GnuCash मुळे तुम्ही बँक खाती, समभाग, उत्पन्न व खर्चाचा आढावा घेता येतो. याचा तपासणीपुस्तक नोंदवहीच्या स्वरुपात झटपट व नाविन्यपूर्ण उपयोग करता येतो, ते दुहेरी-नोंद लेखांकन यासारख्या व्यवसायिक लेखांकनाच्या तत्वांवर आधारित आहेत ज्याद्वारे चोख ताळेबंद असलेल्या पुस्तकांची व अचूक अहवालांची खात्री केली जाते.</p>
    <p>GnuCash द्वारे तुम्ही पुढील बाबी करु शकतात (मात्र त्यापुरते मर्यादित नाही):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>तुमचे दैनंदिन उत्पन्न व खर्चांवर लक्ष ठेवणे</li>
      <li>तुमचे समभाग, रोखे व म्युच्युअल फंड खात्यांचे सहजपणे व्यवस्थापन करणे</li>
      <li>तुमच्या लहान व्यवसायाचे लेखांकन अद्ययावत ठेवणे</li>
      <li>तुमच्या आर्थिक माहितीमधून अचूक अहवाल व आलेख तयार करणे</li>
      <li>माहिती नोंदीची पुनरावृत्ती टाळण्यासाठी अनुसूचित व्यवहार निश्चित करा</li>
      <li>आर्थिक हिशेब करणे, उदाहरणार्थ कर्ज परतफेड</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Med GnuCash kan du (dog ikke begrenset til):</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>GnuCash is boekhoudsoftware voor thuis en voor kleine ondernemingen.</p>
    <p>GnuCash stelt u in staat om heel eenvoudig bankrekeningen, beleggingen, inkomsten en uitgaven bij te houden, zonder in te leveren op kracht of flexibiliteit. Net zo snel en intuïtief te gebruiken als een dagboek, maar gestoeld op boekhoudkundige principes om te zorgen voor een sluitende boekhouding en accurate rapporten.</p>
    <p>Met GnuCash kunt u (maar bent u niet beperkt tot):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Uw persoonlijke inkomsten en uitgaven van dag tot dag volgen</li>
      <li>Uw aandelen, obligaties en beleggingsfondsen eenvoudig beheren</li>
      <li>De boekhouding van uw kleine onderneming bijhouden</li>
      <li>Accurate rapporten en grafieken maken van uw financiële gegevens</li>
      <li>Vaste journaalposten instellen om te voorkomen dat telkens dezelfde gegevens moeten worden ingevoerd</li>
      <li>Data uitwisselen via CSV/FinTS (voormalig HBCI) of data importeren in SWIFT/MT9xx/QIF/OFX formaat, inclusief boekingsherkenning</li>
      <li>Financiële berekeningen maken, zoals de annuïtaire aflossing van een lening</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>GnuCash to program do rachunkowości finansowej osób prywatnych i małych firm.</p>
    <p>Dzięki GnuCash możesz (ale nie tylko):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Śledź swoje codzienne dochody i wydatki</li>
      <li>Z łatwością zarządzaj swoimi akcjami, obligacjami i funduszami inwestycyjnymi</li>
      <li>Twórz dokładne raporty i wykresy na podstawie danych finansowych</li>
      <li>Wymieniaj CSV/FinTS (wcześniej HBCI) lub importuj dane SWIFT-MT9xx/QIF/OFX</li>
      <li>Wykonuj obliczenia finansowe, takie jak spłata kredytu</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O GnuCash é um programa para contabilidade pessoal e micro-empresas.</p>
    <p>Desenhado para ser fácil de usar mas poderoso e flexível, o GnuCash permite controlar contas bancárias, acções, receitas e despesas. Tão fácil e intuitivo de usar como um livro de cheques, é baseado em princípios contabilísticos profissionais, como a contabilidade de dupla entrada, para garantir livros saldados e relatórios precisos.</p>
    <p>Com o GnuCash pode (sem estar limitado a):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Seguir diariamente as suas receitas e despesas pessoais</li>
      <li>Fazer a gestão de acções, obrigações e fundos facilmente</li>
      <li>Manter a sua contabilidade da empresa actualizada</li>
      <li>Criar relatórios e gráficos precisos dos seus dados financeiros</li>
      <li>Preparar transacções agendadas para evitar inserir dados repetidos</li>
      <li>Negociar por CSV/FinTS(antigo HBCI) ou importar dados SWIFT-MT9xx/QIF/OFX, incluindo comparação de transacções</li>
      <li>Realizar cálculos financeiros, tais como o pagamento de um empréstimo</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>GnuCash é um programa de contabilidade financeira pessoal e de pequenas empresas.</p>
    <p>Projetado para ser fácil de usar e ainda poderoso e flexível, o GnuCash permite que você acompanhe as suas contas bancárias, ações, receitas e despesas. Tão rápido e intuitivo de usar como um talão de cheques, tem base nos princípios da contabilidade profissional, como o duplo lançamento contábil para garantir os balanços contábeis e relatórios precisos.</p>
    <p>Com o GnuCash você pode (mas não está limitado a):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Acompanhar as suas receitas e as suas despesas pessoais do dia-a-dia</li>
      <li>Gerenciar as suas contas de ações, títulos e fundos mútuos com facilidade</li>
      <li>Manter a contabilidade da sua pequena empresa atualizada</li>
      <li>Criar relatórios e gráficos precisos a partir de seus dados financeiros</li>
      <li>Configurar as transações programadas para evitar a entrada repetida dos dados</li>
      <li>Troque por CSV / serviços de operações financeiras (antigo HBCI) ou importe os dados do SWIFT-MT9xx / QIF / OFX incluindo as transações combinadas</li>
      <li>Executar cálculos financeiros, como o reembolso de um empréstimo</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>GnuCash это программа для персонального учета финансов и ведения бухгалтерского учета для малого бизнеса.</p>
    <p>Спроектированная чтобы быть простой, но в то же время мощной и гибкой в использовании, GnuCash позволяет вам вести учёт ваших банковских счетов, акций, доходов и расходов. Будучи такой же удобной и интуитивной как чековая книжка, она основана на профессиональных принципах ведения бухгалтерии, таких как использование двойной записи для исключения ситуации расхождения счетов и создания точных отчётов.</p>
    <p>Вот неполный список того, что вы можете делать при помощи GnuCash:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Отслеживать ваши ежедневные доходы и расходы </li>
      <li>С легкостью вести учёт ваших акций, облигаций и взаимных фондов</li>
      <li>Поддерживать бухгалтерию вашего малого бизнеса в актуальном состоянии</li>
      <li>Создавать точные отчеты и графики на основе ваших финансовых данных</li>
      <li>Настроить плановые проводки для упрощения повторяющихся трат</li>
      <li>Выполнять финансовые расчёты, например выплаты по займу</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <ul>
      <li>Vykoná finančné výpočty, napr. splácanie pôžičky</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Гнуов новчић је програм финансијског рачуноводства за личну и употребу у малим пословањима.</p>
    <p>Осмишљен да буде једноставан за коришћење, али моћан и прилагодљив, Гнуов новчић вам омогућава праћење банковних рачуна, деоница, прихода и расхода. Како је брз и интуитиван за коришћење као регистар чековне књижице, заснива се на професионалним рачуноводственим начелима као што је двојно књиговодство да би осигурао књиге биланса и тачне извештаје.</p>
    <p>Са Гнуовим новчићем можете да (али нисте ограничени):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Пратите ваше дневне приходе и расходе</li>
      <li>Управљајте са лакоћом налозима ваших деоница, обвезница и инвестиционог фонда</li>
      <li>Одржавате ваше мало пословно рачуноводство</li>
      <li>Направите тачне извештаје и графике из ваших финансијских података</li>
      <li>Подесите заказане трансакције како бисте избегли понављање датума уноса</li>
      <li>Обавите финансијска израчунавања, као што је отплаћивање зајма</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>GnuCash är ett program för privat- och småföretagsbokföring.</p>
    <p>Utformat för att vara lätt att använda, men ändå kraftfullt och flexibelt, ger GnuCash dig möjligheten att spåra bankkonton, aktier, inkomster och utgifter. Så snabbt och intuitivt att använda som en checkbok, och bygger på professionella bokföringsprinciper som dubbel bokföring för att säkerställa balanserade böcker och tillförlitliga rapporter.</p>
    <p>Med GnuCash kan du (men är inte begränsad till):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Spåra dina dagliga privata inkomster och utgifter</li>
      <li>Smidigt hantera dina aktie-, obligations, och investeringsfondskonton</li>
      <li>Håll ditt småföretags bokföring aktuell</li>
      <li>Skapa tillförlitliga rapporter och diagram från dina finansdata</li>
      <li>Ställa in schemalagda transaktioner för att undvika upprepad inmatning</li>
      <li>Dela information genom CSV/FinTS (tidigare HBCI) eller importera SWIFT-MT9xx/QIF/OFX-data inklusive transaktionsmatchning</li>
      <li>Utför finansiella uträkningar, som återbetalning av lån</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ta">
    <p>GnuCash என்பது தனிப்பட்ட மற்றும் சிறிய-வணிக நிதி-மேலாண்மைக்கான பிரோகிராம்.</p>
    <p>பயன்படுத்த எளிதாக இருந்தும், சக்தி வாய்ந்ததாக மற்றும் சாதகமானதாக வடிவமைக்கப்பட்டுள்ளதால், GnuCash நீங்கள் வங்கி கணக்குகள், பங்குகள், வருமானம் மற்றும் செலவுகளை கண்காணிக்க அனுமதிக்கிறது. ஒரு காசோலை பதிவேட்டாக பயன்படுத்த விரைவானதாக மற்றும் உள்ளுணர்வுடன் இருப்பதால், இது சரியான இருப்பு புத்தகங்கள் மற்றும் துல்லியமான அறிக்கைகளை உறுதி செய்ய இரட்டை-பதிவு கணக்கியல் போன்ற தொழில்முறை கணக்கியல் கொள்கைகளை அடிப்படையாக கொண்டுள்ளது.</p>
    <p>GnuCash-உடன் நீங்கள் செய்யமுடிவது (ஆனால் அவை மட்டுமே வரம்பாக இல்லை):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>உங்கள் தினசரி தனிநபர் வருமானம் மற்றும் செலவுகளை கண்காணிக்கலாம்</li>
      <li>உங்கள் பங்குகள், மியூசுவல் ஃபன்ட் கணக்குகளை எளிதாக நிர்வகிக்கலாம்</li>
      <li>உங்கள் சிறு-வணிகத்தை கணக்கீடை நவீனமானதாக வைத்துக்கொள்ளலாம்</li>
      <li>உங்கள் நிதி தரவில் இருந்து துல்லியமான அறிக்கைகள் மற்றும் வரைபடங்களை உருவாக்கலாம்</li>
      <li>மீண்டும் தரவு உள்ளீடை தவிர்க்க திட்டமிடப்பட்ட பரிமாற்றங்களை அமைக்கவும்</li>
      <li>கடனை திருப்பி செலுத்துவது போன்ற, நிதி கணக்கீடுகளை செய்யவும்</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="te">
    <p>Gnuక్యాష్‌ అనేది వ్యక్తిగత మరియు చిన్న-వ్యాపార ఫైనాన్షియల్-అకౌంటింగ్ కోసం ఉద్దేశించిన కార్యక్రమం.</p>
    <p>ఉపయోగించడానికి సులభమైనది అయినప్పటికీ, శక్తివంతంగా, సర్దుకుపోయేదిగా రూపొందించబడిన Gnuక్యాష్ బ్యాంకు ఖాతాలు, స్టాకులు, రాబడి మరియు ఖర్చులను గుర్తు పెట్టేందుకు మిమ్మల్ని అనుమతిస్తుంది. చెక్ బాక్స్ రిజిష్టర్‌గా ఉపయోగించడానికి త్వరిత గతి సహజ జ్ఞానం కలిగినదిగా ఉండడంతో అది బ్యాలెన్స్ పుస్తకాలు, ఖచ్చితమైన నివేదికలు ఉండేలా చూసోందుకు డబుల్ ఎంట్రీ అకౌంటింగ్ లాంటి వ్యక్తిగత వృత్తినైపుణ్య అకౌంటింగ్ సూత్రాల మీద ఆధారపడుతుంది.</p>
    <p>Gnuక్యాష్‌తో మీరు చేయగలరు (కానీ దీనికి పరిమితం కాదు):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>మీ రోజు వారీ వ్యక్తిగత రాబడి, ఖర్చుల జాడను గుర్తు పెట్టు.</li>
      <li>మీ స్టాకు, బాండ్, మ్యూచువల్ ఫండ్ ఖాతాలను సులభంగా నిర్వహించు</li>
      <li>మీ చిన్న వ్యాపారం యొక్క అకౌంటింగ్‌ను ఈ తేదీ వరకు నిర్వహించు</li>
      <li>మీ ఆర్థిక డేటా నుంచి ఖచ్చితమైన నివేదికలు, గ్రాఫ్‌లను రూపొందించు</li>
      <li>తిరిగి చేసే డేటా ఎంట్రీని నివారించడానికి షెడ్యూల్ చేసిన లావాదేవీలను ఏర్పాటు చేయి</li>
      <li>రుణం తిరిగి చెల్లింపు లాంటి ఆర్థిక లెక్కలను వేయి,</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>GnuCash, kişisel ve küçük işletme finansal muhasebesi için bir programdır.</p>
    <p>Kullanımı kolay, aynı zamanda güçlü ve esnek olacak şekilde tasarlanmış olan GnuCash, banka hesaplarını, hisse senetlerini, gelir ve giderleri izlemenize olanak tanır. Çek defteri kaydı olarak hızlı ve sezgisel olarak, dengeli kitapların ve doğru raporların sağlanması için çift giriş muhasebesi gibi mesleki muhasebe ilkelerine dayanır.</p>
    <p>GnuCash ile şunları yapabilirsiniz (ancak bunlarla sınırlı değildir):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Günlük kişisel gelir ve harcamalarınızı takip edin</li>
      <li>Hisse senedi, tahvil ve yatırım fonu hesaplarınızı kolaylıkla yönetin</li>
      <li>Küçük işletmelerinizin muhasebesini güncel tutun</li>
      <li>Finansal verilerinizden doğru raporlar ve grafikler oluşturun</li>
      <li>Tekrarlanan veri girişini önlemek için zamanlanmış işlemleri ayarlayın</li>
      <li>Bir kredi geri ödeme gibi mali hesaplamalar yapın</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>GnuCash — програма для фінансового обліку на особистому рівні і на рівні малого бізнесу.</p>
    <p>Програму створено простою у користуванні або потужною і гнучкою. Тому GnuCash надає вам змогу стежити за станом банківських рахунків, курсом акцій, прибутками і витратами. Швидка та інтуїтивно зрозуміла як чекова книжка, програма заснована на принципах професійного обліку, вона веде подвійний запис для забезпечення балансу у книгах та здатна формувати точні звіти.</p>
    <p>За допомогою GnuCash ви можете робити такі речі (і не лише такі речі):</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Стежити за щоденними особистими надходженнями і витратами</li>
      <li>Без проблем керувати вашими акціями, облігаціями та рахунками інвестиційних фондів</li>
      <li>Вести поточний облік фінансових аспектів вашого малого бізнесу</li>
      <li>Створювати точні звіти та графіки на основі ваших фінансових даних</li>
      <li>Налаштовувати заплановані транзакції для уникнення повторень у записах даних</li>
      <li>Обмін за CSV/FinTS (раніше HBCI) або імпорт даних SWIFT-MT9xx/QIF/OFX з встановленням відповідності транзакцій</li>
      <li>Виконувати фінансові обчислення, зокрема визначення виплат за позичками</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ur">
    <p>GnuCash ذاتی اور چھوٹے کاروبار کے مالی اکاؤنٹنگ کے لئے ایک پروگرام ہے.</p>
    <p>ایسا ڈیزائن كیا گیا ہے كہ استعمال کرنا آسان ہے، ابھی تک طاقتور اور لچکدار ہے ، GnuCash آپ کے بینک اکاؤنٹس، اسٹاکس، آمدنی اور اخراجات پر نظر رکھنے کے لئے اجازت دیتا ہے. چیك بُك رجسٹر كے طور پر استعمال كرنے كے لئے كوئك اور انشیوٹیو ہے یہ پیشہ ورانہ اکاؤنٹنگ اصولوں پر مبنی ہے. جیسے ڈبل انٹری اکاؤنٹنگ بیلنس بُكس اور اكیورٹ رپورٹس یقینی بنانے كےلیے۔</p>
    <p>GnuCash کے ساتھ آپ (لیکن تک محدود نہیں ) کر سکتے ہیں:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>آپ كے دن بہ دن كی ذاتی آمدنی اور اخراجات كو یاد رکھیں</li>
      <li>آپ كے اسٹاک، بانڈ اور باہمی فنڈ اکاؤنٹس مینج كریں</li>
      <li>آپ کے چھوٹے کاروبار كی اكاؤنٹنگ اپ ٹو ڈیٹ 'رکھیں</li>
      <li>آپ کے مالی اعداد و شمار سے رپورٹیں اور گرافس بنائیں</li>
      <li>بار بار ڈاٹا انٹری سے بچنے کے لئے شیڈول کے مطابق لین دین مقرر کریں</li>
      <li>مالی حساب، انجام دیں ، جیسے قرض كی باز ادائیگی </li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>GnuCash 是一个适用于个人与小企业财务管理的程序。</p>
    <p>GnuCash 易于使用，功能强大且灵活，可让您跟踪银行账户、股票，以及收入与支出。作为支票登记簿，它使用起来既快速又直观。它基于专业的会计原则，如复式记账，以确保账簿收支平衡，报表准确无误。</p>
    <p>借助 GnuCash，您可以做到（但不限于）：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>追踪您的日常个人收入和支出</li>
      <li>轻松管理您的股票，债券以及共同基金账户</li>
      <li>保证您的小型企业账务永不落后</li>
      <li>依照财务数据创建精确的报告与图表</li>
      <li>设置计划交易事项，避免重复数据输入</li>
      <li>通过CSV / FinTS（以前的HBCI）进行交换或导入SWIFT-MT9xx / QIF / OFX数据（包括交易匹配）</li>
      <li>执行贷款偿还等各种财务计算</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>GnuCash 是一給個人或小企業的財務會計軟體。</p>
    <p>設計成簡單易用，但又強大並具有彈性。GnuCash 可以讓您追蹤銀行帳戶、股票、收入和開支。雖然和記帳簿一樣直覺和快速，但它使用了專業的會計原則，像是複式計帳，以確保帳簿平衡，以及精確的報表。</p>
    <p>透過 GnuCash，您可以做到以下的事情(以及更多)：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>追蹤日常的收入和開支</li>
      <li>輕鬆管理您的股票、債券以及共同基金</li>
      <li>替您的小企業的會計資訊維持在最新的狀態</li>
      <li>從您的財務資料中建立精確的報表與圖表</li>
      <li>設定排程交易來避免重覆輸入資料</li>
      <li>以 CSV/TinTS (前 HBCI) 交換資料，或從 SWIFT-MT9xx/QIF/OFX 匯入資料，並包括交易配對</li>
      <li>進行財務計算，例如貸款償還</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>gnucash</pkgname>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">gnucash-icon.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">gnucash-icon.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnucash.GnuCash</id>
  <name>GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="ur">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="uk">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="tr">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="te">Gnuక్యాష్</name>
  <name lang="ta">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="ru">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="sv">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="sr">Гнуов новчић</name>
  <name lang="sk">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="ro">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="pt">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="nl">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="nb">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="mr">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="mni@bengali">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="mni">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="mai">ग्नूकैश</name>
  <name lang="lv">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="lt">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="ks">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="kok@latin">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="kok">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="kn">ಗ್ನುಕ್ಯಾಶ್</name>
  <name lang="ja">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="it">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="id">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="hr">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="hi">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="he">גנוקאש</name>
  <name lang="fr">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="fi">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="fa">گنوکش</name>
  <name lang="es">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="de">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="da">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="ca">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="brx">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="as">GnuCash</name>
  <name lang="ar">جنوكاش</name>
  <summary>Manage your finances, accounts, and investments</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">管理您的財務、帳目和投資</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">管理您的财务、账户与投资</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Quản lý tài chính, các tài khoản và vốn cố định</summary>
  <summary lang="ur">آپ اپنے مالگزاری، اكاؤنٹس اور سرمایہ كاری كا بندوبست كرو</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Керування вашими фінансами, рахунками та інвестиціями</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Maliyet, hesap ve yatırımlarınızı yönetin</summary>
  <summary lang="te">మీ ఆర్ధికాలను, ఖాతాలను, పెట్టుబడులను నిర్వహించు</summary>
  <summary lang="ta">உங்கள் நிதிகள், கணக்குகள், மற்றும் முதலீடுகளை பராமரிக்கவும்</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Управляйте своими финансами, счетами и инвестициями</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Hantera dina finanser, konton och investeringar</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Управљајте вашим финансијама, налозима, и улагањима</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Administrează-ți finanțele, conturile și investițiile</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Gerencie suas finanças, contas e investimentos</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Faça a gestão das suas finanças, contas e investimentos</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Zarządzaj swoimi finansami, kontami i inwestycjami</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Om uw financiën, rekeningen en investeringen te beheren</summary>
  <summary lang="ne">तपाईँको वित्तहरू, खाताहरू, र लगानीहरू प्रबन्ध गर्नुहोस्</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Forvalt dine finanser, kontoer og investeringer</summary>
  <summary lang="mr">तुमचे आर्थिक व्यवहार, खाते आणि गुंतवणुकी यांचे व्यवस्थापन करा</summary>
  <summary lang="mni@bengali">অদোমগী ফাইনান্সেস, একাউন্তস, অমসুং ইনভেস্তমেন্তস শীল-লাংউ</summary>
  <summary lang="mni">ꯑꯗꯣꯝꯒꯤ ꯐꯥꯏꯅꯥꯟꯁꯦꯁ, ꯑꯦꯀꯥꯎꯟꯠꯁ, ꯑꯃꯁꯨꯡ ꯏꯟꯚꯦꯁꯃꯦꯟꯠꯁ ꯁꯤꯜ-ꯂꯥꯡꯎ</summary>
  <summary lang="mai">अपन वित्त, खाता आओर निवेश क' प्रबंधन करू</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Pārvaldiet savas finanses, kontus un investīcijas</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Valdykite savo finansus, sąskaitas ir investicijas</summary>
  <summary lang="ks">पनॊन फायनानोस,एिकावुंट, तॊ ईनवीसटेमींट कॊरीव मनिज</summary>
  <summary lang="kok@latin">Tuji duddu, khatim ani guntovnnuk hatall</summary>
  <summary lang="kok">तुमचे वित्त,खाती आणि गुंतवणूकींचे व्यवस्थापन करात</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">재정, 계정 및 투자 관리</summary>
  <summary lang="kn">ನಿಮ್ಮ ಹಣಕಾಸುಗಳನ್ನು, ಖಾತೆಗಳನ್ನು ಹಾಗು ಹೂಡಿಕೆಗಳನ್ನು ನಿರ್ವಹಿಸಿ</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">財務、口座および投資を管理します</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Gestisci le tue finanze, i conti e gli investimenti</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Kelola keuangan, akun, dan investasi Anda</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Igazgassa pénzügyeit, számláit és befektetéseit</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Upravljaj novčanim sredstvima, kontima i ulaganjima</summary>
  <summary lang="hi">अपने वित्त, खातों और निवेशों का प्रबंधन करें</summary>
  <summary lang="he">ניהול הכספים, החשבונות וההשקעות</summary>
  <summary lang="gu">તમારા નાણાકીય, હિસાબો અને રોકાણનું સંચાલન કરો</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Gérez vos finances, vos comptes et vos investissements</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Hallitse rahavirtojasi, tilejäsi ja sijoituksiasi</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">امور مالی،حساب‌ها و سرمایه‌گذاری خود را مدیریت کن</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Kudeatu zure finantzak, kontuak eta inbertsioak</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Gestione sus finanzas, cuentas e inversiones</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Manage your finances, accounts, and investments</summary>
  <summary lang="doi">अपने फाइनांस, खातें ते निवेशें दा प्रबंधन करो</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Verwaltung der Finanzen von Privatanwendern und Kleinbetrieben.</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Håndter dine finanser, konti og investeringer</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Spravovat vaše finance, účty a investice</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Gestioneu les vostres finances, comptes i inversions</summary>
  <summary lang="brx">नोंथांनि रां, एकाउन्ट, आरो रांखामानियाव बाहायनायखौ सामलाय</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Управлявайте финанси, сметки и инвестиции</summary>
  <summary lang="as">আপোনাৰ বিত্তবোৰ, একাউন্টবোৰ, আৰু বিনিয়োগবোৰ পৰিচালনা কৰক</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">إدارة الشؤون المالية والحسابات والاستثمارات الخاص بك</summary>
  <categories>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </categories>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="social-info">mild</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <developer_name>GnuCash Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">GnuCash 專案</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">GnuCash 项目</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Проєкт GnuCash</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">GnuCash-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">GnuCash projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">Projeto GnuCash</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Projecto GnuCash</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">GnuCash project</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Progetto GnuCash</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Proyek GnuCash</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">GnuCash projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">מיזם גנוקאש</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Projet GnuCash</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">GnuCash-projekti</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Proyecto GnuCash</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">GnuCash-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">Projecte GnuCash</developer_name>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">gnucash.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-06-25" version="4.11+" />
  </releases>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="1049" height="590" type="source">https://www.gnucash.org/images/features/feature_accounts_lg.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image height="590" type="source" width="1049">https://www.gnucash.org/images/features/feature_register_lg.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image width="1049" type="source" height="590">https://www.gnucash.org/images/features/feature_bar_chart_lg.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <update_contact>gnucash-devel@gnucash.org</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">gnucash</translation>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.gnucash.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.gnucash.org</url>
  <url type="faq">https://wiki.gnucash.org/wiki/FAQ</url>
  <url type="help">https://gnucash.org/docs.phtml</url>
  <url type="donation">https://gnucash.org/donate.phtml</url>
  <url type="translate">https://wiki.gnucash.org/wiki/Translation</url>
</component>