<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>gnumeric</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">gnumeric.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">gnumeric.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" height="128" type="cached">gnumeric.png</icon>
  <name>The Gnumeric Spreadsheet</name>
  <name lang="ca">El full de càlcul Gnumeric</name>
  <name lang="cs">Tabulkový kalkulátor Gnumeric</name>
  <name lang="da">Gnumeric Regneark</name>
  <name lang="de">Die Gnumeric Tabellenkalkulation</name>
  <name lang="es">La hoja de cálculo Gnumeric</name>
  <name lang="eu">Gnumeric kalkulu-orria</name>
  <name lang="fr">Le Tableur Gnumeric</name>
  <name lang="hu">A Gnumeric táblázatkezelő</name>
  <name lang="id">Lembar Kerja Gnumeric</name>
  <name lang="kk">Gnumeric электрондық кестелері</name>
  <name lang="nb">Gnumeric regneark</name>
  <name lang="pl">Arkusz kalkulacyjny Gnumeric</name>
  <name lang="pt">A folha de cálculo Gnumeric</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Planilha eletrônica Gnumeric</name>
  <name lang="ru">Электронная таблица Gnumeric</name>
  <name lang="sl">Preglednica Gnumeric</name>
  <name lang="sr">Табеларни прорачун Гнумерик</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Tabelarni proračun Gnumerik</name>
  <name lang="sv">Gnumeric kalkylprogram</name>
  <name lang="uk">Електронна таблиця Gnumeric</name>
  <id type="desktop">org.gnumeric.gnumeric</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0 or GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>Gnumeric is a spreadsheet application for interactive manipulation of data.</p>
    <p>Gnumeric aims to provide high-accuracy computations, expressive graphs, and a wide selection of statistical analysis tools. Gnumeric can share files with Microsoft Excel and programs supporting the ODS standard.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Gnumeric je tablična aplikacija za interaktivnu manipulaciju podacima</p>
    <p>Gnumeric ima za cilj da pruži račun visoke preciznosti, izražajne grafove i širok izbor statističkih alata. Gnumeric može dijeliti datoteke s MS Excel i programima koji podržavaju ODS standard.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El Gnumeric és una aplicació de full de càlcul per a la manipulació interactiva de dades.</p>
    <p>L'objectiu del Gnumeric és proporcionar càlculs d'alta precisió, gràfics expressius i un ampli ventall d'eines d'anàlisi estadística. El Gnumeric permet de compartir fitxers amb el Microsoft Excel i els programes compatibles amb l'estàndard ODS.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Gnumeric je tabulkový kalkulátor služící k interaktivní práci s daty.</p>
    <p>Zaměřuje se na poskytování velmi přesných výpočtů, názorné grafy a rozsáhlý výběr nástrojů pro statistickou analýzu. Gnumeric umí sdílet soubory s aplikací Microsoft Excel a programy podporujícími standardní formát ODS.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Gnumeric er et regnearksprogram til interaktiv manipulering af data.</p>
    <p>Gnumeric bestræber sig på at levere udregninger af høj præcision, udtryksfulde grafer og et bred udvalg af værktøjer til statistisk analyse. Gnumeric kan dele filer med Microsoft Excel og programmer der understøtter ODS-standarden.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Gnumeric ist eine Tabellenkalkulation zur interaktiven Manipulation von Daten.</p>
    <p>Gnumeric zielt darauf ab, Berechnungen hoher Genauigkeit, ausdrucksstarke Diagramme und eine breite Auswahl von Werkzeugen für statistische Analysen bereitzustellen. Gnumeric kann Dateien mit Microsoft Excel sowie allen anderen Programmen austauschen, die dem ODS-Standard folgen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το Gnumeric είναι μια εφαρμογή λογιστικών φύλλων για διαδραστική διαχείριση δεδομένων.</p>
    <p>Το Gnumeric στοχεύει σε υψηλής ακρίβειας υπολογισμούς, αναλυτικά γραφήματα και σε μια μεγάλη ποικιλία από εργαλεία στατιστικής ανάλυσης. Το Gnumeric μπορεί να διαμοιράσει αρχεία με το Microsoft Excel και άλλα προγράμματα που υποστηρίζουν το πρότυπο ODS.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Gnumeric es una aplicación de hojas de cálculo para manipular datos interactivamente.</p>
    <p>Gnumeric aspira a proporcionar cálculos de alta precisión, gráficos expresivos y una selección amplia de herramientas para análisis estadístico. Gnumeric puede compartir archivos con Microsoft Excel y programas que soportan el estándar ODS.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Gnumeric datuak maneiatzeko kalkulu-orrien aplikazio bat da.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Gnumeric est un tableur interactif.</p>
    <p>Gnumeric a pour objectif de fournir des calculs de haute précision, des graphiques clairs et une large panoplie d'outils d'analyse statistique. Gnumeric peut partager des fichiers avec Microsoft Excel et des programmes supportant le format standard ODS.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Gnumeric az adatok interaktív manipulálásához készült táblázatkezelő alkalmazás.</p>
    <p>A Gnumeric célja nagy pontosságú számítások, kifejező grafikonok, továbbá statisztikai elemző eszközök széles választékának biztosítása. A Gnumeric képes megosztani a fájlokat Microsoft Excel és az ODS szabványt támogató programokkal.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Gnumeric adalah aplikasi lembar kerja untuk manipulasi data interaktif.</p>
    <p>Gnumeric bertujuan untuk memberikan perhitungan akurasi tinggi, grafik ekspresif, dan berbagai pilihan alat analisis statistik. Gnumeric dapat berbagi berkas dengan Microsoft Excel dan program yang mendukung standar ODS.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <p>Gnumeric — деректерді интерактивті өңдеуге арналған электрондық кесте қолданбасы.</p>
    <p>Gnumeric жоғары дәлдікті есептеулерді, мәнерлі графиктерді және статистикалық талдау құралдарының кең таңдауын ұсынуға бағытталған. Gnumeric файлдарын Microsoft Excel бағдарламасымен және ODS стандартын қолдайтын бағдарламалармен ортақ пайдалануға болады.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Gnumeric er et regnearkprogram for interaktiv manipulasjon av data.</p>
    <p>Gnumeric sikter mot beregninger med høy nøyaktighet, uttrykksfulle grafer og et bredt utvalg av verktøy for statistisk analyse. Gnumeric kan dele filer med Microsoft Excel og programmer som støtter ODS-standarden.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Gnumeric to arkusz kalkulacyjny do interaktywnego manipulowania danymi.</p>
    <p>Gnumeric dostarcza obliczenia o wysokiej dokładności, wykresy i szeroki wybór narzędzi do analizy statystycznej. Gnumeric może używać plików programu Microsoft Excel i programów obsługujących standard ODS.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Gnumeric é uma aplicação de folha de cálculo para manipulação interativa de dados.</p>
    <p>O Gnumeric destina-se a fornecer computação altamente precisa, gráficos expressivos e uma vasta seleção de ferramentas análise estatística. Pode partilhar ficheiros com o Microsoft Excel e programas que suportem o padrão ODS.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Gnumeric é um aplicativo de planilhas para manipulação interativa de dados.</p>
    <p>O Gnumeric tem como objetivo fazer cálculos de alta precisão, gerar gráficos expressivos, e prover uma grande variedade de ferramentas de análise estatística. O Gnumeric pode compartilhar arquivos com o Microsoft Excel e programas que suportem o padrão ODS.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Program Gnumeric je preglednično pisarniško orodje za interaktivno obdelavo podatkov.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Гнумерик је програм табеларног прорачуна за међудејствену обраду података.</p>
    <p>Гнумерик има за циљ да обезбеди прорачуне велике тачности, обилне графиконе, и велики избор алата статистичке анализе. Гнумерик може да размењује датотеке са Мајкрософт Екселом и програмима који подржавају ОДС стандард.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Gnumerik je program tabelarnog proračuna za međudejstvenu obradu podataka.</p>
    <p>Gnumerik ima za cilj da obezbedi proračune velike tačnosti, obilne grafikone, i veliki izbor alata statističke analize. Gnumerik može da razmenjuje datoteke sa Majkrosoft Ekselom i programima koji podržavaju ODS standard.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Gnumeric är ett kalkylprogram för interaktiv manipulering av data.</p>
    <p>Gnumeric strävar efter att tillhandahålla beräkningar med hög noggrannhet, uttrycksfulla diagram och ett brett urval av statistiska analysverktyg. Gnumeric kan dela filer med Microsoft Excel och program som använder standarden ODS.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Gnumeric — електронна таблиця для інтерактивної обробки даних.</p>
    <p>Gnumeric призначено для виконання високоточних обчислень, створення чудових графіків та використання широкого спектра засобів статистичного аналізу. Gnumeric може працювати із файлами Microsoft Excel та програму, у яких передбачено підтримку стандарту ODS.</p>
  </description>
  <summary>A High-Precision Spreadsheet Program</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Un programa de full de càlcul d'alta precisió</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Tabulkový kalkulátor s vysokou přesností výpočtů</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Et regnearksprogram med høj præcision</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Eine Tabellenkalkulation mit hoher Genauigkeit</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Un programa de hojas de cálculo de alta precisión</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Kalkulu-orrien programa bat, doitasun handikoa</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Un tableur de haute précision</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Egy nagy pontosságú táblázatkezelő program</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Sebuah Program Lembar Kerja Presisi Tinggi</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">Жоғары дәлдікті электрондық кесте бағдарламасы</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Et regnearkprogram med høy nøyaktighet</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Arkusz kalkulacyjny o wysokiej dokładności</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Uma aplicação de folha de cálculo de alta precisão</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Um programa de planilhas de alta precisão</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Програм табеларног прорачуна високе тачности</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Program tabelarnog proračuna visoke tačnosti</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Ett kalkylprogram med hög precision</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Електронна таблиця високої точності</summary>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.gnumeric.org/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnumeric-web/raw/master/screenshots/gnumeric-sample.png</screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <mediatype>application/x-gnumeric</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/vnd.ms-excel</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/excel</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/msexcel</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-excel</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-ms-excel</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-msexcel</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-xls</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/xls</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-dos_ms_excel</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/vnd.openxmlformats-officedocument.spreadsheetml.sheet</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/tab-separated-values</mediatype>
    <mediatype>text/csv</mediatype>
    <mediatype>text/x-csv</mediatype>
    <mediatype>text/spreadsheet</mediatype>
    <mediatype>text/tab-separated-values</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/vnd.lotus-1-2-3</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-123</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/vnd.sun.xml.calc</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/vnd.sun.xml.calc.template</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-applix-spreadsheet</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-mps</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-oleo</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-planperfect</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-quattropro</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-sc</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-sylk</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-dbase</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-dbf</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/x-xbase</mediatype>
    <mediatype>application/vnd.oasis.opendocument.spreadsheet</mediatype>
    <binary>gnumeric</binary>
    <binary>ssconvert</binary>
  </provides>
  <updatecontact>gnumeric-list@gnome.org</updatecontact>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <developer_name>The Gnumeric Team</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">L'equip del Gnumeric</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Tým Gnumeric</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">Gnumericholdet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Das Gnumeric-Team</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">La Gnumeriko-teamo</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">El equipo de Gnumeric </developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">Gnumeric taldea</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">L'équipe Gnumeric</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A Gnumeric csapat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Tim Gnumeric</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="kk">Gnumeric командасы</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb">Gnumeric utviklerene</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Zespół programu Gnumeric</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">A equipa do Gnumeric</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">O time do Gnumeric</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Команда Gnumeric</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Skupina Gnumeric</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Екипа Гнумерика</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr@latin">Ekipa Gnumerika</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">Gnumeric-utvecklarna</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Команда Gnumeric</developer_name>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnumeric/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">http://www.amnestyusa.org/</url>
  <url type="help">https://help.gnome.org/users/gnumeric/stable/gnumeric.html</url>
  <releases>
    <release date="2021-06-10" version="1.12.52" />
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>