<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>gtranslator</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.Gtranslator.desktop</launchable>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">org.gnome.Gtranslator.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" width="128" type="cached">org.gnome.Gtranslator.png</icon>
  <id>org.gnome.Gtranslator</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+ AND GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="vi">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="uk">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="tr">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="th">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="te">జిట్రాన్స్‍లేటర్</name>
  <name lang="sv">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Gnomov prevodilac</name>
  <name lang="sr">Гномов преводилац</name>
  <name lang="sl">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="sk">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="ru">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="ro">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="pt">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="pl">gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="nn">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="nl">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="nds">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="nb">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="lv">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="lt">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="ko">지트랜스레이터</name>
  <name lang="ja">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="it">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="id">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="hu">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="hr">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="he">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="gl">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="fur">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="fr">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="fi">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="fa">جی‌ترنسلیتور</name>
  <name lang="eu">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="et">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="es">Editor de traducciones</name>
  <name lang="eo">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="el">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="de">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="da">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="cs">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="ca">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="bs">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="be">Gtranslator</name>
  <name lang="ar">مترجم‌ج</name>
  <summary>Translate and localize applications and libraries</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">進行應用程式與函式庫的翻譯與本地化</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_HK">進行應用程式與函式庫的翻譯與本地化</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">对应用程序和库进行翻译和本地化</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Dịch và bản địa hóa các ứng dụng và thư viện</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Переклад та локалізація програм та бібліотек</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Uygulamaları ve kütüphaneleri çevir ve yerelleştir</summary>
  <summary lang="th">แปลและปรับโปรแกรมและไลบรารีให้เหมาะกับผู้ใช้ในท้องถิ่น</summary>
  <summary lang="te">అనువర్తనాలను మరియు లైబ్రరీలను అనువదించు, స్థానీకరించు</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Översätt och lokalanpassa program och bibliotek</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Prevodite i lokalizujte programe i biblioteke</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Преводите и локализујте програме и библиотеке</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Prevajanje in jezikovno prilagajanje vmesnikov programov in knjižnic</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Prekladá a lokalizuje aplikácie a knižnice</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Перевод и локализация файлов и приложений</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Tradu și localizează aplicații și biblioteci</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Traduza e localize aplicativos e bibliotecas</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Traduzir e localizar aplicações e bibliotecas</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Tłumaczenie i lokalizowanie programów oraz bibliotek</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Set om og tilpassar program og bibliotek</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Vertaal en lokaliseer toepassingen en bibliotheken</summary>
  <summary lang="nds">Översett un lokaliser Programme un Bökerien</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Oversett og lokaliser programmer og biblioteker</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Tulko un lokalizē lietotnes un bibliotēkas</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Verskite ir lokalizuokite programas ir bibliotekas</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">프로그램과 라이브러리를 변역하고 지역화합니다</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">アプリケーションやライブラリのメッセージを翻訳します</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Traduce e localizza applicazioni e librerie</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Terjemahkan dan lokalkan aplikasi dan pustaka</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Programkönyvtárak és programok fordítása</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Prevedite i lokalizirajte aplikacije i biblioteke</summary>
  <summary lang="he">תרגום והתאמה מקומית של יישומים וספריות</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Traduza e localice aplicativos e bibliotecas</summary>
  <summary lang="ga">Aistrigh agus logánaigh feidhmchláir agus leabharlanna</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Tradûs e localize aplicazions e librariis</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Traduit et localise des programmes et des bibliothèques</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Käännä ja kotoista ohjelmia sekä kirjastoja</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">ترجمه و بومی‌سازی برنامه‌ها و کتابخانه‌ها</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Itzuli eta lokalizatu aplikazio eta liburutegiak</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Rakenduste ning teekide tõlkimine ja lokaliseerimine</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Traduzca y localice aplicaciones y bibliotecas</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Traduki kaj allokigi aplikaĵojn kaj bibliotekojn</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Translate and localise applications and libraries</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Μεταφράστε και τοπικοποιήστε εφαρμογές και βιβλιοθήκες</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Anwendungen und Bibliotheken übersetzen und an lokale Gegebenheiten anpassen</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Oversæt og sprogtilpas programmer og biblioteker</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Překládejte a lokalizujte aplikace a knihovny</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Traduïu i localitzeu aplicacions i biblioteques</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Traduïu i localitzeu aplicacions i biblioteques</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Prevedi i lociraj prijave i knjige</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Пераклад i лакалiзацыя праграм і бібліятэк</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">ترجم التطبيقات والمكتبات</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Gtranslator is an enhanced gettext po file editor for the GNOME desktop
      environment.
      It handles all forms of gettext po files and includes very useful features
      like find/replace, translation memory, different translator profiles,
      messages table (for having an overview of the translations/messages in the
      po file), easy navigation and editing of translation messages and comments
      of the translation where accurate.
    </p>
    <p>
      Gtranslator includes also a plugin system with many interesting plugins like alternate language, insert tags, integration with subversion and a source code viewer.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Gtranslator je napredniji "gettext po" uređivač datoteke za GNOME desktop okruženje. Ona obrađuje sve oblike "gettext po" datoteka i uključuje vrlo korisne funkcije kao što su pronađi / zamijeni, prevođenje memorije, različite profile prevoditelja, poruke stola (da bi postojao pregled prevodi / poruke u po datoteci), jednostavnu navigaciju i uređivanje prevođenih poruka i komentara prijevoda gdje je precizno.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Gtranslator és un editor de fitxers PO del gettext millorat per a l'entorn d'escriptori GNOME. Gestiona totes les formes de fitxers po de gettext i inclou característiques molt útils com cerca/reemplaça, memòria de traducció, diferents perfils de traductors, taula de missatges (per a tenir una visió general de les traduccions/missatges al fitxer po), una fàcil navegació i edició de missatges de traducció i comentaris de la traducció.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator inclou també un sistema de connectors amb molts connectors interessants com ara idioma alternatiu, etiquetes d'inserció, integració amb Subversion i un visor de codi font.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Gtranslator je vylepšený editor souborů getttext po pro pracovní prostředí GNOME. Umí zacházet se všemy formami souborů gettext po a jeho součástí jsou velmi užiteční funkce jako hledat/nahradit, paměť překladů, různé profily překladů, tabulka zpráv (poskytující přehled o překladech/zprávách v souboru po), snadný pohyb po zprávách a úprava jejich překladu a komentářů.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator také obsahuje systém zásuvných modulů s řadou zajímavých zásuvných modulů, jako je alternativní jazyk, vkládání značek, integrace se správou verzí a zobrazení zdrojového kódu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Gtranslator er et forbedret program til GNOMEs skrivebordsmiljø til redigering af gettext-po-filer. Det håndterer alle former for gettext-po-filer og indeholder mange nyttige funktioner såsom søg/erstat, oversættelseshukommelse, forskellige oversætterprofiler, beskedtabeller (giver overblik over oversættelser/beskeder i po-filen) samt nem navigering i og redigering af oversættelsesbeskeder og -kommentarer.</p>
    <p>Det er også muligt at udvide Gtranslator med udvidelsesmoduler. Der er mange interessante udvidelsesmoduler såsom alternativt sprog, tilføj mærker, integration med subversion og en fremviser til kildekoden.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Gtranslator ist ein erweitertes Bearbeitungsprogramm für Gettext-po-Dateien für die GNOME Arbeitsumgebung. Es kann sämtliche Arten von Gettext-po-Dateien bearbeiten und enthält sehr nützliche Funktionen wie Suchen/Ersetzen, einen Übersetzungsspeicher, unterschiedliche Übersetzungsprofile, eine Übersetzungsliste (für eine Übersicht der Übersetzungen/Zeichenketten in der po-Datei), einfache Navigation und Bearbeitung von übersetzten Textstellen und Kommentieren von Übersetzungen.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator bietet zudem ein Plugin-System mit vielen interessanten Erweiterungen wie alternative Sprachen, Einfügen von XML-Elementen, Subversion-Integration und einer Quelltextansicht.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το Gtranslator είναι ένας βελτιωμένος επεξεργαστής αρχείου po gettext για το περιβάλλον επιφάνειας εργασίας GNOME. Διαχειρίζεται όλες τις μορφές αρχείων po gettext και περιλαμβάνει πολύ χρήσιμα χαρακτηριστικά όπως εύρεση/αντικατάσταση, μεταφραστική μνήμη, διαφορετικά προφιλ μεταφραστή, πίνακα μηνυμάτων (για να έχετε μια επισκόπηση των μεταφράσεων/μηνυμάτων στο αρχείο po), εύκολη περιήγηση και επεξεργασία των μηνυμάτων μετάφρασης και σχόλια της μετάφρασης.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Gtranslator is an enhanced gettext po file editor for the GNOME desktop environment. It handles all forms of gettext po files and includes very useful features like find/replace, translation memory, different translator profiles, messages table (for having an overview of the translations/messages in the po file), easy navigation and editing of translation messages and comments of the translation where accurate.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator includes also a plugin system with many interesting plugins like alternate language, insert tags, integration with subversion and a source code viewer.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p>Gtranslator estas gettext po-dosier-redaktilo por la GNOME labortablo. Ĝi traktas ĉiajn gettext po-dosierojn kaj inkluzivas ege utilajn funkciojn kiel serĉi/anstataŭigi, tradukmemoron, diversajn tradukprofilojn, mesaĝtabulon (por havi superrigardon de la tradukoj/mesaĝoj en la po-dosiero), facila navigadon kaj redaktadon de la tradukmesaĝoj kaj komentojn de la traduko se necesa.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator ankaŭ inkluzivas kromprogramsistemon kun multe da interesaj kromprogramoj kiel alterna lingvo, enmetaj etikedoj, integrigo kun subversion kaj fontkodvidilo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>El Editor de traducciones es un editor de archivos PO de gettext mejorado para el entorno de escritorio GNOME. Maneja todos los tipos de archivos PO e incluye características muy útiles, tales como buscar y reemplazar, memoria de traducción, diferentes perfiles de traductor, tabla de mensajes (para tener una visión general de las cadenas del archivo PO), navegación sencilla,edición y traducción de mensajes y comentarios precisos sobre la traducción.</p>
    <p>El Editor de traducciones también incluye un sistema de complementos que incluyen idioma alternativo, insertar etiquetas, integración con subversion y un visor de código fuente.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Gtranslator gettext-eko PO fitxategien hobetutako editorea da GNOME mahaigainerako. Gettext-eko PO fitxategien forma guztiak kudeatzen ditu, eta bilatu/ordeztu, itzulpen-memoriak, itzultzaileen profil desberdinak, mezuen taula, itzulpenen mezuak editatzeko eta arakatzeko bezalako eginbide erabilgarriak ditu.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator-ek pluginen sistema bat ere badauka: bestelako hizkuntza, etiketak txertatzea, subversion-ekin bateragarritasuna eta iturburuaren kodearen ikustailea bezalako plugin interesgarriekin.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fa">
    <p>جی‌ترنسلیتور یک ویرایشگر پروندهٔ gettext po برای محیط دسکتاپ گنوم است. این برنامه همهٔ اَشکال پرونده‌های gettext po را مدیریت می‌کند و شامل ویژگی‌های بسیار مفیدی مانند یافتن/جای‌گزینی، حافظهٔ ترجمه، نمایه‌های مختلف مترجم، جدول پیام‌ها (برای مرور کلی ترجمه‌ها/پیام‌ها در پروندهٔ po)، ناوبری آسان و ویرایش پیام‌های ترجمه است و دیدگاه‌های ترجمه در آنجا دقیق است.</p>
    <p>جی‌ترنسلیتور همچنین شامل یک سامانهٔ افزایه با افزایه‌های جالب مانند زبان متناوب، درج برچسب‌ها، ادغام با واژگونی و نمایشگر کدمنبع است.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Gtranslator on gettext-po-tiedostojen muokkain Gnome-työpöydälle. Se hallitsee kaikenlaisia gettextin mukaisia po-tiedostoja ja sisältää hyödyllisiä ominaisuuksia, kuten "etsi ja korvaa"-toiminnon, käännösmuistin, useita eri käännösprofiileja, viestitaulun, kommenttien esittämisen ja ennen kaikkea helpon tavan muokata käännettäviä viestejä.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator sisältää myös liitännäisjärjestelmän. Liitännäisistä mainittakoon vaihtoehtoiskielten liitännäinen, merkintöjen lisäys, integraatio Subversion-versionhallintajärjestelmään kanssa sekä lähdekoodikatselin.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Gtranslator est un éditeur avancé de fichier gettext pour l’environnement GNOME. Il gère tous les fichiers po de gettext et fournit d’intéressantes fonctions comme Chercher/Remplacer, une Mémoire de traduction, différents profils de traduction, un tableau des messages (pour avoir une vue des traductions/messages du fichier .po), une navigation et une édition faciles et précises des messages et des commentaires.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator fournit aussi un système de greffons intéressants, comme « Autre langue », « Insérer les balises », « Intégration avec Subversion » et « Affichage du code source ».</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Gtranslator al è un editôr di file po di gettext avanzât pal ambient scritori GNOME. Al gjestìs dutis lis formis di file po gettext e al inclût funzionalitâts utilis come cjate/sostituìs, memorie di traduzion, profîi di tradutôr diferents, tabele dai messaçs (par vê une panoramiche des traduzions/messaçs intal file po), navigazion facilitade, modifiche dai messaçs di traduzion e coments de traduzion dulà che si è precîs.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator al inclût ancje un sisteme di plugin cun tancj interessants plugin come lenghe alternative, inserî etichetis, integrazion cun subversion e un visualizadôr di codiç sorzint.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Gtranslator é un editor de ficheiros po gettext mellorado para o ambiente de escritorio GNOME. Xestiona todos os formatos de ficheiros po gettext e inclúe características moi útiles como buscar/substituír, memorias de tradución, xestión de varios perfiles de tradutor, táboa de mensaxes (para ter unha vista previa das traducións/mensaxes nun ficheiro po), navegación e edición doada dos mensaxes de tradución e dos comentarios das traducións.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator inclúe tamén un sistema de engadidos con varios engadidos interesantes como o de idioma alternativo, insertar etiquetas, integración con subversion e un visor de código fonte.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Gtranslator je poboljšani gettext uređivač po datoteka za GNOME radno okruženje. Obrađuje sve formate gettext po datoteka i uključuje vrlo korisne značajke poput pretrage/zamjene, prevoditeljske memorije, različitih profila prevoditelja, tablice poruka (za pregled prijevoda/poruka u po datoteci) i jednostavnu navigaciju i uređivanje poruka i komentara prijevoda.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator još uključuje i sustav priključaka s mnoštvom zanimljivih priključaka poput zamjenskog jezika, umetanje oznaka, integracija sa subverzijom i preglednik izvornog kôda.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Gtranslator egy továbbfejlesztett gettext po fájl szerkesztő a GNOME asztali környezethez. A gettext po fájlok összes formáját kezeli és nagyon hasznos szolgáltatásokat tartalmaz, úgymint a keresés és csere, fordítómemória, különböző fordító profilok, üzenettáblák (a fordítások és üzenetek áttekintéséhez a po fájlban), egyszerű navigáció és a fordítás fordítási üzeneteinek és megjegyzéseinek szerkesztése, ahol pontos.</p>
    <p>A Gtranslator tartalmaz továbbá egy bővítményrendszert számos érdekes bővítménnyel, úgymint alternatív nyelv, címkék beszúrása, integráció a subversion verziókezelővel és forráskód megjelenítő.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Gtranslator adalah penyunting berkas po gettext  yang ditingkatkan bagi lingkungan desktop GNOME. Ini menangani semua bentuk berkas po gettext dan memiliki fitur yang sangat berguna seperti cari/ganti, memori terjemahan, profil penerjemah yang berbeda, tabel pesan (untuk memiliki ringkasan dari terjemahan/pesan dalam berkas po), navigasi yang mudah, dan penyuntingan pesan terjemahan serta komentar terjemahan yang akurat.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator juga memiliki sistem plugin dengan banyak plugin menarik seperti bahasa alternatif, sisip tag, integrasi dengan subversion, dan penilik kode sumber.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Gtranslator è un editor avanzato di file gettext PO per l'ambiente desktop GNOME. Gestisce tutte le forme di file gettext PO e include funzioni molto utili come trova/sostituisci, memoria di traduzione, diversi profili di traduttore, tabella dei messaggi (per avere una panoramica delle traduzioni/messaggi nel file PO), facile navigazione e modifica dei messaggi di traduzione e commenti della traduzione dove richiesti.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator include anche un sistema di plugin che permettono di usare una lingua alternativa, inserire etichette, integrarsi con subversion e visualizzare il codice sorgente.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>Gtranslator は GNOME デスクトップ環境用の高機能な gettext PO ファイルエディターです。すべての gettext PO ファイル形式に対応し、検索/置換、翻訳メモリ、複数の翻訳者プロファイル、PO ファイル内の翻訳/メッセージの概要を表示するメッセージ表、簡易ナビゲーション、翻訳メッセージとコメントの編集といった非常に便利な機能を備えています。</p>
    <p>Gtranslator はプラグインシステムも備えており、Alternate Language (言語の切り替え)、Insert Tags (タグの挿入)、Subversion の統合、ソースコードビューアーなどのプラグインが利用できます。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>지트랜스레이터는 그놈 데스크톱 환경용으로 개선한 gettext po 파일 편집기입니다. 모든 형태의 gettext po 파일을 다루며, 찾기/바꾸기, 번역 기억장소, 제각각의 번역자 프로파일, 메시지 표(po 파일에서 번역/메시지를 미리보는 용도), 쉬운 탐색, 번역문 편집, 정확성을 부여하기 위한 번역 주석 달기 같은 매우 쓸만한 기능도 있습니다.</p>
    <p>지트랜스레이터에는 대체언어, 태그 삽입, 서브버전 및 소스코드 보기 기능 통합을 지원하는 등 흥미로운 여러 플러그인을 갖춘 플러그인 체계를 지니고 있습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Gtranslator yra galingas gettext po failų redaktorius GNOME darbalaukio aplinkai. Jis apdoroja visų tipų gettext po failus ir turi naudingų funkcijų, tokių kaip paieška ir pakeitimas, vertimų atmintis, skirtingi vertėjo profiliai, eilučių lentelė (eilučių ir jų vertimų apžvalgai po faile), lengvas judėjimas tarp eilučių ir jų redagavimas bei vertimų komentarai, kur tikslu.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator taip pat turi įskiepių sistemą su daug įdomių įskiepių, tokių kaip papildoma kalba, žymų įterpimas, integracija su subversion bei pradinio kodo žiūryklė.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>Gtranslator ir po datņu redaktors GNOME darbvirsmas videi. Tas strādā ar visa veida gettext po datnēm un iekļauj noderīgas iespējas, piemēram, meklēšanu/aizvietošanu, tulkošanas atmiņu, dažādus tulkošanas profilus, ziņojumu tabulas (pārskats pār tulkojumiem/ziņojumiem po datnē), vieglu tulkošanas ziņojumu rediģēšanu un navigāciju, kā arī tulkojumu komentārus.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator iekļauj arī spraudņu sistēmu, kur ir daudzi interesanti spraudņi, piemēram, papildu valoda, birku ievietošana, integrācija ar subversion un pirmkoda skatītājs.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Gtranslator is een verbeterde gettext-PO-bestandsbewerker voor Gnome. Hij verwerkt alle soorten gettext-PO-bestanden, en bevat veel nuttige functies, zoals zoeken/vervangen, vertaalgeheugen, verschillende vertaalprofielen, een berichtentabel (voor een overzicht van de vertalingen/berichten in het PO-bestand), eenvoudige navigatie en bewerken van vertalingsberichten en opmerkingen.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator bevat ook een plug-insysteem met veel interessante plug-ins, zoals verschillende talen, invoegen van tags, integratie met subversion en een broncodeviewer.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>gtranslator to ulepszony edytor plików PO biblioteki gettext dla środowiska GNOME. Obsługuje wszystkie rodzaje plików PO biblioteki gettext i zawiera bardzo przydatne funkcje, takie jak znajdź/zamień, pamięć tłumaczeń, różne profile tłumaczy, tablica komunikatów (dostarczającą przegląd tłumaczeń/komunikatów w pliku PO), łatwa nawigacja oraz modyfikowanie komunikatów tłumaczeń i komentarzy.</p>
    <p>gtranslator zawiera także system wtyczek z wieloma interesującymi wtyczkami, takimi jak alternatywny język, wstawianie znaczników, integracja z systemem Subversion i przeglądarka kodu źródłowego.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Gtranslator é um editor de ficheiros gettext po melhorado para o ambiente GNOME. Gere todas as formas de ficheiros gettext po e inclui muitas funcionalidades úteis, tais como Localizar e substituir, memória de tradução, diferentes perfis de tradução, tabela de mensagens (para uma visão geral das traduções/mensagens no ficheiro po), navegação fácil e edição das mensagens e comentários de tradução, onde necessário.</p>
    <p>O Gtranslator também inclui várias extensões tais como idioma alternativo, inserção de etiquetas, tradução aberta, integração com subversion e um visualizador de código fonte.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>O Gtranslator é um editor avançado de arquivos gettext po para o ambiente de área de trabalho GNOME. Ele manipula todas as formas de arquivos gettext po e inclui funcionalidades muito úteis como localizar/substituir, memória de tradução, diferentes perfis de tradução, tabela de mensagens (para prover uma visão geral sobre as traduções/mensagens no arquivo po), navegação simplificada e a edição de mensagens e comentários de tradução tornou-se mais precisa.</p>
    <p>O Gtranslator também inclui um sistema de plug-in com plug-ins muito interessantes como idioma alternativo, inserir marcas, integração com subversion e um visualizador de código fonte.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Gtranslator este un editor de fișiere po îmbunătățit, bazat pe gettext, pentru mediul desktop GNOME. Administrează toate formele de fișiere po și include funcționalități folositoare precum căutare/înlocuire, memorie de traduceri, profile diferite de traducător, tabel de mesaje (pentru a avea o vedere de ansamblu a traducerilor/mesajelor din fișierul po), navigare facilă și editarea mesajelor traducerii și comentariilor unde este nevoie.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator include de asemenea un sistem de module cu multe module interesante cum ar fi limbi alternative, introducerea de etichete, integrarea cu subversion și un vizualizator de cod sursă.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Gtranslator — это улучшенный редактор po-файлов для среды рабочего стола GNOME. Он обрабатывает все формы gettext и включает в себя некоторые полезные функции: поиск/замена, память переводов, профили для перевода, таблица сообщений (для получения обзора переводов/сообщений в po-файле), простая навигация, редактирование сообщений и комментирование переводов.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator также включает в себя систему модулей: альтернативный язык, вставка тэгов, вставка тэгов, интеграция с subversion, просмотрщик исходного кода.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Gtranslator je pokročilý editor súborov typu gettext s príponou po pre prostredie GNOME. Dokáže spracovať všetky formy súborov typu gettext s príponou po a disponuje veľmi užitočnými funkciami ako je nájdenie/nahradenie, pamäť prekladov, odlišné profily pre každého prekladateľa, tabuľka správ (pre lepší prehľad nad prekladmi/správami v súbore po), jednoduchá orientácia a upravovanie správ prekladu a komentárov k prekladu.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator obsahuje tiež systém zásuvných modulov s mnohými zaujímavými zásuvnými modulmi ako je iný jazyk, vkladanie značiek, integrácia do systému subversion a prehliadač zdrojového kódu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Program Gtranslator je napredni urejevalnik datotek gettext *.po za namizje GNOME. Podpira se vrste datotek gettext in vključuje zelo uporabne zmožnosti, kot so najdi in zamenjaj, pomnilnik prevodov, različne profile prevajalcev, razpredelnico nizov (za pregled nad prevodi v datoteki *.po), enostavno krmarjenje in urejanje opomb k prevodu.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator vključuje tudi sistem vstavkov s številnimi zanimivimi dodatki, kot so nadomestni jezik, vstavljanje značk, povezovanje s sistemom za sledenje različic in pregledovalnikom izvorne kode.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Гномов преводилац је побољшани уређивач геттекстових по датотека за Гномово радно окружење. Рукује свим облицима геттекстових по датотека и укључује врло корисне функције као што су нађи/замени, преводилачка меморија, различити профили преводиоца, табела порука (зарад прегледа превода/порука у по датотеци), лако кретање и уређивање порука превода и напомена о преводу.</p>
    <p>Гномов преводилац такође укључује систем прикључака са многим занимљивим прикључцима као што је изборни језик, ознаке уметања, обједињавање са прегледачем субверзије и изворног кода.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Gnomov prevodilac je poboljšani uređivač gettekstovih po datoteka za Gnomovo radno okruženje. Rukuje svim oblicima gettekstovih po datoteka i uključuje vrlo korisne funkcije kao što su nađi/zameni, prevodilačka memorija, različiti profili prevodioca, tabela poruka (zarad pregleda prevoda/poruka u po datoteci), lako kretanje i uređivanje poruka prevoda i napomena o prevodu.</p>
    <p>Gnomov prevodilac takođe uključuje sistem priključaka sa mnogim zanimljivim priključcima kao što je izborni jezik, oznake umetanja, objedinjavanje sa pregledačem subverzije i izvornog koda.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Gtranslator är en förbättrad gettext po-filredigerare för skrivbordsmiljön GNOME. Den hanterar alla former av gettext po-filer och innehåller användbara funktioner som sök / ersätt, översättningsminne, olika översättarprofiler, meddelandetabell (för överblick över översättningar / meddelanden i po-filen), enkel navigering och redigering av översättningsmeddelanden och kommentarer i översättningen.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator innehåller också ett instickssystem med många intressanta insticksmoduler, som alternativa språk, taggning, integration med subversion och källkodsläsare.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="th">
    <p>Gtranslator เป็นเครื่องมือแก้ไขแฟ้ม po ของ gettext แบบพิเศษสำหรับสภาพแวดล้อมเดสก์ท็อป GNOME สามารถจัดการกับแฟ้ม po ของ gettext ได้ทุกรูปแบบ และมีความสามารถที่เป็นประโยชน์ เช่น การหา/แทนที่, คลังคำแปล, โพรไฟล์นักแปลหลายคน, ตารางข้อความ (เพื่อให้เห็นภาพรวมของการแปล/ข้อความในแฟ้ม po), การเลื่อนและแก้ไขที่ง่ายดายสำหรับข้อความแปลและหมายเหตุของการแปลในจุดที่ถูกต้อง</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Gtranslator, GNOME masaüstü ortamı için gelişmiş gettext po dosyası düzenleyicisidir. Her tür gettext po dosyası üzerinde işlem yapabilir ve bul/değiştir, çeviri belleği, başka çevirmen profilleri, ileti tablosu, çeviri iletilerinde kolay gezinme ve bunları kolay düzenleme, ayrıca uygun olan yerlerde çeviri notları gibi çok kullanışlı özellikler içerir.</p>
    <p>Gtranslatorʼda ayrıca alternatif dil, etiket ekleme, subversion tümleşimi ve kaynak kod görüntüleyicisi gibi ilgi çekici birçok eklenti içeren eklenti sistemi de bulunuyor.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Gtranslator — редактор файлів PO gettext із додатковими можливостями. Програму призначено для стільничного середовища GNOME. Вона може працювати із усіма формами файлів PO, до неї включено дуже корисні інструменти, зокрема пошук із заміною, пам'ять перекладів, різні профілі перекладачів, таблицю повідомлень (для огляду перекладів і повідомлень у файлі PO), просту навігацію і редагування повідомлень перекладу та можливість коментування перекладів, де це потрібно.</p>
    <p>Крім того, у Gtranslator передбачено систему додатків, до якої включено багато цікавих додатків, зокрема додаток альтернативної мови перекладу, додаток вставлення теґів, додаток інтеграції із subversion та додаток перегляду початкового коду програм.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="vi">
    <p>Gtranslator là ứng dụng dịch tập tin po của gettext cao cấp dành cho môi trường GNOME. Nó xử lý mọi kiểu tập tin po và bao gồm các tính năng hữu dụng như là tìm kiếm và thay thế, dịch từ bộ nhớ có sẵn, dùng nhiều hồ sơ người dịch, bảng chuỗi (để xem chuỗi gốc và bản dịch của tập tin po), dễ dàng di chuyển và sửa đổi chuỗi bản dịch và lời ghi chú của bản dịch.</p>
    <p>Gtranslator cũng bao gồm một hệ thống phần bổ sung với nhiều tính năng thú vị như là ngôn ngữ thay thế, thêm thẻ, tích hợp với subversion và bộ xem mã nguồn.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>Gtranslator 是一个为 GNOME 桌面环境开发的增强型 gettext po 文件编辑器。它能处理所有形式的 gettext po 文件，并且包含如查找/替换，翻译记忆，不同翻译者配置文件，消息表格（为 po 文件中的翻译/消息提供一个概览），对翻译消息和注释易于使用的精确导览和编辑等很有用的特性。</p>
    <p>Gtranslator 也包含一个集合如替换语言、插入标签、open tran、与 subversion 和源代码查看器集成等许多有趣插件的插件系统。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gtranslator/-/raw/master/doc/screenshots/screenshot1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="42.0" date="2022-04-11">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an stable release in the 42.0 development series, with the
          following improvements:
          <ul>
            <li>Prepare code for Gtk4 migration</li>
            <li>Shorcut ctrl-k for clearing</li>
            <li>Some memory fixes</li>
            <li>Fix DL downloaded file names</li>
          </ul>
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="41.0" date="2021-09-18">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an stable release in the 41.0 development series, with the
          following improvements:
          <ul>
            <li>Allow adding comments when uploading to l10n.gnome.org</li>
          </ul>
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="40.0" date="2021-03-23">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an stable release in the 40.0 development series, with the
          following improvements:
          <ul>
            <li>Add new integration with l10n.gnome.org so now it's possible to reserve a
                file and upload using the desktop app</li>
            <li>Add libhandy widgets to improve the user interface for different sizes</li>
          </ul>
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-09-12" version="3.38.0">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an stable release in the 3.38 development series, with the
          following improvements:
          <ul>
            <li>Add save file dialog when open from DL</li>
            <li>Enable wrap-around by default in search bar</li>
            <li>search-bar: error style when not found</li>
            <li>Use base language to get the plural form on assistant</li>
            <li>Download DL files to Download folder</li>
            <li>Use GtkFileChooserNative for open and save dialogs</li>
            <li>Editor font configurable on preferences</li>
          </ul>
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-03-14" version="3.36.0">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an stable release in the 3.36 development series, with the
          following improvements:
          <ul>
            <li>Translations updates</li>
            <li>New search/replace popover</li>
            <li>Open from DL button</li>
            <li>Help doc improvements</li>
            <li>Fix profile edit and remove</li>
          </ul>
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.34.0" date="2019-09-10">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an stable release in the 3.34 development series.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.33.90" date="2019-08-05">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.33 development series,
          with the following improvements:
          <ul>
            <li>https://l10n.gnome.org/ initial integration</li>
            <li>Fixes in the search dialog</li>
          </ul>
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.32.0" date="2019-03-11">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an stable release in the 3.32 development series.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.31.90" date="2019-02-03">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.31 development series,
          with the following improvements:
          <ul>
            <li>XML language syntax for the source view</li>
            <li>Fix msg status management</li>
            <li>Use theme_fg_color for translated texts</li>
            <li>Better prj id version default header</li>
            <li>Header with default values when doesn't exists</li>
            <li>codeview: Recover codeview plugin</li>
            <li>Show context in the original message bar</li>
            <li>List of languages in a config file instead iso-codes</li>
            <li>Find &amp; replace and copy text to shortcuts window</li>
            <li>Ctrl+space to copy original text into translated</li>
            <li>Native File Chooser for the translation memory</li>
          </ul>
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-11-11" version="3.30.1" />
  </releases>
  <developer_name>Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="vi">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fur">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fa">دانیل گارسیا مورنو</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">Daniel García MORENO</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Daniel García Moreno</developer_name>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Gtranslator</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gtranslator/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.gnome.org/donate/</url>
  <update_contact>danigm@gnome.org</update_contact>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>AppMenu</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>UserDocs</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <provides>
    <id>gtranslator</id>
  </provides>
  <translation type="gettext">gtranslator</translation>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0" />
</component>