<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <description>
    <p>Join, create and manage Hamachi networks in a breeze.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Searchable, sortable and collapsible network list</li>
      <li>Sidebar for easy access to details and actions</li>
      <li>Desktop notifications</li>
      <li>Fully customizable commands</li>
      <li>Backup and restore your Hamachi configuration folder</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Please note: Requires installation of Hamachi on the system in order to use.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ast">
    <p>Xúnite, crea y xestiona redes Hamachi con cenciellez</p>
    <p>Carauterístiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Llista de redes espandible, que se pue ordenar y onde se pue guetar</li>
      <li>Barra llateral p'acceder fácilmente a los detalles y les aiciones</li>
      <li>Avisos d'escritoriu</li>
      <li>Comandos personalizables dafechu</li>
      <li>Fai copies de seguranza y restaura la carpeta de configuración de Hamachi</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Присъединявайте се, създавайте и управлявайте Hamachi мрежи с лекота.</p>
    <p>Характеристики:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Търсим, подреждащ се и сгъваем списък с мрежи</li>
      <li>Страничен панел за лесен достъп до детайли и действия</li>
      <li>Известия на работния плот</li>
      <li>Напълно персонализиращи се команди</li>
      <li>Бекъп и възстановяване на вашата Hamachi директория</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Cree, gestione y únase a redes Hamachi al instante.</p>
    <p>Prestaciones:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Organice, contraiga y filtre la lista de redes</li>
      <li>Barra lateral para un fácil acceso a los detalles y las acciones</li>
      <li>Notificaciones de escritorio</li>
      <li>Órdenes completamente personalizables</li>
      <li>Respalde y restaure la carpeta de configuración de Hamachi</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Rejoignez, créez et gérez les réseaux Hamachi en un rien de temps.</p>
    <p>Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>liste de réseau consultable et triable ;</li>
      <li>barre latérale pour un accès facile aux détails et aux actions ;</li>
      <li>notifications de bureau ;</li>
      <li>commandes entièrement personnalisables ;</li>
      <li>sauvegarde et restauration de votre dossier de configuration Hamachi.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Bergabung, membuat dan mengelola jaringan Hamachi dengan mudah.</p>
    <p>Fitur:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Senarai Jaringan yang dapat ditelusuri, diurutkan dan diciutkan</li>
      <li>Bilah samping untuk memudahkan akses ke detail dan tindakan</li>
      <li>Notifikasi destop</li>
      <li>Perintah yang sepenuhnya dapat disesuaikan</li>
      <li>Cadangkan dan simpang ulang pelipat konfigurasi Hamachi anda</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Aggiungi, crea e gestisci le reti Hamachi in un batter d'occhio.</p>
    <p>Funzionalità:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Cerca, ordina e compatta la lista delle reti</li>
      <li>Barra laterale per l'accesso a dettagli e azioni</li>
      <li>Notifiche desktop</li>
      <li>Comandi totalmente personalizzabili</li>
      <li>Salva e ripristina la tua cartella della configurazione di Hamachi</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>簡単に Hamachi ネットワークに参加したり、作成したり、管理したりしましょう。</p>
    <p>機能:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>検索・並べ替え・折りたたみ可能なネットワークリスト</li>
      <li>詳細やアクションに簡単にアクセスできるサイドバー</li>
      <li>デスクトップ通知</li>
      <li>十分にカスタマイズ可能なコマンド</li>
      <li>Hamachi 設定フォルダーをバックアップし復元できます</li>
    </ul>
    <p>ご注意ください: このアプリを使用するには、システムに Hamachi をインストールする必要があります。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Lengvai prisijunkite, kurkite ir tvarkykite Hamachi tinklus.</p>
    <p>Ypatybės:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Randamas, rikiuojamas ir suskleidžiamas tinklų sąrašas</li>
      <li>Šoninė juosta, skirta lengvai prieigai prie išsamesnės informacijos ir veiksmų</li>
      <li>Darbalaukio pranešimai</li>
      <li>Pilnai tinkinamos komandos</li>
      <li>Galimybė daryti savo Hamachi konfigūracijos aplanko atsarginę kopiją ir ją atkurti</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Maak, treed toe en beheer Hamachi netwerken in een handomdraai.</p>
    <p>Eigenschappen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Doorzoekbare, sorteerbare en inklapbare netwerklijst</li>
      <li>Zijbalk voor snelle toegang tot info and acties</li>
      <li>Bureaubladnotificaties</li>
      <li>Volledig aanpasbare opdrachten</li>
      <li>Backup en herstel uw Hamachi configuratiemap</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Let op: Vereist installatie van Hamachi op het systeem om volledig te kunnen gebruiken.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Łatwe dołączanie, tworzenie i zarządzanie sieciami Hamachi.</p>
    <p>Funkcje:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Lista sieci, którą można przeszukiwać, porządkować i zwijać</li>
      <li>Panel boczny z łatwym dostępem do informacji i działań</li>
      <li>Powiadomienia na pulpicie</li>
      <li>W pełni konfigurowalne polecenia</li>
      <li>Tworzenie kopii zapasowej i przywracanie katalogu z konfiguracją Hamachi</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Proszę zauważyć: do użycia wymagana jest instalacja programu Hamachi na komputerze.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Junte-se, crie e administre redes Hamachi facilmente.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Lista de redes com pesquisa, ordenação e agrupamento</li>
      <li>Barra lateral para um acesso fácil aos detalhes e ações</li>
      <li>Notificações no ambiente de trabalho</li>
      <li>Comandos completamente personalizáveis</li>
      <li>Faça uma cópia de segurança para restaurar a sua pasta de configuração do Hamachi</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Nota: É necessária a instalação do Hamachi no sistema para ser usado.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Acesse, crie e gerencie suas redes Hamachi com facilidade</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Lista de redes com busca, ordenação e agrupamento</li>
      <li>Barra lateral para acesso fácil aos detalhes e ações</li>
      <li>Notificações da área de trabalho</li>
      <li>Comandos totalmente customizáveis</li>
      <li>Faça backup e restaure sua pasta de configuração do Hamachi</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Присоединяйтесь, создавайте и управляйте сетями Hamachi на одном дыхании.</p>
    <p>Возможности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Список сетей с возможностью поиска, сортировки и складывания</li>
      <li>Боковая панель для быстрого доступа к деталям и действиям</li>
      <li>Уведомления на рабочем столе</li>
      <li>Полностью настраиваемые команды</li>
      <li>Создать резервную копию и восстановить вашу папку конфигурации Hamachi</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Важно: Для использования необходим установленный Hamachi</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Gå med, skapa och hantera Hamachi-nätverk enkelt.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Sökbar, sorterbar och utfällbar nätverkslista</li>
      <li>Sidorad för enkel åtkomst till information och åtgärder</li>
      <li>Skrivbordsnotifieringar</li>
      <li>Fullt anpassningsbara kommandon</li>
      <li>Säkerhetskopiera och återskapa din konfigurationsmapp för Hamachi</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Приєднуйся, створюй та керуй мережею Hamachi.</p>
    <p>Можливості:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Список мереж з можливістю пошуку, сортування, складання</li>
      <li>Бічна панель для швидкого доступу до деталей та дій</li>
      <li>Сповіщення</li>
      <li>Повністю настроювані команди</li>
      <li>Резервне копіювання та відновлення каталогу з налаштуваннями Hamachi</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Зверніть увагу: Для використання, Hamachi має бути встановленно</p>
  </description>
  <pkgname>haguichi</pkgname>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">com.github.ztefn.haguichi.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" height="128" type="cached">com.github.ztefn.haguichi.png</icon>
  <id>com.github.ztefn.haguichi</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="uk">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="tr">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="sv">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="sk">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="ru">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="pt">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="pl">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="nl">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="lt">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="kk">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="ja">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="it">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="id">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="fr">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="es">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="de">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="cs">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="bg">Haguichi</name>
  <name lang="ast">Haguichi</name>
  <summary>A graphical frontend for Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Графічна оболонка Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Hamachi için görsel arayüz</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Ett grafiskt gränssnitt för Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Grafické rozhranie pre Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Графическая оболочка к Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Uma interface gráfica para o Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Uma interface gráfica para o Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Graficzny interfejs dla Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Een grafische schil voor Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Hamachi grafinė naudotojo sąsaja</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">Hamachi бағдарламасы үшін графикалық қабықша</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">Hamachi 用のグラフィカルフロントエンド</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Un frontend grafico per Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Tampilan grafis bagi Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Une interface graphique pour Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Una interfaz gráfica para Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Eine grafische Oberfläche für Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Grafické rozhraní pro Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Графичен интерфейс за Hamachi</summary>
  <summary lang="ast">Un frontal gráficu p'Hamachi</summary>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://haguichi.net/appdata/screenshot-1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://haguichi.net/appdata/screenshot-2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://haguichi.net/appdata/screenshot-3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://haguichi.net/appdata/screenshot-4.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://haguichi.net/appdata/screenshot-5.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.github.ztefn.haguichi.desktop</launchable>
  <provides>
    <binary>haguichi</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.4.5" date="2021-12-08">
      <description>
        <p>Haguichi 1.4.5 is gifted with the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Notifications are now send using GNotification instead of libnotify (fixes issue #47).</li>
          <li>Removed support for upstart to control the Hamachi service.</li>
          <li>Switch to show indicator is now disabled if there is no connection to a watcher.</li>
          <li>Now using the RDNN com.github.ztefn.haguichi as prefix for the indicator icons.</li>
          <li>Ported wingpanel indicator to version 3.</li>
          <li>Updated elementary stylesheet to target version 6.</li>
          <li>Updated Japanese and Russian translations.</li>
          <li>Other minor fixes and improvements.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-06-09" version="1.4.4">
      <description>
        <p>Haguichi 1.4.4 has undergone a small spring cleanup and is ready to face the world:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added build support for libayatana-indicator as alternative to libappindicator (fixes issue #39).</li>
          <li>Added invisible tooltips to action buttons in headerbar for screen readers and applications like Plotinus.</li>
          <li>Tweaked action area margins for dialogs without headerbar.</li>
          <li>Added Control+? accelerator for opening the shortcuts window.</li>
          <li>Retired application menu and reorganized the primary menu to follow GNOME HIG.</li>
          <li>Improved init system detection for systemctl by checking if the system has actually been booted with systemd (fixes issues #35 and #36).</li>
          <li>Dropped support for gksu(do), gnomesu and kdesu(do) to gain super user privileges.</li>
          <li>Removed dconf migration for settings in old schema location.</li>
          <li>Fixed build warnings about deprecated methods and error handling.</li>
          <li>Updated Ukrainian translation.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-10-03" version="1.4.3">
      <description>
        <p>Haguichi 1.4.3 has emerged to deliver a compilation of little fixes and tweaks:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixed search entry leaving out the trigger character when activated by typing for the first time.</li>
          <li>Added fallback method to detect if Hamachi configuration path exists when running inside a Flatpak sandbox while the path is not yet mounted.</li>
          <li>Added symlinks to hicolor status icons in Yaru theme in order to prevent the indicator from falling back to the application icon.</li>
          <li>Moved symbolic application icons for hicolor theme to a more specific folder to make sure they are rendered properly.</li>
          <li>Symbolic icons are now used for the indicator on Cinnamon desktops.</li>
          <li>Client side decorations are now used on MATE desktops.</li>
          <li>Removed "Donate" menu item due to little use.</li>
          <li>Translator credits are now part of the translations themselves.</li>
          <li>Added complete Portuguese translation (thanks to André Barata).</li>
          <li>Updated Dutch and Polish translations.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.2" date="2019-12-18">
      <description>
        <p>Haguichi 1.4.2 is made up of the following list. Which has been checked twice:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Implemented FileChooserNative for GTK+ version 3.20 and later.</li>
          <li>Updated hicolor icons to follow the new GNOME style.</li>
          <li>Added Yaru icons in new non-squircle style (big thanks to ubuntujaggers).</li>
          <li>Nodes are now drawn using a custom cell renderer with specific style context instead of separate icon resources.</li>
          <li>Changed symbol to indicate network ownership from outlined to filled star.</li>
          <li>Added support for tilix.</li>
          <li>Added stylesheet for Mint themes.</li>
          <li>Added stylesheet for Yaru themes.</li>
          <li>Added support for Flatpak.</li>
          <li>Removed autostart desktop file.</li>
          <li>Updated Russian translation.</li>
          <li>Other minor improvements and optimizations.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-11-07" version="1.4.1">
      <description>
        <p>Haguichi 1.4.1 has embarked on a great journey packing the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Initialization is now completely multi-threaded.</li>
          <li>Now using a thread pool for determining network ownership and retreiving long nicks.</li>
          <li>Made improvements to configuring and restarting the Hamachi service (fixes issue #16).</li>
          <li>Made network properties extraction more robust.</li>
          <li>Added wingpanel integration as build option.</li>
          <li>Added support for io.elementary.files and io.elementary.terminal.</li>
          <li>Added support for using the Delete key to trigger delete, leave and evict actions.</li>
          <li>Custom command buttons and menu items that don't use the %A address variable are not shown greyed out anymore for members that are offline.</li>
          <li>Client side decorations are now used on LXQt desktops.</li>
          <li>Updated elementary stylesheets for Juno release.</li>
          <li>Added specific application icons for elementary OS.</li>
          <li>Node icons are now included as resources instead of installed into hicolor icon theme.</li>
          <li>Suru icons for Ubuntu are now installed in /usr/share/icons/Yaru.</li>
          <li>AppData XML and .desktop files are now completely translatable (fixes bug #1753846).</li>
          <li>Updated Asturian, Brazilian Portuguese, Bulgarian, Dutch, French, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Lithuanian, Polish, Spanish, Swedish and Ukrainian translations.</li>
          <li>Other minor fixes, improvements and optimizations.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.0" date="2018-05-10">
      <description>
        <p>Haguichi 1.4.0 has washed ashore carrying bulk of new features and updates:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Implemented shortcuts window for GTK+ version 3.20 and later.</li>
          <li>Revamped preferences dialog using stack, list box and switch widgets.</li>
          <li>Integrated appindicator as build option and added accompanying switch to preferences dialog.</li>
          <li>Added dark theme switch to preferences dialog (only available when client side decorations are used).</li>
          <li>Added Suru application icons for Ubuntu (big thanks to Sam Hewitt).</li>
          <li>Tweaked sidebar content alignment and margins.</li>
          <li>Improved window position and size handling.</li>
          <li>Improved modal dialog management.</li>
          <li>Improved compatibility with GTK+ 3.20 and 3.22.</li>
          <li>Fixed crash that could occur when adding a network while the network list was being filtered.</li>
          <li>Now using stylesheets to implement theme specific tweaks and fixes.</li>
          <li>Now using the RDNN com.github.ztefn.haguichi for .desktop files, GSettings schema and D-Bus name.</li>
          <li>Updated Brazilian Portuguese, Bulgarian, Czech, Dutch, French, Italian, Polish, Slovak, Spanish, Swedish, Turkish and Ukrainian translations.</li>
          <li>Bumped minimum required versions of Vala (0.30), GLib (2.48) and GTK+ (3.18).</li>
          <li>Other minor fixes, improvements and optimizations.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>HighContrast</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>Notifications</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <url type="homepage">https://haguichi.net</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/ztefn/haguichi/issues</url>
  <url type="faq">https://haguichi.net/faq/</url>
  <url type="help">https://haguichi.net/tips-and-tricks/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://haguichi.net/donate/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://translations.launchpad.net/haguichi</url>
  <developer_name>Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="kk">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="bg">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ast">Stephen Brandt</developer_name>
  <update_contact>stephen_at_stephenbrandt.com</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">haguichi</translation>
  <languages>
    <lang percentage="100">ast</lang>
    <lang percentage="100">bg</lang>
    <lang percentage="96">cs</lang>
    <lang percentage="89">de</lang>
    <lang percentage="100">es</lang>
    <lang percentage="100">fr</lang>
    <lang percentage="100">id</lang>
    <lang percentage="100">it</lang>
    <lang percentage="100">ja</lang>
    <lang percentage="89">kk</lang>
    <lang percentage="100">lt</lang>
    <lang percentage="100">nl</lang>
    <lang percentage="100">pl</lang>
    <lang percentage="100">pt</lang>
    <lang percentage="100">pt_BR</lang>
    <lang percentage="100">ru</lang>
    <lang percentage="96">sk</lang>
    <lang percentage="100">sv</lang>
    <lang percentage="96">tr</lang>
    <lang percentage="100">uk</lang>
  </languages>
</component>