<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>hexchat</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.Hexchat.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="cached" height="64" width="64">io.github.Hexchat.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" width="128" type="cached">io.github.Hexchat.png</icon>
  <id>io.github.Hexchat.desktop</id>
  <name>HexChat</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="tr">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="sv">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="sr">ХексЧет</name>
  <name lang="sq">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="sl">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="ru">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="pt">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="pl">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="nb">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="lv">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="lt">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="ko">헥스채트</name>
  <name lang="ja_JP">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="it">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="id">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="gl">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="fr">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="fi">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="eu">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="et">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="es">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="el">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="de">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="da">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="cs">HexChat</name>
  <name lang="ca">HexChat</name>
  <developer_name>HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">ХексЧет</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sq">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lv">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">헥스채트</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja_JP">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="et">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">HexChat</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">HexChat</developer_name>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <translation type="gettext">hexchat</translation>
  <summary>IRC Client</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">IRC 客户端</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">IRC İstemcisi</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">IRC klient</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">ИРЦ клијент</summary>
  <summary lang="sq">Klient IRC</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">IRC Client</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">IRC Клиент</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Cliente IRC</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Cliente de IRC</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Klient IRC</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">IRC-klient</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">IRC klients</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">IRC klientas</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">IRC 클라이언트</summary>
  <summary lang="ja_JP">IRCクライアント</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Client IRC</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Klien IRC</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">IRC kliens</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Cliente de IRC</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Client IRC</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">IRC-asiakassovellus</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">IRC bezeroa</summary>
  <summary lang="et">IRC klient</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Cliente de IRC</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">IRC Client</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Πελάτης IRC</summary>
  <summary lang="de">IRC-Client</summary>
  <summary lang="da">IRC-klient</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">IRC klient</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Client IRC</summary>
  <description>
    <p>HexChat is an easy to use yet extensible IRC Client. It allows you to securely join multiple networks and talk to users privately or in channels using a customizable interface. You can even transfer files.</p>
    <p>HexChat supports features such as: DCC, SASL, proxies, spellcheck, alerts, logging, custom themes, and Python/Perl scripts.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>HexChat és un client IRC extensible i fàcil d'utilitzar. Et permet unir-te a múltiples xarxes amb seguretat i parlar amb altres usuaris en privat o en canals utilitzant una interfície personalitzable. Fins i tot pots transferir fitxers.</p>
    <p>HexChat té suport per: DCC, SASL, proxis, correcció d'escriptura, notificacions, registre, temes personalitzats i scripts en Python o Perl.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>HexChat je snadno použitelný a rozšířitelný IRC klient. Umožňuje vám se bezpečně připojit k více sítím a psát si s lidmi soukromě nebo v kanálech pomocí přizpůsobitelného prostředí. Dokonce můžete přenášet soubory.</p>
    <p>HexChat podporuje funkce jako DCC, SASL, brány proxy, kontrolu pravopisu, ukládání záznamů, vlastní motivy a skripty v jazycích Python nebo Perl.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>HexChat er en IRC-klient, der er nem at bruge, men som alligevel også kan udvides. Den tillader dig sikkert at forbinde til flere netværk og tale med brugere privat eller i kanaler ved brug af en tilpasselig grænseflade. Du kan endda overføre filer.</p>
    <p>HexChat understøtter funktioner som: DCC, SASL, proxyer, stavekontrol, underretninger, logning, tilpassede temaer og Python-/Perl-scripts.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>HexChar ist ein einfach zu benutzender, aber dennoch erweiterbarer IRC-Client. Er erlaubt es, sicher mehreren Netzwerken beizutreten und sich mithilfe der anpassbaren Benutzerschnittstelle privat oder auch in Kanälen zu unterhalten. Sogar Dateiübertragungen sind möglich.</p>
    <p>HexChat unterstützt Features wie: DCC, SASL, Proxies, Rechtschreibprüfung, Benachrichtigungen, Logging, Benutzerdesigns und Python/Perl-Skripte</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το HexChat υποστηρίζει λειτουργίες όπως: DCC, SASL, διαμεσολαβητές, ορθογραφική διόρθωση, ειδοποιήσεις, logging, προσαρμοσμένα θέματα, και Python/Perl scripts.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>HexChat is an easy to use yet extensible IRC Client. It allows you to securely join multiple networks and talk to users privately or in channels using a customisable interface. You can even transfer files.</p>
    <p>HexChat supports features such as: DCC, SASL, proxies, spellcheck, alerts, logging, custom themes, and Python/Perl scripts.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>HexChat es un cliente de IRC fácil de usar. Permite unirse a múltiples redes de manera segura y hablar con los usuarios en privado o en los canales usando una interfaz personalizable. Incluso puede enviar archivos.</p>
    <p>HexChat soporta características como: DCC, SASL, proxies, autocorrector, alertas, registro automático, temas personalizados, y scripts en Python/Perl.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>HexChat on lihtne ja paljude võimalustega IRC klient. See võimaldab turvaliselt ühenduda mitme võrguda samaaegselt ja suhelda inimestega privaatselt või liituda vestluskanalitega, kasutades selleks kohandatavat rakendust. Samuti on võimalus failivahetuseks.</p>
    <p>HexChat toetab kasutamiseks: DCC, SASL, hoiatusi, logide koguminst, kohandatud teemasid ja Python/Perl skripte.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>HexChat on helppokäyttäinen IRC-asiakassovellus, joka on helposti laajennettavissa. Sen avulla voit liittyä lukuisiin eri verkkoihin ja keskustella muiden kanssa kanavilla tai yksityiskeskusteluissa. Voit myös siirtää tiedostoja muiden käyttäjien kanssa.</p>
    <p>HexChat tukee muun muassa seuraavia ominaisuuksia: DCC, SASL, välityspalvelimet, oikoluku, hälytykset, lokitus, mukautettavat teemat ja Python-/Perl-skriptit.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>HexChat est un client IRC facile à utiliser et extensible. Il vous permet de rejoindre en toute sécurité plusieurs réseaux et de parler à d'autres utilisateurs en privé ou dans des canaux grâce à une interface personnalisable. Vous pouvez même transférer des fichiers.</p>
    <p>HexChat prend en charge des fonctionnalités telles que : DCC, SASL, serveurs mandataires, vérification orthographique, alertes, journalisation, thèmes personnalisés et scripts Python et Perl.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>HexChat adalah klien IRC yang mudah digunakan tetapi bisa diperluas. Hal ini memungkinkan anda aman dalam bergabung ke beberapa jaringan dan berbicara ke pengguna secara pribadi atau dalam saluran dengan menggunakan antarmuka yang dapat disesuaikan. Anda bahkan dapat mentransfer berkas.</p>
    <p>HexChat mendukung fitur seperti: DCC, SASL, proksi, periksa ejaan, peringatan, pencatatan, tema kustom, dan skrip Python/Perl.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>HexChat è un client IRC semplice ed estensibile. Consente di accedere in modo sicuro a più reti e comunicare con altri utenti privatamente o nei canali usando una interfaccia personalizzabile. È inoltre possibile trasferire file.</p>
    <p>HexChat supporta caratteristiche come: DCC, SASL, proxy, controllo ortografico, avvisi, registrazione delle conversazioni, temi personalizzati e script Python e Perl.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja_JP">
    <p>HexChatは使いやすく、しかも拡張可能なIRCクライアントです。安全に複数のネットワークに参加でき、カスタマイズ可能なインターフェイスを使用してチャネルのユーザーと話すことが可能、さらにファイルを転送することができます。</p>
    <p>HexChatは、次の機能をサポートしています: DCC, SASL, プロキシ, スペルチェック, アラート, カスタムテーマ, Python/Perl スクリプト</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>헥스채트는 사용하기 쉽고 확장성이 뛰어난 IRC 클라이언트 입니다. 여러 네트워크에 안전하게 참여할 수 있으며, 여러분이 직접 유연하게 꾸밀 수 있는 인터페이스를 사용하여 다른 사람과 개인적으로 대화하거나 대화방에서 대화할 수 있습니다. 게다가 파일도 보낼 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p>핵스채트는 DCC, SASL, 프록시 서버, 철자 검사, 경고, 기록, 사용자 정의 테마, 파이썬/펄 스크립트 같은 기능을 지원합니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>HexChat yra paprastas naudoti IRC klientas, leidžiantis jums saugiai prisijungti prie kelių tinklų, privačiai kalbėtis su atskirais naudotojais arba kanaluose, naudojant tinkinamą sąsają. Jūs netgi galite persiųsti failus.</p>
    <p>HexChat palaiko tokias galimybes kaip: DCC, SASL, įgaliotuosius serverius, rašybos tikrinimą, signalizavimą, registravimą, tinkintas temas bei Phyton/Perl scenarijus.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>HexChat er en enkel og fleksibel IRC-klient. Den gir deg muligheten til å sikkert koble deg til nettverk, ha samtaler i kanaler eller privat med brukere, og dette med et tilpassbart grensesnitt. Du kan også utføre filoverføringer.</p>
    <p>HexChat støtter funksjoner som: DCC, SASL, mellomtjenere, stavekontroll, varslinger, logging, tilpassbare temaer, samt Python-/Perl-skript.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>HexChat jest prostym, lecz dowolnie poszerzalnym klientem IRC. Pozwala na bezpieczne dołączenie do wielu sieci i rozmawianie z użytkownikami prywatnie bądź na kanałach. Można nawet przesyłać pliki.</p>
    <p>HexChat wspiera takie funkcje, jak: DCC, SASL, serwery proxy, sprawdzanie pisowni, alerty, logi, własne motywy i skrypty w Pythonie/Perlu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O HexChat é um Cliente de IRC fácil de usar, mas também fácil de expandir. Ele permite que te juntes de forma segura a várias redes e que fales com outros utilizadores em privado ou em canais através de uma interface personalizável. Se quiseres, podes até transferir ficheiros!</p>
    <p>O HexChat suporta funcionalidades como: DCC, SASL, proxies, verificação de erros ortográficos, alertas, registos, temas personalizados, e scripts em Python/Perl.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>HexChat é um cliente IRC extensível e fácil de usar. Ele permite que, de forma segura, você acesse múltiplas redes e tenha conversas privadas com outros usuários ou ainda em canais públicos, tudo isso através de uma interface personalizável. Você poderá até mesmo transferir arquivos.</p>
    <p>HexChat suporta recursos como: DCC, SASL, proxies, corretor ortográfico, alertas, registros, temas personalizados, e scripts em Python/Perl</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>HexChat - это лёгкий в использовании, но расширяемый IRC Клиент. Он позволяет безопасно соединяться со множеством сетей и общаться с пользователями лично или на каналах, используя настраиваемый интерфейс. Вы даже можете передавать файлы.</p>
    <p>HexChat поддерживает следующие функции: DCC, SASL, прокси, проверка орфографии, уведомления, ведение логов, настраиваемые темы и скрипты на Python/Perl.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sq">
    <p>HexChat-i është një klient IRC-je i lehtë për t’u përdorur, por prapëseprapë shumë i zgjerueshëm. Ju lejon të hyni në mënyrë të sigurt, në shumë rrjete njëherësh, dhe të bisedoni me përdoruesit privatisht ose në kanale, duke përdorur një ndërfaqe të personalizueshme. Mundeni madje edhe të shkëmbeni kartela.</p>
    <p>HexChat-i mbulon veçori të tilla si: DCC, SASL, ndërmjetës, drejtshkrim, sinjalizime, regjistrim veprimtarie, tema të personalizueshme, dhe programthe Python/Perl.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>HexChat är en lättanvänd men även utbyggbar IRC-klient. Den låter dig ansluta säkert till flera nätverk och prata med användare privat eller i kanaler med ett anpassningsbart utseende. Du kan till och med överföra filer.</p>
    <p>HexChat stödjer funktioner som: DCC, SASL, proxytjänster, stavningskontroll, notifikationer, loggning, egna teman, och Python/Perl-skript.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>HexChat kullanımı kolay ve işlevleri arttırılabilir bir IRC İstemcisidir. Kişiselleştirilebilir bir arayüz kullanarak birden fazla ağa güvenli şekilde bağlanmanızı ve kullanıcılarla özel olarak veya kanallar üzerinde sohbet etmenizi sağlar. Hatta dosya aktarımı da yapabilirsiniz.</p>
    <p>HexChat şu özellikleri destekler: DCC, SASL, vekil sunucular, yazım denetimi, alarmlar, günlük kaydı, kişisel temalar ve Python/Perl betikleri.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>HexChat 是一款易于使用的可扩展 IRC 客户端。它允许以安全的方式进入多个网络，与用户进行私密聊天，或者在频道中使用自定义界面，甚至还可以传送文件。</p>
    <p>HexChat 支持以下特性: DCC、SASL、代理、拼写检查、消息提醒、聊天记录、自定义主题和 Python/Perl 脚本。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://hexchat.github.io</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/hexchat/hexchat</url>
  <url type="donation">https://goo.gl/jESZvU</url>
  <url type="help">https://hexchat.readthedocs.io/en/latest/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://i.imgur.com/tLMguQz.png</image>
      <caption>Main Chat Window</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">主聊天窗口</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Ana Sohbet Penceresi</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Primärt chattfönster</caption>
      <caption lang="sq">Dritarja Kryesore e Fjalosjeve</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Главное окно чата</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Janela principal de bate-papo</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Janela de Chat Principal</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Główne okno czatu</caption>
      <caption lang="nb">Hovedsludrevinduet </caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Pagrindinis pokalbių langas</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">주 대화 창</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Finestra di chat principale</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Fenêtre de conversation principale</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Ventana principal de charla</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">Main Chat Window</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Κεντρικό Παράθυρο Συζήτησης</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Hauptchatfenster</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Primære chatvindue</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Hlavní okno chatu</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Finestra de xat principal</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <!-- Renamed from this -->
    <id>hexchat.desktop</id>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="2.16.1" date="2022-02-12">
      <description>
        <p>This is a minor release with mostly bug-fixes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add `-NOOVERRIDE` flag to the `GUI COLOR` command</li>
          <li>Add `-q` (quiet) flag to the `EXECWRITE` command</li>
          <li>Rename installed icon to match app-id (Fixes notification icon)</li>
          <li>Fix escaping already escaped URLs when opening them</li>
          <li>Fix Python scripts not being opened as UTF-8</li>
          <li>Fix `TIMER` command supporting decimals regardless of locale</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.16.0" date="2021-10-01">
      <description>
        <p>This is a feature release:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add support for IRCv3 SETNAME, invite-notify, account-tag, standard replies, and UTF8ONLY</li>
          <li>Add support for strikethrough formatting</li>
          <li>Fix text clipping issues by respecting font line height</li>
          <li>Fix URLs not being escaped when opened</li>
          <li>Fix possible hang when showing notifications</li>
          <li>Print ChanServ notices in the front tab by default</li>
          <li>Update network list</li>
          <li>python: Rewrite plugin improving memory usage and compatibility</li>
          <li>fishlim: Add support for CBC and other improvements</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-12-20" version="2.14.3">
      <description>
        <p>This is a bug-fix release:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix various incorrect parsing of IRC messages relating to trailing parameters</li>
          <li>Fix SASL negotiation combined with multi-line cap</li>
          <li>Fix input box theming with Yaru theme</li>
          <li>python: Work around Python 3.7 regression causing crash on unload</li>
          <li>sysinfo: Add support for /etc/os-release</li>
          <li>sysinfo: Ignore irrelevant mounts when calculating storage size</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-08-29" version="2.14.2">
      <description>
        <p>This is a minor release:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Remove shift+click to close tab binding</li>
          <li>Always unminimize when opening from tray</li>
          <li>Fix some translations containing invalid text events</li>
          <li>Fix sending server passwords starting with ":"</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-03-13" version="2.14.1">
      <description>
        <p>This is a very minor bug-fix release:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix performance regression</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.14.0" date="2018-03-10">
      <description>
        <p>This is largely a bug fix release though it has some large behind the scenes changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Rename data files to use *io.github.Hexchat* name</li>
          <li>Add option (irc_reconnect_rejoin) to disable auto-rejoin on reconnect</li>
          <li>Add ability to set custom tray icon separate of app icon</li>
          <li>Fix Enchant 2.0+ support</li>
          <li>Fix input box theming with Adwaita-dark</li>
          <li>Fix custom sounds not respecting omit if away option</li>
          <li>Fix detecting if a tray doesn't exist on x11</li>
          <li>Fix cutting off ctcp text after ending \01</li>
          <li>Fix /ignore not accepting full hosts</li>
          <li>Fix characters getting cut off when their width changes</li>
          <li>Fix various possible crashes</li>
          <li>Change preference window to be scroll-able</li>
          <li>Remove ctrl+w binding by default</li>
          <li>doat: Fix channels with / in them</li>
          <li>fishlim: Fix key exchange</li>
          <li>fishlim: Fix building against LibreSSL</li>
          <li>sysinfo: Fix pci.ids file not being found on some distros</li>
          <li>sysinfo: Make libpci optional</li>
          <li>lua: Avoid loading the same script multiple times</li>
          <li>Update translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-12-10" version="2.12.4">
      <description>
        <p>This is another bug fix release:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix issue with timers causing ping timeouts</li>
          <li>Fix building against OpenSSL 1.1</li>
          <li>Fix /exec output printing invalid utf8</li>
          <li>Replace doat plugin with an internal command</li>
          <li>Change how tab colors interact with plugins</li>
          <li>Enable filtering the beep character by default</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-10-22" version="2.12.3">
      <description>
        <p>This is a minor bug fix release just cleaning up a few issues:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix crash with bad translations</li>
          <li>Add new mhop command</li>
          <li>Change ping timeout to 60 by default</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>UserDocs</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>Notifications</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <update_contact>tingping_at_fedoraproject.org</update_contact>
</component>