<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <description>
    <p>
      Kile is a user-friendly TeX/LaTeX editor by KDE. Kile gives you the ability to use all the functionality of LaTeX in a graphical interface and has interactive preview mechanisms to readily see the results of editing.
    </p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Compile, convert and view your document with one click</li>
      <li>Auto-completion of (La)TeX commands</li>
      <li>Templates and wizards make starting new documents very little work</li>
      <li>Easy insertion of many standard tags and symbols and the option to define (an arbitrary number of) user defined tags</li>
      <li>Inverse and forward search: click in the DVI viewer and jump to the corresponding LaTeX line in the editor, or jump from the editor
          to the corresponding page in the viewer</li>
      <li>Finding chapter or sections is very easy, Kile constructs a list of all the chapter etc. in your document. You can use the list to
          jump to the corresponding section</li>
      <li>Collect documents that belong together into a project</li>
      <li>Easy insertion of citations and references when using projects</li>
      <li>Flexible and smart build system to compile your LaTeX documents</li>
      <li>QuickPreview: preview a selected part of your document</li>
      <li>Easy access to various help sources</li>
      <li>Advanced editing commands</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>الميزات:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>صرّف مستنداتك وحوّلها واعرضها بنقرة واحدة</li>
      <li>إكمال آليّ لأوامر (لا)تخ</li>
      <li>تجعل القوالب والمُرشدات بدء المستندات الجديدة مهمّة سهلة</li>
      <li>إدراج سهل للعديد من الوسوم والرّموز القياسيّة، إضافة إلى إمكانيّة تعريف المستخدم لوسوم بالعدد الذي يريد</li>
      <li>اجمع المستندات ذات العلاقة ببعضها البعض في مشروع</li>
      <li>نظام بناء مرن ذكيّ لتصريف مستندات لاتخ</li>
      <li>المعاينة السّريعة: عاين جزءًا من مستندك</li>
      <li>وصول سهل إلى مختلف مصادر المساعدة</li>
      <li>أوامر تحرير متقدّمة</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El Kile és un editor TeX/LaTeX amigable fet per la comunitat KDE. El Kile proporciona la possibilitat d'usar totes les funcionalitats del LaTeX en una interfície gràfica i té mecanismes de previsualització interactius per veure immediatament els resultats de l'edició.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Compila, converteix i mostra el document amb un clic</li>
      <li>Compleció automàtica d'ordres del (La)TeX</li>
      <li>Les plantilles i els assistents fan que sigui molt poca feina iniciar els documents nous</li>
      <li>Inserció fàcil de moltes etiquetes i símbols estàndard, i l'opció de definir (amb un nombre arbitrari) etiquetes definides per l'usuari</li>
      <li>Cerca directa i inversa: cliqueu en el visualitzador del DVI i salteu a la línia LaTeX corresponent de l'editor, o salteu des de l'editor a la pàgina corresponent del visualitzador</li>
      <li>La cerca de capítols o seccions és molt senzilla, El Kile construeix una llista de tots els capítols, etc. en el document. Podeu usar la llista per saltar a la secció corresponent</li>
      <li>Reuneix els documents relacionats en un projecte</li>
      <li>Inserció fàcil de cites i referències en usar projectes</li>
      <li>Sistema de construcció flexible i intel·ligent per compilar els documents LaTeX</li>
      <li>QuickPreview: vista prèvia d'una part seleccionada del document</li>
      <li>Accés fàcil a diverses fonts d'ajuda</li>
      <li>Edició avançada d'ordres</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>El Kile és un editor TeX/LaTeX amigable fet per la comunitat KDE. El Kile proporciona la possibilitat d'usar totes les funcionalitats del LaTeX en una interfície gràfica i té mecanismes de previsualització interactius per veure immediatament els resultats de l'edició.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Compila, converteix i mostra el document amb un clic</li>
      <li>Compleció automàtica d'ordres del (La)TeX</li>
      <li>Les plantilles i els assistents fan que siga molt poca faena iniciar els documents nous</li>
      <li>Inserció fàcil de moltes etiquetes i símbols estàndard, i l'opció de definir (amb un nombre arbitrari) etiquetes definides per l'usuari</li>
      <li>Cerca directa i inversa: cliqueu en el visualitzador del DVI i salteu a la línia LaTeX corresponent de l'editor, o salteu des de l'editor a la pàgina corresponent del visualitzador</li>
      <li>La cerca de capítols o seccions és molt senzilla, El Kile construeix una llista de tots els capítols, etc. en el document. Podeu usar la llista per saltar a la secció corresponent</li>
      <li>Reuneix els documents relacionats en un projecte</li>
      <li>Inserció fàcil de cites i referències en usar projectes</li>
      <li>Sistema de construcció flexible i intel·ligent per compilar els documents LaTeX</li>
      <li>QuickPreview: vista prèvia d'una part seleccionada del document</li>
      <li>Accés fàcil a diverses fonts d'ajuda</li>
      <li>Edició avançada d'ordres</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Vlastnosti:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Funktionen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Dokumente mit einem Klick kompilieren, umwandeln und anzeigen</li>
      <li>Automatische Vervollständigung von (La)TeX-Befehlen</li>
      <li>Vorlagen und Assistenten helfen beim Erstellen neuer Dokumente</li>
      <li>Zusammenfassung von zusammengehörigen Dokumenten zu einem Projekt</li>
      <li>Flexibles und intelligentes Build-System, um Ihre LaTeX-Dokumente zu kompilieren</li>
      <li>Schnellvorschau: Vorschau eines ausgewählten Teils eines Dokuments</li>
      <li>Einfacher Zugang zu verschiedenen Hilfsquellen</li>
      <li>Erweiterte Bearbeitungsbefehle</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>Kile is a user-friendly TeX/LaTeX editor by KDE. Kile gives you the ability to use all the functionality of LaTeX in a graphical interface and has interactive preview mechanisms to readily see the results of editing.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Compile, convert and view your document with one click</li>
      <li>Auto-completion of (La)TeX commands</li>
      <li>Templates and wizards make starting new documents very little work</li>
      <li>Easy insertion of many standard tags and symbols and the option to define (an arbitrary number of) user defined tags</li>
      <li>Inverse and forward search: click in the DVI viewer and jump to the corresponding LaTeX line in the editor, or jump from the editor to the corresponding page in the viewer</li>
      <li>Finding chapter or sections is very easy, Kile constructs a list of all the chapter etc. in your document. You can use the list to jump to the corresponding section</li>
      <li>Collect documents that belong together into a project</li>
      <li>Easy insertion of citations and references when using projects</li>
      <li>Flexible and smart build system to compile your LaTeX documents</li>
      <li>QuickPreview: preview a selected part of your document</li>
      <li>Easy access to various help sources</li>
      <li>Advanced editing commands</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Kile es un editor de TeX/LaTeX amigable creado por KDE. Kile le permite usar toda la funcionalidad de LaTeX mediante una interfaz gráfica y posee mecanismos interactivos de vista previa para comprobar rápidamente el resultado de la edición.</p>
    <p>Funciones:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Compile, convierta y visualice documentos con un solo clic</li>
      <li>Terminación automática de órdenes de (La)TeX</li>
      <li>Plantillas y asistentes para facilitar la creación de nuevos documentos</li>
      <li>Fácil inserción de numerosas etiquetas y símbolos estándares, además de la opción de definir (cualquier número) de etiquetas del usuario</li>
      <li>Búsqueda hacia atrás y hacia adelante: pulse en el visor DVI y vaya a la correspondiente línea de LaTeX en el editor, o vaya del editor a la página correspondiente del visor</li>
      <li>Encontrar capítulos y secciones es muy fácil: Kile construye una lista de todos los capítulos, etc. del documento. Puede usar dicha lista para ir a la sección correspondiente.</li>
      <li>Reunir documentos que deben ir juntos en un proyecto</li>
      <li>Fácil inserción de citas y referencias al usar proyectos</li>
      <li>Sistema de construcción flexible e inteligente para compilar documentos LaTeX</li>
      <li>Vista rápida: vista previa de la parte seleccionada del documento</li>
      <li>Fácil acceso a diversas fuentes de ayuda</li>
      <li>Órdenes de edición avanzadas</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Käännä, muunna ja näytä tiedostosi yhdellä napsautuksella</li>
      <li>Täydennä (La)TeX-komennot automaattisesti</li>
      <li>Aloita uusi tiedosto helposti mallipohjien ja opastettujen toimintojen avulla</li>
      <li>Lisää vaivattomasti vakiotunnisteita ja -symboleja sekä määrittele (mielivaltainen määrä) omia tunnisteitasi</li>
      <li>Etsi molempiin suuntiin: napsauta DVI-katselinta ja siirry muokkaimessa vastaavalla LaTeX-riville tai siirry muokkaimesta vastaavalle kohtaa katselimessa</li>
      <li>Löydä (ala-) luku helposti: Kile pitää niistä yllä luetteloa, jonka avulla voit siirtyä luvusta toiseen</li>
      <li>Kokoa yhteen kuuluvat tiedostot projektiksi</li>
      <li>Lisää projekteja käytettäessä lainaukset ja viitteet helposti</li>
      <li>Käännä LaTeX-tiedostosi joustavasti ja älykkäästi</li>
      <li>Esikatsele nopeasti tiedoston valittua osa pikaesikatselulla</li>
      <li>Löydä eri lähteiden ohjeet nopeasti</li>
      <li>Kehittyneet muokkauskomennot</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Kile est un éditeur TeX/LaTeX intuitif par KDE. Kile vous offre la possibilité d'utiliser toutes les fonctionnalités de LaTeX au sein d'une interface graphique et dispose de mécanismes d'aperçu interactifs qui vous permettent d'afficher les résultats de l'édition.</p>
    <p>Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Compiler, convertir et afficher vos documents en un clic</li>
      <li>Auto-complètement des balises (La)TeX</li>
      <li>Modèles et assistants pour créer de nouveaux documents en très peu de temps</li>
      <li>Insertion facile de nombreuses balises et symboles standards avec la possibilité de définir des balises personnalisées</li>
      <li>Recherche inversée et en avant : cliquez sur l'afficheur DVI et passez directement à la ligne LaTeX correspondante dans l'éditeur ou passez de l'éditeur à la page correspondante dans l'afficheur</li>
      <li>Il n'a jamais été aussi facile de trouver des chapitres ou des sections, Kile construit une liste de tous les chapitres, sections, etc. de vos documents. Vous pouvez utiliser cette liste pour aller directement à la section correspondante.</li>
      <li>Collection de documents appartenant au même projet</li>
      <li>Insertion facile de citations et de références au sein de vos projets</li>
      <li>Système de compilation de documents LaTeX flexible et intelligent</li>
      <li>Aperçu rapide : aperçu rapide d'un passage sélectionné de votre document</li>
      <li>Accès rapide à de nombreuses sources d'assistance</li>
      <li>Commandes d'édition avancées</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Kile é un editor de TeX e LaTeX fácil de usar creado por KDE. Kile permítelle usar toda a funcionalidade de LaTeX nunha interface gráfica e ten un mecanismo de vista previa para ver rapidamente os resultados da edición.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Compilar, converter e visualizar o documento cun clic.</li>
      <li>Completación automática de ordes de (La)TeX.</li>
      <li>Modelos e asistentes para facilitar o inicio de novos documentos.</li>
      <li>Inserción fácil de moitas etiquetas e símbolos estándar, e a posibilidade de definir etiquetas de usuario.</li>
      <li>Busca inversa e cara adiante: prema o visualizador de DVI e salte á liña correspondente de LaTeX no editor, ou salte do editor á páxina correspondente no visualizador.</li>
      <li>Atopar capítulos ou seccións é moi doado, Kile constrúe unha lista de capítulos, etc. no documento. Podes usar a lista para saltar á sección correspondente.</li>
      <li>Recolle documentos que van xuntos nun proxecto.</li>
      <li>Inserción fácil de citas e referencias ao usar proxectos.</li>
      <li>Sistema de construción flexíbel e intelixente para compilar documentos de LaTeX.</li>
      <li>Previsualización da parte seleccionada dun documento.</li>
      <li>Acceso doado a varios recursos de axuda.</li>
      <li>Ordes de edición avanazda.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Kile adalah editor TeX/LaTeX yang mudah digunakan oleh KDE. Kile memberi Anda kemampuan untuk menggunakan semua fungsi LaTeX dalam antarmuka grafis dan memiliki mekanisme pratinjau interaktif untuk kesiapan melihat hasil pengeditan.</p>
    <p>Fitur:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Kompilasi, konversi, dan lihat dokumen Anda dengan satu klik</li>
      <li>Penyelesaian otomatis perintah-perintah (La)TeX</li>
      <li>Template dan asisten membuat pemulaian dokumen baru sangat sedikit bekerja</li>
      <li>Penyisipan mudah banyak tag dan simbol standar dan opsi untuk menentukan (sebuah nomor semaunya) tag yang ditentukan pengguna</li>
      <li>Pencarian mundur dan maju: klik di DVI viewer dan lompat ke baris LaTeX yang sesuai di editor, atau lompat dari editor ke halaman terkait di viewer</li>
      <li>Penemuan bab atau bagian sangat mudah, Kile menyusun daftar semua bab dll. di dokumen Anda. Anda dapat menggunakan daftar untuk melompat ke bagian yang sesuai</li>
      <li>Kumpulkan dokumen-dokumen yang menjadi bagian dari suatu projek</li>
      <li>Menyisipkan kutipan dan referensi dengan mudah saat menggunakan projek</li>
      <li>Sistem pembangunan yang fleksibel dan cerdas untuk mengkompilasi dokumen LaTeX Anda</li>
      <li>QuickPreview: mempratinjau bagian yang dipilih dari dokumen Anda</li>
      <li>Akses mudah untuk berbagai sumberdaya bantuan</li>
      <li>Perintah pengeditan tingkat-lanjut</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Kile è un editor TeX/LaTeX della comunità KDE facile da usare. Ti dà la possibilità di utilizzare tutte la funzionalità di LaTeX in un'interfaccia grafica e dispone di un meccanismo di anteprima interattiva per vedere prontamente i risultati della modifica.</p>
    <p>Caratteristiche:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Compila, converte e visualizza i tuoi documenti con un clic</li>
      <li>Completamento automatico dei comandi (La)TeX</li>
      <li>I modelli e le procedure guidate ti fanno iniziare i nuovi documenti con pochissimo lavoro</li>
      <li>Inserimento semplice di molti tag standard e simboli, inoltre è possibile definire (un numero arbitrario di) tag definiti dall'utente</li>
      <li>Ricerca in avanti e indietro: fai clic nel visore DVI per saltare alla riga LaTeX corrispondente nell'editor, oppure salta dalla riga dell'editor alla pagina corrispondente nel visore</li>
      <li>Trovare i capitoli o le sezioni è molto semplice: Kile costruisce un elenco di tutti i capitoli ecc. nel tuo documento, che puoi usare per saltare alla sezione corrispondente</li>
      <li>Raccoglie i documenti che appartengono ad un progetto</li>
      <li>Inserimento semplice di citazioni e di riferimenti quando usi i progetti</li>
      <li>Sistema flessibile e intelligente per compilare i tuoi documenti LaTeX</li>
      <li>Anteprima rapida: anteprima di una parte selezionata del tuo documento</li>
      <li>Semplice accesso a varie risorse di aiuto</li>
      <li>Comandi di modifica avanzati</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>Kile은 KDE의 TeX/LaTeX 편집기입니다. Kile을 사용하여 그래픽 환경에서 LaTeX 기능을 활용할 수 있으며 편집 결과를 즉시 볼 수 있는 미리 보기를 제공합니다.</p>
    <p>기능:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>문서를 간단하게 컴파일, 변환, 보기</li>
      <li>(La)TeX 명령 자동 완성</li>
      <li>새 문서를 빠르게 시작할 수 있는 템플릿과 마법사</li>
      <li>표준 태그와 기호 및 사용자 정의 태그 추가</li>
      <li>전방 및 후방 검색: DVI 뷰어에서 항목을 누르면 LaTeX 편집기의 해당하는 줄로 이동하며, 그 반대도 가능합니다</li>
      <li>문서에 포함된 모든 장과 절을 목록으로 구성하여 쉽게 찾을 수 있습니다. 목록을 통해서 해당하는 부분으로 이동할 수 있습니다</li>
      <li>프로젝트에 포함되는 여러 문서 모으기</li>
      <li>프로젝트 모드에서 인용과 참고 문헌 간단하게 삽입</li>
      <li>LaTeX 문서를 컴파일할 수 있는 유연하고 똑똑한 빌드 시스템</li>
      <li>빠른 미리 보기: 문서의 선택한 부분 미리 보기</li>
      <li>여러 도움말 정보에 쉽게 접근</li>
      <li>고급 편집 명령</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Kile is een gebruikersvriendelijke TeX/LaTeX bewerker door KDE. Kile geeft u de mogelijkheid om alle functionaliteit van LaTeX in een grafisch interface te gebruiken en heeft interactieve voorbeeldweergave om op een redelijke manier het resultaat van de bewerking te zien.</p>
    <p>Kenmerken:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Compileert, converteert en toont uw document met één klik</li>
      <li>Automatische aanvulling van (La)TeX commando's</li>
      <li>Sjablonen en assistenten maken het begin van nieuwe documenten tot weinig werk</li>
      <li>Gemakkelijk invoegen van vele standaard tags en symbolen en de optie om (een willekeurig aantal) gebruikergedefinieerde tags te definiëren</li>
      <li>Omgekeerd en voorwaards zoeken: klik in de DVI-viewer en spring naar de overeenkomstige LaTeX regel in de bewerker of spring uit de bewerker naar de overeenkomstige pagina in de viewer</li>
      <li>Vinden van hoofdstuk of sectie is erg gemakkelijk, Kile maakt een lijst met alle hoofdstukken etc. in uw document. U kunt de lijst gebruiken om naar de overeenkomstige sectie te springen</li>
      <li>Verzamelt documenten die bij elkaar behoren in een project</li>
      <li>Gemakkelijk invoegen van citaten en referenties bij gebruik van projecten</li>
      <li>Flexibel en slim bouwsysteem om uw LaTeX documenten te compileren</li>
      <li>QuickPreview: bekijk een geselecteerd deel van uw document</li>
      <li>Gemakkelijke toegang tot verschillende hulpbronnen</li>
      <li>Geavanceerde commando's voor bewerking</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Kile jest przyjaznym użytkownikowi edytorem TeX/LaTeX dla KDE. Kile umożliwia wykorzystanie wszystkich możliwości LaTeX przy użyciu interfejsu graficznego i ma mechanizm interaktywnego podglądu, aby szybko podejrzeć wyniki edycji.</p>
    <p>Możliwości:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Kompiluj, przekształcaj i oglądaj swoje dokumenty na kliknięcie</li>
      <li>Samouzupełnianie poleceń (La)TeX</li>
      <li>Szablony i pomocnicy ułatwiający tworzenie nowych dokumentów</li>
      <li>Łatwe wstawianie wielu standardowych znaczników i symboli oraz opcja do definiowania (dowolnej liczby) znaczników użytkownika</li>
      <li>Wyszukiwanie odwrotne i wprzód: kliknij w przeglądarce DVI i przejdź do odpowiadającego wiersza LaTeX w edytorze lub przejdź z edytora do odpowiadającej strony w przeglądarce</li>
      <li>Znajdowanie rozdziałów lub sekcji jest bardzo proste. Kile tworzy listę wszystkich rozdziałów itp. w twoim dokumencie. Możesz uzyć tej listy do przeskakiwania do danej sekcji.</li>
      <li>Zbieranie dokumentów należących razem do projektu</li>
      <li>Łatwe wstawianie cytowań i odwołań przy użyciu projektów</li>
      <li>Eleastyczny i mądry system budowania do kompilowania twoich dokumentów LaTeX</li>
      <li>SzybkiPodgląd: podgląd wybranej części dokumentu</li>
      <li>Łatwy dostęp do źródeł pomocy</li>
      <li>Zaawansowane polecenia edytowania</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Kile é um editor amigável de TeX/LaTeX para o KDE. O Kile dá-lhe a capacidade de usar todas as funcionalidades do LaTeX numa interface gráfica e tem mecanismos de antevisão interactiva para ler de forma imediata os resultados da edição.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Compilar, converter e ver o seu documento com um 'click'</li>
      <li>Completação automática de comandos de (La)TeX</li>
      <li>Os modelos e assistentes tornam a criação de documentos novos um esforço mínimo</li>
      <li>Inserção simples de muitas marcas-padrão e símbolos, assim como a opção para definir (um número arbitrário de) marcas definidas pelo utilizador</li>
      <li>Pesquisa inversa e directa: carregue no visualizador de DVI e vá para a linha de LaTeX correspondente no editor, ou salte do editor para a página correspondente no visualizador</li>
      <li>A pesquisa de capítulos ou secções é muito simples - o Kile constrói uma lista com todos os capítulos, etc. no seu documento. Poderá usar a lista para ir para a secção correspondente</li>
      <li>Colecção de documentos que pertencem em conjunto a um projecto</li>
      <li>Inserção simpless de citações e referências ao usar os projectos</li>
      <li>Sistema flexível e inteligente de compilação dos seus documentos em LaTeX</li>
      <li>Antevisão Rápida: antevisão de uma parte seleccionada do seu documento</li>
      <li>Acesso simples a diversas fontes de ajuda</li>
      <li>Comandos de edição avançados</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>O Kile é um editor de TeX/LaTeX fácil de usar criado pela comunidade KDE. Ele permite usar toda a funcionalidade do LaTeX com uma interface gráfica, possuindo ainda pré-visualização interative para ver dinamicamente os resultados da sua edição.</p>
    <p>Recursos:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Compile, converta e visualize seu documento com apenas um clique</li>
      <li>Função de auto-completar para comandos do (La)TeX</li>
      <li>Modelos e assistentes permitem criar novos documentos sem esforço</li>
      <li>Inserção fácil de várias tags e símbolos comuns, assim como a opção de definir (uma quantidade arbitrária de) tags feitas pelo usuário</li>
      <li>Achar o capítulo ou seção correta é muito fácil, o Kile constrói uma lista de todos os capítulos e afins do seu documento, permitindo pular para a seção correspondente rapidamente</li>
      <li>Reúna documentos que pertencem a um mesmo projeto</li>
      <li>Inserção fácil de citações e referências ao usar projetos</li>
      <li>Sistema de depuração flexível e inteligente para compilar seus documentos do LaTeX</li>
      <li>Visualização rápida: pré-visualize uma parte específica do seu documento</li>
      <li>Acesso fácil a várias fontes de ajuda</li>
      <li>Comandos de edição avançados</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Возможности:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Funkcie:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Kile är en användarvänlig Tex- och Latex-editor av KDE. Kile ger dig möjlighet att använda hela Latex funktionalitet i ett grafiskt gränssnitt, och har en interaktiv förhandsgranskningsmekanism för att enkelt kunna se redigeringsresultatet.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Kompilera, konvertera och visa dokumentet med ett klick</li>
      <li>Automatisk komplettering av Tex- och Latex-kommandon</li>
      <li>Mallar och guider gör att mycket lite arbete behövs för att påbörja nya dokument</li>
      <li>Enkelt att infoga många standardtaggar och symboler, och möjlighet att definiera (ett godtyckligt antal) användardefinerade taggar</li>
      <li>Invers och framåtsökning: Klicka i DVI-visningen och gå till motsvarande Latex-rad i editorn, eller gå från editorn till motsvarande sida i visningen</li>
      <li>Det är mycket enkelt att hitta kapitel eller avsnitt. Kile skapar en lista av alla kapitel, etc., i dokumentet. Listan kan användas för att gå till motsvarande avsnitt</li>
      <li>Samla dokument som hör ihop i ett projekt</li>
      <li>Enkelt att infoga hänvisningar och referenser vid användning av projekt</li>
      <li>Flexibelt och smart byggsystem för att kompilera Latex-dokument</li>
      <li>Snabbgranskning: Förhandsgranska en markerad del av dokumentet</li>
      <li>Enkel tillgång till olika hjälpkällor</li>
      <li>Avancerade redigeringskommandon</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Özellikler:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Tek tıklama ile belgenizi derleyin, dönüştürün ve görüntüleyin</li>
      <li>(La)TeX komutlarının Otomatik-Tamamlanması</li>
      <li>Şablonlar ve sihirbazlar yeni belgelere başlamayı çok küçük bir işe çevirirler</li>
      <li>Pek çok standart etiketin ve sembolün kolayca eklenmesi ve kullanıcı tanımlı etiketleri (isteğe bağlı sayıda) tanımlama seçeneği</li>
      <li>Tersine ve ileri arama: DVI görüntüleyiciyi tıklatın ve düzenleyicideki ilgili LaTeX satırına atlayın veya düzenleyiciden görüntüleyicideki ilgili sayfaya atlayın</li>
      <li>Bölüm veya kısımları bulmak çok kolay, Kile belgenizdeki tüm bölümlerin vb. bir listesini oluşturur. İlgili bölüme atlamak için listeyi kullanabilirsiniz</li>
      <li>Birlikte bir projeye ait olan belgeleri toplayın</li>
      <li>Projeleri kullanırken alıntıların ve başvuruların kolay eklenmesi</li>
      <li>LaTeX belgelerinizi derlemek için esnek ve akıllı bir inşa sistemi</li>
      <li>QuickPreview: belgenizin seçili bir bölümünü önizleyin</li>
      <li>Çeşitli yardım kaynaklarına kolay erişim</li>
      <li>İleri seviye düzenleme komutları</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Kile — дружня до користувача програма для редагування коду TeX/LaTeX від KDE. Kile надає вам змогу скористатися усіма функціональними можливостями LaTeX за допомогою графічного інтерфейсу та має механізми інтерактивного попереднього перегляду для негайного отримання результатів редагування.</p>
    <p>Можливості:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Збирання, перетворення та перегляд документів у одне клацання кнопкою миші.</li>
      <li>Автодоповнення команд (La)TeX.</li>
      <li>Шаблони і допоміжні засоби для створення документів з мінімальними зусиллями.</li>
      <li>Просте вставлення багатьох стандартних команд і символів, можливість додаткового визначення користувачем довільної кількості команд.</li>
      <li>Зворотний і прямий пошук: клацання на тексті у програмі для перегляду DVI призведе до переходу до відповідного рядка коду LaTeX у редакторі, а з редактора можна перейти до відповідного місця у програмі для перегляду документів.</li>
      <li>Знайти потрібну главу або розділ дуже просто: Kile будує список усіх розділів у документі. Ви можете скористатися цим списком для переходу до відповідного розділу.</li>
      <li>Збирання документів у проєкти.</li>
      <li>Просте вставлення посилань у межах проєктів.</li>
      <li>Гнучка та інтелектуальна система збирання для обробки ваших документів LaTeX.</li>
      <li>Швидкий перегляд: можливість швидко переглянути частину вашого документа.</li>
      <li>Простий доступ до різноманітних довідкових джерел.</li>
      <li>Розширені команди редагування.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxKile is a user-friendly TeX/LaTeX editor by KDE. Kile gives you the ability to use all the functionality of LaTeX in a graphical interface and has interactive preview mechanisms to readily see the results of editing.xx</p>
    <p>xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>xxCompile, convert and view your document with one clickxx</li>
      <li>xxAuto-completion of (La)TeX commandsxx</li>
      <li>xxTemplates and wizards make starting new documents very little workxx</li>
      <li>xxEasy insertion of many standard tags and symbols and the option to define (an arbitrary number of) user defined tagsxx</li>
      <li>xxInverse and forward search: click in the DVI viewer and jump to the corresponding LaTeX line in the editor, or jump from the editor to the corresponding page in the viewerxx</li>
      <li>xxFinding chapter or sections is very easy, Kile constructs a list of all the chapter etc. in your document. You can use the list to jump to the corresponding sectionxx</li>
      <li>xxCollect documents that belong together into a projectxx</li>
      <li>xxEasy insertion of citations and references when using projectsxx</li>
      <li>xxFlexible and smart build system to compile your LaTeX documentsxx</li>
      <li>xxQuickPreview: preview a selected part of your documentxx</li>
      <li>xxEasy access to various help sourcesxx</li>
      <li>xxAdvanced editing commandsxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>一键对您的文档进行编译、转换和查看</li>
      <li>(La)TeX 命令自动补全</li>
      <li>模板和向导让创建新文档变得简单高效</li>
      <li>便捷插入很多标准标签和符号，以及可以定义任意数量用户自定义标签</li>
      <li>反向和正向搜索：点击 DVI 查看器并在编辑器中跳到相应的 LaTex 行，或者从编辑器中跳到查看器中对应的页面</li>
      <li>查找章节非常容易，Kile 构建了文档的所有章节的列表。您可以使用列表跳转到对应的节</li>
      <li>收集属于同一项目的文档于一处</li>
      <li>使用项目时可以轻松插入引文和引用</li>
      <li>灵活且智能的构建系统来编译您的 LaTex 文档</li>
      <li>快速预览：预览文档中选中的部分</li>
      <li>便捷访问各种帮助资源</li>
      <li>高级编辑命令</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>kile</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kile.desktop</launchable>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">kile.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">kile.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.kile</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kile</name>
  <name lang="ar">كايل</name>
  <name lang="ca">Kile</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">Kile</name>
  <name lang="cs">Kile</name>
  <name lang="de">Kile</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">Kile</name>
  <name lang="es">Kile</name>
  <name lang="fi">Kile</name>
  <name lang="fr">Kile</name>
  <name lang="gl">Kile</name>
  <name lang="id">Kile</name>
  <name lang="it">Kile</name>
  <name lang="ko">Kile</name>
  <name lang="nl">Kile</name>
  <name lang="pl">Kile</name>
  <name lang="pt">Kile</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">Kile</name>
  <name lang="ru">Kile</name>
  <name lang="sk">Kile</name>
  <name lang="sv">Kile</name>
  <name lang="tr">Kile</name>
  <name lang="uk">Kile</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxKilexx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">Kile</name>
  <summary>TeX/LaTeX Editor</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">محرّر تخ/لاتخ</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Editor de TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Editor de TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Editor pro TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary lang="de">TeX-/LaTeX-Editor</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">TeX/LaTeX Editor</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Editor TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">TeX/LaTeX-muokkain</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Éditeur TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Editor de TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Editor TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Editor TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">TeX/LaTeX 편집기</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">TeX/LaTeX-bewerker</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Edytor TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Editor de TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Editor TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Tex/Latex-editor</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">TeX/LaTeX Düzenleyici</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Редактор TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxTeX/LaTeX Editorxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">TeX/LaTeX 编辑器</summary>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Document editing in Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Edició d'un document al Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Edició d'un document al Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Vytváření dokumentu v Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Bearbeitung eines Dokuments in Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">Document editing in Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Edición de documentos en Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Édition de documents dans Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Edición de documentos en Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Pengeditan dokumen di Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Modifica dei documenti in Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">Kile로 문서 편집</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Bewerking van documenten in Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Edytowanie dokumentów w Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Edição de documentos no Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Edição de documentos no Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Dokumentredigering i Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Редагування документа у Kile</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxDocument editing in Kilexx</caption>
      <image>https://kde.org/images/screenshots/kile.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">http://kile.sourceforge.net/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kile</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kile</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kile</binary>
  </provides>
</component>