<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>ktimetracker</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.ktimetracker.desktop</launchable>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">ktimetracker.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" type="cached" width="128">ktimetracker.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.ktimetracker.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <name>KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="ca">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="cs">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="de">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="es">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="et">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="fr">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="gl">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="id">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="it">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="ko">KTimetracker</name>
  <name lang="nl">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="pl">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="pt">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="ru">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="sk">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="sv">Ktimerracker</name>
  <name lang="uk">KTimeTracker</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxKTimeTrackerxx</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">KTimeTracker</name>
  <summary>Personal Time Tracker</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Seguidor personal del temps</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Seguidor personal del temps</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Persönliche Zeiterfassung</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Personal Time Tracker</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Seguimiento del tiempo personal</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Isikliku aja arvestamine</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Outil de gestion du temps personnel</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Seguimento do tempo persoal</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Pelacak Waktu Personal</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Segnatempo personale</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">개인 시간 추적기</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Persoonlijk tijdgebruik</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Osobisty czasomierz</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Gestor do Tempo Pessoal</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Учёт времени</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Osobný sledovač času</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Personlig tidmätning</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Програма для керування особистим часом</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxPersonal Time Trackerxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-TW">個人時間追蹤器</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KTimeTracker helps you track your personal time spent on various tasks and projects.</p>
    <p>It is useful for tracking billable hours and can report the hours logged by task and day.</p>
    <p>With KTimeTracker, you can organize a broken-down project as subtasks with unlimited nesting. The standard keyboard and mouse shortcuts are simple and make the tool really comfortable and intuitive to use.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El KTimeTracker ajuda a fer un seguiment del vostre temps personal dedicat a diverses tasques i projectes.</p>
    <p>És útil per al seguiment de les hores facturables i pot informar de les hores registrades per tasca i dia.</p>
    <p>Amb el KTimeTracker, podreu organitzar un projecte desglossat com a subtasques amb nidificació il·limitada. Les dreceres de teclat i ratolí estàndard són senzilles i fan que l'eina sigui molt còmoda i intuïtiva.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>El KTimeTracker ajuda a fer un seguiment del vostre temps personal dedicat a diverses tasques i projectes.</p>
    <p>És útil per al seguiment de les hores facturables i pot informar de les hores registrades per tasca i dia.</p>
    <p>Amb el KTimeTracker, podreu organitzar un projecte desglossat com a subtasques amb nidificació il·limitada. Les dreceres de teclat i ratolí estàndard són senzilles i fan que l'eina siga molt còmoda i intuïtiva.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>KTimeTracker misst die Zeit, die Sie für verschiedene Aufgaben und Projekte benötigen</p>
    <p>Das Programm ist nützlich, wenn z. B. die für verschiedene Kunden aufgewendeten Stunden verrechnet werden müssen.</p>
    <p>Mit KTimeTracker können Sie ein Projekt als Teilaufgaben mit unbegrenzter Verschachtelung organisieren. Die standardmäßigen Tastenkombinationen für Tastatur und Maus sind einfach und komfortabel und ermöglichen eine komfortable und intuitive Bedienung.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>KTimeTracker helps you track your personal time spent on various tasks and projects.</p>
    <p>It is useful for tracking billable hours and can report the hours logged by task and day.</p>
    <p>With KTimeTracker, you can organize a broken-down project as subtasks with unlimited nesting. The standard keyboard and mouse shortcuts are simple and make the tool really comfortable and intuitive to use.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>KTimeTracker le ayuda a hacer un seguimiento del tiempo personal invertido en diversas tareas y proyectos.</p>
    <p>Es útil para hacer un seguimiento de las horas facturables y puede informar de las horas registradas por tarea y día.</p>
    <p>Con KTimeTracker puede organizar un proyecto desglosado como subtareas con anidación ilimitada. Los accesos rápidos estándares del teclado y del ratón son sencillos y hacen que la herramienta resulte cómoda e intuitiva.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>KTimeTracker aitab silma peal hoida ajal, mis sul kulub mitmesugustele ülesannetele ja projektidele.</p>
    <p>Sellest on eriti abi tasustataval ajal silma peal hoidmiseks ja sellest ülesannete ja päevade kaupa aru andmiseks.</p>
    <p>KTimeTracker võimaldab projekte liigendada alamülesanneteks, kusjuures tasandite arv ei ole piiratud. Standardseid kiirklahve on hõlpus meelde jätta, mis muudab rakenduse käsitsemise tõeliselt mugavaks ja kasutajasõbralikuks.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>KTimeTracker vous aide à suivre le temps que vous passez sur différentes tâches et projets.</p>
    <p>Il vous permet de calculer vos heures facturables et de créer des rapports par tâche et par jour.</p>
    <p>Grâce à KTimeTracker, vous pouvez organiser un projet en sous-tâches avec un nombre illimité de niveaux. Les raccourcis clavier et souris sont simples, de manière à ce que l'outil soit intuitif et confortable à utiliser.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>KTimeTracker axuda a facer un seguimento do tempo persoal que se dedica a distintas tarefas e proxectos.</p>
    <p>Resulta útil para facer un seguimento de horas de traballo e pode informar das horas rexistradas por tarefa e día.</p>
    <p>Con KTimeTracker pode  organizar un proxecto en tarefas aniñadas en niveis ilimitados. Os atallos de teclado e rato estándar son simples e fornecer unha experiencia cómoda e intuitiva.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>KTimeTracker membantu kamu melacak waktu personal yang dihabiskan pada berbagai tugas dan projekmu.</p>
    <p>Ini berguna untuk melacak jam terbang dan bisa melaporkan jam yang dicatat berdasarkan tugas dan harian.</p>
    <p>Dengan KTimeTracker,kamu bisa mengatur projek yang kacau sebagai subtugas dengan bersarang tanpa batas. Pintasan keyboard dan mouse standar yang sederhana dan membuat alat ini benar-benar nyaman dan intuitif untuk digunakan.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>KTimeTracker ti aiuta a tenere traccia del tempo personale speso in varie attività e progetti.</p>
    <p>È utile per tracciare ore fatturabili e fornire resoconti delle ore registrate per attività e giorno.</p>
    <p>Con KTimeTracker, puoi organizzare un progetto frammentato come sotto-attività con nidificazione illimitata. Le scorciatoie standard per tastiera e mouse sono semplici e rendono lo strumento davvero comodo e intuitivo da utilizzare.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>KTimeTracker는 다양한 작업과 프로젝트에 투자한 개인 시간을 추적합니다.</p>
    <p>작업별과 업무일별로 시간을 보고하고 공임 계산에 사용할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p>KTimeTracker를 사용하여 프로젝트를 다단계의 하위 작업으로 구성할 수 있습니다. 키보드 단축키와 마우스 동작을 사용하여 사용 편의성을 극대화합니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>KTimeTracker helpt u uw persoonlijk gebruikte tijd aan verschillende taken and projecten te volgen.</p>
    <p>Het is nuttig voor het volgen van in rekening te brengen uren en kan de vastgelegde uren rapporteren per taak en dag.</p>
    <p>Met KTimeTracker kunt u een in subtaken opgebroken project organiseren met onbeperkte nesting. De standaard sneltoetsen voor toetsenbord en muis zijn eenvoudig en maken het hulpmiddel echt comfortabel en intuïtief te gebruiken.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>KTimeTracker pomaga zliczyć osobisty czas poświęcony na różne zadania i projekty.</p>
    <p>Użyteczny do liczenia płatnych godzin oraz tworzenia sprawozdań z godzin wykorzystanych na dane zadanie i w danym dniu.</p>
    <p>Z KTimeTracker, można podzielić projekt na podzadania bez ograniczenia zagnieżdżeń. Podstawowe skróty klawiszowe i myszy są proste i czynią narzędzie przyjemne i intuicyjne w użyciu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O KTimeTracker ajuda-nos a acompanhar o seu tempo pessoal gasto em várias tarefas e projectos.</p>
    <p>É útil para gerir as horas para facturação e poderá relatar as horas registadas por tarefa e por dia.</p>
    <p>Com o KTimeTracker, poderá organizar um projecto decomposto em sub-tarefas com níveis ilimitados. Os atalhos-padrão do teclado e rato são simples e tornam a ferramenta realmente confortável e intuitiva para usar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Ktimerracker hjälper till att hålla reda på personlig tid spenderad på diverse aktiviteter och projekt.</p>
    <p>Det är användbart för att hålla reda på debiterbara timmar och kan rapportera timmar loggade enligt aktivitet och dag.</p>
    <p>Med Ktimetracker man kan organisera ett nerbrutet projekt som delaktiviteter med obegränsat djup. De vanliga tangentbords- och musgenvägarna är enkla och gör verktyget verkligt bekvämt och intuitivt att använda.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>KTimeTracker допоможе вам стежити за вашим особистим часом, який ви витрачаєте на виконання різноманітних завдань та проєктів.</p>
    <p>Ця програма корисна для стеження за обліком годин, вона може створювати звіти за даними, записаними для задачі або протягом дня.</p>
    <p>За допомогою KTimeTracker ви можете упорядкувати поділ проєкту на підзавдання (рівень вкладеності не обмежено). Стандартні клавіатурні скорочення та дії за допомогою миші є простими — вони забезпечують зручність та інтуїтивну зрозумілість принципів керування програмою.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxKTimeTracker helps you track your personal time spent on various tasks and projects.xx</p>
    <p>xxIt is useful for tracking billable hours and can report the hours logged by task and day.xx</p>
    <p>xxWith KTimeTracker, you can organize a broken-down project as subtasks with unlimited nesting. The standard keyboard and mouse shortcuts are simple and make the tool really comfortable and intuitive to use.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=ktimetracker</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="de">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="es">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="et">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="id">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="it">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">KTimetracker</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Ktimerracker</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxKTimeTrackerxx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-TW">KTimeTracker</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/ktimetracker/ktimetracker.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>ktimetracker</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release date="2019-12-21" version="5.0.1" />
    <release version="5.0.0" date="2019-12-19" />
    <release version="4.14.10" date="2015-07-01" />
    <release version="4.14.9" date="2015-06-02" />
    <release version="4.14.8" date="2015-05-12" />
    <release version="4.14.7" date="2015-04-15" />
  </releases>
</component>