<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <description>
    <p>
      KAppTemplate is an application to start development quickly using existing templates providing basic
      repeatedly written code and a proper structure.
    </p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Templates for C++, Ruby, Python and PHP</li>
      <li>Categories</li>
      <li>Templates for different build-systems and frameworks</li>
      <li>Templates especially for KDE-development (plugins for Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>It is easy to create new templates using space holders and a simple CMake-command</li>
      <li>Integrated into KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Svojstva:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Kategorije</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El KAppTemplate és una aplicació per a iniciar ràpidament el desenvolupament usant les plantilles existents que proporcionen codi bàsic escrit i una estructura adequada.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Plantilles per a C++, Ruby, Python i PHP</li>
      <li>Categories</li>
      <li>Plantilles per a sistemes de construcció i marcs de treball diferents</li>
      <li>Plantilles pel desenvolupament del KDE especialment (connectors pel Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>És fàcil crear plantilles noves usant espais variables i una ordre CMake senzilla</li>
      <li>S'integra en el KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>KAppTemplate és una aplicació per a iniciar ràpidament el desenvolupament utilitzant les plantilles existents que proporcionen codi bàsic escrit i una estructura adequada.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Plantilles per a C++, Ruby, Python i PHP</li>
      <li>Categories</li>
      <li>Plantilles per a sistemes de construcció i marcs de treball diferents</li>
      <li>Plantilles pel desenvolupament de KDE especialment (connectors per Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>És fàcil crear plantilles noves utilitzant espais variables i una ordre CMake senzilla</li>
      <li>S'integra en KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Vlastnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Šablony pro C++, Ruby, Python a PHP</li>
      <li>Kategorie</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Kategorier</li>
      <li>Integreret med KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>KAppTemplate ist ein Programm mit dem die Entwicklung schnell mit vorhandenen Vorlagen mit immer wieder zu schreibendem Quelltext und richtiger Struktur begonnen werden kann.</p>
    <p>Funktionen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Vorlagen für C++, Ruby, Python und PHP</li>
      <li>Kategorien</li>
      <li>Vorlagen für verschiedene Erstellungs-Systeme und Frameworks</li>
      <li>Spezielle Vorlagen für KDE-Entwicklung (Module für Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>Neue Vorlagen können leicht mit Platzhaltern und einfachen CMake-Befehlen erstellt werden</li>
      <li>Integriert in KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>KAppTemplate είναι μια εφαρμογή για να ξεκινήσετε την ανάπτυξη γρήγορα χρησιμοποιώντας τα υπάρχονταπρότυπα που παρέχουν βασικό επανειλημμένο γραμμένο κώδικα και μια κατάλληλη δομή.</p>
    <p>Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Πρότυπα για C++, Ruby, Python και PHP</li>
      <li>Κατηγορίες</li>
      <li>Πρότυπα για διαφορετικά συστήματα κατασκευής και πλαίσια εργασίας</li>
      <li>Πρότυπα ειδικά για το ανάπτυξη στο KDE (πρόσθετα για το πλάσμα, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>Είναι εύκολο να δημιουργήσετε νέα πρότυπα χρησιμοποιώντας space holders και μία απλή CMake-εντολή</li>
      <li>Ενσωμάτωση στο KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>KAppTemplate is an application to start development quickly using existing templates providing basic repeatedly written code and a proper structure.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Templates for C++, Ruby, Python and PHP</li>
      <li>Categories</li>
      <li>Templates for different build-systems and frameworks</li>
      <li>Templates especially for KDE-development (plugins for Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>It is easy to create new templates using space holders and a simple CMake-command</li>
      <li>Integrated into KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>KAppTemplate es una aplicación para comenzar a desarrollar rápidamente usando plantillas existentes que proporcionan un código básico que se suele escribir repetidamente y una estructura correcta.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Plantillas para C++, Ruby, Python y PHP</li>
      <li>Categorías</li>
      <li>Plantillas para distintos sistemas de compilación e infraestructuras</li>
      <li>Plantillas especiales para el desarrollo de KDE (complementos para Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>Resulta fácil crear nuevas plantillas usando parámetros de sustitución y órdenes CMake sencillas</li>
      <li>Integrado en KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>KAppTemplate on rakendus arendustegevuse kiireks käivitamiseks olemasolevate mallide alusel, mis pakuvad peamist korduvat koodi ja vajalikku struktuuri.</p>
    <p>Omadused:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>C++, Ruby, Pythoni ja PHP mallid</li>
      <li>Kategooriad</li>
      <li>Eri ehitussüsteemide ja raamistike mallid</li>
      <li>Spetsiaalselt KDE arendamiseks mõeldud mallid (Plasma, QtQuicki, KTextEditori, KRunneri, Akonadi pluginad)</li>
      <li>Hõlpus uute mallide loomine kohatäitjate ja lihtsa CMake'i käsu abil</li>
      <li>Lõimimine KDevelopiga</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>KAppTemplate dauden txantiloiak erabiliz garapena azkar hasteko aplikazio bat da. Txantiloiek behin eta berriz idazten den oinarrizko kodea eta egitura egokia hornitzen dute.</p>
    <p>Ezaugarriak:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>C++, Ruby, Python eta PHP-rako txantiloiak</li>
      <li>Kategoriak</li>
      <li>Eraikitze-sistema eta azpiegitura ezberdinetarako txantiloiak</li>
      <li>Txantiloiak bereziki KDE-garapenerako (Plasmarako pluginak, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>Erraza da txantiloi berriak sortzea leku-markak eta CMake-komando erraz bat erabiliz</li>
      <li>KDevelop-en integratua</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>KAppTemplate on sovellus kehityksen nopeaan aloittamiseen käyttämällä valmiita malleja, joissa on jo tehty jatkuvasti toistuvat perusasiat sekä kunnollinen rakenne.</p>
    <p>Ominaisuuksia:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Malleja C++:lle, Rubylle, Pythonille ja PHP:lle</li>
      <li>Luokat</li>
      <li>Malleja useille koostamisjärjestelmille ja sovelluskehyksille</li>
      <li>Malleja erityisesti KDE-kehitykseen (Plasma-, QtQuick-, KTextEditor-, KRunner- ja Akonadi-liitännäiset)</li>
      <li>Uusia malleja voi luoda helposti käyttämällä paikanvarauksia ja yksinkertaisia CMake-komentoja.</li>
      <li>KDevelop-integraatio</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>KAppTemplate est une application permettant de commencer rapidement de nouveaux développements en utilisant des modèles existants fournissant une structure appropriée et le code répétitif de base.</p>
    <p>Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Modèles pour C++, Ruby, Python et PHP</li>
      <li>Catégories</li>
      <li>Modèles pour différents systèmes de compilations et environnements</li>
      <li>Modèles dédiés au développement KDE (modules externes pour Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>Vous pouvez facilement créer de nouveaux modèles en utilisant des caractères spéciaux et une simple commande CMake</li>
      <li>Intégré à KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>KAppTemplate é unha aplicación para comezar calquera desenvolvemento rapidamente usando modelos existentes que fornecen código básico e repetitivo, así como unha estrutura axeitada.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Modelos para C++, Ruby, Python e PHP.</li>
      <li>Categorías</li>
      <li>Modelos para distintos sistemas de construción e infraestruturas.</li>
      <li>Modelos para o desenvolvemento de KDE (complementos para Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, e Akonadi).</li>
      <li>É doado crear novos modelos usando marcas e ordes sinxelas de CMake.</li>
      <li>Integrado con KDevelop.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>KAppTemplate adalah sebuah aplikasi untuk memulai pengembangan secara cepat menggunakan template yang ada menyediakan kode yang ditulis secara bertubi-tubi dan struktur yang layak.</p>
    <p>Fitur:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Template untuk C++, Ruby, Python dan PHP</li>
      <li>Kategori</li>
      <li>Template untuk kerangka-kerja dan bangun-sistem yang berbeda</li>
      <li>Template khususnya untuk pengembangan KDE (plugins untuk Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>Ini mudah untuk menciptakan template baru menggunakan space holders dan perintah CMake yang sederhana</li>
      <li>Terintegrasi ke dalam KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>KAppTemplate è un'applicazione per iniziare velocemente lo sviluppo con modelli preesistenti che forniscono del codice di base che viene spesso ripetuto in una struttura appropriata.</p>
    <p>Funzionalità:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Modelli per C++, Ruby, Python e PHP</li>
      <li>Categorie</li>
      <li>Modelli per diversi sistemi di generazione e infrastrutture</li>
      <li>Modelli speciali per lo sviluppo di KDE (estensioni di Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>È facile creare nuovi modelli con dei segnaposti e un semplice comando di CMake</li>
      <li>Integrato con KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>KAppTemplate은 반복적으로 작성되는 코드와 구조를 기반으로 한 템플릿을 제공하여 프로그램 개발을 빠르게 시작하도록 도와 줍니다.</p>
    <p>기능:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>C++, Ruby, 파이썬, PHP 템플릿</li>
      <li>분류</li>
      <li>다양한 빌드 시스템과 프레임워크 템플릿</li>
      <li>KDE 개발용 템플릿(Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi 플러그인)</li>
      <li>자리 비움자와 CMake 명령을 통한 새 템플릿 생성</li>
      <li>KDevelop 통합</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Ypatybės:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Kategorijos</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>KAppTemplate is een toepassing om ontwikkelen snel te laten starten met bestaande sjablonen die basis herhaald geschreven code en een juiste structuur leveren.</p>
    <p>Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Sjablonen voor C++, Ruby, Python en PHP</li>
      <li>Categorieën</li>
      <li>Sjablonen voor verschillende bouwsystemen en frameworks</li>
      <li>Sjablonen speciaal voor KDE-ontwikkeling (plug-ins voor Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>Het is gemakkelijk om nieuwe sjablonen te genereren met variabelen voor ruimten en een eenvoudig CMake-commando</li>
      <li>Geïntegreerd in KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>KAppTemplate er eit program som hjelper deg å raskt komma i gang med utvikling, basert på malar med hyppig brukt kode og ein skikkeleg struktur.</p>
    <p>Funksjonar:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Malar for C++, Ruby, Python og PHP</li>
      <li>Kategoriar</li>
      <li>Malar for forskjellige byggjesystem og rammeverk</li>
      <li>Malar laga for KDE-utvikling (programtillegg for Plasma, Qt Quick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>Det er lett å laga nye malar med plasshaldarar og ein enkel CMake-kommando</li>
      <li>Integrert i KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>KAppTemplate jest programem do szybkiego rozpoczynania programowania przy użyciu istniejących szablonów, który zapewnia podstawowy, często pisany kod i właściwą strukturę.</p>
    <p>Możliwości:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Szablony dla C++, Ruby, Python oraz PHP</li>
      <li>Kategorie</li>
      <li>Szablony dla różnych systemów budowania i szkieletów</li>
      <li>Szablony szczególnie dla programowania dla KDE (wtyczki dla Plazmy, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>Tworzenie nowych szablonów jest łatwe poprzez używanie pól wieloznacznych i prostych poleceń CMake</li>
      <li>Integracja z KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O KAppTemplate é uma aplicação para iniciar rapidamente o desenvolvimento, usando modelos existentes que oferecem algum do código escrito repetitivo e uma estrutura adequada.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Modelos para o C++, Ruby, Python e PHP</li>
      <li>Categorias</li>
      <li>Modelos para diferentes sistemas de compilação e plataformas</li>
      <li>Modelos especiais para o desenvolvimento no KDE ('plugins' para o Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>É fácil de criar modelos novos com blocos de substituição e um comando simples de CMake</li>
      <li>Integrado no KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>KAppTemplate é um aplicativo para iniciar rapidamente o desenvolvimento, usando modelos existentes que oferecem código escrito de forma repetitiva e uma estrutura adequada.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Modelos para C++, Ruby, Python e PHP</li>
      <li>Categorias</li>
      <li>Modelos para diferentes sistemas de compilação e plataformas</li>
      <li>Modelos especiais para o desenvolvimento no KDE (plugins para o Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>É fácil criar modelos novos usando blocos de substituição e um comando simples de CMake</li>
      <li>Integrado ao KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>KAppTemplate — программа, помогающая быстро начать разработку, отталкиваясь от готовых шаблонов приложений.</p>
    <p>Возможности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Шаблоны на языках C++, Ruby, Python и PHP</li>
      <li>Категории</li>
      <li>Шаблоны для различных систем сборки и платформ</li>
      <li>Специальные шаблоны для разработки с использованием технологий KDE (модули для Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>Легко создавать новые шаблоны</li>
      <li>Интеграция в KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>KAppTemplate je aplikácia na rýchle začatie vývoja pomocou existujúcich šablón poskytujúcich základný opakovateľné písaný kód a správnu štruktúru.</p>
    <p>Funkcie:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Šablóny pre C++, Ruby, Python a PHP</li>
      <li>Kategórie</li>
      <li>Šablóny pre rôzne systémy zostavenia a frameworky</li>
      <li>Šablóny špeciálne pre vývoj KDE (pluginy pre Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>Je jednoduché vytvoriť nové šablóny pomocou space holderov a jednoduchého príkazu CMake</li>
      <li>Integrované do KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>KAppTemplate je program za hiter začetek razvoja z uporabo obstoječih predlog, ki ponujajo osnovno, pogosto uporabljeno kodo in strukturo.</p>
    <p>Zmožnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Predloge za C++, Ruby, Python in PHP</li>
      <li>Kategorije</li>
      <li>Predloge za različne sisteme za izgradnjo in ogrodja</li>
      <li>Predloge, posebej za razvoj KDE (vtičniki za Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>Nove predloge lahko enostavno ustvarite s pomočjo vsebnikov in preprostega ukaza CMake</li>
      <li>Vgrajen v KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>К‑шаблон-програма је програм за брзо започињање развоја, преко постојећих шаблона који дају основни, често писани код и правилну структуру.</p>
    <p>Могућности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>шаблони за Ц++, руби, питон и ПХП</li>
      <li>категорије</li>
      <li>шаблони за различите системе градње и радне оквире</li>
      <li>лако стварање нових шаблона, преко местодржача и једноставне наредбе Ц‑мејка</li>
      <li>уклапање у К‑девелоп</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-Latn">
    <p>K‑šablon-programa je program za brzo započinjanje razvoja, preko postojećih šablona koji daju osnovni, često pisani kod i pravilnu strukturu.</p>
    <p>Mogućnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>šabloni za C++, Ruby, Python i PHP</li>
      <li>kategorije</li>
      <li>šabloni za različite sisteme gradnje i radne okvire</li>
      <li>lako stvaranje novih šablona, preko mestodržača i jednostavne naredbe CMakea</li>
      <li>uklapanje u KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-ijekavian">
    <p>К‑шаблон-програма је програм за брзо започињање развоја, преко постојећих шаблона који дају основни, често писани код и правилну структуру.</p>
    <p>Могућности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>шаблони за Ц++, руби, питон и ПХП</li>
      <li>категорије</li>
      <li>шаблони за различите системе градње и радне оквире</li>
      <li>лако стварање нових шаблона, преко местодржача и једноставне наредбе Ц‑мејка</li>
      <li>уклапање у К‑девелоп</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">
    <p>K‑šablon-programa je program za brzo započinjanje razvoja, preko postojećih šablona koji daju osnovni, često pisani kod i pravilnu strukturu.</p>
    <p>Mogućnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>šabloni za C++, Ruby, Python i PHP</li>
      <li>kategorije</li>
      <li>šabloni za različite sisteme gradnje i radne okvire</li>
      <li>lako stvaranje novih šablona, preko mestodržača i jednostavne naredbe CMakea</li>
      <li>uklapanje u KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>KDE-mallgenerator är ett program för att snabbt påbörja utveckling med befintliga mallar som tillhandahåller grundläggande kod som skrivs upprepade gånger och en lämplig struktur.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Mallar för C++, Ruby, Python och PHP</li>
      <li>Kategorier</li>
      <li>Mallar för olika byggsystem och ramverk</li>
      <li>Mallar särskilt för KDE-utveckling (insticksprogram för Plasma, QtQuick, Ktexteditor, Krunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>Det är enkelt att skapa nya mallar genom att använda platsmarkörer och ett enkelt CMake-kommando</li>
      <li>Integrerad med KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>KAppTemplate mevcut şablonları kullanarak tekrarlanan kodları ve uygun yapıyı sağlayan ve hızlıca geliştirmeye başlayabileceğiniz bir araçtır.</p>
    <p>Özellikler:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>C++, Ruby, Python ve PHP için şablonlar</li>
      <li>Kategoriler</li>
      <li>Farklı yapı sistemleri ve kod kitaplıkları için şablonlar</li>
      <li>KDE geliştirmesi için şablonlar (Plasma, KOffice, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi için eklentiler)</li>
      <li>Yer tutucular ve basit CMake komutları kullanarak yeni şablonlar oluşturmak çok kolaydır</li>
      <li>KDevelop ile tümleşik çalışır</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>KAppTemplate — програма для пришвидшення початкового етапу розробки на основі наявних шаблонів, у яких міститься стандартний код та відповідна структура проєкту.</p>
    <p>Можливості:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Шаблони для C++, Ruby, Python та PHP.</li>
      <li>Категорії.</li>
      <li>Шаблони для різних систем збирання та комплексів.</li>
      <li>Особливі шаблони для розробників KDE (додатки до Плазми, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)</li>
      <li>Простота створення нових шаблонів на основі заповнювачів та простої команди CMake.</li>
      <li>Інтеграція з KDevelop.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxKAppTemplate is an application to start development quickly using existing templates providing basic repeatedly written code and a proper structure.xx</p>
    <p>xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>xxTemplates for C++, Ruby, Python and PHPxx</li>
      <li>xxCategoriesxx</li>
      <li>xxTemplates for different build-systems and frameworksxx</li>
      <li>xxTemplates especially for KDE-development (plugins for Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi)xx</li>
      <li>xxIt is easy to create new templates using space holders and a simple CMake-commandxx</li>
      <li>xxIntegrated into KDevelopxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>KAppTemplate 是使用已有模板开始快速开发的应用程序，它提供了可重用的代码和良好的结构。</p>
    <p>功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>C++，Ruby，Python 和 PHP 的模板</li>
      <li>分类</li>
      <li>不同构建系统和框架的模板</li>
      <li>专为 KDE 开发使用的模板 (Plasma 插件，QtOffice，KTextEditor，KRunner，Akonadi)</li>
      <li>创建新模板非常简单，只需使用占位符和简单的 CMake 命令</li>
      <li>集成到 KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-TW">
    <p>KAppTemplate 是一套讓您用現有的樣本快速開發的應用程式。樣本裡已包括基本常用的程式碼，以及適當的程式結構。</p>
    <p>功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>C++, Ruby, Python 與 PHP 的樣本</li>
      <li>類別</li>
      <li>不同編譯系統與框架的樣本</li>
      <li>特別是 KDE 開發使用的樣本（如 Plasma, QtQuick, KTextEditor, KRunner, Akonadi 等）</li>
      <li>只要用空間符與簡單的 CMake 指令即可建立新的樣本</li>
      <li>整合進 KDevelop</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.kapptemplate</pkgname>
  <icon width="64" height="64" type="cached">kapptemplate.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" height="128" type="cached">kapptemplate.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.kapptemplate.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="bs">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="ca">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="cs">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="da">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="de">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="el">Πρότυπο KApp</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="es">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="et">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="eu">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="fi">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="fr">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="gl">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="id">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="it">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="ko">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="lt">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="nl">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="nn">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="pl">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="pt">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="ru">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="sk">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="sl">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="sr">К‑шаблон-програма</name>
  <name lang="sr-Latn">K‑šablon-programa</name>
  <name lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑шаблон-програма</name>
  <name lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">K‑šablon-programa</name>
  <name lang="sv">Kapptemplate</name>
  <name lang="tr">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="uk">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxKAppTemplatexx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">KAppTemplate</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">KAppTemplate</name>
  <summary>App Code Template Generator</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Generador de plantilles de codi d'aplicació</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Generador de plantilles de codi d'aplicació</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Generátor šablon App Code</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Vorlagengenerator für Programmcode</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Γεννήτρια προτύπων κώδικα εφαρμογών</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">App Code Template Generator</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Generador de plantillas de código de aplicaciones</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Rakenduse koodi malli generaator</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Aplikazio kodearen txantiloi sortzailea</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Sovelluskoodimallin luontiohjelma</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Générateur de modèles de code d'application</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Xerador de modelos de código de aplicativo</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Penghasil Template Kode Apl</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Generatore di modelli di applicazioni</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">앱 코드 템플릿 생성기</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Sjabloongenerator van App Code</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Malgenerator for programkode</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Twórca szablonów kodu aplikacji</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Gerador de Modelos de Código de Aplicações</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Gerador de modelo de código de aplicativo</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Генератор шаблонов приложений</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Generátor šablón aplikačného kódu</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Generator predlog kode</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Generering av programkodsmallar</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Uygulama Kod Şablonu Oluşturucu</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Генератор шаблонів коду програм</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxApp Code Template Generatorxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">应用代码模板生成器</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-TW">App 程式碼範本產生器</summary>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kapptemplate</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kapptemplate</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kapptemplate/kapptemplate.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>Development</category>
  </categories>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kapptemplate.desktop</launchable>
  <provides>
    <binary>kapptemplate</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.1.22043" date="2022-07-07" />
    <release version="0.1.22042" date="2022-06-09" />
    <release version="0.1.22041" date="2022-05-12" />
    <release version="0.1.22040" date="2022-04-21" />
  </releases>
</component>