<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.kteatime</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kteatime.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" type="cached" height="64">kteatime.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.kteatime.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="ar">وقت شايك</name>
  <name lang="bg">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="bs">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="ca">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="cs">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="da">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="de">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="el">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="es">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="et">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="eu">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="fi">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="fr">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="gl">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="hu">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="ia">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="id">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="it">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="ko">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="lt">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="nl">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="nn">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="pl">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="pt">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="ro">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="ru">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="sk">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="sl">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="sr">К‑чајанка</name>
  <name lang="sr-Latn">K‑čajanka</name>
  <name lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑чајанка</name>
  <name lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">K‑čajanka</name>
  <name lang="sv">Tekokaren</name>
  <name lang="tr">K Çay Zamanı</name>
  <name lang="uk">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxKTeaTimexx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">KTeaTime</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">KTeaTime</name>
  <summary>Tea Cooker</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">منقّع شاي</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Приготвяне на чай</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Kuhač čaja</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">El cuiner de te</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">El cuiner de te</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Vařič čaje</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Tekoger</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Teekocher</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Βραστήρας τσαγιού</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Tea Cooker</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Calentador de té</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Teekann</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Te-eltzea</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Teenkeitin</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Tea Cooker</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Quece-tés</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Teafőző</summary>
  <summary lang="ia">Tea Cooker (Cocinero de The)</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Pemasak Teh</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Teiera</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">차 요리 도구</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Arbatos virėjas</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Theezetter</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Tekokar</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Zaparzanie herbaty</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Preparação de Chás</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Hora do chá</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Ceainic</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Таймер для заваривания чая</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Varič čaju</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Kuhalnik čaja</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Чајник</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-Latn">Čajnik</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-ijekavian">Чајник</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Čajnik</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Tekokare</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Çaycı</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Програма для заварювання чаю</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxTea Cookerxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">煮茶器</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-TW">煮茶器</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KTeaTime is a handy timer for steeping tea. No longer will you have to guess at how long it takes for your tea to be ready. Simply select the type of tea you have, and it will alert you when the tea is ready to drink.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>«وقت شايك» هو مؤقّت خفيف لنقع الشّاي. لم يعد عليك تخمين كم سيأخذ الشّاي حتّى يجهز. اختر نوع الشّاي الذي تريد، وسينبّهك عندما يكون الشّاي جاهزًا للشّرب.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>KTeaTime е удобен часовник за варене на чай. Няма нужда вече да отгатвате колко време трябва, за да е готов чаят ви. Просто изберете вида чай и програмата ще ви уведоми, когато чаят е готов за пиене.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El KTeaTime és un temporitzador còmode per a fer el te. Ja no haureu d'endevinar quan falta perquè el vostre te estigui llest. Simplement seleccioneu el tipus de te que voleu, i l'aplicació us avisarà quan està llest.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>KTeaTime és un temporitzador còmode per a fer el te. Ja no haureu d'endevinar quan falta perquè el vostre te estiga llest. Simplement seleccioneu el tipus de te que voleu, i l'aplicació vos avisarà quan està llest.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>KTeaTime je užitečný pomocník pro louhování čaje. Už nemusíte hádat za jak dlouho bude váš čaj připraven. Jednoduše vyberte typ čaje a vyčkejte na upozornění, že je čaj hotov.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>KTeaTime er en handy timer til tetrækning. Så behøver du ikker længere at gætte hvor lang tid det tager inden din te er klar. Vælg den type te du har og den giver dig besked når teen er klar til at drikke.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>KTeaTime ist ein praktischer Zeitmesser für ziehenden Tee. Sie brauchen nicht länger schätzen, wie lange es dauert, bis Ihr Tee fertig ist. Wählen Sie einfach die Teesorte, die Sie haben, und Sie werden informiert, sobald Ihr Tee trinkfertig ist.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το KTeaTime είναι ένα πρακτικό χρονόμετρο για το τσάι σας. Δε χρειάζεται πλέον να μαντεύετε πόσο θα χρόνο χρειαστεί το τσάι σας για να ετοιμαστεί. Απλά επιλέξτε τον τύπο τσαγιού που έχετε και αυτό θα σας ειδοποιήσει όταν το τσάι σας είναι έτοιμο να το πιείτε. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>KTeaTime is a handy timer for steeping tea. No longer will you have to guess at how long it takes for your tea to be ready. Simply select the type of tea you have, and it will alert you when the tea is ready to drink.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>KTeaTime es un útil temporizador para tomar té. Usted nunca más tendrá que adivinar cuanto tiempo tarda en estar listo el té. Sencillamente, seleccione el tipo de té del que disponga y le avisará cuando esté listo para beber.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>KTeaTime on taimer tee tõmbamise aja mõõtmiseks. Enam ei pea sa arvama, kui kaua võtab aega tee valmimine. Vali lihtsalt tee tüüp ning taimer annab sulle märku, kui tee on joomiseks valmis.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>KTeaTime tea prestatzeko denboragailu erabilgarri bat da. Aurrerantzean ez duzu igarri beharko zure tea prest egoteko zenbat denbora behar den. Zure te mota aukeratu eta jakinaraziko dizu tea edateko prest dagoenean.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>KTeaTime on kätevä kello teen hautumisajan mittaamiseksi. Enää ei tarvitse arvata milloin tee on valmis. Valitse vain teelaji ja KTeaTime hälyttää, kun tee on valmista juotavaksi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>KTeaTime est un chronomètre pratique pour mesurer le temps d'infusion de votre thé. Vous n'aurez plus besoin d'estimer la durée nécessaire à la préparation de votre thé à vue de nez. Sélectionnez simplement le type de thé que vous souhaitez préparer et vous serez alerté lorsque votre boisson sera prête.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>KTeaTime é un temporizador útil para deixar té en infusión. Xa non terás que adiviñar o tempo que lle falta ao teu té para estar listo. Só tes que seleccionar o tipo de té, e KTeaTime informarate cando o té estea listo para tomar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A KTeaTime egy kezes időzítő teafőzéshez. Nem kell többé azon gondolkoznia, mikor lesz kész a teája: egyszerűen válassza ki a tea típusát, és a KTeaTime értesíti, mikor ihatja a teáját.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ia">
    <p>KTeaTimer es un commode horologio per facer infusion de the. Tu non debera plus conjecturar quanto tempore necessita tu the per esser preste. Simplemente tu selige le typo de the que tu ha, e illo te avisara quando le the es preste de biber.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>KTeaTime adalah penghitung waktu praktis untuk seduhan teh. Kamu tidak perlu lagi menebak berapa lama tehmu siap. Cukup pilih jenis teh yang kamu miliki, dan itu akan mengingatkan kamu ketika teh siap untuk diminum.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>KTeaTime è un comodo timer per preparare il tè. Non è più necessario indovinare quanto tempo ci vuole prima che il tè sia pronto. Seleziona il tipo di tè che desideri e il programma ti avviserà quanto è pronto da bere.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>KTeaTime은 차를 끓일 때 사용할 수 있는 타이머입니다. 차가 다 우러날 때까지 시간을 기억하지 않아도 됩니다. 끓일 차 종류를 선택한 다음 다 우러났을 때 알려 줍니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>KTeaTime is een handige tijdklok voor het zetten van thee. U hoeft niet langer te gokken wanneer uw thee sterk genoeg is. Selecteer de theesoort en een waarschuwing verschijnt wanneer de thee klaar is om opgedronken te worden.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>KTeaTime er ein nyttig tidtakar når du skal la te trekkja. No treng du ikkje lenger gjetta kor lang tid det tar før teen er klar. Berre vel kva type te du har, og du vert varsla når teen er ferdigtrekt.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>KTeaTime jest poręcznym czasomierzem do zaparzania herbaty. Nigdy więcej nie będziesz musiał zgadywać ile jeszcze czasu potrzebuje twoja herbata. Po prostu wybierz rodzaj herbaty, którą posiadasz, a program powiadomi cię kiedy kiedy będzie gotowa do picia.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O KTeaTime é um cronómetro útil para preparar chás. Nunca mais terá de adivinhar quanto tempo leva para o seu chá estar pronto. Basta seleccionar o tipo de chá que tem, para que ele o alerte de quando o chá está pronto para ser bebido.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>KTeaTime é um temporizador prático para preparar um chá. Já não terá mais que adivinhar quanto tempo leva para que o seu chá fique pronto. Basta escolher o tipo de chá que deseja, e ele o alertará quando estiver pronto para beber.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>KTeaTime — удобный таймер для заваривания чая. Избавляет вас от необходимости запоминать, сколько минут готовится каждый сорт чая. Просто выберите сорт чая, — и программа сообщит, когда чай будет готов.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>KTeaTime je užitočný časovač pre máčanie čaju. Už nikdy nebudete musieť hádať, koľko trvá pripravenie vášho čaju. Jednoducho vyberte typ vášho čaju a on vás upozorní, kedy bude pripravený na pitie.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>KTeaTime je priročen časomer za kuhanje čaja. Nič več vam ne bo treba ugibati, kako dolgo bo trajalo, preden bo vaš čaj gotov. Enostavno izberite vrsto čaja, ki ga imate, in opozorjeni boste, ko bo čaj pripravljen za pitje.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>К‑чајанка је згодан одбројавач за преливање чаја. Више не морате да памтите колико треба да се чај припреми. Само изаберите врсту чаја, и бићете обавештени кад буде спреман за испијање.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-Latn">
    <p>K‑čajanka je zgodan odbrojavač za prelivanje čaja. Više ne morate da pamtite koliko treba da se čaj pripremi. Samo izaberite vrstu čaja, i bićete obavešteni kad bude spreman za ispijanje.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-ijekavian">
    <p>К‑чајанка је згодан одбројавач за преливање чаја. Више не морате да памтите колико треба да се чај припреми. Само изаберите врсту чаја, и бићете обавештени кад буде спреман за испијање.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">
    <p>K‑čajanka je zgodan odbrojavač za prelivanje čaja. Više ne morate da pamtite koliko treba da se čaj pripremi. Samo izaberite vrstu čaja, i bićete obavešteni kad bude spreman za ispijanje.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Tekokaren är ett praktiskt tidur för att brygga te. Du behöver inte längre gissa hur länge det tar innan ditt te är klart. Välj helt enkelt vilken typ av te du använder, och tekokaren talar om för dig när det är klart att dricka.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>K Çay Zamanı, çay demlemek için bir araçtır. Artık çayınızın ne kadar zaman sonra hazır olacağını tahmin etmenize gerek yok. Basitçe çayınızı seçin ve içmeye hazır olduğunda KTeaTime sizi uyarsın.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>KTeaTime — це зручний таймер для заварювання чаю. Вам більше не доведеться вгадувати час, коли ваш чай буде готовим. Просто виберіть сорт чаю, і програма повідомить вам, коли чай можна буде пити.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxKTeaTime is a handy timer for steeping tea. No longer will you have to guess at how long it takes for your tea to be ready. Simply select the type of tea you have, and it will alert you when the tea is ready to drink.xx</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>KTeaTime 是一个实用的煮茶定时器。您再也不用猜何时茶已完成。只要选择您拥有的茶的类型，它将会提醒您何时茶可以享用。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-TW">
    <p>KTeaTime 是煮茶用的計時器。您不再需要猜測您的茶要煮或泡多久。只要選擇茶的種類，時間到它就會提醒你。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kteatime</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kteatime</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kteatime&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kteatime/kteatime.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kteatime</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="22.04.3" date="2022-07-07" />
    <release date="2022-06-09" version="22.04.2" />
    <release version="22.04.1" date="2022-05-12" />
    <release version="22.04.0" date="2022-04-21" />
  </releases>
</component>