<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.kspaceduel</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kspaceduel.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">kspaceduel.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">kspaceduel.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.kspaceduel.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="ar">لعبة مبارزة الفضاء</name>
  <name lang="ca">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="cs">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="da">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="de">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="el">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="es">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="et">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="eu">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="fi">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="fr">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="gl">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="hi">के-स्पेसड्यूएल</name>
  <name lang="hu">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="id">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="it">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="ko">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="nl">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="nn">Romduell</name>
  <name lang="pl">KosmicznyPojedynek</name>
  <name lang="pt">Duelo Espacial</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="ro">Duel spațial</name>
  <name lang="ru">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="sk">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="sl">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="sr">К‑свемирски-двобој</name>
  <name lang="sr-Latn">K‑svemirski-dvoboj</name>
  <name lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑свемирски-двобој</name>
  <name lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">K‑svemirski-dvoboj</name>
  <name lang="sv">Rymdduell</name>
  <name lang="tr">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="uk">Космічна дуель</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxKSpaceDuelxx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">KSpaceDuel</name>
  <summary>Space Arcade Game</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">لعبة ممرات الفضاء</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Joc arcade de l'espai</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Joc arcade de l'espai</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Vesmírná arkádová hra</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Rum arkadespil</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Weltraum-Spiel</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Διαστημικό παιχνίδι arcade</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Space Arcade Game</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Juego recreativo espacial</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Arkaadmäng kosmoses</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Espazioko arkupeko jokoa</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Avaruusarkadipeli</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Jeu d'arcade dans l'espace</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Xogo arcade espacial</summary>
  <summary lang="hi">स्पेस आर्केड खेल</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Kétszemélyes űrhajós játék</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Permainan Arkade Ruang Angkasa</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Gioco spaziale arcade</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">우주 아케이드 게임</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Ruimte-arcadespel</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Arkade-romspel</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Gra zręcznościowa w kosmosie</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Jogo Espacial de Arcada</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Jogo de Arcade espacial</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Joc de aventuri spațiale</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Космическая аркадная игра</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Vesmírna arkádová hra</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Vesoljska arkadna igra</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Свемирска аркадна игра</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-Latn">Svemirska arkadna igra</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-ijekavian">Свемирска аркадна игра</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Svemirska arkadna igra</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Spelhallsspel</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Uzay Macera Oyunu</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Космічна аркадна гра — дуель</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxSpace Arcade Gamexx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">空间型街机游戏</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      In KSpaceDuel each of two possible players control a satellite spaceship orbiting the sun.
      As the game progresses players have to eliminate the opponent's spacecraft with bullets or mines.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>في مبارزة الفضاء ، يتحكم كل اثنين من اللاعبين المحتملين في مركبة فضائية تابعة للأقمار الصناعية تدور حول الشمس. مع تقدم اللعبة ، يتعين على اللاعبين القضاء على المركبة الفضائية للخصم بالرصاص أو الألغام.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>En el KSpaceDuel cada un dels dos possibles jugadors controla una nau espacial satèl·lit que orbita el Sol. A mesura que el joc avança, els jugadors han d'eliminar les naus espacials del contrari amb bales o mines.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>En KSpaceDuel cada un dels dos possibles jugadors controla una nau espacial satèl·lit que orbita el Sol. A mesura que el joc avança, els jugadors han d'eliminar les naus espacials del contrari amb bales o mines.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>I KSpaceDuel styrer hver af op til to spillere et satellitrumskib  som er i kredsløb om solen. Som spillet skrider frem skal spillerne eliminere  modstanderens rumskib med kugler eller miner.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>In KSpaceDuel steuert jeder der maximal zwei Spieler ein Satellitenraumschiff auf einer Umlaufbahn um die Sonne. Im Spiel müssen die Spieler das gegnerische Raumschiff mit Kanonen oder Minen zerstören, um die Runde zu gewinnen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Στο KSpaceDuel κάθε παίκτης ελέγχει ένα διατημόπλοιο σε τροχιά γύρω από τον ήλιο. Καθώς το παιχνίδι εξελίσσεται οι παίκτες πρέπει να εξαλείψουν το σκάφος του αντιπάλου με σφαίρες ή νάρκες.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>In KSpaceDuel each of two possible players control a satellite spaceship orbiting the sun. As the game progresses players have to eliminate the opponent's spacecraft with bullets or mines.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>En KSpaceDuel, cada uno de los dos posibles jugadores controla una nave espacial en órbita alrededor del Sol. A medida que el juego avanza, los jugadores deben eliminar la nave espacial del oponente con disparos o con minas.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>KSpaceDuel annab kahe mängija käsutusse ümber päikese tiirlevad kosmoselaevad. Mängu siht on hävitada vastase kosmoselaev mürskude või miinidega.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>KSpaceDuel-en, izan daitezkeen bi jokalarietako bakoitzak eguzkia orbitatzen duen espazio-ontzi satelite bat kontrolatzen du. Jokoa aurrera doan heinean, jokalariek aurkariaren espazio-ontzia deuseztatu behar dute.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>KSpaceDuelissa kukin kahdesta mahdollisesta pelaajasta ohjaa aurinkoa kiertävää avaruusalusta. Pelin edetessä pelaajan täytyy tuhota vastustajan alukset luodein tai miinoin.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Dans KSpaceDuel chaque joueur contrôle un vaisseau spatial satellite en orbite autour du soleil. Au cours du jeu, les joueurs doivent éliminer le vaisseau spatial de leur adversaire en utilisant des balles ou des mines.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>En KSpaceDuel cada un dos dous xogadores posíbeis controla unha nave espacial satélite que orbita arredor do Sol. Durante unha partida, os xogadores teñen que eliminar a nave espacial do opoñente con balas ou minas.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hi">
    <p>के-स्पेसड्यूएल में दो संभावित खिलाड़ियों में से प्रत्येक सूर्य की परिक्रमा करने वाले उपग्रह अंतरिक्ष यान को नियंत्रित करता है। जैसे-जैसे खेल आगे बढ़ता है खिलाड़ियों को प्रतिद्वंद्वी के अंतरिक्ष यान को गोलियों या खानों के बम से खत्म करना होता है।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A KSpaceDuelben mindkét játékos egy, a nap körül keringő műholdat irányít. A játék során a feleknek lövedékekkel és aknákkal kell megsemmisíteniük az ellenfél űrjárművét.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Di KSpaceDuel masing-masing dari dua pemain yang mungkin mengendalikan pesawat-ruang-angkasa satelit yang mengorbit matahari. Ketika permainan berlangsung, pemain harus menyingkirkan pesawat ruang angkasa lawan dengan peluru atau ranjau.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>In KSpaceDuel ciascun giocatore controlla una nave spaziale che orbita intorno al Sole. All'avanzare della partita, i giocatori devono eliminare la navicella dell'avversario con missili o mine.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>KSpaceDuel에서 두 플레이어는 태양 주위를 도는 인공 위성 우주선을 제어합니다. 게임이 진행되는 동안 두 플레이어는 서로의 우주선을 지뢰나 총알로 파괴해야 합니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>In KSpaceDuel besturen elk van de twee mogelijke spelers een satelliet ruimteschip dat om de zon draait. Als het spel voortgaat moeten spelers het ruimteschip van de tegenstander met kogels of mijnen vernietigen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>I Romduell styrer to spelarar kvart sitt romskip i bane rundt sola. Spelarane skal øydeleggje motstandaren sitt romskip med kuler eller miner.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>W KosmicznymPojedynku każdy z dwóch graczy steruje orbitalnym statkiem kosmicznym krążącym wokół słońca. W trakcie gry, gracze muszą pozbyć się statku przeciwnika przy użyciu pocisków lub min.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>No KSpaceDuel, cada um dos dois possíveis jogadores controlam uma nave espacial que orbita em torno do Sol. À medida que o jogo evolui, os jogadores têm de eliminar a nave espacial do adversário com balas ou minas.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>No KSpaceDuel, cada um dos dois possíveis jogadores controlam uma nave espacial que orbita em torno do Sol. À medida que o jogo evolui, os jogadores devem eliminar a nave espacial do adversário com balas ou minas.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>În Duel Spațial, fiecare dintre cei doi posibili jucători controlează o navă spațială satelit ce orbitează Soarele. Pe măsură ce jocul progresează, jucătorii trebuie să elimine nava spațială a oponentului folosind gloanțe și mine.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>В KSpaceDuel каждый из двух возможных игроков управляет космическим кораблем-спутником, вращающимся вокруг Солнца. Цель игры состоит в уничтожении космического корабля противника пулями или минами.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>V hre KSpaceDuel dvaja hráči ovládajú vesmírnu loď obiehajúcu okolo Slnka. Hráči majú eliminovať protivníkovu kozmickú loď strelami alebo mínami.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Vsak izmed dveh igralcev v KSpaceDuelu nadzira satelit, ki kroži okrog sonca. Cilj igre je, da nasprotnikovo ladjo uničite s kroglami ali minami.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>У К‑свемирском-двобоју сваки од два могућа играча управља сателитским свемирским бродом у орбити сунца. Како партија одмиче, играчи покушавају да униште противнички свемирски брод мецима или минама.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-Latn">
    <p>U K‑svemirskom-dvoboju svaki od dva moguća igrača upravlja satelitskim svemirskim brodom u orbiti sunca. Kako partija odmiče, igrači pokušavaju da unište protivnički svemirski brod mecima ili minama.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-ijekavian">
    <p>У К‑свемирском-двобоју сваки од два могућа играча управља сателитским свемирским бродом у орбити сунца. Како партија одмиче, играчи покушавају да униште противнички свемирски брод мецима или минама.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">
    <p>U K‑svemirskom-dvoboju svaki od dva moguća igrača upravlja satelitskim svemirskim brodom u orbiti sunca. Kako partija odmiče, igrači pokušavaju da unište protivnički svemirski brod mecima ili minama.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>I Rymdduell styr var och en av två möjliga spelare ett rymdskepp som kretsar kring solen. Under spelets gång måste spelarna eliminera motståndarens rymdskepp med kulor eller minor.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>KSpaceDuel'de olası iki oyuncu güneş etrafında dönen bir uydu uzay gemisini denetler. Oyun ilerledikçe oyuncular, mermi veya mayın ile rakibin uzay aracını yenmek için savaşırlar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>У «Космічній дуелі» кожен з двох можливих гравців керує космічним супутником, який обертається навколо сонця. Протягом гри гравці мають намагатися знищити супутник суперника кулями та мінами.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxIn KSpaceDuel each of two possible players control a satellite spaceship orbiting the sun. As the game progresses players have to eliminate the opponent's spacecraft with bullets or mines.xx</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>在 KSpaceDuel 中，每两名玩家控制太阳轨道上的卫星飞船。随着游戏的推进，玩家必须使用子弹或地雷消灭对手的太空飞船。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://kde.org/applications/games/org.kde.kspaceduel</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kspaceduel</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kspaceduel</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kspaceduel&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kspaceduel/kspaceduel.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kspaceduel</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="2.1.22043" date="2022-07-07" />
    <release version="2.1.22042" date="2022-06-09" />
    <release version="2.1.22041" date="2022-05-12" />
    <release date="2022-04-21" version="2.1.22040" />
  </releases>
</component>