<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.kmines</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kmines.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" height="64" type="cached">kmines.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" height="128" type="cached">kmines.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.kmines.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KMines</name>
  <name lang="ar">الألغام ك</name>
  <name lang="ca">KMines</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">KMines</name>
  <name lang="cs">KMines</name>
  <name lang="da">KMines</name>
  <name lang="de">KMines</name>
  <name lang="el">KMines</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">KMines</name>
  <name lang="es">KMines</name>
  <name lang="et">KMines</name>
  <name lang="eu">KMines</name>
  <name lang="fi">KMines</name>
  <name lang="fr">KMines</name>
  <name lang="gl">KMines</name>
  <name lang="hu">KMines</name>
  <name lang="id">KMines</name>
  <name lang="is">KMines</name>
  <name lang="it">KMines</name>
  <name lang="ko">KMines</name>
  <name lang="nl">KMines</name>
  <name lang="nn">KMinesveipar</name>
  <name lang="pl">KMiny</name>
  <name lang="pt">Campo Minado</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">KMines</name>
  <name lang="ro">KMine</name>
  <name lang="ru">KMines</name>
  <name lang="sk">KMines</name>
  <name lang="sl">KMines</name>
  <name lang="sr">К‑мине</name>
  <name lang="sr-Latn">K‑mine</name>
  <name lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑мине</name>
  <name lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">K‑mine</name>
  <name lang="sv">Minröjaren</name>
  <name lang="tr">KMines</name>
  <name lang="uk">KMines</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxKMinesxx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">KMines</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">KMines</name>
  <summary>Minesweeper-like Game</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">لعبة مثل كاسحة الألغام</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Joc a l'estil del dragamines</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Joc a l'estil del dragamines</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Hra s minovým polem</summary>
  <summary lang="de">„Minesweeper“-Spiel</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Παιχνίδι παρόμοιο με το Ναρκαλιευτή</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Minesweeper-like Game</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Juego similar al Buscaminas</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Minesweeperi moodi mäng</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Mina bilatzailearen antzeko jokoa</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Miinaharava-tyylinen peli</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Jeu dans le style du démineur</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Xogo como o busca minas</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Aknakeresőszerű játék</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Permainan Seperti Minesweeper</summary>
  <summary lang="is">KMines er hefðbundinn sprengjuleitarleikur sem líkist Minesweeper</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Gioco simile a Mine</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">지뢰찾기 게임</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Mijnenvegerachtig spel</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Minesveipar-liknande spel</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Gra typu saper</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Jogo semelhante ao Minesweeper</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Jogo semelhante ao Campo Minado</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Un joc ca Detectorul de mine</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Игра в сапёра</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Hra typu hľadanie mín</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Igra podobna Minolovcu</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Игра налик на Миноловац</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-Latn">Igra nalik na Minolovac</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-ijekavian">Игра налик на Миноловац</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Igra nalik na Minolovac</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Minröjarliknande spel</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Mayın Tarlası benzeri Oyun</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Гра у сапера</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxMinesweeper-like Gamexx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">扫雷游戏</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KMines is a classic Minesweeper game. The idea is to uncover all the squares without blowing up any mines. When a mine is blown up, the game is over.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>الألغام ك هي لعبة كاسحة ألغام كلاسيكية. الفكرة هي الكشف عن جميع المربعات دون تفجير أي ألغام. عندما يتم تفجير لغم ، تنتهي اللعبة.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El KMines és un joc clàssic de dragamines. La idea és descobrir tots els quadrats sense que exploti cap mina. Quan una mina explota, el joc acaba.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>KMines és un joc clàssic de dragamines. La idea és descobrir tots els quadrats sense que explote cap mina. Quan una mina explota, el joc acaba.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>KMines je klasická hra Miny. Úkolem je odkrýt všechny čtverce aniž byste odpálili jakoukoliv minu. Pokud mina vybuchne, hra skončila.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>KMines ist ein klassische Minesweeper-Spiel. Ziel ist es, alle leeren Felder aufzudecken, ohne dass eine Mine explodiert. Das Spiel ist beendet, wenn eine Mine explodiert.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το KMines είναι ένα κλασικό παιχνίδι Ναρκαλιευτής. Η ιδέα είναι να αποκαλυφθούν όλα τα τετράγωνα χωρίς να εκραγεί καμία νάρκη. Όταν μία νάρκη εκρήγνυται, το παιχνίδι τελειώνει.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>KMines is a classic Minesweeper game. The idea is to uncover all the squares without blowing up any mines. When a mine is blown up, the game is over.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>KMines es el clásico juego de Buscaminas. El objetivo consiste en descubrir todos los cuadrados sin hacer estallar las minas. Si una mina estalla, el juego acaba.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>KMines on klassikaline Minesweeperi mäng. Selle siht on avada kõik ruudud, ilma ühelgi miinil õhku lendamata. Kui miin plahvatab, on mäng läbi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>KMines mina bilatzaile joko klasikoa da. Ideia nagusia, minak eztandarik egin gabe lauki guztiak estalgabetzea da. Mina batek eztanda egiten badu, jokoa amaitu da.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>KMines on perinteinen miinaharavapeli. Tavoitteena on paljastaa kaikki ruudut räjäyttämättä miinoja. Miinan räjähdettyä peli loppuu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>KMines est un jeu dans le style du démineur. L'objectif est de révéler tous les carrés sans faire exploser la moindre mine. Lorsqu'une mine explose, la partie est terminée.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>KMines é un xogo clásico de buscaminas. A idea é descubrir todos os cadrados sen estourar ningunha mina. Cando unha mina estoura acaba a partida.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A KMines egy klasszikus aknakereső játék. A cél az összes mező felfedése anélkül, hogy egy aknát is felrobbantana. Ha egy akna felrobban, a játék véget ér.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>KMines adalah permainan Minesweeper klasik. Gagasannya adalah untuk mengungkap semua persegi tanpa meledakkan ranjau apa pun. Ketika sebuah ranjau diledakkan, tamatlah permainan.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>KMines er hefðbundinn sprengjuleitarleikur sem líkist Minesweeper. Hugmyndin er að afhjúpa alla reiti nema þá sem springa í andlitið á manni. Ef það gerist, er leiknum lokið.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>KMines è un classico gioco del campo minato. Si devono individuare tutte le caselle libere senza saltare in aria su una mina. Quando una mina esplode, il gioco termina.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>KMines는 고전 지뢰찾기 게임입니다. 지뢰를 터트리지 않고 모든 사각형을 드러내십시오. 지뢰가 터지면 게임이 끝납니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>KMines is het klassieke mijnenvegerspel. Het idee is alle vierkantjes open te maken zonder een mijn op te blazen. Als er een mijn ontploft is het spel afgelopen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>KMinesveipar er eit klassisk minesveiparspel. Målet er å avdekkja alle ruter som ikkje har miner på seg. Treff du derimot på ei rute med ei mine, går mina av og du tapar spelet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>KMiny jest klasyczną grą w sapera. Polega ona na odkryciu wszystkich pól bez wysadzenia żadnej z min. Po napotkaniu na minę, gra się kończy.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O KMines é um jogo clássico de Campo Minado (Minesweeper). A ideia é destapar todos os quadrados sem rebentar nenhuma mina. Quando for estoirada uma mina, o jogo termina.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>KMines é o jogo clássico chamado Campo Minado. Você precisa descobrir todos os quadrados vazios sem explodir nenhuma mina. O jogo termina quando uma mina explode.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>KMine e un joc clasic ca „Detectorul de mine”. Ideea e să descoperiți cât mai multe pătrate fără a declanșa vreo mină. Jocul e pierdut la explozia unei mine.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>KMines je klasická hra Hľadanie mín. Cieľom je odkryť všetky štvorce bez odpálenia mín. Ak sa mína odpáli, hra končí.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>KMines je klasična igra Minolovca. Cilj igre je odkriti vse kvadratke, brez da bi naleteli na mino. Ko se slednje zgodi, je igre konec.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>К‑мине је класична игра Миноловца. Треба открити сва поља тако да се не активира ниједна мина. Ако мина експлодира, то је крај партије.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-Latn">
    <p>K‑mine je klasična igra Minolovca. Treba otkriti sva polja tako da se ne aktivira nijedna mina. Ako mina eksplodira, to je kraj partije.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-ijekavian">
    <p>К‑мине је класична игра Миноловца. Треба открити сва поља тако да се не активира ниједна мина. Ако мина експлодира, то је крај партије.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">
    <p>K‑mine je klasična igra Minolovca. Treba otkriti sva polja tako da se ne aktivira nijedna mina. Ako mina eksplodira, to je kraj partije.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Minröjaren är ett klassiskt minröjarspel. Idén är att frilägga alla rutor utan att detonera några minor. När en mina detonerar är spelet slut.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>KMines klasik bir Mayın Tarlası oyunudur. Amacı, tüm kareleri herhangi bir mayını patlamadan ortaya çıkarmaktır. Bir mayın patladığında oyun sona erer.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>KMines — це класична гра у сапера. Ідея гри полягає у тому, щоб розкрити всі клітинки без підриву жодної з мін. Якщо ви натрапите на міну, гру буде програно.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxKMines is a classic Minesweeper game. The idea is to uncover all the squares without blowing up any mines. When a mine is blown up, the game is over.xx</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>KMines 是一款经典扫雷游戏。目标是不引爆地雷的情况下，揭开所有方格。当地雷被引爆时，游戏结束。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kmines&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kmines/kmines.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>kmines</binary>
  </provides>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <releases>
    <release version="4.0.22043" date="2022-07-07" />
    <release version="4.0.22042" date="2022-06-09" />
    <release version="4.0.22041" date="2022-05-12" />
    <release date="2022-04-21" version="4.0.22040" />
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">mild</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>