<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <description>
    <p>
      KolourPaint is a simple painting program to quickly create raster images.
      It is useful as a touch-up tool and simple image editing tasks.
    </p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Support for drawing various shapes - lines, rectangles, rounded rectangles, ovals and polygons</li>
      <li>Curves, lines and text</li>
      <li>Colour picker</li>
      <li>Selections</li>
      <li>Rotation, monochrome and other advanced effects</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>الرسام هو برنامج رسم بسيط لإنشاء صور نقطية بسرعة. إنه مفيد كأداة تحسين ومهام بسيطة لتحرير الصور.</p>
    <p>الميزات:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>دعم لرسم أشكال مختلفة - خطوط ومستطيلات ومستطيلات مستديرة الشكل وأشكال بيضاوية ومضلعات</li>
      <li>المنحنيات والخطوط والنص</li>
      <li>منتق الألوان</li>
      <li>التّحديدات</li>
      <li>دوران ، أحادية اللون وتأثيرات متقدمة أخرى</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>KolourPaint е проста програма за рисуване на растерни изображения. Тя е полезна като инструмент за ретуширане и при стандартни задачи за редактиране на изображения. </p>
    <p>Функции:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Поддръжка на чертане на различни фигури - линии, правоъгълници, овали и полигони. </li>
      <li>Криви, линии и текст</li>
      <li>Избор на цвят</li>
      <li>Селекции</li>
      <li>Ротация, монохромност и други ефекти</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>KolourPaint je jednostavan crtaći program za brzo staranje rasterskih slika. On je koristan kao sredstvo retuširanja i jednostavne zadatke za uređivanje slika.</p>
    <p>Svojstva:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Podrška za crtanje raznih oblika - linija, pravougaonika, zaobljenih pravougaonika, ovala i poligona</li>
      <li>Krive, linije i tekst</li>
      <li>Dobavljač boja</li>
      <li>Selekcije</li>
      <li>Rotacija, monohrom i drugi napredni efekti</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El KolourPaint és un programa senzill de dibuix per a crear ràpidament imatges ràster. És útil com a eina de retoc i tasques senzilles per a l'edició d'imatges.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Permet dibuixar diverses formes: línies, rectangles, rectangles arrodonits, ovals i polígons</li>
      <li>Corbes, línies i text</li>
      <li>Selector de color</li>
      <li>Seleccions</li>
      <li>Gir, monocrom i altres efectes avançats</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>KolourPaint és un programa senzill de dibuix per a crear ràpidament imatges ràster. És útil com a eina de retoc i tasques senzilles per a l'edició d'imatges.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Permet dibuixar diverses formes: línies, rectangles, rectangles arredonits, ovals i polígons</li>
      <li>Corbes, línies i text</li>
      <li>Selector de color</li>
      <li>Seleccions</li>
      <li>Gir, monocrom i altres efectes avançats</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Vlastnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Křivky, čáry a text</li>
      <li>Kapátko</li>
      <li>Výběry</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>KolourPaint er et simpelt tegneprogram til hurtigt at skabe raster-billeder. Det er et nyttigt værktøj til at tegne skitser eller udføre simple billedredigeringsopgaver.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Understøtter at tegne diverse former - linjer, firkanter, afrundede firkanter, ovaler og polygoner</li>
      <li>Kurver, linjer og tekst</li>
      <li>Farvevælger</li>
      <li>Markeringer</li>
      <li>Rotation, monokrom og andre avancerede effekter</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>KolourPaint ist ein einfach zu benutzendes Mal- und Zeichenprogramm um schnell Rasterbilder zu erstellen. Es kann für die Korrektur und einfache Bildbearbeitungsaufgaben benutzt werden.</p>
    <p>Leistungsmerkmale:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Das Zeichnen verschiedener Objekte wie Linien, Rechtecke, abgerundete Rechtecke, Ellipsen und Polygone wird unterstützt.</li>
      <li>Kurven, Linien und Text</li>
      <li>Farbwähler</li>
      <li>Mehre Auswahlarten</li>
      <li>Drehung, Umwandlung in Schwarzweiß und weitere Effekte können angewendet werden</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το KolourPaint είναι λενα απλό πρόγραμμα ζωραφικής για τη γρήγορη δημιουργία εικόνων χρωματικής περίπλεξης. Χρησιμεύει ως διορθωτικό και για απλές εργασίες επεξεργασίας εικόνων.</p>
    <p>Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Υποστήριξη για σχεδίαση διαφόρων σχημάτων - ευθείες, ορθογώνια παραλληλόγραμμα, στρογγυλεμένα ορθογώνια, ελλείψεις και πολύγωνα</li>
      <li>Καμπύλες, ευθείες και κείμενο</li>
      <li>Επιλογέας χρωμάτων</li>
      <li>Επιλογές</li>
      <li>Περιστροφή, μονοχρωμία και άλλα προηγμένα εφέ</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>KolourPaint is a simple painting program to quickly create raster images. It is useful as a touch-up tool and simple image editing tasks.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Support for drawing various shapes - lines, rectangles, rounded rectangles, ovals and polygons</li>
      <li>Curves, lines and text</li>
      <li>Colour picker</li>
      <li>Selections</li>
      <li>Rotation, monochrome and other advanced effects</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>KolourPaint es un sencillo programa de dibujo que permite crear imágenes de mapas de bits de una forma rápida. Resulta útil como herramienta de retoque y para tareas de edición sencillas.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Permite dibujar distintas formas (líneas, rectángulos, rectángulos de esquinas redondeadas, óvalos y polígonos)</li>
      <li>Curvas, líneas y texto</li>
      <li>Selección de color</li>
      <li>Selecciones</li>
      <li>Rotación, conversión a monocromo y otros efectos avanzados</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>KolourPaint on lihtne joonistamisrakendus rasterpiltide kiireks loomiseks. Sellega on hõlpus luua visandeid ja täita lihtsamaid piltide töötlemise ülesandeid.</p>
    <p>Omadused:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Mitmesuguste kujundite joonistamise toetus: jooned, ristkülikud, ümarnurksed ristkülikud, ovaalid, hulknurgad</li>
      <li>Kõverad, sirged ja tekst</li>
      <li>Värvivalija</li>
      <li>Valikud</li>
      <li>Pööramine, ühevärvilisus ja veel mõned efektid</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>KolourPaint margotzeko aplikazio xume bat da, «raster» irudiak azkar sortzeko balio duena. Baliagarria da berrukipen tresna gisa eta oinarrizko irudi editatzeko atazetarako.</p>
    <p>Eginbideak:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Hainbat forma marraztu ditzake - lerroak, laukizuzenak, laukizuzen borobilduak, obaloak eta poligonoak</li>
      <li>Kurbak, lerroak eta testua</li>
      <li>Kolore hautatzailea</li>
      <li>Hautapenak</li>
      <li>Biraketa, monokromoa eta beste efektu aurreratu batzuk</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>KolourPaint on yksinkertainen piirto-ohjelma, jolla voi luoda nopeasti bittikartakuvia. Sitä voi käyttää myös kuvien parantamiseen ja yksinkertaiseen kuvankäsittelyyn.</p>
    <p>Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Piirtämistuki useille muodoille – viivoille, suorakaiteille, pyöristetyille suorakaiteille, ellipseille ja monikulmioille</li>
      <li>Käyrät, viivat ja teksti</li>
      <li>Värivalitsin</li>
      <li>Valintatyökalu</li>
      <li>Kierto, pelkistäminen yksiväriseksi sekä muita tehosteita</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>KolourPaint est logiciel de dessin simple qui permet de créer rapidement des images. Il est pratique pour retoucher ou modifier simplement des images.</p>
    <p>Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Dessin de formes variées : lignes, rectangles, rectangles à bords arrondis, ovales, polygones</li>
      <li>Courbes, lignes et textes</li>
      <li>Sélecteur de couleur</li>
      <li>Sélections</li>
      <li>Rotation, monochrome et autres effets avancés</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>KolourPaint é un programa para pintar sinxelo que permite crear imaxes de mapa de bits rapidamente. É útil como ferramenta de retoque e para realizar tarefas sinxelas de edición de imaxes.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Permite debuxar varias formas: liñas, rectángulos, rectángulos arredondados, óvalos e polígonos.</li>
      <li>Curvas, liñas e texto.</li>
      <li>Selector de cor</li>
      <li>Seleccións</li>
      <li>Rotación, monocroma e outros efectos avanzados.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A KolourPaint egy egyszerű rajzolóprogram raszteres képek gyors létrehozásához. Hasznos retusálóeszközként és egyszerű képszerkesztő feladatokhoz.</p>
    <p>Szolgáltatások:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Különféle alakzatok rajzolásának támogatása - vonalak, téglalapok, lekerekített téglalapok, oválisok és sokszögek</li>
      <li>Görbék, vonalak és szöveg</li>
      <li>Színválasztó</li>
      <li>Kijelölések</li>
      <li>Forgatás, fekete-fehér és egyéb speciális hatások</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ia">
    <p>KolourPAint es un simple programma per pinger o designar  per crear rapidemente imagines raster. Il es utile como instrumento de retocco e per cargas simplice de modificar imagines.</p>
    <p>Characteristicas:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Supporto pro designar varie formas - lineas, rectangulos, rectangulos tundite, ovales e polygonos</li>
      <li>Curvas, lineas e texto</li>
      <li>Selector de color</li>
      <li>Selectiones</li>
      <li>Rotation, monochrome e altere effectos avantiate</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>KolourPaint adalah program melukis sederhana untuk membuat gambar raster dengan cepat. Ini berguna sebagai alat bantu dan tugas pengeditan gambar sederhana.</p>
    <p>Fitur:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Dukungan untuk menggambar berbagai bentuk - garis, persegi panjang, persegi panjang, bulat, oval dan poligon</li>
      <li>Lengkung, garis, dan teks</li>
      <li>Penukil warna</li>
      <li>Pemilihan</li>
      <li>Perotasian, monokrom, dan efek tingkat lanjut lainnya</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>KolourPaint è un semplice programma di disegno per la creazione rapida di immagini. È utile come strumento da usare «al volo» e per effettuare semplici modifiche alle immagini.</p>
    <p>Caratteristiche:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Supporto per il disegno di varie forme - linee, rettangoli, rettangoli arrotondati, ovali e poligoni</li>
      <li>Curve, linee e testo</li>
      <li>Selettore del colore</li>
      <li>Selezioni</li>
      <li>Rotazione, monocromia e altri effetti avanzati</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>KolourPaint는 래스터 그림을 빠르게 만드는 프로그램입니다. 간단한 보정 도구 및 편집 도구로 사용할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p>기능:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>다양한 도형 그리기 - 직선, 사각형, 둥근 사각형, 타원형, 다각형</li>
      <li>곡선, 직선 및 텍스트</li>
      <li>색 선택기</li>
      <li>선택</li>
      <li>회전, 흑백, 기타 고급 효과</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Galimybės:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Kreivės, tiesės ir tekstas</li>
      <li>Spalvų parinkiklis</li>
      <li>Žymėjimai</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>KolourPaint er et enkelt maleprogram som kjapt kan lage rasterbilder. Det er et nyttig verktøy for retusjering og enkle redigeringsoppgaver.</p>
    <p>Funksjoner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Støtte for å tegne mange former – linjer, rektangler, avrundede rektangler, ovaler og polygoner</li>
      <li>Kurver, linjer og tekst</li>
      <li>Fargevelger</li>
      <li>Utvalg</li>
      <li>Dreiing, monokrom og andre avanserte effekter</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nds">
    <p>KolourPaint is en eenfach Maalprogramm, mit dat sik gau Pixelbiller opstellen laat. Dat is goot för lütte Utbetern un eenfache Bildbewerken.</p>
    <p>Markmalen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ünnerstütt dat Teken vun en Reeg vun Formen - Lienen, Rechtecks, afrundt Rechtecks, Ovalen un Veelecks</li>
      <li>Bagens, Lienen un Text</li>
      <li>Klöörköör</li>
      <li>Köören</li>
      <li>Dreihen, Swatt-Witt un en Reeg verwiedert Effekten</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>KolourPaint is een eenvoudig tekenprogramma om snel rasterafbeeldingen te maken. Het is nuttig als een hulpmiddel voor bijwerken en eenvoudige taken voor bewerking van afbeeldingen.</p>
    <p>Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ondersteuning voor het tekenen van verschillende vormen - lijnen, rechthoeken, afgeronde rechthoeken, ovalen en polygonen</li>
      <li>Krommen, lijnen en tekst</li>
      <li>Kleurkiezer</li>
      <li>Selecties</li>
      <li>Roteren, monochroom en andere geavanceerde effecten</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>KolourPaint er eit enkelt teikne­program for punkt­grafikk. Det er eit nyttig verktøy for retusjering og enkle redigerings­oppgåver.</p>
    <p>Funksjonar:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Støtte for å teikna mange former – linjer, rektangel, avrunda rektangel, ellipsar og mangekantar</li>
      <li>Kurver, linjer og tekst</li>
      <li>Fargeveljar</li>
      <li>Utval</li>
      <li>Dreiing, fargeredusering og fleire avanserte effektar</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>KolourPaint jest prostym programem do malowania i szybkiego tworzenia obrazów rastrowych. Jest przydatny przy retuszowaniu i prostych pracach edytowania.</p>
    <p>Cechy:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Obsługa rysowania rozmaitych kształtów - proste, prostokąty, zaokrąglone prostokąty, owale i wielokąty</li>
      <li>Krzywe, proste i teks</li>
      <li>Wybierak barwy</li>
      <li>Zaznaczenia</li>
      <li>Obrót, monochromatyczność i inne zaawansowane efekty</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O KolourPaint é um programa simples de pintura que cria rapidamente imagens rasterizadas. É útil como uma ferramenta de retoques e para tarefas simples de edição de imagens.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Suporte para desenhar várias formas - linhas, rectângulos, rectângulos arredondados, ovais e polígonos</li>
      <li>Curvas, linhas e texto</li>
      <li>Selecção de cores</li>
      <li>Selecções</li>
      <li>Rotação, monocromáticos e outros efeitos avançados</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>KolourPaint é um programa de desenho simples, que cria rapidamente imagens rasterizadas. É útil como uma ferramenta de retoques e para tarefas simples de edição de imagens.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Suporte para desenhar várias formas - linhas, retângulos, retângulos arredondados, ovais e polígonos</li>
      <li>Curvas, linhas e texto</li>
      <li>Seleção de cor</li>
      <li>Seleções</li>
      <li>Rotação, monocromático e outros efeitos avançados</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>KolourPaint — простая программа для рисования и создания растровых изображений. Может быть полезна для внесения небольших правок в изображения.</p>
    <p>Возможности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Рисование различных фигур: отрезков, прямоугольников, скруглённых прямоугольников, овалов и многоугольников</li>
      <li>Рисование гладких кривых, произвольных линий и вставка текста</li>
      <li>Окно палитры</li>
      <li>Выделение областей</li>
      <li>Инструменты поворота, преобразования в чёрно-белое изображение и другие</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>KolourPaint je jednoduchý kresliaci program na rýchlu tvorbu rastrových obrázkov. Je užitočný ako touch-up nástroj a na jednoduché úpravy obrázkov.</p>
    <p>Funkcie:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Podpora pre kreslenie rôznych tvarov - čiary, obdĺžniky, zaoblené obdĺžniky, ovály a polygóny</li>
      <li>Krivky, čiary a text</li>
      <li>Výber farieb</li>
      <li>Výbery</li>
      <li>Otáčanie, monochromatické a iné pokročilé efekty</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>KolourPaint je preprost program za risanje in hitro ustvarjanje rastrskih slik. Uporaben je za izboljšave slik in preprosto urejanje slik.</p>
    <p>Zmožnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Podpora risanju različnih oblik - črt, pravokotnikov, zaobljenih pravokotnikov, ovalov in mnogokotnikov</li>
      <li>Krivulje, črte in besedilo</li>
      <li>Izbirnik barv</li>
      <li>Izbire</li>
      <li>Vrtenje, monokromatski in drugi napredni učinki</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>KolourPaint är ett enkelt ritprogram för att snabbt skapa punktavbildningar. Det är användbart som förbättringsverktyg och för enkla bildredigeringsuppgifter.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Stöd för att rita diverse former: linjer, rektanglar, rundade rektanglar, ovaler och polygoner</li>
      <li>Kurvor, linjer och text</li>
      <li>Färgväljare</li>
      <li>Markeringar</li>
      <li>Rotation, svartvitt och andra avancerade effekter</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>KolourPaint hızlıca taramalı resimler oluşturabileceğiniz basit bir boyama programıdır. Bir rötuş aracı ve basit resim düzenleme görevleri için yararlıdır.</p>
    <p>Özellikler:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Çeşitli şekiller, çizgiler, dörtgenler, yuvarlatılmış dörtgenler, ovaller ve poligonlar desteği</li>
      <li>Eğriler, çizgiler ve metin</li>
      <li>Renk seçici</li>
      <li>Seçimler</li>
      <li>Döndürme, tek renkli resim ve diğer gelişmiş efektler</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>KolourPaint — проста програма для малювання, за допомогою якої можна швидко створювати растрові зображення. Ця програма може бути корисною для виконання простих завдань з редагування зображень.</p>
    <p>Можливості:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Підтримка малювання різноманітних форм: прямих, прямокутників, прямокутників із заокругленими кутами, овалів та багатокутників.</li>
      <li>Можливість малювання кривих, прямих та тексту.</li>
      <li>Піпетка для отримання кольору із зображення.</li>
      <li>Можливість позначення ділянок зображення.</li>
      <li>Можливість обертання частин зображення, перетворення зображення на чорно-біле, різноманітні ефекти перетворення зображення.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxKolourPaint is a simple painting program to quickly create raster images. It is useful as a touch-up tool and simple image editing tasks.xx</p>
    <p>xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>xxSupport for drawing various shapes - lines, rectangles, rounded rectangles, ovals and polygonsxx</li>
      <li>xxCurves, lines and textxx</li>
      <li>xxColour pickerxx</li>
      <li>xxSelectionsxx</li>
      <li>xxRotation, monochrome and other advanced effectsxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>KolourPaint 是一个简单易用的绘图程序，可以创建点阵图像。可用来对图片进行润色和简单编辑。</p>
    <p>功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>支持绘制各种图形 - 直线、正方向、圆角正方形、椭圆和多边形</li>
      <li>曲线，直线和文本</li>
      <li>颜色拾取器</li>
      <li>选择</li>
      <li>旋转，纯黑白和其他高级效果</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-TW">
    <p>KolourPaint 是一套類似小畫家的簡易繪圖程式。</p>
    <p>功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>支援繪出不同的形狀 -- 線條、矩形、圓角矩形、橢圓與多邊形等</li>
      <li>曲線、線條與文字</li>
      <li>顏色挑選器</li>
      <li>選取區</li>
      <li>旋轉、單色與其他進階效果</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.kolourpaint</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kolourpaint.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" type="cached" height="64">kolourpaint.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" width="128" type="cached">kolourpaint.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.kolourpaint.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>BSD-2-Clause and LGPL-2.0+ and GFDL-1.2</project_license>
  <name>KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="ar">الرسام</name>
  <name lang="bg">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="bs">KolurPaint</name>
  <name lang="ca">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="cs">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="da">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="de">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="el">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="es">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="et">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="eu">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="fi">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="fr">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="gl">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="hu">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="ia">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="id">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="it">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="ko">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="lt">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="nb">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="nds">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="nl">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="nn">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="pl">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="pt">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="ru">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="sk">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="sl">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="sv">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="tr">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="uk">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxKolourPaintxx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">KolourPaint</name>
  <summary>Paint Program</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">برنامج تلوين</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Програма за рисуване</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Program za slikanje</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Programa de dibuix</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Programa de dibuix</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Program pro malování</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Tegneprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Mal- und Zeichenprogramm</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Πρόγραμμα ζωγραφικής</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Paint Program</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Programa de dibujo</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Joonistamisrakendus</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Marrazteko programa</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Piirto-ohjelma</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Logiciel de dessin</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Programa para pintar</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Rajzolóprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="ia">Programma per pinger</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Program Lukis</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Programma di disegno</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">그리기 프로그램</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Piešimo programa</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Malepogram</summary>
  <summary lang="nds">Maalprogramm</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Tekenprogramma</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Teikneprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Program Paint</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Programa de Pintura</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Programa de desenho</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Простой редактор изображений</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Kresliaci program</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Program za risanje</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Ritprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Boyama Programı</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Програма для малювання</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxPaint Programxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">绘图程序</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-TW">繪圖程式</summary>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.kolourpaint.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kolourpaint</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kolourpaint</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kolourpaint&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Painting in KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">الرسم على الرسام</caption>
      <caption lang="bg">Рисуване с KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Pintant al KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Pintant a KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Malování v KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Tegner i Kolourpaint</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Malen mit KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Ζωγραφική στο KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">Painting in KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Dibujando con KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Joonistamine KolourPaintis</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Margako KolourPaint erabiliz</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Maalaaminen KolourPaintissä</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Dessin dans KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Pintando en KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="ia">Pingente in KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Melukis di KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Dipingere in KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">KolourPaint로 그림 그리기</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">In KolourPaint tekenen</caption>
      <caption lang="nn">Teikning med KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Malowanie w KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Pintura no KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Pintando no KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Рисование в KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Kreslenie v KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Slikanje v KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Rita med KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">KolourPaint'te Boyama</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Малювання у KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxPainting in KolourPaintxx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-CN">在 KolourPaint 中绘画</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-TW">在 KolourPaint 繪圖</caption>
      <image>https://kde.org/images/screenshots/kolourpaint.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <provides>
    <binary>kolourpaint</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-07-07" version="22.04.3" />
    <release date="2022-06-09" version="22.04.2" />
    <release date="2022-05-12" version="22.04.1" />
    <release date="2022-04-21" version="22.04.0" />
  </releases>
</component>