<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.kwave</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kwave.desktop</launchable>
  <id>org.kde.kwave.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kwave</name>
  <name lang="bs">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="ca">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="cs">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="da">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="de">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="el">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="es">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="et">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="eu">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="fi">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="fr">KWave</name>
  <name lang="gl">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="ia">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="id">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="it">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="ko">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="nl">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="nn">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="pl">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="pt">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="ro">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="ru">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="sk">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="sl">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="sv">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="tr">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="uk">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxKwavexx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">Kwave</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">Kwave</name>
  <summary>Kwave is a sound editor built on KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">El Kwave és un editor de so construït amb els Frameworks 5 del KDE</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Kwave és un editor de so construït amb els Frameworks 5 de KDE</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">KWave je editor zvuku postavený na KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Kwave er et lydredigeringsprogram som er bygget på KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Kwave ist ein Sound-Editor für die KDE-Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Το Kwave είναι ένας επεξεργαστής ήχου στη βάση του KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Kwave is a sound editor built on KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Kwave es un editor de sonido construido sobre KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Kwave on KDE Frameworks 5 peale ehitatud heliredaktor</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Kwave KDE Frameworks 5ekin eraikitako soinu editore bat da</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Kwave on KDE Frameworks 5 -alustalle suunniteltu äänimuokkain</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">KWave est un éditeur de sons développé sous KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Kwave é un editor de son construído coa versión 5 das infraestruturas de KDE</summary>
  <summary lang="ia">Kwave es un editor e sono construite ur KDE Framework 5</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Kwave adalah sebuah editor sound yang  dibangun pada KDE Framework 5</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Kwave è un editor per il suono basato su KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">Kwave는 KDE 프레임워크 5를 사용하는 소리 편집기입니다</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Kwave is een geluidsbewerker gebouwd op KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Kwave er eit lydredigeringsprogram bygd på KDE Frameworks 5.</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Kwave jest edytorem dźwięku zbudowanym na Szkieletetach KDE 5</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">O Kwave é um editor de som baseado nas Plataformas do KDE 5</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Kwave é um editor de som construído no KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">KWave e un redactor de sunet construit pe KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Kwave — аудиоредактор на основе KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Kwave je editor zvuku navrhnutý pre KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Kwave je urejevalnik zvoka, zgrajen na KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Kwave är en ljudeditor konstruerad med KDE Ramverk 5</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Kwave, KDE Frameworks 5 üzerine kurulu bir ses düzenleyicidir</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Kwave — звуковий редактор, створений на основі KDE Frameworks 5</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxKwave is a sound editor built on KDE Frameworks 5xx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">Kwave 是构建于 KDE Frameworks 5 之上的音频编辑器</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-TW">Kwave 是一套架構在 KDE Frameworks 5 上的音效編輯器</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      With Kwave you can record, play back, import and edit many sorts of audio files including multi channel files.
    </p>
    <p>
      Kwave includes some plugins to transform audio files in several ways and presents a graphical view with a complete zoom- and scroll capability.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Sa KWave možete snimati, reprodukovati, uvoziti i uređivati mnogo vrsta audio datoteka uključujući višekanalne datoteke.</p>
    <p>Kwave uključuje neke dodatke za transformaciju audio datoteka na više načina i predstavlja grafički pogled s kompletnom mogućnošću uvećanja i klizanja.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Amb el Kwave podeu enregistrar, escoltar, importar i editar molts tipus de fitxers d'àudio inclosos els fitxers multicanal.</p>
    <p>El Kwave inclou alguns connectors per a transformar els fitxers d'àudio de diverses formes, i presenta una vista gràfica amb un capacitat de zoom i desplaçament complets.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>Amb Kwave podeu enregistrar, escoltar, importar i editar molts tipus de fitxers d'àudio inclosos els fitxers multicanal.</p>
    <p>Kwave inclou alguns connectors per a transformar els fitxers d'àudio de diverses formes, i presenta una vista gràfica amb un capacitat de zoom i desplaçament complets.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Med Kwave kan du optage, afspille, importere og redigere mange slags lydfiler, inklusiv multikanalfiler.</p>
    <p>Kwave inkluderer nogle plugins til at transformere lydfiler på flere måder og viser en grafisk visning med en fuld mulighed for at zoome og rulle.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Mit Kwave können Sie aufnehmen, abspielen und viele Arten von Audio-Dateien importieren und bearbeiten, einschließlich Dateien mit mehreren Spuren.</p>
    <p>Kwave enthält einige Module zum Umwandeln von Audio-Dateien auf verschiedene Arten und bietet eine grafische Ansicht mit umfassenden Möglichkeiten zur Änderung von Größe und Ausschnitt.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Με το Kwave μπορείτε να κάνετε ηχογράφηση, αναπαραγωγή, εισαγωγή και επεξεργασία πολλών ειδών αρχείων ήχου συμπεριλαμβανομένων και πολυκάναλων.</p>
    <p>Το Kwave περιλαμβάνει κάποια πρόσθετα για το μετασχηματισμό των αρχείων ήχου με διάφορους τρόπους και παρουσιάζει μια γραφική προβολή με πλήρη δυνατότητα εστίασης και κύλισης.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>With Kwave you can record, play back, import and edit many sorts of audio files including multi channel files.</p>
    <p>Kwave includes some plugins to transform audio files in several ways and presents a graphical view with a complete zoom- and scroll capability.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Con Kwave puede grabar, reproducir, importar y editar muchos tipos de archivos de sonido, incluidos los archivos multicanal.</p>
    <p>Kwave contiene algunos complementos para transformar archivos de sonido de varias formas y presenta una interfaz gráfica con completas funciones de ampliación y de desplazamiento.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>KWave võimaldab salvestada, esitada, importida ja muuta väga mitut laadi helifaile, kaasa arvatud mitme kanaliga faile.</p>
    <p>Kwave pakub mõningaid pluginaid helifailide muutmiseks mitmel viisil, samuti graafilist vaadet igakülgse suurendamise ja kerimise toetusega.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Kwaverekin audio fitxategi mota asko, tartean kanal anitzeko fitxategiak, grabatu, atzera jo, inportatu eta editatu ditzakezu.</p>
    <p>Kwavek audio fitxategiak hainbat eratan transformatzeko plugin batzuk ditu eta ikuspegi grafiko bat aurkezten du zoom eta labaintzeko gaitasun osoak dituen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Kwavella voit äänittää, toistaa, tuoda ja muokata monenlaisia äänitiedostoja, myös useampikanavaisia.</p>
    <p>Kwavessa on liitännäisiä äänen erilaisiin muunnoksiin, ja sen käyttöliittymässä on täydelliset lähennys/loitonnus- ja vieritysominaisuudet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>KWave vous permet d'enregistrer, lire, importer et éditer des fichiers audio sous plusieurs formats, y compris les fichiers multi-pistes.</p>
    <p>KWave comprend des modules externes pour transformer de différentes façons des fichiers audio ainsi qu'une interface graphique permettant le zoom et le défilement.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Kwave permítelle gravar, reproducir, importar e editar moitos tipos de ficheiros de son, incluídos ficheiros de varias canles.</p>
    <p>Kwave inclúe algúns complementos para transformar ficheiros de son de varios xeitos, e fornece unha visualización gráfica que pode achegar e afastar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ia">
    <p>Con Kwave tu pote registrar, resonar, importar e modificar multe typos de files audio includente files multi canal</p>
    <p>Kwave include alcun pluginper transformar files in multe modos e presenta un vista graphic conun complete capacitate de zoom e rolar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Dengan Kwave kamu bisa merekam, memutar kembali, mengimpor dan mengedit banyak file-file audio pendek termasuk file-file channel multi.</p>
    <p>Kwave menyertakan beberapa plugin untuk mentransfer file audio dalam banyak cara dan menghadirkan tampilan grafik dengan kelengkapan kemampuan gulir dan zoom.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Con Kwave puoi registrare, riprodurre, importare e modificare molti tipi di file audio, inclusi i file multicanale.</p>
    <p>Kwave include diverse estensioni per la trasformazione dei file audio con diversi metodi e offre una vista grafica con funzioni complete di ingrandimento e scorrimento.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>Kwave를 사용하여 오디오 파일을 녹음, 재생, 편집할 수 있으며 멀티채널 오디오 파일도 지원합니다.</p>
    <p>Kwave는 오디오 파일을 변형할 수 있는 여러 플러그인을 지원하며 그래픽 보기를 지원합니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Met Kwave kunt u vele soorten audiobestanden opnemen, afspelen, importeren en bewerken inclusief multi-channel bestanden.</p>
    <p>Kwave bevat enige plug-ins om geluidsbestanden op verschillenden manieren te transformeren en biedt een grafische weergave met de mogelijkheid van volledig te zoomen en te schuiven.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>Med Kwave kan du spela inn, spela av, importera og redigera lydfiler i ulike format, også fleirkanalsfiler.</p>
    <p>Kwave inneheld fleire programtillegg for transformering av lydfiler på ulike måtar og for visualisering av lyddata.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Dzięki Kwave możesz nagrywać, odtwarzać, importować i edytować wiele różnych plików dźwiękowych uwzględniając w tym pliki wielokanałowe.</p>
    <p>Kwave zawiera kilka wtyczek do przekształcania plików dźwiękowych na różne sposoby i do przedstawiania widoku graficznego z możliwością jego powiększania i przewijania.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Com o Kwave, poderá gravar, reproduzir, importar e editar diversos tipos de ficheiros de áudio, incluindo ficheiros multi-canais.</p>
    <p>O Kwave inclui alguns 'plugins' para transformar os ficheiros de áudio de diversas formas e apresenta uma vista gráfica com uma capacidade completa de ampliação e deslocamento.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>Com o Kwave, você pode gravar, reproduzir, importar e editar diversos tipos de arquivos de áudio, incluindo arquivos multicanais.</p>
    <p>O Kwave inclui alguns plugins para transformar os arquivos de áudio de diversas formas e apresenta um visual gráfico com capacidade completa zoom e deslocamento.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Записывайте, проигрывайте, импортируйте и редактируйте различные типы звуковых файлов, включая многоканальные, с помощью Kwave.</p>
    <p>В Kwave включены модули для преобразования звуковых файлов различными способами, и возможен просмотр с полной поддержкой увеличения и прокрутки.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Pomocou Kwave môžete nahrávať, prehrávať, importovať a editovať mnoho druhov audio súborov vrátane viackanálových súborov.</p>
    <p>Kwave zahŕňa niektoré pluginy na transformáciu audio súborov v niekoľkých spôsoboch a má grafický pohľad s kompletnou schopnosťou priblíženia a rolovania.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>S programom Kwave lahko snemate, predvajate, uvozite in urejate številne vrste zvočnih datotek, vključno z večkanalnimi datotekami.</p>
    <p>Kwave vključuje nekaj vtičnikov za preoblikovanje zvočnih datotek na več načinov in omogoča tudi grafični prikaz s popolno možnostjo povečave in drsenja.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Man kan spela in, spela upp, importera och redigera många sorters ljudfiler, inklusive filer med flera kanaler, med Kwave.</p>
    <p>Kwave inkluderar några insticksmoduler för att omvandla ljudfiler på flera sätt, och visar en grafisk vy med fullständig zoom- och panoreringsförmåga.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Kwave ile kayıt yapabilir, dinleyebilir, içe aktarabilir ve çoklu kanal dosyalarınıda barındıran bir çok ses dosyasını düzenleyebilirsiniz.</p>
    <p>Kwave, farklı yollarla ses dosyalarını dönüştürmeniz için bazı eklentiler barındırır ve tamamen yakınlaştırma ve kaydırma yeteneği ile grafiksel bir görünüm sunar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>За допомогою Kwave ви можете записувати, відтворювати, імпортувати та редагувати файли звукових даних багатьох типів, зокрема файли з багатоканальним звуком.</p>
    <p>До складу Kwave включено декілька додатків для перетворення звукових даних. Передбачено графічне представлення дати із усіма можливостями масштабування та гортання.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxWith Kwave you can record, play back, import and edit many sorts of audio files including multi channel files.xx</p>
    <p>xxKwave includes some plugins to transform audio files in several ways and presents a graphical view with a complete zoom- and scroll capability.xx</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>使用 Kwave 您可以录制，播放，导入和编辑许多音频文件，包括多声道文件。</p>
    <p>Kwave 包括了一些插件从而提供了多种方式转换音频文件，以及通过可缩放滚动的图形视图展示它们。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-TW">
    <p>您可以用 Kwave 來錄音、播放、匯入與編輯許多音效檔，包括多音軌的檔案。</p>
    <p>Kwave 包含一些外掛程式，來用不同的方法轉換音效檔，並以圖形化方式呈現。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://kwave.sourceforge.net/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kwave</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kwave&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Kwave in action</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">El Kwave en acció</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Kwave en acció</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Kwave in Aktion</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Το Kwave σε δράση</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">Kwave in action</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Kwave en acción</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Kwave töös</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Kwave martxan</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Kwave toiminnassa</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">KWave en action</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Kwave en acción</caption>
      <caption lang="ia">Kwave in action</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Kwave beraksi</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Kwave in azione</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">Kwave 사용 모습</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Kwave in actie</caption>
      <caption lang="nn">Kwave i praksis</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Kwave w działaniu</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">O Kwave em acção</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">O Kwave em ação</caption>
      <caption lang="ro">Kwave în acțiune</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Работа в Kwave</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Kwave v akcií</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Kwave v akciji</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Kwave i aktion</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Kwave çalışırken</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Сеанс роботи у Kwave</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxKwave in actionxx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-CN">Kwave 使用过程中</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-TW">Kwave 正使用中</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kwave/kwave.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kwave</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-07-07" version="22.04.3" />
    <release date="2022-06-09" version="22.04.2" />
    <release version="22.04.1" date="2022-05-12" />
    <release version="22.04.0" date="2022-04-21" />
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>