<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <description>
    <p>
      Ark is a graphical file compression/decompression utility with support for multiple formats,
      including tar, gzip, bzip2, rar and zip, as well as CD-ROM images.
      Ark can be used to browse, extract, create, and modify archives.
    </p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Several formats supported: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z and more</li>
      <li>Preview file contents without extracting files</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>آرك أداة رسوميّة لضغط وفكّ ضغط الملفات مع دعم لصيغ متعدّدة، منها tar، وgzip، وbzip2، وrar، وzip، إضافة إلى صور الأقراص الضوئيّة. يمكن استخدام آرك لتصفح، واستخراج، وإنشاء، وتعديل الأرشيفات.</p>
    <p>المزايا</p>
    <ul>
      <li>دعم صيغ متعدّدة: مثل gzip، و bzip2، و zip، و rar، و 7z وغيرها</li>
      <li>استعراض محتوى الملف دون استخراج الملفات منه</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ast">
    <p>Ark ye una utilidá gráfica de des/compresión de ficheros con sofitu pa munchos formatos de ficheros, incluyendo TAR, gzip, bzip2, RAR y zip, amás d'imáxenes de DVD/CD-ROM. Ark pue usase pa restolar, estrayer, crear y modificar archivos.</p>
    <p>Carauterístiques</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Sofítense munchos formatos: gzip, bzip2, zip, RAR, 7z y más</li>
      <li>Previsualización d'archivos ensin estrayer los sos ficheros</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="az">
    <p>Ark, tar, gzip, bzip2, rar və zip və CD-ROM görünüşü də daxil olmaqla bir çox formatı dəstəkləyən qrafik, faylları sıxmaq/dekompressiya etmək üçün yardımçı proqramıdır. Ark arxivlərə baxmaq, çıxarmaq, onları yaratmaq və dəyişdirmək üçün istifadə edilə bilər.</p>
    <p>İmkanlar:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Bir neçə format dəstəklənir: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z və bir çoxları</li>
      <li>Fayl tərkiblərini çıxartmadan onlara öncədən baxış</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Ark е графичен инструмент за архивиране/разархивиране, поддържащ множество формати, включително tar, gzip, bzip2, rar и zip, както и образи на CD-ROM. Ark може да се използва за разглеждане, извличане, създаване и променяне на архиви.</p>
    <p>Функции:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Поддържани са много формати: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z и други</li>
      <li>Преглеждане съдържанието на файла, без извличане на файловете</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Ark je grafički alat za kompresiju/dekompresiju s podrškom za više formata, uključujući tar, gzip, bzip2, rar i zip, kao i CD-ROM slike. Ark se može koristiti za kreiranje, izdvjanje i modifikaciju arhiva.</p>
    <p>Svojstvo:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Više podržanih formata: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z i drui</li>
      <li>Pregled sadržaja datoteka bez njihovog izdvajanja</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>L'Ark és una utilitat gràfica de compressió/descompressió de fitxers que admet múltiples formats, incloent-hi tar, gzip, bzip2, rar i zip, i també imatges de CD-ROM. L'Ark es pot utilitzar per a explorar, extreure, crear, i modificar arxius.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Diversos formats admesos: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z i més</li>
      <li>Vista prèvia del contingut de fitxers sense extreure'ls</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>Ark és una utilitat gràfica de compressió/descompressió de fitxers que admet múltiples formats, incloent-hi tar, gzip, bzip2, rar i zip, i també imatges de CD-ROM. Ark es pot utilitzar per a explorar, extreure, crear, i modificar arxius.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Diversos formats admesos: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z i més</li>
      <li>Vista prèvia del contingut de fitxers sense extreure'ls</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Ark je grafický nástroj pro kompresi/dekompresi souborů s podporou formátů jako je tar, gzip, bzip2, rar a zip a obrazů disků CD-ROM. Ark lze použít k prohlížení, rozbalování a úpravám archivů.</p>
    <p>Vlastnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Je podporováno několik formátů: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z a další</li>
      <li>Náhled obsahu souborů bez jejich rozbalení</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Ark er et grafisk værktøj til komprimering/dekomprimering, med understøttelse for flere formater, derunder tar, gzip, bzip2, rar og zip, såvel som cd-rom-imagefiler. Ark kan bruges til at gennemse, udtrække, oprette og redigere.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Flere understøttede formater: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z og flere</li>
      <li>Forhåndsvis filindhold uden at udtrække filer</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Ark ist ein grafisches Dienstprogramm zum Packen/Entpacken von Dateien mit Unterstützung für mehrere Formate wie tar, gzip, bzip2, rar, zip und auch CD-Abbilder. Mit Ark können Sie können Sie Archive durchsehen, entpacken, erstellen und bearbeiten.</p>
    <p>Leistungsmerkmale:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Mehrere unterstützte Formate wie gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z und mehr</li>
      <li>Vorschau der Dateiinhalte ohne das Entpacken der Dateien</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το Ark είναι ένα γραφικό εργαλείο συμπίεσης/αποσυμπίεσης αρχείων με υποστήριξη για πολλούς τύπους αποθήκευσης, όπως tar, gzip, bzip2, rar και zip, καθώς επίσης και εικόνες CD-ROM. To Ark χρησιμεύει για την περιήγηση, εξαγωγή, δημιουργία και τροποποίηση αρχειοθηκών.</p>
    <p>Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Υποστηρίζονται πολλοί τύποι αποθήκευσης: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z και άλλοι</li>
      <li>Προεπισκόπηση περιεχομένων αρχείου χωρίς εξαγωγή αρχείων</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>Ark is a graphical file compression/decompression utility with support for multiple formats, including tar, gzip, bzip2, rar and zip, as well as CD-ROM images. Ark can be used to browse, extract, create, and modify archives.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Several formats supported: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z and more</li>
      <li>Preview file contents without extracting files</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Ark es una utilidad gráfica de compresión y descompresión de archivos que permite usar diversos formatos, como tar, gzip, bzip2, rar y zip, así como imágenes de CD-ROM. Ark se puede usar para explorar, extraer, crear y modificar archivos comprimidos.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Permite el uso de diversos formatos: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z y más</li>
      <li>Vista previa del contenido de archivos sin extraerlos</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Ark on graafiline failide tihendamise ehk kokkupakkimise ja nende lahtipakkimise tööriist, mis toetab väga paljusid vorminguid, sealhulgas tar, gzip, bzip2, rar and zip, samuti CD-ROM-i tõmmised. Arki abil saab arhiivifaile sirvida, lahti pakkida, luua ja muuta.</p>
    <p>Omadused:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Paljude vormingute toetus: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z ja veel paljud.</li>
      <li>Failide sisu näitamine ilma neid lahti pakkimata.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Ark fitxategien konprimatze-lanetarako utilitate grafiko bat da formatu ugari onartzen dituena, hauen artean tar, gzip, bzip2, rar eta zip, baita CD-ROM irudiak ere. Ark erabili daiteke artxiboak arakatu, erauzi, sortu eta aldatzeko.</p>
    <p>Ezaugarriak:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Hainbat formatu onartuak: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z eta gehiago</li>
      <li>Aurreikusi fitxategiaren edukia fitxategiak erauzi gabe</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Ark on graafinen tiedostojen pakkaus-/purkuohjelma, joka tukee useita tiedostomuotoja kuten tar, gzip, bzip2, rar and zip sekä myös CD-ROM-levykuvia. Arkilla voi selata, purkaa, luoda ja muuttaa arkistoja.</p>
    <p>Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Tukee useita tiedostomuotoja: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z ja monia muita</li>
      <li>Tiedoston sisällön esikatselu purkamatta tiedostoa</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Ark est un utilitaire graphique de compression / décompression de fichiers prenant en charge de multiples formats, notamment tar, gzip, bzip2, rar et zip, ainsi que les images de CD-ROM. Ark peut être utilisé pour parcourir, extraire, créer et modifier des archives.</p>
    <p>Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Plusieurs formats sont pris en charge : gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z et d'autres</li>
      <li>Affichage du contenu des fichiers sans les extraire</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Ark é unha ferramenta gráfica de compresión e descompresión de ficheiros compatíbel con múltiplos formatos, como «tar», «gzip», «bzip2», «rar» e «zip», así como imaxes de CD-ROM. Ark pode usarse para navegar, extraer, crear e modificar arquivos.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Compatíbel con moitos formatos: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z e máis.</li>
      <li>Obteña unha vista previa dos ficheiros comprimidos sen extraelos.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>‏Ark הוא יישום גרפי לדחיסה וחילוץ ארכיונים עם תמיכה בפורמטים שונים, כולל tar, gzip, bzip2, rar ו־zip, כמו כן בקובצי תמונת דיסק. Ark משומש לדפדוף, חילוץ, יצירה ושינוי ארכיונים.</p>
    <p>תכונות:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>מספר פורמטים נתמכים: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z ועוד</li>
      <li>הצג את תוכן הקובץ ללא חילוץ הקבצים</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>Az Ark egy grafikus fájltömörítő és kibontó segédprogram többféle formátum támogatásával, beleértve a tar, gzip, bzip2, rar és zip formátumokat, valamint a CD-ROM képfájlokat. Az Ark használható archívumok böngészéséhez, kibontásához, létrehozásához és módosításához.</p>
    <p>Szolgáltatások:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Számos formátum támogatott: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z és továbbiak</li>
      <li>Fájltartalom előnézete a fájlok kibontása nélkül</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ia">
    <p>Ark es un utilitate graphic de compression/decompression de file con supporto per formatos multiple, includente tar, gzip, bzip2, rar e zip, tal como images de CD-ROM. Ark pote esser usate per navigar, extraher, crear e modificar archivos.</p>
    <p>Characteristicas:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Plure formatos supportate: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z e altere</li>
      <li>Contentos de file de previsualisation sin extraher files</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Ark adalah utilitas kompresi/dekompresi file grafis dengan dukungan untuk berbagai format, termasuk tar, gzip, bzip2, rar dan zip, serta citra CD-ROM. Ark dapat digunakan untuk menelusuri, mengekstrak, menciptakan, dan memodifikasi arsip.</p>
    <p>Fitur:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>beberapa format yang didukung: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z dan banyak lagi</li>
      <li>Pratinjau konten file tanpa mengekstrak filenya</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Ark è uno strumento grafico per la compressione/decompressione dei file che supporta molti formati, tra i quali tar, gzip, bzip2, rar e zip, così come le immagini dei CD-ROM. Ark può essere utilizzato per sfogliare, estrarre, creare e modificare archivi.</p>
    <p>Funzionalità:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Diversi formati supportati: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z e altri</li>
      <li>Anteprima dei file senza estrarre i file</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>特徴:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>gzip、bzip2、zip、rar、7z などの様々な形式をサポートしています</li>
      <li>ファイルを展開せずにファイルの内容をプレビュー</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>Ark는 그래픽 압축 파일 관리 도구이며, tar, gzip, bzip2, rar, zip, CD-ROM 이미지 등 여러 파일 형식을 지원합니다. Ark를 사용하여 압축 파일을 열고, 생성하고, 수정하고, 압축을 풀 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p>기능:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>다양한 형식 지원: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z 등</li>
      <li>압축 풀지 않고 파일 내용 미리 보기</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Galimybės:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Ark er et verktøy med grafisk brukerflate, for komprimering/dekomprimering, med støtte for mange formater, deriblant tar, gzip, rar og zip, samt CD-ROM-bilder. Ark kan brukes til å bla i, pakke opp, opprette og endre arkiver.</p>
    <p>Egenskaper:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Mange formater støttet: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z og mer</li>
      <li>Forhåndsvis innhold uten å pakke ut filer</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nds">
    <p>Ark is en graafsch Komprimeer- un Dekomprimeerwarktüüch, dat en Barg Formaten ünnerstütten deit. Dor sünd tar, gzip, bzip2, rar un zip bi, un ok CD-ROM-Afbiller. Mit Ark kannst Du Archiven dörkieken, opstellen un ännern un Dateien dor ruttrecken.</p>
    <p>Markmalen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>En Reeg Fomaten warrt ünnerstütt: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z un anner</li>
      <li>Datein ahn Ruttrecken vörweg ankieken</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Ark is een grafisch hulpmiddel om bestanden te comprimeren/uit te pakken met ondersteuning van meerdere formaten, inclusief tar, gzip, bzip2, rar en zip, evenals cd-ROM images. Ark kan gebruikt worden om door archieven te bladeren, deze uit te pakken, te maken en te wijzigen.</p>
    <p>Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ondersteuning voor een aantal formaten: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z en meer</li>
      <li>Voorvertoning van inhoud van bestand zonder bestanden uit te pakken</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>Ark er eit grafisk filkomprimerings- og dekomprimeringsverktøy med støtte for ulike format, blant anna tar, gzip, bzip2, rar, zip og CD-ROM-bilete. Det kan brukast til å sjå gjennom, pakka ut, laga eller endra filarkiv.</p>
    <p>Funksjonar:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Støtte for fleire format, blant anna gzip, bzip2, zip, rar og 7z</li>
      <li>Førehandsvising av filinnhald utan fullstendig utpakking</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pa">
    <p>ਲੱਛਣ:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Ark jest graficznym narzędziem do pakowania/rozpakowywania plików wraz z obsługą różnych formatów, włączając w to tar, gzip, bzip2, rar oraz zip, a także obrazy CD-ROM. Programu Ark można używać do przeglądania, tworzenia, zmieniania oraz wydobywania z archiwów</p>
    <p>Cechy:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Obsługa kilku formatów: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z oraz więcej</li>
      <li>Podejrzyj zawartość pliku bez jego wypakowywania</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Ark é um utilitário de compressão/descompressão com o suporte para diversos formatos, incluindo o 'tar', 'gzip', 'bzip2', 'rar' e 'zip', assim como imagens de CD-ROM. O Ark pode ser usado para navegar, extrair, criar e modificar esses pacotes.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Diversos formatos suportados: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z, entre outros</li>
      <li>Antevisão do conteúdo dos ficheiros sem os extrair</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>O Ark é um utilitário de compressão/descompressão com o suporte a diversos formatos, incluindo tar, gzip, bzip2, rar e zip, assim como imagens de CD-ROM. O Ark pode ser usado para navegar, extrair, criar e modificar esses arquivos.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Diversos formatos suportados: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z, entre outros</li>
      <li>Visualização do conteúdo dos arquivos sem precisar extraí-los</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Ark este un utilitar grafic de comprimare/decomprimare cu suport pentru formate multiple, inclusiv tar, gzip, bzip2, rar și zip, precum și imagini CD-ROM. Ark poate fi folosit pentru a răsfoi, extrage, crea și modifica arhive.</p>
    <p>Caracteristici:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Câteva formate susținute: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z și altele</li>
      <li>Previzualizează conținutul fișierelor fără a le extrage</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Ark — графическая утилита для упаковки и распаковки файлов, поддерживающая множество форматов архивов, включая TAR, GZIP, BZip2, RAR, ZIP и образы компакт-дисков. Ark позволяет просматривать, распаковывать, создавать и редактировать архивы.</p>
    <p>Возможности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Поддержка нескольких форматов: GZIP, BZip2, ZIP, RAR, 7z и другие</li>
      <li>Предварительный просмотр содержимого файлов из архива без их сохранения на диск.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Ark je grafický nástroj na kompresiu a dekompresiu súborov s podporou pre mnoho formátov, vrátane tar, gzip bzip2, rar a zip, ako ako CD-ROM obrazy. Ark sa dá použiť na prehliadanie, rozbaľovanie vytváranie a úpravu archívov.</p>
    <p>Funkcie:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Niektoré z podporovaných formátov: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z a viac</li>
      <li>Náhľad obsahu súboru bez rozbalenia súborov</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Ark je grafično orodje za stiskanje/razširjanje datotek, ki podpira večje število arhivov (med podprtimi so tudi tar, gzip, bzip2, rar in zip) kot tudi odtise CD-ROM. Ark lahko uporabite za brskanje po, razširjanje, ustvarjanje in spreminjanje arhivov.</p>
    <p>Zmožnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Številne podprte vrste arhivov: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z in druge</li>
      <li>Predogled vsebine datoteke brez razširjanja</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Арк је графичка алатка за компресовање и декомпресовање фајлова. Подржава више формата, међу њима и: тар, гзип, бзип2, РАР, ЗИП, као и ЦД одразе. Може се користити за прегледање, распакивање, стварање и мењање архива.</p>
    <p>Могућности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Више подржаних формата: гзип, бзип2, ЗИП, РАР, 7зип, итд.</li>
      <li>Преглед садржаја фајлова без распакивања.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-Latn">
    <p>Ark je grafička alatka za kompresovanje i dekompresovanje fajlova. Podržava više formata, među njima i: tar, gzip, bzip2, RAR, ZIP, kao i CD odraze. Može se koristiti za pregledanje, raspakivanje, stvaranje i menjanje arhiva.</p>
    <p>Mogućnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Više podržanih formata: gzip, bzip2, ZIP, RAR, 7zip, itd.</li>
      <li>Pregled sadržaja fajlova bez raspakivanja.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-ijekavian">
    <p>Арк је графичка алатка за компресовање и декомпресовање фајлова. Подржава више формата, међу њима и: тар, гзип, бзип2, РАР, ЗИП, као и ЦД одразе. Може се користити за прегледање, распакивање, стварање и мењање архива.</p>
    <p>Могућности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Више подржаних формата: гзип, бзип2, ЗИП, РАР, 7зип, итд.</li>
      <li>Преглед садржаја фајлова без распакивања.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">
    <p>Ark je grafička alatka za kompresovanje i dekompresovanje fajlova. Podržava više formata, među njima i: tar, gzip, bzip2, RAR, ZIP, kao i CD odraze. Može se koristiti za pregledanje, raspakivanje, stvaranje i menjanje arhiva.</p>
    <p>Mogućnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Više podržanih formata: gzip, bzip2, ZIP, RAR, 7zip, itd.</li>
      <li>Pregled sadržaja fajlova bez raspakivanja.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Ark är ett grafiskt verktyg för komprimering och uppackning av filer med stöd för flera format, inklusive tar, gzip, bzip2, rar och zip, samt cd-rom avbilder. Ark kan användas för att bläddra i, packa upp, skapa och ändra arkiv.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>En mängd format stöds: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z med flera</li>
      <li>Förhandsgranska filinnehåll utan att packa upp filer</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Ark; tar, gzip, bzip2, rar ve zip dosyalarının yanında CD-ROM kalıplarını da destekleyen grafiksel bir dosya sıkıştırma/açma yardımcısıdır. Ark arşivlerde gezinmek, arşiv ayıklamak, oluşturmak ve değiştirmek için kullanılabilir.</p>
    <p>Özellikler:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Çeşitli biçimler desteklenir: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z ve dahası</li>
      <li>Dosyaları ayıklamadan dosya içeriği önizlemesi</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Ark — програма з графічним інтерфейсом, призначена для стискання даних у архіви та видобування даних з архівів. Передбачено підтримку декількох форматів архівів, зокрема tar, gzip, bzip2, rar та zip, а також образів дисків. Ark можна використовувати для перегляду, видобування, створення та внесення змін до архівів.</p>
    <p>Можливості:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Підтримка декількох форматів: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z тощо</li>
      <li>Попередній перегляд вмісту файлів без розпаковування</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxArk is a graphical file compression/decompression utility with support for multiple formats, including tar, gzip, bzip2, rar and zip, as well as CD-ROM images. Ark can be used to browse, extract, create, and modify archives.xx</p>
    <p>xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>xxSeveral formats supported: gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z and morexx</li>
      <li>xxPreview file contents without extracting filesxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>Ark 是一款具备图形界面的文件压缩/解压缩工具。它支持多种格式，包括 tar、gzip、bzip2、rar、zip 和 CD-ROM 镜像文件等。您可以使用 Ark 来浏览、解压、创建和修改各种压缩包文件。</p>
    <p>程序功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>支持多种格式：gzip、bzip2、zip、rar 和 7z 等</li>
      <li>无需解压即可预览压缩包内容</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-TW">
    <p>Ark 是一套圖形介面的檔案壓縮/解壓縮工具，支援多種格式，包括 tar, gzip, bzip2, rar 與 zip 等，還有 CD-ROM 映像檔等。Ark 有瀏覽、解開、建立與變更壓縮檔的功能。</p>
    <p>功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>支援格式：gzip, bzip2, zip, rar, 7z 等等</li>
      <li>不需解壓縮即可預覽檔案內容</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.ark</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.ark.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" height="64" type="cached">ark.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" type="cached" width="128">ark.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.ark.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Ark</name>
  <name lang="ar">آرك</name>
  <name lang="ast">Ark</name>
  <name lang="az">Ark</name>
  <name lang="bg">Ark</name>
  <name lang="bs">Ark</name>
  <name lang="ca">Ark</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">Ark</name>
  <name lang="cs">Ark</name>
  <name lang="da">Ark</name>
  <name lang="de">Ark</name>
  <name lang="el">Ark</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">Ark</name>
  <name lang="es">Ark</name>
  <name lang="et">Ark</name>
  <name lang="eu">Ark</name>
  <name lang="fi">Ark</name>
  <name lang="fr">Ark</name>
  <name lang="gl">Ark</name>
  <name lang="he">Ark</name>
  <name lang="hu">Ark</name>
  <name lang="ia">Ark</name>
  <name lang="id">Ark</name>
  <name lang="it">Ark</name>
  <name lang="ja">Ark</name>
  <name lang="ko">Ark</name>
  <name lang="lt">Ark</name>
  <name lang="nb">Ark</name>
  <name lang="nds">Ark</name>
  <name lang="nl">Ark</name>
  <name lang="nn">Ark</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਆਕ</name>
  <name lang="pl">Ark</name>
  <name lang="pt">Ark</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">Ark</name>
  <name lang="ro">Ark</name>
  <name lang="ru">Ark</name>
  <name lang="sk">Ark</name>
  <name lang="sl">Ark</name>
  <name lang="sr">Арк</name>
  <name lang="sr-Latn">Ark</name>
  <name lang="sr-ijekavian">Арк</name>
  <name lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Ark</name>
  <name lang="sv">Ark</name>
  <name lang="tr">Ark</name>
  <name lang="uk">Ark</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxArkxx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">Ark 压缩包管理工具</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">Ark</name>
  <summary>Archiving Tool</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">أداة أرشفة</summary>
  <summary lang="ast">Ferramienta p'archivar</summary>
  <summary lang="az">Arxivləmə Aləti</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Работа с архиви</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Alat za arhiviranje</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Eina d'arxivament</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Eina d'arxivament</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Archivační nástroj</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Arkiveringsværktøj</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Archivprogramm</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Εργαλείο αρχειοθέτησης</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Archiving Tool</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Herramienta de archivado</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Arhiivide haldamise rakendus</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Artxibatzeko tresna</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Pakkausohjelma</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Outil d'archivage</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Ferramenta para arquivar</summary>
  <summary lang="he">כלי לניהול ארכיונים</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Fájltömörítő</summary>
  <summary lang="ia">Instrumento per archivar</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Alat Pengarsipan</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Strumento di archiviazione</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">アーカイブツール</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">압축 도구</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Archyvavimo įrankis</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Arkiveringsverktøy</summary>
  <summary lang="nds">Archievwarktüüch</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Archiefgereedschap</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Arkiveringsverktøy</summary>
  <summary lang="pa">ਅਕਾਇਵ ਬਣਾਉਣ ਟੂਲ</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Narzędzie do archiwizowania</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Ferramenta de Arquivo</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Ferramenta de arquivamento</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Utilitar de arhivare</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Архиватор файлов</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Archivačný nástroj</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Orodje za ravnanje z arhivi</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Алатка за архивирање</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-Latn">Alatka za arhiviranje</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-ijekavian">Алатка за архивирање</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Alatka za arhiviranje</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Arkiveringsverktyg</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Arşivleme Aracı</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Інструмент роботи з архівами</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxArchiving Toolxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">压缩文件管理工具</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-TW">壓縮工具</summary>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Managing archives with Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">يدير الأرشيفات بواسطة ارك</caption>
      <caption lang="ast">Xestión d'archivos con Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="az">Arxivlərin Ark ilə idarə edilməsi</caption>
      <caption lang="bg">Управление на архиви с Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Gestió d'arxius amb l'Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Gestió d'arxius amb Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Správa archivů pomocí Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Håndtering af arkiver med Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Verwaltung von Archiven mit Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Διαχείριση αρχειοθηκών με το Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">Managing archives with Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Gestión de archivos comprimidos con Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Arhiivide haldamine Arkis</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Ark erabiliz artxiboak kudeatzea</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Hallitse arkistoja Arkilla</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Gestion d'archives avec Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Xestionando arquivos con Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Archívumok kezelése az Arkkal</caption>
      <caption lang="ia">Gerer archivos con Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Mengelola arsip dengan Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Gestione archivi con Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">Ark でアーカイブを管理</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">Ark로 압축 파일 관리</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Archieven beheren met Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="nn">Handsaming av arkiv med Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Zarządzanie archiwami w Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">A gerir pacotes com Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Gerenciando arquivos compactados com o Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="ro">Gestiunea arhivelor cu Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Управление архивами в Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Spravovanie archívov s Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Upravljanje arhivov z Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Hantera arkiv med Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Ark ile arşivleri yönetme</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Керування архівами за допомогою Ark</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxManaging archives with Arkxx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-CN">使用 Ark 来管理压缩包文件</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-TW">使用 Ark 管理封存檔</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/ark/ark.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/ark</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=ark</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=ark</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=ark&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <update_contact>kde-utils-devel_AT_kde.org</update_contact>
  <provides>
    <binary>ark</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="22.04.3" date="2022-07-07" />
    <release version="22.04.2" date="2022-06-09" />
    <release date="2022-05-12" version="22.04.1" />
    <release version="22.04.0" date="2022-04-21" />
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>