<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.kolourpaint</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kolourpaint.desktop</launchable>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">kolourpaint.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" width="128" type="cached">kolourpaint.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.kolourpaint.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>BSD-2-Clause and LGPL-2.0+ and GFDL-1.2</project_license>
  <name>KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="ar">الرسام</name>
  <name lang="bg">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="bs">KolurPaint</name>
  <name lang="ca">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="cs">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="da">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="de">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="el">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="es">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="et">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="eu">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="fi">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="fr">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="gl">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="hu">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="ia">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="id">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="it">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="ko">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="lt">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="nb">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="nds">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="nl">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="nn">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="pl">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="pt">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="ru">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="sk">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="sl">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="sv">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="tr">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="uk">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxKolourPaintxx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">KolourPaint</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">KolourPaint</name>
  <summary>Paint Program</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">برنامج تلوين</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Програма за рисуване</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Program za slikanje</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Programa de dibuix</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Programa de dibuix</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Program pro malování</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Tegneprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Mal- und Zeichenprogramm</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Πρόγραμμα ζωγραφικής</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Paint Program</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Programa de dibujo</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Joonistamisrakendus</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Marrazteko programa</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Piirto-ohjelma</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Logiciel de dessin</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Programa para pintar</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Rajzolóprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="ia">Programma per pinger</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Program Lukis</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Programma di disegno</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">그리기 프로그램</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Piešimo programa</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Malepogram</summary>
  <summary lang="nds">Maalprogramm</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Tekenprogramma</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Teikneprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Program Paint</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Programa de Pintura</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Programa de desenho</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Простой редактор изображений</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Kresliaci program</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Program za risanje</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Ritprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Boyama Programı</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Програма для малювання</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxPaint Programxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">绘图程序</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-TW">繪圖程式</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KolourPaint is a simple painting program to quickly create raster images.
      It is useful as a touch-up tool and simple image editing tasks.
    </p>
    <p lang="ar">الرسام هو برنامج رسم بسيط لإنشاء صور نقطية بسرعة. إنه مفيد كأداة تحسين ومهام بسيطة لتحرير الصور.</p>
    <p lang="bg">KolourPaint е проста програма за рисуване на растерни изображения. Тя е полезна като инструмент за ретуширане и при стандартни задачи за редактиране на изображения. </p>
    <p lang="bs">KolourPaint je jednostavan crtaći program za brzo staranje rasterskih slika. On je koristan kao sredstvo retuširanja i jednostavne zadatke za uređivanje slika.</p>
    <p lang="ca">El KolourPaint és un programa senzill de dibuix per a crear ràpidament imatges ràster. És útil com a eina de retoc i tasques senzilles per a l'edició d'imatges.</p>
    <p lang="ca-valencia">KolourPaint és un programa senzill de dibuix per a crear ràpidament imatges ràster. És útil com a eina de retoc i tasques senzilles per a l'edició d'imatges.</p>
    <p lang="da">KolourPaint er et simpelt tegneprogram til hurtigt at skabe raster-billeder. Det er et nyttigt værktøj til at tegne skitser eller udføre simple billedredigeringsopgaver.</p>
    <p lang="de">KolourPaint ist ein einfach zu benutzendes Mal- und Zeichenprogramm um schnell Rasterbilder zu erstellen. Es kann für die Korrektur und einfache Bildbearbeitungsaufgaben benutzt werden.</p>
    <p lang="el">Το KolourPaint είναι λενα απλό πρόγραμμα ζωραφικής για τη γρήγορη δημιουργία εικόνων χρωματικής περίπλεξης. Χρησιμεύει ως διορθωτικό και για απλές εργασίες επεξεργασίας εικόνων.</p>
    <p lang="en-GB">KolourPaint is a simple painting program to quickly create raster images. It is useful as a touch-up tool and simple image editing tasks.</p>
    <p lang="es">KolourPaint es un sencillo programa de dibujo que permite crear imágenes de mapas de bits de una forma rápida. Resulta útil como herramienta de retoque y para tareas de edición sencillas.</p>
    <p lang="et">KolourPaint on lihtne joonistamisrakendus rasterpiltide kiireks loomiseks. Sellega on hõlpus luua visandeid ja täita lihtsamaid piltide töötlemise ülesandeid.</p>
    <p lang="eu">KolourPaint margotzeko aplikazio xume bat da, «raster» irudiak azkar sortzeko balio duena. Baliagarria da berrukipen tresna gisa eta oinarrizko irudi editatzeko atazetarako.</p>
    <p lang="fi">KolourPaint on yksinkertainen piirto-ohjelma, jolla voi luoda nopeasti bittikartakuvia. Sitä voi käyttää myös kuvien parantamiseen ja yksinkertaiseen kuvankäsittelyyn.</p>
    <p lang="fr">KolourPaint est logiciel de dessin simple qui permet de créer rapidement des images. Il est pratique pour retoucher ou modifier simplement des images.</p>
    <p lang="gl">KolourPaint é un programa para pintar sinxelo que permite crear imaxes de mapa de bits rapidamente. É útil como ferramenta de retoque e para realizar tarefas sinxelas de edición de imaxes.</p>
    <p lang="hu">A KolourPaint egy egyszerű rajzolóprogram raszteres képek gyors létrehozásához. Hasznos retusálóeszközként és egyszerű képszerkesztő feladatokhoz.</p>
    <p lang="ia">KolourPAint es un simple programma per pinger o designar  per crear rapidemente imagines raster. Il es utile como instrumento de retocco e per cargas simplice de modificar imagines.</p>
    <p lang="id">KolourPaint adalah program melukis sederhana untuk membuat gambar raster dengan cepat. Ini berguna sebagai alat bantu dan tugas pengeditan gambar sederhana.</p>
    <p lang="it">KolourPaint è un semplice programma di disegno per la creazione rapida di immagini. È utile come strumento da usare «al volo» e per effettuare semplici modifiche alle immagini.</p>
    <p lang="ko">KolourPaint는 래스터 그림을 빠르게 만드는 프로그램입니다. 간단한 보정 도구 및 편집 도구로 사용할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p lang="nb">KolourPaint er et enkelt maleprogram som kjapt kan lage rasterbilder. Det er et nyttig verktøy for retusjering og enkle redigeringsoppgaver.</p>
    <p lang="nds">KolourPaint is en eenfach Maalprogramm, mit dat sik gau Pixelbiller opstellen laat. Dat is goot för lütte Utbetern un eenfache Bildbewerken.</p>
    <p lang="nl">KolourPaint is een eenvoudig tekenprogramma om snel rasterafbeeldingen te maken. Het is nuttig als een hulpmiddel voor bijwerken en eenvoudige taken voor bewerking van afbeeldingen.</p>
    <p lang="nn">KolourPaint er eit enkelt teikne­program for punkt­grafikk. Det er eit nyttig verktøy for retusjering og enkle redigerings­oppgåver.</p>
    <p lang="pl">KolourPaint jest prostym programem do malowania i szybkiego tworzenia obrazów rastrowych. Jest przydatny przy retuszowaniu i prostych pracach edytowania.</p>
    <p lang="pt">O KolourPaint é um programa simples de pintura que cria rapidamente imagens rasterizadas. É útil como uma ferramenta de retoques e para tarefas simples de edição de imagens.</p>
    <p lang="pt-BR">KolourPaint é um programa de desenho simples, que cria rapidamente imagens rasterizadas. É útil como uma ferramenta de retoques e para tarefas simples de edição de imagens.</p>
    <p lang="ru">KolourPaint — простая программа для рисования и создания растровых изображений. Может быть полезна для внесения небольших правок в изображения.</p>
    <p lang="sk">KolourPaint je jednoduchý kresliaci program na rýchlu tvorbu rastrových obrázkov. Je užitočný ako touch-up nástroj a na jednoduché úpravy obrázkov.</p>
    <p lang="sl">KolourPaint je preprost program za risanje in hitro ustvarjanje rastrskih slik. Uporaben je za izboljšave slik in preprosto urejanje slik.</p>
    <p lang="sv">KolourPaint är ett enkelt ritprogram för att snabbt skapa punktavbildningar. Det är användbart som förbättringsverktyg och för enkla bildredigeringsuppgifter.</p>
    <p lang="tr">KolourPaint hızlıca taramalı resimler oluşturabileceğiniz basit bir boyama programıdır. Bir rötuş aracı ve basit resim düzenleme görevleri için yararlıdır.</p>
    <p lang="uk">KolourPaint — проста програма для малювання, за допомогою якої можна швидко створювати растрові зображення. Ця програма може бути корисною для виконання простих завдань з редагування зображень.</p>
    <p lang="x-test">xxKolourPaint is a simple painting program to quickly create raster images. It is useful as a touch-up tool and simple image editing tasks.xx</p>
    <p lang="zh-CN">KolourPaint 是一个简单易用的绘图程序，可以创建点阵图像。可用来对图片进行润色和简单编辑。</p>
    <p lang="zh-TW">KolourPaint 是一套類似小畫家的簡易繪圖程式。</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p lang="ar">الميزات:</p>
    <p lang="bg">Функции:</p>
    <p lang="bs">Svojstva:</p>
    <p lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p lang="da">Funktioner:</p>
    <p lang="de">Leistungsmerkmale:</p>
    <p lang="el">Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <p lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p lang="es">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p lang="eu">Eginbideak:</p>
    <p lang="fi">Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <p lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p lang="hu">Szolgáltatások:</p>
    <p lang="ia">Characteristicas:</p>
    <p lang="id">Fitur:</p>
    <p lang="it">Caratteristiche:</p>
    <p lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p lang="lt">Galimybės:</p>
    <p lang="nb">Funksjoner:</p>
    <p lang="nds">Markmalen:</p>
    <p lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p lang="nn">Funksjonar:</p>
    <p lang="pl">Cechy:</p>
    <p lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p lang="tr">Özellikler:</p>
    <p lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p lang="zh-CN">功能：</p>
    <p lang="zh-TW">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Support for drawing various shapes - lines, rectangles, rounded rectangles, ovals and polygons</li>
      <li lang="ar">دعم لرسم أشكال مختلفة - خطوط ومستطيلات ومستطيلات مستديرة الشكل وأشكال بيضاوية ومضلعات</li>
      <li lang="bg">Поддръжка на чертане на различни фигури - линии, правоъгълници, овали и полигони. </li>
      <li lang="bs">Podrška za crtanje raznih oblika - linija, pravougaonika, zaobljenih pravougaonika, ovala i poligona</li>
      <li lang="ca">Permet dibuixar diverses formes: línies, rectangles, rectangles arrodonits, ovals i polígons</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Permet dibuixar diverses formes: línies, rectangles, rectangles arredonits, ovals i polígons</li>
      <li lang="da">Understøtter at tegne diverse former - linjer, firkanter, afrundede firkanter, ovaler og polygoner</li>
      <li lang="de">Das Zeichnen verschiedener Objekte wie Linien, Rechtecke, abgerundete Rechtecke, Ellipsen und Polygone wird unterstützt.</li>
      <li lang="el">Υποστήριξη για σχεδίαση διαφόρων σχημάτων - ευθείες, ορθογώνια παραλληλόγραμμα, στρογγυλεμένα ορθογώνια, ελλείψεις και πολύγωνα</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Support for drawing various shapes - lines, rectangles, rounded rectangles, ovals and polygons</li>
      <li lang="es">Permite dibujar distintas formas (líneas, rectángulos, rectángulos de esquinas redondeadas, óvalos y polígonos)</li>
      <li lang="et">Mitmesuguste kujundite joonistamise toetus: jooned, ristkülikud, ümarnurksed ristkülikud, ovaalid, hulknurgad</li>
      <li lang="eu">Hainbat forma marraztu ditzake - lerroak, laukizuzenak, laukizuzen borobilduak, obaloak eta poligonoak</li>
      <li lang="fi">Piirtämistuki useille muodoille – viivoille, suorakaiteille, pyöristetyille suorakaiteille, ellipseille ja monikulmioille</li>
      <li lang="fr">Dessin de formes variées : lignes, rectangles, rectangles à bords arrondis, ovales, polygones</li>
      <li lang="gl">Permite debuxar varias formas: liñas, rectángulos, rectángulos arredondados, óvalos e polígonos.</li>
      <li lang="hu">Különféle alakzatok rajzolásának támogatása - vonalak, téglalapok, lekerekített téglalapok, oválisok és sokszögek</li>
      <li lang="ia">Supporto pro designar varie formas - lineas, rectangulos, rectangulos tundite, ovales e polygonos</li>
      <li lang="id">Dukungan untuk menggambar berbagai bentuk - garis, persegi panjang, persegi panjang, bulat, oval dan poligon</li>
      <li lang="it">Supporto per il disegno di varie forme - linee, rettangoli, rettangoli arrotondati, ovali e poligoni</li>
      <li lang="ko">다양한 도형 그리기 - 직선, 사각형, 둥근 사각형, 타원형, 다각형</li>
      <li lang="nb">Støtte for å tegne mange former – linjer, rektangler, avrundede rektangler, ovaler og polygoner</li>
      <li lang="nds">Ünnerstütt dat Teken vun en Reeg vun Formen - Lienen, Rechtecks, afrundt Rechtecks, Ovalen un Veelecks</li>
      <li lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor het tekenen van verschillende vormen - lijnen, rechthoeken, afgeronde rechthoeken, ovalen en polygonen</li>
      <li lang="nn">Støtte for å teikna mange former – linjer, rektangel, avrunda rektangel, ellipsar og mangekantar</li>
      <li lang="pl">Obsługa rysowania rozmaitych kształtów - proste, prostokąty, zaokrąglone prostokąty, owale i wielokąty</li>
      <li lang="pt">Suporte para desenhar várias formas - linhas, rectângulos, rectângulos arredondados, ovais e polígonos</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Suporte para desenhar várias formas - linhas, retângulos, retângulos arredondados, ovais e polígonos</li>
      <li lang="ru">Рисование различных фигур: отрезков, прямоугольников, скруглённых прямоугольников, овалов и многоугольников</li>
      <li lang="sk">Podpora pre kreslenie rôznych tvarov - čiary, obdĺžniky, zaoblené obdĺžniky, ovály a polygóny</li>
      <li lang="sl">Podpora risanju različnih oblik - črt, pravokotnikov, zaobljenih pravokotnikov, ovalov in mnogokotnikov</li>
      <li lang="sv">Stöd för att rita diverse former: linjer, rektanglar, rundade rektanglar, ovaler och polygoner</li>
      <li lang="tr">Çeşitli şekiller, çizgiler, dörtgenler, yuvarlatılmış dörtgenler, ovaller ve poligonlar desteği</li>
      <li lang="uk">Підтримка малювання різноманітних форм: прямих, прямокутників, прямокутників із заокругленими кутами, овалів та багатокутників.</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxSupport for drawing various shapes - lines, rectangles, rounded rectangles, ovals and polygonsxx</li>
      <li lang="zh-CN">支持绘制各种图形 - 直线、正方向、圆角正方形、椭圆和多边形</li>
      <li lang="zh-TW">支援繪出不同的形狀 -- 線條、矩形、圓角矩形、橢圓與多邊形等</li>
      <li>Curves, lines and text</li>
      <li lang="ar">المنحنيات والخطوط والنص</li>
      <li lang="bg">Криви, линии и текст</li>
      <li lang="bs">Krive, linije i tekst</li>
      <li lang="ca">Corbes, línies i text</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Corbes, línies i text</li>
      <li lang="cs">Křivky, čáry a text</li>
      <li lang="da">Kurver, linjer og tekst</li>
      <li lang="de">Kurven, Linien und Text</li>
      <li lang="el">Καμπύλες, ευθείες και κείμενο</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Curves, lines and text</li>
      <li lang="es">Curvas, líneas y texto</li>
      <li lang="et">Kõverad, sirged ja tekst</li>
      <li lang="eu">Kurbak, lerroak eta testua</li>
      <li lang="fi">Käyrät, viivat ja teksti</li>
      <li lang="fr">Courbes, lignes et textes</li>
      <li lang="gl">Curvas, liñas e texto.</li>
      <li lang="hu">Görbék, vonalak és szöveg</li>
      <li lang="ia">Curvas, lineas e texto</li>
      <li lang="id">Lengkung, garis, dan teks</li>
      <li lang="it">Curve, linee e testo</li>
      <li lang="ko">곡선, 직선 및 텍스트</li>
      <li lang="lt">Kreivės, tiesės ir tekstas</li>
      <li lang="nb">Kurver, linjer og tekst</li>
      <li lang="nds">Bagens, Lienen un Text</li>
      <li lang="nl">Krommen, lijnen en tekst</li>
      <li lang="nn">Kurver, linjer og tekst</li>
      <li lang="pl">Krzywe, proste i teks</li>
      <li lang="pt">Curvas, linhas e texto</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Curvas, linhas e texto</li>
      <li lang="ru">Рисование гладких кривых, произвольных линий и вставка текста</li>
      <li lang="sk">Krivky, čiary a text</li>
      <li lang="sl">Krivulje, črte in besedilo</li>
      <li lang="sv">Kurvor, linjer och text</li>
      <li lang="tr">Eğriler, çizgiler ve metin</li>
      <li lang="uk">Можливість малювання кривих, прямих та тексту.</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxCurves, lines and textxx</li>
      <li lang="zh-CN">曲线，直线和文本</li>
      <li lang="zh-TW">曲線、線條與文字</li>
      <li>Colour picker</li>
      <li lang="ar">منتق الألوان</li>
      <li lang="bg">Избор на цвят</li>
      <li lang="bs">Dobavljač boja</li>
      <li lang="ca">Selector de color</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Selector de color</li>
      <li lang="cs">Kapátko</li>
      <li lang="da">Farvevælger</li>
      <li lang="de">Farbwähler</li>
      <li lang="el">Επιλογέας χρωμάτων</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Colour picker</li>
      <li lang="es">Selección de color</li>
      <li lang="et">Värvivalija</li>
      <li lang="eu">Kolore hautatzailea</li>
      <li lang="fi">Värivalitsin</li>
      <li lang="fr">Sélecteur de couleur</li>
      <li lang="gl">Selector de cor</li>
      <li lang="hu">Színválasztó</li>
      <li lang="ia">Selector de color</li>
      <li lang="id">Penukil warna</li>
      <li lang="it">Selettore del colore</li>
      <li lang="ko">색 선택기</li>
      <li lang="lt">Spalvų parinkiklis</li>
      <li lang="nb">Fargevelger</li>
      <li lang="nds">Klöörköör</li>
      <li lang="nl">Kleurkiezer</li>
      <li lang="nn">Fargeveljar</li>
      <li lang="pl">Wybierak barwy</li>
      <li lang="pt">Selecção de cores</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Seleção de cor</li>
      <li lang="ru">Окно палитры</li>
      <li lang="sk">Výber farieb</li>
      <li lang="sl">Izbirnik barv</li>
      <li lang="sv">Färgväljare</li>
      <li lang="tr">Renk seçici</li>
      <li lang="uk">Піпетка для отримання кольору із зображення.</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxColour pickerxx</li>
      <li lang="zh-CN">颜色拾取器</li>
      <li lang="zh-TW">顏色挑選器</li>
      <li>Selections</li>
      <li lang="ar">التّحديدات</li>
      <li lang="bg">Селекции</li>
      <li lang="bs">Selekcije</li>
      <li lang="ca">Seleccions</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Seleccions</li>
      <li lang="cs">Výběry</li>
      <li lang="da">Markeringer</li>
      <li lang="de">Mehre Auswahlarten</li>
      <li lang="el">Επιλογές</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Selections</li>
      <li lang="es">Selecciones</li>
      <li lang="et">Valikud</li>
      <li lang="eu">Hautapenak</li>
      <li lang="fi">Valintatyökalu</li>
      <li lang="fr">Sélections</li>
      <li lang="gl">Seleccións</li>
      <li lang="hu">Kijelölések</li>
      <li lang="ia">Selectiones</li>
      <li lang="id">Pemilihan</li>
      <li lang="it">Selezioni</li>
      <li lang="ko">선택</li>
      <li lang="lt">Žymėjimai</li>
      <li lang="nb">Utvalg</li>
      <li lang="nds">Köören</li>
      <li lang="nl">Selecties</li>
      <li lang="nn">Utval</li>
      <li lang="pl">Zaznaczenia</li>
      <li lang="pt">Selecções</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Seleções</li>
      <li lang="ru">Выделение областей</li>
      <li lang="sk">Výbery</li>
      <li lang="sl">Izbire</li>
      <li lang="sv">Markeringar</li>
      <li lang="tr">Seçimler</li>
      <li lang="uk">Можливість позначення ділянок зображення.</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxSelectionsxx</li>
      <li lang="zh-CN">选择</li>
      <li lang="zh-TW">選取區</li>
      <li>Rotation, monochrome and other advanced effects</li>
      <li lang="ar">دوران ، أحادية اللون وتأثيرات متقدمة أخرى</li>
      <li lang="bg">Ротация, монохромност и други ефекти</li>
      <li lang="bs">Rotacija, monohrom i drugi napredni efekti</li>
      <li lang="ca">Gir, monocrom i altres efectes avançats</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Gir, monocrom i altres efectes avançats</li>
      <li lang="da">Rotation, monokrom og andre avancerede effekter</li>
      <li lang="de">Drehung, Umwandlung in Schwarzweiß und weitere Effekte können angewendet werden</li>
      <li lang="el">Περιστροφή, μονοχρωμία και άλλα προηγμένα εφέ</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Rotation, monochrome and other advanced effects</li>
      <li lang="es">Rotación, conversión a monocromo y otros efectos avanzados</li>
      <li lang="et">Pööramine, ühevärvilisus ja veel mõned efektid</li>
      <li lang="eu">Biraketa, monokromoa eta beste efektu aurreratu batzuk</li>
      <li lang="fi">Kierto, pelkistäminen yksiväriseksi sekä muita tehosteita</li>
      <li lang="fr">Rotation, monochrome et autres effets avancés</li>
      <li lang="gl">Rotación, monocroma e outros efectos avanzados.</li>
      <li lang="hu">Forgatás, fekete-fehér és egyéb speciális hatások</li>
      <li lang="ia">Rotation, monochrome e altere effectos avantiate</li>
      <li lang="id">Perotasian, monokrom, dan efek tingkat lanjut lainnya</li>
      <li lang="it">Rotazione, monocromia e altri effetti avanzati</li>
      <li lang="ko">회전, 흑백, 기타 고급 효과</li>
      <li lang="nb">Dreiing, monokrom og andre avanserte effekter</li>
      <li lang="nds">Dreihen, Swatt-Witt un en Reeg verwiedert Effekten</li>
      <li lang="nl">Roteren, monochroom en andere geavanceerde effecten</li>
      <li lang="nn">Dreiing, fargeredusering og fleire avanserte effektar</li>
      <li lang="pl">Obrót, monochromatyczność i inne zaawansowane efekty</li>
      <li lang="pt">Rotação, monocromáticos e outros efeitos avançados</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Rotação, monocromático e outros efeitos avançados</li>
      <li lang="ru">Инструменты поворота, преобразования в чёрно-белое изображение и другие</li>
      <li lang="sk">Otáčanie, monochromatické a iné pokročilé efekty</li>
      <li lang="sl">Vrtenje, monokromatski in drugi napredni učinki</li>
      <li lang="sv">Rotation, svartvitt och andra avancerade effekter</li>
      <li lang="tr">Döndürme, tek renkli resim ve diğer gelişmiş efektler</li>
      <li lang="uk">Можливість обертання частин зображення, перетворення зображення на чорно-біле, різноманітні ефекти перетворення зображення.</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxRotation, monochrome and other advanced effectsxx</li>
      <li lang="zh-CN">旋转，纯黑白和其他高级效果</li>
      <li lang="zh-TW">旋轉、單色與其他進階效果</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.kolourpaint.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kolourpaint</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kolourpaint</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kolourpaint&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Painting in KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">الرسم على الرسام</caption>
      <caption lang="bg">Рисуване с KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Pintant al KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Pintant a KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Malování v KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Tegner i Kolourpaint</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Malen mit KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Ζωγραφική στο KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">Painting in KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Dibujando con KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Joonistamine KolourPaintis</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Margako KolourPaint erabiliz</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Maalaaminen KolourPaintissä</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Dessin dans KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Pintando en KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="ia">Pingente in KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Melukis di KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Dipingere in KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">KolourPaint로 그림 그리기</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">In KolourPaint tekenen</caption>
      <caption lang="nn">Teikning med KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Malowanie w KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Pintura no KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Pintando no KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Рисование в KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Kreslenie v KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Slikanje v KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Rita med KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">KolourPaint'te Boyama</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Малювання у KolourPaint</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxPainting in KolourPaintxx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-CN">在 KolourPaint 中绘画</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-TW">在 KolourPaint 繪圖</caption>
      <image>https://kde.org/images/screenshots/kolourpaint.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <provides>
    <binary>kolourpaint</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="22.04.3" date="2022-07-07" />
    <release date="2022-06-09" version="22.04.2" />
    <release date="2022-05-12" version="22.04.1" />
    <release date="2022-04-21" version="22.04.0" />
  </releases>
</component>