<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.kalendar</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kalendar.desktop</launchable>
  <icon height="64" width="64" type="cached">org.kde.kalendar.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" type="cached" height="128">org.kde.kalendar.png</icon>
  <!--
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2021 Carl Schwan <carl@carlschwan.eu>
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2021 Claudio Cambra <claudio.cambra@gmail.com>
  SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
  -->
  <id>org.kde.kalendar</id>
  <name>Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="ar">التقويم</name>
  <name lang="az">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="ca">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="cs">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="de">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="el">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="es">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="fi">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="fr">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="hu">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="it">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="ko">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="nl">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="pl">Kalendarz</name>
  <name lang="pt">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="sk">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="sl">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="sv">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="uk">Kalendar</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxKalendarxx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">Kalendar</name>
  <summary>Manage your tasks and events with speed and ease</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">أدر المهام والأحداث بسرعة وسهولة</summary>
  <summary lang="az">Tapşırıqlarınızı və təqdbirlərinizi sürətlə və asan idarə edin</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Gestioneu les tasques i esdeveniments amb rapidesa i facilitat</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Gestioneu les tasques i esdeveniments amb rapidesa i facilitat</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Spravujte své úkoly a události rychle a jednoduše</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Verwalten Sie schnell und einfach Ihre Aufgaben und Termine</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Διαχειριστείτε εργασίες και γεγονότα με ταχύτητα και ευκολία</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Manage your tasks and events with speed and ease</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Gestione tareas y eventos con rapidez y facilidad</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Hallitse tehtäviä ja tapahtumia nopeasti ja vaivatta</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Gérer vos tâches et vos évènements avec efficacité et facilité</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Kezelje feladatait és eseményeit gyorsan és könnyedén</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Gestisci le tue attività e gli eventi con velocità e facilità</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Uw taken en afspraken beheren met snelheid en gemak</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Zarządzaj swoimi zadaniami i wydarzeniami szybko i z łatwością</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Faça a gestão das suas tarefas e eventos rápida e facilmente</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Gerencie suas tarefas e eventos com velocidade e facilidade</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Spravujte svoje úlohy a udalosti rýchlo a jednoducho</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Upravljajte vaše naloge in dogodke hitro in enostavno</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Hantera dina uppgifter och händelser snabbt och lätt</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Швидко і ефективно керуйте вашими записами завдань і подій</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxManage your tasks and events with speed and easexx</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <developer_name>KDE Community, Clau Cambra and Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ar">مجتمع كدي،  وكلاو كامبرا وكارل شوان</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="az">KDE Cəmiyyəti, Clau Cambra və Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">Comunitat KDE, Clau Cambra i Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca-valencia">Comunitat KDE, Clau Cambra i Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Komunita KDE, Clau Cambra a Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">KDE-Gemeinschaft, Clau Cambra und Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Η Κοινότητα του KDE, Clau Cambra και Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en-GB">KDE Community, Clau Cambra and Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">La Comunidad de KDE, Clau Cambra y Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">KDE-yhteisö, Clau Cambra ja Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Communauté KDE, Clau Cambra et Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A KDE közösség, Clau Cambra és Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Comunità KDE, Clau Cambra e Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">KDE 커뮤니티, Clau Cambra, Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">KDE-gemeenschap, Clau Cambra en Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Społeczność KDE, Clau Cambra oraz Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Comunidade do KDE, Clau Cambra e Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt-BR">Comunidade KDE, Clau Cambra e Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">KDE Komunita, Clau Cambra a Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Skupnost KDE, Clau Cambra in Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">KDE-gemenskapen, Clau Cambra och Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Спільнота KDE, Clau Cambra і Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="x-test">xxKDE Community, Clau Cambra and Carl Schwanxx</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh-CN">KDE 社区、Clau Cambra 和 Carl Schwan</developer_name>
  <description>
    <p>Kalendar is a calendar application that allows you to manage your tasks and events. Kalendar supports both local calendars as well as a multitude of online calendars: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, and many more.</p>
    <p>Kalendar gives you many ways to interact with your events. The month view provides an overview of the entire month; the week view presents a detailed hour-by-hour overview of your week; and the schedule view lists all of your upcoming events so that you can easily and quickly plan ahead.</p>
    <p>A tasks view is also available, making it possible for you to manage your tasks and subtasks with Kalendar's powerful tree view and its customisable filtering capabilities.</p>
    <p>Kalendar was built with the idea to be usable on desktop, on mobile and everything in between.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>التقويم هو تطبيق تقويم يسمح لك بإدارة مهامك وأحداثك. ويدعم كلاً من التقويمات المحلية بالإضافة إلى العديد من التقاويم عبر الإنترنت: Nextcloud و Google® Calendar و Outlook® و Caldav وغيرها الكثير.</p>
    <p>يمنحك التقويم العديد من الطرق للتفاعل مع الأحداث الخاصة بك. يوفر عرض الشهر نظرة عامة على الشهر بأكمله، ويقدم عرض الأسبوع نظرة عامة مفصلة ساعة بساعة لأسبوعك، ويسرد عرض الجدول جميع الأحداث القادمة بحيث يمكنك التخطيط مسبقًا بسهولة وسرعة.</p>
    <p>يتوفر أيضًا عرض المهام، مما يتيح لك إدارة المهام والمهام الفرعية باستخدام عرض الشجرة القوي للتقويم وإمكانيات التصفية القابلة للتخصيص.</p>
    <p>صمم التقويم بفكرة أن تكون قابل للاستخدام على سطح المكتب وعلى الهاتف المحمول وكل شيء بينهما.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="az">
    <p>Kalendar, sizə tapşırıqlarınızı və tədbirlərinizi idarə etməyə imkan verən bir təqvim tətbiqidir. Kalendar, həm yerli həm də NextCloud, Google® Təqvim, Outlook®, CalDav və bir çoxları kimi onlayn təqvimləri dətəkləyir.</p>
    <p>Kalendar, sizə tədbirlərinizi əlaqələndirməyin bir çox yolunu təqdim edir. Ay görünüşü bütün ayın icmalını təqdim edir; həftə görünüşü həftənizin ətraflı saat-saat icmalını təqdim edir; və gündəlik görünüşü bütün qarşıdan gələn hadisələrinizin siyahısını verir ki, siz gələcək işlərinizi asanlıqla və cəld planlaşdıra biləsiniz.</p>
    <p>Kalendarda budaqlanma görünüşü və onun fərdiləşdirilə bilən filtrləmə imkanları ilə tapşırıqlarınızı və alt tapşırıqlarınızı idarə etməyə imkan verən tapşırıqlar görünüşü də mövcuddur.</p>
    <p>Kalendar, Masaüstü, mobil və onlar arasındakı cihazlarda istifadə ediləbiləcək şəkildə hazırlanmışdır.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El Kalendar és una aplicació de calendari que permet gestionar les tasques i esdeveniments. Dona suport a dos calendaris locals, així com una multitud de calendaris en línia: NextCloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav i molts més.</p>
    <p>El Kalendar ofereix moltes maneres d'interactuar amb els esdeveniments. La vista mensual proporciona una visió general de tot el mes. La vista setmanal presenta una visió general detallada de la vostra setmana. I la vista de llista enumera tots els pròxims esdeveniments de manera que pugueu planificar amb facilitat i rapidesa.</p>
    <p>També hi ha disponible una vista de tasques, la qual permet gestionar les tasques i subtasques amb la potent vista en arbre del Kalendar i les seves capacitats personalitzables de filtratge.</p>
    <p>El Kalendar s'ha construït amb la idea de ser usable a l'escriptori, al mòbil i tot el que hi ha entre ells.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>Kalendar és una aplicació de calendari que permet gestionar les tasques i esdeveniments. Dona suport a dos calendaris locals, així com una multitud de calendaris en línia: NextCloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav i molts més.</p>
    <p>Kalendar oferix moltes maneres d'interactuar amb els esdeveniments. La vista mensual proporciona una visió general de tot el mes. La vista setmanal presenta una visió general detallada de la vostra setmana. I la vista de llista enumera tots els pròxims esdeveniments de manera que pugueu planificar amb facilitat i rapidesa.</p>
    <p>També hi ha disponible una vista de tasques, la qual permet gestionar les tasques i subtasques amb la potent vista en arbre de Kalendar i les seues capacitats personalitzables de filtratge.</p>
    <p>Kalendar s'ha construït amb la idea de ser usable a l'escriptori, al mòbil i tot el que hi ha entre ells.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Kalendar byl navržen s myšlenkou vysoké použitelnosti na počítači, mobilním telefonu a čímkoliv mezi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το Kalendar είναι μια εφαρμογή ημερολογίου που σας επιτρέπει να διαχειρίζεστε εργασίες και γεγονότα. Το Kalendar υποστηρίζει τοπικά ημερολόγια καθώς επίσης και μαι πληθώρα επιγραμμικών (online) ημερολογίων: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, και πολλά άλλα.</p>
    <p>Το Kalendar δίνει πολλούς τρόπους αλληλεπίδρασης με γεγονότα. Η προβολή του μήνα παρέχει μια επισκόπηση όλου του μήνα. Η προβολή της εβδομάδας παρουσιάζει μια λεπτομερή ανά ώρα επισκόπηση της εβδομάδας. Και η προβολή χρονοπρογραμματισμού εμφανίζει όλα τα επερχόμενα γεγονότα έτσι ώστε εύκολα και γρήγορα να οργανώνετε το χρόνο σας.</p>
    <p>Μια προβολή εργασιών είναι επίσης διαθέσιμη, ώστε να να διαχειρίζεστε εργασίες και υπο-εργασίες με την ισχυρή δενδρική προβολή του Kalendar και τις προσαρμόσιμες δυνατότητες φιλτραρίσματος που διαθέτει.</p>
    <p>το Kalendar κατασκευάστηκε με την ιδέα της χρηστικότητας στην επιφάνεια εργασίας, στο κινητό και σε οτιδήποτε ενδιάμεσα.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>Kalendar is a calendar application that allows you to manage your tasks and events. Kalendar supports both local calendars as well as a multitude of online calendars: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, and many more.</p>
    <p>Kalendar gives you many ways to interact with your events. The month view provides an overview of the entire month; the week view presents a detailed hour-by-hour overview of your week; and the schedule view lists all of your upcoming events so that you can easily and quickly plan ahead.</p>
    <p>A tasks view is also available, making it possible for you to manage your tasks and subtasks with Kalendar's powerful tree view and its customisable filtering capabilities.</p>
    <p>Kalendar was built with the idea to be usable on desktop, on mobile and everything in between.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Kalendar es una aplicación de calendarios que permite la gestión de tareas y eventos. Kalendar puede usar calendarios locales y muchos tipos de calendarios en línea: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook® y Caldav, entre otros.</p>
    <p>Kalendar le proporciona muchos modos de interactuar con los eventos. La vista mensual muestra un resumen de todo el mes; la vista semanal presenta un detallado resumen de la semana por horas; y la vista de planificación lista todos los eventos futuros para que pueda programarlos con antelación de una forma fácil y rápida.</p>
    <p>También dispone de una vista de tareas, haciendo posible la gestión de tareas y subtareas con la potente vista de árbol de Kalendar y sus personalizables capacidades de filtrado.</p>
    <p>Kalendar se ha creado con la idea de que se pueda usar en el escritorio, en el móvil y en cualquier dispositivo entre ambos.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Kalendar on kalenterisovellus, jolla hallita tehtäviä ja tapahtumia. Se tukee niin paikallisia kuin monia verkkokalentereitakin: Nextcloudia, Googlen® kalenteria, Outlookia®, CalDAVia ja monia muita.</p>
    <p>Kalendar tarjoaa useita tapoja vuorovaikuttaa tapahtumiin. Kuukausinäkymä tarjoaa koko kuun yleisnäkymän, viikkonäkymä antaa yksityiskohtaisen tunneittaisen näkymän koko viikosta ja aikataulunäkymä luettelee tulevat tapahtumat, jotta eteenpäin suunnitteleminen on helppoa.</p>
    <p>Käytettävissä on myös tehtävänäkymä, jolla tehtäviä voi hallita Kalendarin tehokkaassa puunäkymässä mukautettavine suodatusominaisuuksineen.</p>
    <p>Kalendar on luotu olemaan hyödyksi niin työpöydällä, mobiilissa kuin kaikkialla siltä väliltäkin.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Kalendar est une application d'agendas, vous permettant de gérer vos tâches et vos évènements. Kalendar prend en charge les calendriers locaux ainsi qu'une multitude de calendriers en ligne comme Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, et bien d'autres.</p>
    <p>Kalendar vous offre de nombreuses façons d'interagir avec vos évènements. L'affichage par mois vous donne un aperçu de l'ensemble du mois. L'affichage par semaines vous présente un aperçu détaillé heure par heure de votre semaine. L'affichage en calendrier vous présente une liste de tous vos évènements à venir afin que vous puissiez facilement et rapidement les planifier.</p>
    <p>Un affichage par tâches est aussi disponible. Il vous permet ainsi de gérer vos tâches et sous-tâches avec l'affichage très efficace en arborescence et des capacités de filtrage personnalisé.</p>
    <p>Kalendar a été conçu avec l'idée d'être utilisable sur un ordinateur de bureau, sur un téléphone portable et dans tous les périphériques intermédiaires.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Kalendar egy naptáralkalmazás, amely lehetővé teszi feladatai és eseményei kezelését. Támogatja a helyi naptárakat és számos online naptárat: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, és sok-sok egyebet.</p>
    <p>Számos módon kezelheti az eseményeit. A havi nézetben áttekinthet egy-egy hónapot; a heti nézetben óráról-órára megtervezheti egy hetét; az ütemezés nézetben pedig listázhatja az összes soron következő eseményt, egyszerűen és gyorsan tervezhet előre.</p>
    <p>A feladat nézet sem maradt ki, melyben a Kalendarból ismert hatékony faszerkezetben kezelhetőek a feladatok és részfeladatok, testre szabható szűrőkkel.</p>
    <p>A Kalendart úgy tervezték, hogy használható legyen mindenféle eszközön, az asztali számítógépektől kezdve a mobiltelefonokig.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Kalendar è un'applicazione di calendario che ti consente di gestire le tue attività e gli eventi. Kalendar supporta sia i calendari locali che una moltitudine di calendari in linea: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav e molti altri.</p>
    <p>Kalendar ti offre molti modi per interagire con i tuoi eventi. La vista mensile fornisce una panoramica dell'intero mese; la vista settimanale presenta una panoramica dettagliata ora per ora della tua settimana e la visualizzazione delle pianificazioni elenca tutti i tuoi eventi imminenti in modo da poter pianificare in anticipo in modo facile e veloce.</p>
    <p>È inoltre disponibile una visualizzazione delle attività, che consente di gestire le attività e le sottoattività con la potente visualizzazione ad albero di Kalendar e le sue capacità di filtraggio personalizzabili.</p>
    <p>Kalendar è stato creato con l'idea di essere utilizzabile su desktop, mobile e tutto il resto.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Kalendar is een agenda-toepassing die u uw taken en afspraken laat beheren. Kalendar ondersteunt zowel lokale agenda's alsook een veelheid aan online agenda's: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav en vele anderen.</p>
    <p>Kalendar geeft u veel manieren om te interageren met uw afspraken. De maandweergave biedt een overzicht over de gehele maand; de weekweergave presenteert een gedetailleerde uur-voor-uur overzicht van uw week; en de planningweergavelijsten al uw komende afspraken zodat u gemakkelijk en snel vooruit kunt plannen.</p>
    <p>Een takenweergave is ook beschikbaar, waarmee u uw taken en subtaken met de krachtige boomstructuur weergave van Kalendar en zijn aanpasbare mogelijkheden voor filtering kunt beheren.</p>
    <p>Kalendar is gebouwd met het idee om bruikbaar te zijn op een bureaublad, op een mobiel en alles er tussenin.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Kalendar jest aplikacją kalendarza, która umożliwia zarządzanie twoimi zadaniami i wydarzeniami. Kalendar obsługuje zarówno kalendarze lokalne, a także mnogość kalendarzy zdalnych: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav i wiele innych.</p>
    <p>Kalendarz daje wiele sposobów do obsługi twoich wydarzeń. Widok miesiąca daje pogląd na cały miesiąc; widok tygodnia daje pogląd na tydzień godzina po godzinie; a widok harmonogramu zestawia wszystkie twoje nadchodzące wydarzenia tak, abyś mógł planować na przyszłość.</p>
    <p>Dostępny jest także widok zadań, co umożliwia zarządzanie zadaniami i ich podzadaniami, dzięki rozbudowanemu widokowi drzewa i możliwością dostosowania jego filtrowania.</p>
    <p>Kalendar został zbudowany z zamysłem bycia użytecznym na urządzeniach biurkowych, przenośnych i wszystkich innych.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Kalendar é uma aplicação de calendário que lhe permite gerir as suas tarefas e eventos. O Kalendar suporta tanto os calendários locais como uma variedade de calendários 'online': Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav e muitos outros.</p>
    <p>O Kalendar oferece-lhe várias formas de interagir com os seus eventos. A vista mensal dá-lhe uma visão geral sobre todo o mês; a vista semanal apresenta-lhe uma visão geral hora-a-hora da sua semana e a área do horário mostra todos os seus próximos eventos, para que possa planear antecipadamente de forma rápida e simples.</p>
    <p>Também está disponível uma área de tarefas, tornando possível para si gerir as suas tarefas e sub-tarefas com a vista em árvore do Kalendar, bem como as suas capacidades personalizadas de filtragem.</p>
    <p>O Kalendar foi compilado com a ideia de ser útil em computadores pessoais, dispositivos móveis, entre outros.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Kalendar je kalendárová aplikácia, ktorá vám umožňuje spravovať vaše úlohy a udalosti. Kalendar podporuje miestne kalendáre, ako aj množstvo online kalendárov: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav a mnohé ďalšie.</p>
    <p>Kalendar vám ponúka mnoho spôsobov interakcie s vašimi udalosťami. Zobrazenie mesiaca poskytuje prehľad celého mesiaca; týždenný náhľad predstavuje podrobný hodinový prehľad vášho týždňa; a zobrazenie plánu uvádza všetky vaše nadchádzajúce udalosti, aby ste mohli ľahko a rýchlo plánovať dopredu.</p>
    <p>K dispozícii je aj zobrazenie úloh, ktoré vám umožňuje spravovať vaše úlohy a podúlohy pomocou výkonného stromového zobrazenia Kalendára a jeho prispôsobiteľných možností filtrovania.</p>
    <p>Kalendar bol vytvorený s myšlienkou, aby bol použiteľný na počítačoch, mobilných zariadeniach a všetkom medzi tým.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Kalendar je aplikacija koledarja, ki vam dovoljuje upravljati vaše naloge in dogodke. Kalendar podpira tako lokalne koledarje kakor tudi različne spletne koledarje: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, in več drugih.</p>
    <p>Kalendar vam nudi veliko načinov za interakcijo z vašimi dogodki. Mesečni pogled zagotavlja pregled celotnega meseca; tedenski pogled predstavlja podrobni pregled uro po uro vašega tedna; in časovni pogled pogled navaja vse vaše prihajajoče dogodke, tako da lahko enostavno in hitro načrtujete plan za naprej.</p>
    <p>Na voljo je tudi pogled nalog, kar vam omogoča upravljanje nalog in podnalog z močnim drevesnim pogledom Kalendarja in njegovo prilagodljivo zmogljivost filtriranja.</p>
    <p>Kalendar je bil izdelan z idejo, da je uporaben na namizju, na mobilnem telefonu in vse vmes.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Kalendar är ett kalenderprogram som tillåter dig att hantera dina uppgifter och händelser. Kalendar stöder både lokala kalendrar samt en mängd nätkalendrar: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, och många fler.</p>
    <p>Kalendar ger dig många sätt att interagera med dina händelser. Månadsvyn tillhandahåller en översikt av hela månaden, veckovyn presenterar en detaljerad översikt av veckan timme för timme, och schemaläggningsvyn listar alla dina kommande händelser så att du enkelt och snabbt kan planera framåt.</p>
    <p>En uppgiftsvy är också tillgänglig, vilket gör det möjligt för dig att hantera dina uppgifter och deluppgifter med Kalendars kraftfulla trädvy och dess anpassningsbara filtreringsmöjligheter.</p>
    <p>Kalender är byggd med idén att vara användbar på skrivbordsdatorer eller mobiler och allting däremellan.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Kalendar — програма-календар, за допомогою якої ви можете керувати вашими записами завдань і подій. У Kalendar передбачено підтримку локальних календарів, а також цілого спектру інтернет-календарів: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav та багатьох інших.</p>
    <p>За допомогою Kalendar ви зможете працювати із вашими записами подій у багато способів. На панелі перегляду місяця буде показано загальний огляд подій місяця; на панелі перегляду тижня ви зможете побачити погодинних розклад подій тижня; а на панелі розкладу буде показано список усіх наступних подій, який надасть вам змогу без проблем швидко спланувати свої дії.</p>
    <p>Також доступна панель перегляду завдань, за допомогою якої ви можете керувати записами завдань і підзавдань у потужній ієрархічній структурі записів Kalendar із гнучкими можливостями фільтрування.</p>
    <p>Kalendar побудовано так, що програмою можна користуватися на звичайному комп'ютері, на мобільному телефоні і на усіх проміжних пристроях.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxKalendar is a calendar application that allows you to manage your tasks and events. Kalendar supports both local calendars as well as a multitude of online calendars: Nextcloud, Google® Calendar, Outlook®, Caldav, and many more.xx</p>
    <p>xxKalendar gives you many ways to interact with your events. The month view provides an overview of the entire month; the week view presents a detailed hour-by-hour overview of your week; and the schedule view lists all of your upcoming events so that you can easily and quickly plan ahead.xx</p>
    <p>xxA tasks view is also available, making it possible for you to manage your tasks and subtasks with Kalendar's powerful tree view and its customisable filtering capabilities.xx</p>
    <p>xxKalendar was built with the idea to be usable on desktop, on mobile and everything in between.xx</p>
  </description>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
  <recommends>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalendar/month_view.png</image>
      <caption>Month View</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">عرض الشهر</caption>
      <caption lang="az">Ay görünüşü</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Vista mensual</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Vista mensual</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Pohled na měsíc</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Monatsansicht</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Προβολή μήνα</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">Month View</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Vista mensual</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Kuukausinäkymä</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Affichage en mois</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Havi nézet</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Vista mensile</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Maandweergave</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Widok miesiąca</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Vista Mensal</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Mesačný pohľad</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Mesečni pogled</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Månadsvy</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Перегляд місяця</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxMonth Viewxx</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalendar/week_view.png</image>
      <caption>Week View</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">عرض الأسبوع</caption>
      <caption lang="az">Həftə görünüşü</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Vista setmanal</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Vista setmanal</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Týdenní pohled</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Wochenansicht</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Προβολή εβδομάδας</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">Week View</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Vista semanal</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Viikkonäkymä</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Affichage en semaines</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Heti nézet</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Vista settimanale</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Weekweergave</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Widok tygodnia</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Vista da Semana</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Pohľad týždňa</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Tedenski pogled</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Veckovy</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Перегляд тижня</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxWeek Viewxx</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalendar/schedule_view.png</image>
      <caption>Schedule View</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">عرض الجدولة</caption>
      <caption lang="az">Gündəlik görünüşü</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Vista de la Planificació</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Vista de la Planificació</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Pohled na plánování</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Terminplanansicht</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Προβολή χρονοπρογραμματισμού</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">Schedule View</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Vista de planificación</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Aikataulunäkymä</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Affichage en calendrier</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Ütemezés nézet</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Vista delle pianificazioni</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Periodieke transactie venster</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Widok harmonogramu</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Área de Calendarização</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Pohľad rozvrhu</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Časovni plan</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Schemaläggningsvy</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Перегляд розкладу</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxSchedule Viewxx</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalendar/task_view.png</image>
      <caption>Task View</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">عرض المهام</caption>
      <caption lang="az">Tapşırıq görünüşü</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Vista de tasca</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Vista de tasca</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Pohled na úlohy</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Aufgabenansicht</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Προβολή εργασιών</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">Task View</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Vista de tareas</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Tehtävänäkymä</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Affichage en tâches</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Feladat nézet</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Vista delle attività</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Taakweergave</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Widok zadań</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Vista das Tarefas</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Pohľad úloh</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Pregled nalog</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Uppgiftsvy</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Перегляд завдання</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxTask Viewxx</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalendar/mobile_view.png</image>
      <caption>Mobile</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">المحمول</caption>
      <caption lang="az">Mobile</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Mòbil</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Mòbil</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Mobilní</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Mobil</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Κινητό</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">Mobile</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Móvil</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Mobiili</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Mobile</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Mobil</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Mobile</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Mobiel</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Telefon komórkowy</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Telemóvel</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Mobil</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Mobilno</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Mobil</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Мобільний</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxMobilexx</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>kalendar</binary>
  </provides>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/kalendar/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://invent.kde.org/pim/kalendar/-/issues</url>
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-07-07" version="22.04.3" />
    <release version="22.04.2" date="2022-06-09" />
    <release date="2022-05-12" version="22.04.1" />
    <release date="2022-04-21" version="22.04.0" />
  </releases>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::matrix">#kalendar:kde.org</value>
  </custom>
</component>