<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <description>
    <p>
     KGet is a versatile and user-friendly download manager.
    </p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Downloading files from FTP and HTTP(S) sources.</li>
      <li>Pausing and resuming of downloading files, as well as the ability to restart a download.</li>
      <li>Tells lots of information about current and pending downloads.</li>
      <li>Embedding into system tray.</li>
      <li>Integration with the Konqueror web browser.</li>
      <li>Metalink support which contain multiple URLs for downloads, along with checksums and other information.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>كجت هو مدير تنزيل متعدد الاستخدامات وسهل الاستخدام.</p>
    <p>المميزات:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>تحميل الملفات من مصادر FTP و HTTP(s)</li>
      <li>إيقاف تنزيل الملفات مؤقتًا واستئنافها ، بالإضافة إلى القدرة على إعادة تشغيل التنزيل.</li>
      <li>يعطي الكثير من المعلومات حول التنزيلات الحالية والمعلقة.</li>
      <li>مضمّن في صينية النظام.</li>
      <li>متكامل مع متصفح الويب كنكرر.</li>
      <li>دعم ميتالينك الذي يحتوي على عناوين متعددة للتنزيل، جنبًا إلى جنب مع المجاميع والمعلومات الأخرى.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ast">
    <p>KGet ye un xestor de descargues versátil y amañosu.</p>
    <p>Carauterístiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Descarga de ficheros dende oríxenes FTP, HTTP y HTTPS.</li>
      <li>Posa y sigue colos ficheros de descarga, amás de poder reaniciar les descargues.</li>
      <li>Diz muncha información tocante a les descargues actuales y pendientes.</li>
      <li>Incrustación na bandexa del sistema.</li>
      <li>Integración col restolador web Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Sofitu pa metaenllaces que contienen munches URLs pa descargues, xunto coles sumes de comprobación y otra información.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>KGet е гъвкава и потребителска ориентирана програма за управления на изтегляния.</p>
    <p>Функции:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Изтегляне на файлове от FTP и HTTP(S) източници.</li>
      <li>Паузиране и възобновяване на изтегляния, както и възможност за рестартиране на изтегляне.</li>
      <li>Дава много информация за текущи и предстоящи изтегляния.</li>
      <li>Интегрира се в системната област.</li>
      <li>Интегриране в Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Поддръжка на Metalink с множество URL-адреси за сваляне, наред с контролни суми и друга информация.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El KGet és un gestor de baixades versàtil i fàcil d'emprar.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Baixa fitxers des de fonts FTP i HTTP/S.</li>
      <li>Fa pausa i reprèn la baixada de fitxers, així com la possibilitat de reiniciar una baixada.</li>
      <li>Dona molta informació sobre les baixades actuals i pendents.</li>
      <li>Està incrustat a la safata del sistema.</li>
      <li>S'integra amb el navegador web Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Admet el «Metalink», el qual conté múltiples URL per a baixades, juntament amb les sumes de verificació i altra informació.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>KGet és un gestor de baixades versàtil i fàcil d'emprar.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Baixa fitxers des de fonts FTP i HTTP/S.</li>
      <li>Fa pausa i reprén la baixada de fitxers, així com la possibilitat de reiniciar una baixada.</li>
      <li>Dona molta informació sobre les baixades actuals i pendents.</li>
      <li>Està incrustat a la safata del sistema.</li>
      <li>S'integra amb el navegador web Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Admet «Metalink», el qual conté múltiples URL per a baixades, juntament amb les sumes de verificació i altra informació.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Vlastnosti:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>KGet er en alsidig og brugervenlig downloadhåndtering.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Download af filer fra FTP- og HTTP(S)-kilder.</li>
      <li>Sæt downloadede filer på pause og genoptag dem, og muligheden for at genstarte en download.</li>
      <li>Viser massere af information om nuværende og afventende downloads.</li>
      <li>Indlejring i systembakken.</li>
      <li>Integration med Konqueror-webbrowseren.</li>
      <li>Understøttelse af metalink med flere URL'er til downloads, samt checksumme og andre informationer.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Ein vielseitiges und einfach zu benutzendes Verwaltungsprogramm zum Herunterladen.</p>
    <p>Funktionen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Herunterladen von Dateien aus FTP- und HTTP(s)-Adressen.</li>
      <li>Anhalten und Fortsetzen des Herunterladens von Dateien, außerdem gibt es auch die Möglichkeit, das Herunterladen neu zu starten.</li>
      <li>Viele Informationen über aktuelle und anstehende Downloads.</li>
      <li>Eingebettet in den Systemabschnitt der Kontrollleiste.</li>
      <li>Integration mit dem Internet-Browser Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Unterstützung für Metalinks, die mehrere Adressen (Urls) zum Herunterladen enthalten, zusammen mit Prüfsummen und weiteren Informationen.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το KGet είναι ένας ευέλικτος και φιλικός διαχειριστής λήψεων.</p>
    <p>Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Κάνει λήψη αρχείων από ftp και http(s) πηγές.</li>
      <li>Παύει και συνεχίζει τη λήψη αρχείων, και έχει τη δυνατότητα επανάληψης μιας λήψης.</li>
      <li>Δίνει πολλές πληροφορίες για τις τρέχουσες και τις εκκρεμείς λήψεις.</li>
      <li>Ενσωμάτωση στο πλαίσιο συστήματος.</li>
      <li>Ολοκλήρωση με τον περιηγητή ιστού Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Υποστήριξη Metalink, η οποία περιέχει πολλά URL για λήψη, μαζί με αθροίσματα ελέγχου και άλλες πληροφορίες.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>KGet is a versatile and user-friendly download manager.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Downloading files from FTP and HTTP(S) sources.</li>
      <li>Pausing and resuming of downloading files, as well as the ability to restart a download.</li>
      <li>Tells lots of information about current and pending downloads.</li>
      <li>Embedding into system tray.</li>
      <li>Integration with the Konqueror web browser.</li>
      <li>Metalink support which contain multiple URLs for downloads, along with checksums and other information.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>KGet es un gestor de descargas versátil y amigable.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Descarga de archivos de fuentes FTP y HTTP(S).</li>
      <li>Pausa y reanudación de los archivos en descarga, así como la posibilidad de reiniciar descargas.</li>
      <li>Muestra gran cantidad de información sobre las descargas actuales y pendientes.</li>
      <li>Se puede empotrar en la bandeja del sistema.</li>
      <li>Integración con el navegador web Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Permite usar Metalink, que contiene múltiples URL para las descargas, además de sumas de verificación y otra información.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>KGet on töökindel ja kasutajasõbralik allalaadimiste haldur.</p>
    <p>Omadused:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Failide allalaadimine FTP ja HTTP(S) allikatest.</li>
      <li>Failide allalaadimise peatamine ja taasalustamine, samuti võimalus allalaadimist taaskäivitada.</li>
      <li>Mitmesuguse teabe pakkumine käimasolevate ja eesootavate allalaadimiste kohta.</li>
      <li>Põimitud süsteemisalve.</li>
      <li>Põimitud veebilehitsejaga Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Metalinki toetus, mis sisaldab mitmeid URL-e allalaadimiseks ühes kontrollsummade ja muu teabega.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>KGet trebezia anitzeko deskarga kudeatzaile lagunkoia da.</p>
    <p>Eginbideak:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Jaitsi fitxategiak FTP eta HTTP(S) sorburuetatik.</li>
      <li>Fitxategi jaitsierak eten eta berrekitea, baita jaitsiera bat berriz hasteko gaitasuna ere.</li>
      <li>Informazio asko ematen du uneko eta zain dauden deskargei buruz.</li>
      <li>Sistema-erretiluan kapsulatzea.</li>
      <li>Integrazioa Konqueror web arakatzailearekin.</li>
      <li>«Metalink» onartzen du, jaisteko URL ugari ditu, egiaztapen-batura eta beste informazio batzuekin batera.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>KGet on monipuolinen ja käyttäjäystävällinen lataustenhallintaohjelma.</p>
    <p>Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Tiedostojen lataus FTP- ja HTTP(S)-lähteistä.</li>
      <li>Tiedostojen latauksen keskeytys ja jatkaminen kuten myös latauksen uudelleenkäynnistys.</li>
      <li>Antaa runsaasti tietoa käynnistä olevasta ja odottavista latauksista.</li>
      <li>Upotus järjestelmän ilmoitusalueelle.</li>
      <li>Yhdistyy Konqueror-verkkoselaimeen.</li>
      <li>Tukee metalinkkejä, jotka sisältävät useampia latauslinkkejä tarkistussummineen ja muine tietoineen.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>KGet est un gestionnaire de téléchargements intuitif et polyvalent</p>
    <p>Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Téléchargement de fichiers depuis des sources FTP et HTTP(S).</li>
      <li>Mise en pause et reprise du téléchargement de fichiers, possibilité de relancer un téléchargement.</li>
      <li>Affichage de nombreuses informations relatives aux téléchargements en cours et en attente.</li>
      <li>Intégration dans la boîte à miniatures.</li>
      <li>Intégration avec le navigateur Internet Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Prise en charge des méta-liens contenant plusieurs URL de téléchargement, des sommes de contrôle et d'autres informations.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>KGet é un xestor de descargar versátil e fácil de usar.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Descargar ficheiros de fontes FTP, HTTP e HTTPS.</li>
      <li>Pausa e continuación de descargas de ficheiros, así como a posibilidade de reiniciar a descarga.</li>
      <li>Fornece unha morea de información sobre as descargas actuais e pendentes.</li>
      <li>Integración coa zona de notificacións.</li>
      <li>Integración co navegador web Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Compatibilidade con metaligazóns que conteñen varios enderezos URL de descarga, xunto con sumas de comprobación e outra información.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ia">
    <p>KGet es un gerente per discargar versatile e amical.</p>
    <p>Characteristicas:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Discargante files ex fontes FTP e HTTP(S). </li>
      <li>Pausar e resumer discargamento de files, assi comole habilitate de reinitiar un discargamento.</li>
      <li>Dice multe information re discargamentos currente e pendente.</li>
      <li>Incorporate in le tabuliero de systema.</li>
      <li>Integration  con le navigator web Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Supporto de metalink que contine URLs multiple per discargamentos, preter checksums e altere information.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>KGet adalah unduh manager yang serbaguna dan mudah digunakan.</p>
    <p>Fitur-fitur:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Mengunduh file dari sumber-sumber FTP dan HTTP(S)</li>
      <li>Menjeda dan melanjutkan pengunduhan file-file, begitu pula kemampuan untuk memulai kembali sebuah unduh-an.</li>
      <li>Memberikan banyak informasi tentang unduh-an yang ada sekarang dan yang sedang dihentikan.</li>
      <li>Menanamkan ke dalam baki sistem.</li>
      <li>Integrasi dengan web browser Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Dukungan Metalink yang terdiri dari banyak bagian URL untuk unduh-an, bersamaan dengan checksums dan informasi lain.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>KGet è un gestore degli scaricamenti versatile e facile da usare.</p>
    <p>Caratteristiche:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Scaricamento di file da fonti FTP e HTTP(S).</li>
      <li>Interruzione e ripresa dello scaricamento dei file, oltre alla capacità di riavviare uno scaricamento.</li>
      <li>Fornisce molte informazioni sugli scaricamenti in corso e in attesa.</li>
      <li>Integrato nel vassoio di sistema.</li>
      <li>Integrazione con il browser web Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Supporto per Metalink che contiene diversi URL da scaricare, oltre a codici di controllo ed altre informazioni.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>KGet은 기능이 다양하고 사용하기 편리한 다운로드 관리자입니다.</p>
    <p>기능:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>FTP, HTTP(S)에서 파일을 다운로드합니다.</li>
      <li>파일 다운로드를 일시 정지 및 재시작할 수 있습니다.</li>
      <li>현재 및 진행 예정인 다운로드 항목에 대한 정보를 제공합니다.</li>
      <li>시스템 트레이에 통합됩니다.</li>
      <li>Konqueror 웹 브라우저에 통합됩니다.</li>
      <li>다운로드 URL 여러 개 및 체크섬 등 정보가 들어 있는 Metalink를 지원합니다.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>KGet is een veelzijdige en gebruikersvriendelijke downloadbeheerder.</p>
    <p>Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Downloaden van bestanden uit FTP en HTTP(S) bronnen.</li>
      <li>Pauzeren en hervatten van downloaden van bestanden, evenals de mogelijkheid om een download opnieuw te starten.</li>
      <li>Vertelt veel informatie over huidige en in behandeling zijnde downloads.</li>
      <li>Ingebed in het systeemvak.</li>
      <li>Integratie met de webbrowser Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Ondersteuning van Metalink die meerdere URL's voor downloads bevat, samen met controlesommen en andere informatie.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>KGet jest wszechstronnym i przyjaznym użytkownikowi programem do zarządzania pobieraniem.</p>
    <p>Możliwości:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Pobieranie plików ze źródeł FTP oraz HTTP(S)</li>
      <li>Wstrzymywanie i wznawianie pobieranych plików, a także możliwość pobrania ich na nowo.</li>
      <li>Mówi wiele informacji o obecnych i oczekujących pobieraniach.</li>
      <li>Osadzanie na tacce systemowej.</li>
      <li>Integracja z przeglądarką internetową Konqueror</li>
      <li>Obsługa metałączy, które zawierają wiele adresów URL do pobrania, wraz z sumami sprawdzającymi i innymi informacjami.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O KGet é um gestor de transferências versátil e amigável.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Transferência de ficheiros de fontes em FTP ou HTTP(S).</li>
      <li>Pausa e continuação dos ficheiros transferidos, assim como a capacidade de reiniciar uma transferência.</li>
      <li>Devolve bastantes informações sobre as transferências actuais e pendentes.</li>
      <li>Incorporação na bandeja do sistema.</li>
      <li>Integração com o navegador Web Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Suporte para 'metalink', o qual contém vários URL's para as transferências, em conjunto com os códigos de validação e outras informações.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>KGet é um gerenciador de downloads versátil e amigável.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Download de arquivos com origem em FTP e HTTP(S).</li>
      <li>Pausa e continuação de arquivos durante o download, assim como a capacidade de reiniciar uma transferência.</li>
      <li>Retorna diversas informações sobre os downloads atuais e pendentes.</li>
      <li>Incorporação na área de notificação.</li>
      <li>Integração com o navegador Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Suporte a metalink, que contém várias URLs para os downloads, em conjunto com os códigos de verificação e outras informações.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>KGet — это гибкий и простой в использовании диспетчер загрузок.</p>
    <p>Возможности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Загрузка файлов через FTP и HTTP(S).</li>
      <li>Приостановка и возобновление загрузки файлов, а также возможность перезапуска.</li>
      <li>Подробная информация о текущих и ожидающих загрузках.</li>
      <li>Встраиваемость в системный лоток.</li>
      <li>Интеграция с браузером Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Поддержка Metalink, которая содержит несколько URL-адресов для загрузки, а также контрольные суммы и другую информацию.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>KGet je univerzálny a ľahko použiteľný správca sťahovania.</p>
    <p>Funkcie:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Sťahovanie súborov zo zdrojov FTP a HTTP(S).</li>
      <li>Pozastavenie a obnovenie sťahovania súborov, ako aj možnosť reštartovania sťahovania.</li>
      <li>Poskytuje veľa informácií o aktuálnych a čakajúcich stiahnutiach.</li>
      <li>Vloženie do systémovej lišty.</li>
      <li>Integrácia s webovým prehliadačom Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Podpora Metalink, ktorá obsahuje viac URL na stiahnutie, spolu s kontrolnými súčtami a ďalšími informáciami.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>KGet je vsestranski in uporabniku prijazen upravljalnik prenosov datotek.</p>
    <p>Možnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Prenos datotek iz virov FTP in HTTP (S).</li>
      <li>Zaustavitev in nadaljevanje prenosa datotek ter možnost ponovnega zagona prenosa.</li>
      <li>Sporoča veliko informacij o trenutnih in čakajočih prenosih.</li>
      <li>Vdelan v sistemsko vrstico.</li>
      <li>Integracija s spletnim brskalnikom Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Podpora za Metalink, ki vsebuje več spletnih naslovov za prenos, skupaj s kontrolnimi vsotami in drugimi informacijami.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Kget är en mångsidig och lättanvänd nerladdningshanterare av filer.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Nerladdning av filer från FTP- och HTTP(S)-källor.</li>
      <li>Pausa och återuppta nerladdning av filer, samt möjlighet att starta om en nerladdning.</li>
      <li>Ger mängder av information om aktuella och väntande nerladdningar.</li>
      <li>Inbäddning i systembrickan.</li>
      <li>Integrering i webbläsaren Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Stör för metalänkar som innehåller flera webbadresser för nerladdning, tillsammans med checksummor och annan information.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>KGet — гнучка і зручна програма для отримання даних з мережі.</p>
    <p>Можливості:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Отримання файлів з джерел FTP та HTTP(S).</li>
      <li>Можливість призупинення та відновлення отримання файлів, а також можливість перезапустити отримання.</li>
      <li>Можливість отримання широкого спектра даних щодо поточного сеансу отримання та завдань з отримання даних з черги.</li>
      <li>Можливість вбудовування до лотка системи.</li>
      <li>Інтеграція із програмою для перегляду сторінок інтернету Konqueror.</li>
      <li>Підтримка метапосилань, які містять декілька адрес даних, а також контрольні суми та інші відомості.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxKGet is a versatile and user-friendly download manager.xx</p>
    <p>xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>xxDownloading files from FTP and HTTP(S) sources.xx</li>
      <li>xxPausing and resuming of downloading files, as well as the ability to restart a download.xx</li>
      <li>xxTells lots of information about current and pending downloads.xx</li>
      <li>xxEmbedding into system tray.xx</li>
      <li>xxIntegration with the Konqueror web browser.xx</li>
      <li>xxMetalink support which contain multiple URLs for downloads, along with checksums and other information.xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>KGet 是一个功能多样且用户友好的下载管理器。</p>
    <p>功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>从 FTP 和 HTTP(S) 源下载文件。</li>
      <li>暂停和继续文件下载，还能够重新开始下载。</li>
      <li>显示当前和队列下载的许多信息。</li>
      <li>嵌入到系统托盘。</li>
      <li>Konqueror 网页浏览器集成。</li>
      <li>支持 Metalink ，包含多个下载连接，校验和和其他信息。</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-TW">
    <p>KGet 是款多功能且使用者友善的下載管理器。</p>
    <p>功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>從 FTP 和 HTTP(S) 來源下載檔案。</li>
      <li>暫停及繼續下載檔案，以及重新開始下載的能力。</li>
      <li>顯示關於目前和待下載項目的詳細資訊。</li>
      <li>嵌入到系統通知區塊。</li>
      <li>能與 Konqueror 網頁瀏覽器整合。</li>
      <li>中繼連結 (Metalink) 支援，其能包含多個欲下載 URL、檢查總和值和提供其他資訊。</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.kget</pkgname>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">kget.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">kget.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.kget</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KGet</name>
  <name lang="ar">كجت</name>
  <name lang="ast">KGet</name>
  <name lang="bg">KGet</name>
  <name lang="ca">KGet</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">KGet</name>
  <name lang="cs">KGet</name>
  <name lang="da">KGet</name>
  <name lang="de">KGet</name>
  <name lang="el">KGet</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">KGet</name>
  <name lang="es">KGet</name>
  <name lang="et">KGet</name>
  <name lang="eu">KGet</name>
  <name lang="fi">KGet</name>
  <name lang="fr">KGet</name>
  <name lang="gl">KGet</name>
  <name lang="ia">KGet</name>
  <name lang="id">KGet</name>
  <name lang="it">KGet</name>
  <name lang="ko">KGet</name>
  <name lang="nl">KGet</name>
  <name lang="pl">KGet</name>
  <name lang="pt">KGet</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">KGet</name>
  <name lang="ru">KGet</name>
  <name lang="sk">KGet</name>
  <name lang="sl">KGet</name>
  <name lang="sv">Kget</name>
  <name lang="uk">KGet</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxKGetxx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">KGet</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">KGet</name>
  <summary>Download Manager</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">مدير التّنزيل</summary>
  <summary lang="ast">Xestor de descargues</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Мениджър на изтегляния</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Gestor de baixades</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Gestor de baixades</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Správce stahování</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Downloadhåndtering</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Download-Verwaltung</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Διαχειριστής λήψεων</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Download Manager</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Gestor de descargas</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Allalaadimiste haldur</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Deskarga kudeatzailea</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Lataustenhallinta</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Gestionnaire de téléchargement</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Xestor de descargas</summary>
  <summary lang="ia">Gerente del discargamento</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Unduh Manager</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Gestore degli scaricamenti</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">다운로드 관리자</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Downloadbeheerder</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Zarządzanie pobieraniem</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Gestor de Transferências</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Gerenciador de downloads</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Диспетчер загрузок</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Správca sťahovania</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Upravljalnik prenosov s strežnikov</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Nerladdningshanterare</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Керування отриманням даних</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxDownload Managerxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">下载管理器</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-TW">下載管理器</summary>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kget</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kget&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kget</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org/applications/internet/kget/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Downloading files with KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">تنزيل الملفات بواسطة </caption>
      <caption lang="ast">Descarga de ficheros con KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="bg">Изтегляне на файлове с KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Baixada de fitxers amb el KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Baixada de fitxers amb KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Stahuji soubory KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Downloader filer med KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Herunterladen von Dateien mit KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Λήψη αρχείων με το KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">Downloading files with KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Descargando archivos con KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Failide allalaadimine KGetiga</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Fitxategiak KGet erabiliz jaistea</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Tiedostojen lataaminen KGetillä</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Téléchargement de fichiers avec KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Descargando os ficheiros con KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="ia">Discargante files con KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Mengunduh file-file menggunakan KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Scaricamento di file con KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">KGet으로 파일 다운로드</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Bestanden worden gedownload met KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Pobieranie plików w KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Transferência de ficheiros com o KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Baixando arquivos com o KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Загрузка файлов с помощью KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Sťahovanie súborov s KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Prenos datotek s programom KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Nerladdning av filer med Kget</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Отримання файлів за допомогою KGet</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxDownloading files with KGetxx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-CN">使用 KGet 下载文件</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-TW">使用 KGet 下載檔案</caption>
      <image>https://www.kde.org/images/screenshots/kget.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kget</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kget.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-07-07" version="22.04.3" />
    <release version="22.04.2" date="2022-06-09" />
    <release date="2022-05-12" version="22.04.1" />
    <release date="2022-04-21" version="22.04.0" />
  </releases>
</component>