<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.picmi</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.picmi.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" type="cached" height="64">picmi.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" type="cached" height="128">picmi.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.picmi.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Picmi</name>
  <name lang="ca">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="cs">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="da">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="de">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="el">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="es">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="et">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="eu">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="fi">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="fr">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="gl">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="hu">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="id">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="it">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="ko">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="nl">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="nn">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="pl">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="pt">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="ru">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="sk">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="sl">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="sr">Пикми</name>
  <name lang="sr-Latn">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="sr-ijekavian">Пикми</name>
  <name lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="sv">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="tr">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="uk">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxPicmixx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">Picmi</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">Picmi</name>
  <summary>Puzzle game based on number logic</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Joc de puzle basat en lògica de nombres</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Joc de puzle basat en lògica de nombres</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Hra puzzle založená na číselné logice</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Rätselspiel auf der Grundlage von Zahlenlogik</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Παιχνίδι γρίφος με βάση τη λογική των αριθμών</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Puzzle game based on number logic</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Juego de rompecabezas basado en lógica numérica</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Arvuloogikal põhinev mõistatusmäng</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Zenbaki logikan oinarritutako buruhausteko jokoa</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Lukulogiikkaan perustuva arvoituspeli</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Un jeu de puzzle avec des chiffres</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Quebracabezas baseado en lóxica numérica</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Számlogika alapú kirakós játék</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Permainan teka-teki berdasarkan pada logika angka</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Gioco ad incastro basato sulla logica dei numeri</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">숫자 논리 기반 퍼즐 게임</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Een logisch spel met nummers</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Tenkjespel basert på tallogikk</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Układanka z elementami logiki numerycznej</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">'Puzzle' baseado na lógica de números</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Quebra-cabeça baseado na lógica de números</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Японские кроссворды</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Puzzle hra založené na číselnej logike</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Igra sestavljank temelječa na številkah</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Логичка игра на основу бројевне логике</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-Latn">Logička igra na osnovu brojevne logike</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-ijekavian">Логичка игра на основу бројевне логике</summary>
  <summary lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Logička igra na osnovu brojevne logike</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Pusselspel baserat på sifferlogik</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Sayısal mantığa dayalı bir bulmaca oyunu</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Гра-головоломка, заснована на інтерпретації чисел</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxPuzzle game based on number logicxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">基于数字逻辑的益智游戏</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-TW">數字邏輯的解謎遊戲</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      The goal is to reveal the hidden pattern in the board by coloring or
      leaving blank the cells in a grid according to numbers given at the side
      of the grid.
      This is a single player game.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>L'objectiu és descobrir el patró ocult en el tauler, acolorint o deixant en blanc les cel·les en una quadrícula d'acord amb els nombres indicats en el lateral de la quadrícula. És un joc d'un jugador.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>L'objectiu és descobrir el patró ocult en el tauler, acolorint o deixant en blanc les cel·les en una quadrícula d'acord amb els nombres indicats en el lateral de la quadrícula. És un joc d'un jugador.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Das Ziel ist, das verborgene Muster zu enthüllen, indem Sie Zellen einfärben oder leer lassen. Hinweise geben die Zahlen am Rand des Rasters. Dieses Spiel ist für einen Spieler.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Ο στόχος είναι να αποκαλυφθεί το κρυμμένο μοτίβο στον πίνακα χρωματίζοντας ή αφήνοντας κενά τα κελιά ενός καννάβου σύμφωνα με αριθμούς που δίνονται στο περιθώριο του καννάβου. Είναι παιχνίδι για έναν παίκτη.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>The goal is to reveal the hidden pattern in the board by colouring or leaving blank the cells in a grid according to numbers given at the side of the grid. This is a single player game.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>El objetivo consiste en revelar el patrón oculto en el tablero coloreando o dejando en blanco las casillas de una rejilla según los números que se muestran al lado de la rejilla. Este juego es para un único jugador.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Mängu eesmärk on paljastada mängulauale peidetud muster, andes ruudustiku lahtritele värvi või jättes nad tühjaks vastavalt ruudustiku serval näidatavatele arvudele. See on ühele mängijale mõeldud mäng.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Helburua taulan dagoen ezkutuko eredua azaleratzea da, sareta bateko gelaxkak koloreztatu edo dauden bezala utziz saretaren alboetan emandako zenbakiei erreparatuz. Jokalari bakarreko joko erraz bat da hau.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Tavoitteena on paljastaa laudan salainen hahmo värittämällä tai jättämällä tyhjiksi ruudukon soluja sen sivulla annettujen lukujen mukaan. Tämä on yksinpeli.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>L'objectif est de révéler le motif caché du plateau en colorant ou en laissant les cellules d'une grille blanches selon les nombres affichés sur les côtés de la grille. Ce jeu se joue à un joueur.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>O obxectivo consiste en descubrir o padrón agochado no taboleiro. Para facelo, ten que colorar ou deixar en branco celas nunha grade segundo os números que aparecen nas celas contiguas. Trátase dun xogo para un único xogador.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A cél a táblán elrejtett minta felfedése a cellák beszínezésével vagy üresen hagyásával, a rács szélén megadott számok szerint. Egyjátékos játék.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Tujuannya adalah untuk mengungkap pola yang tersembunyi di dalam papan dengan mewarnai atau membiarkan sel-sel blank dalam sebuah kisi menurut angka yang diberikan di sebelah kisi. Ini adalah permainan pemain tunggal.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>L'obbiettivo è rivelare il motivo nascosto nel tavoliere colorando o lasciando vuote le celle contenute in una griglia in base ai numeri forniti sul lato della griglia. È un gioco per giocatore singolo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>게임의 목표는 그리드 왼쪽과 위쪽에 주어진 숫자 패턴을 통해서 게임 판에 숨겨진 그림을 찾는 것입니다. 1인용 게임입니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Het doel is het onthullen van het verborgen patroon in het bord door kleuren of leeg laten van de cellen in een raster volgens cijfers gegeven aan de rand van het raster. Dit is een spel voor een enkele speler.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>Målet med spelet er å avdekkja eit mønster på eit spelebrett ved å fargeleggja eit rutenettet basert på tal skrivne i margen på rutenettet. Dette er eit spel for éin spelar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Celem jest odkrycie ukrytego wzoru na planszy poprzez kolorowanie lub pozostawianie kratek pustych według liczb podawanych na boku siatki. Jest to gra dla jednego gracza.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O objectivo é revelar o padrão escondido no tabuleiro, colorindo ou deixando em branco as células de uma grelha, de acordo com os números indicados de lado na grelha. Este é um jogo apenas para um jogador.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>O objetivo é revelar o padrão oculto no tabuleiro, colorindo ou deixando em branco as células de uma grade, de acordo com os números indicados ao lado da grade. Este é um jogo para apenas um jogador.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Цель состоит в том, чтобы выявить скрытый узор на доске, раскрасив или оставив пустыми ячейки в сетке в соответствии с числами, указанными сбоку сетки. Это одиночная игра.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Cieľom je odhaliť skrytý vzor na ploche vyfarbením alebo ponechaním buniek v mriežke podľa čísel na stranách mriežky. Je to hra pre jedného hráča.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Cilj je razkriti skrit vzorec na igralni površini z barvanjem celic mreže glede na številčne namige. Gre za enoigralsko igro.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Циљ је открити скривени образац на табли тако што се боје или остављају празним ћелије у мрежи, према бројевима датим са стране мреже. Ово је игра за једног играча.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-Latn">
    <p>Cilj je otkriti skriveni obrazac na tabli tako što se boje ili ostavljaju praznim ćelije u mreži, prema brojevima datim sa strane mreže. Ovo je igra za jednog igrača.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-ijekavian">
    <p>Циљ је открити скривени образац на табли тако што се боје или остављају празним ћелије у мрежи, према бројевима датим са стране мреже. Ово је игра за једног играча.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">
    <p>Cilj je otkriti skriveni obrazac na tabli tako što se boje ili ostavljaju praznim ćelije u mreži, prema brojevima datim sa strane mreže. Ovo je igra za jednog igrača.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Målet är att avslöja det dolda mönstret på spelbrädet genom att färglägga eller lämna rutorna tomma i ett rutmönster enligt de tal som anges vid sidan om rutmönstret. Detta är ett spel för en ensam spelare.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Amaç, tahtadaki gizli desenleri renklendirerek veya hücrelerin ızgaranın kenarında verilen sayılara göre, bir ızgarada boş bırakarak ortaya çıkarmaktır. Bu tek kişilik bir oyundur.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Метою гри є визначення прихованого візерунка у полі для гри зафарбовуванням комірок поля відповідно до чисел, які наведено за бічною рискою поля. Грати у гру одночасно можна лише один гравець.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxThe goal is to reveal the hidden pattern in the board by coloring or leaving blank the cells in a grid according to numbers given at the side of the grid. This is a single player game.xx</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>游戏目标为根据网格周边给定的数字，将网格中的单元着色或留白，从而揭示其中隐藏的图案。这是个单人游戏。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-TW">
    <p>單人遊戲，依據棋盤側邊的數字來標記或留白棋盤上的每一格。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://kde.org/applications/games/org.kde.picmi</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=picmi&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/picmi/picmi.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>