<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <description>
    <p>
      KNotes is a program that lets you write the computer equivalent of sticky notes.
      The notes are saved automatically when you exit the program, and they display when you open the program.
    </p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Write notes in your choice of font and background color</li>
      <li>Use drag and drop to email your notes</li>
      <li>Can be dragged into Calendar to book a time-slot</li>
      <li>Notes can be printed</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>«ملاحظاتك» هو برنامج يتيح لك كعتابة المقابل البرمجيّ للملاحظات اللاصقة. تُحفظ الملاحظات آليًّا عند خروجك من البرنامج وتُعرض عندما تفتحه.</p>
    <p>الميزات:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>إمكانيّة كتابة الملاحظات بما تختار من خطّ ولون خلفيّة</li>
      <li>إمكانيّة استخدام السّحب والإفلات لإرسال ملاحظاتك عبر البريد</li>
      <li>إمكانيّة سحبها إلى تقويم لحجز مكان في الجدول اليوميّ</li>
      <li>إمكانيّة طباعة الملاحظات</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Svojstva:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El KNotes és un programa que permet escriure l'equivalent informàtic a les notes adhesives. Les notes es desen automàticament en sortir del programa, i es mostren en obrir el programa.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Escriu les notes amb el tipus de lletra i el color de fons de la vostra elecció</li>
      <li>Usa arrossegar i deixar anar per a enviar les notes</li>
      <li>Es poden arrossegar al calendari per a reservar un horari</li>
      <li>Les notes es poden imprimir</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>KNotes és un programa que permet escriure l'equivalent informàtic a les notes adhesives. Les notes es guarden automàticament en eixir del programa, i es mostren en obrir el programa.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Escriu les notes amb el tipus de lletra i el color de fons de la vostra elecció</li>
      <li>Utilitza arrossegar i deixar anar per a enviar les notes</li>
      <li>Es poden arrossegar al calendari per a reservar un horari</li>
      <li>Les notes es poden imprimir</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Vlastnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Poznámky lze vytisknout</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>KNotes er et program der lader dig skrive noter på din computer der svarer til post-it-noter. Noterne gemmes automatisk når du afslutter programmet og de vises når du åbner programmet.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Skriv noter med din foretrukne skrifttype og baggrundsfarve</li>
      <li>Brug træk og slip for at sende dine noter med e-mail</li>
      <li>Kan trækkes ind i kalenderen for at booke et tidsrum</li>
      <li>Noter kan udskrives</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>KNotes erlaubt das Anbringen virtueller Haftnotizen ("Post-it") auf dem Bildschirm. Die Notizen werden beim Beenden des Programms automatisch gespeichert und beim Neustart wieder geladen und angezeigt.</p>
    <p>Funktionen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Notizen können in ausgewählter Farbe für Schrift und Hintergrund erstellt werden</li>
      <li>Ziehen und Ablegen (Drag and Drop), um Ihre Notizen als E-Mail zu versenden</li>
      <li>Kann in einen Kalender gezogen werden, um einen Zeitraum zu belegen.</li>
      <li>Notizen können ausgedruckt werden</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το KNotes είναι ένα πρόγραμμα για να γράφετε στον υπολογιστή σημειώματα ισοδύναμα με τα επικολλημένα. Τα σημειώματα αποθηκεύονται αυτόματα όταν τερματίζετε το πρόγραμμα και εμφανίζονται όταν ανοίγετε το πρόγραμμα.</p>
    <p>Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Γράψτε σημειώματα με γραμματοσειρά και χρώμα φόντου της επιλογής σας</li>
      <li>Χρησιμοποιήστε έλξη και εναπόθεση για να ταχυδρομήσετε τα σημειώματά σας</li>
      <li>Μπορεί να εναποτεθεί στο Calendar για να γίνει κράτηση μιας χρονοθυρίδας</li>
      <li>Τα σημειώματα μπορούν να εκτυπωθούν</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>KNotes is a program that lets you write the computer equivalent of sticky notes. The notes are saved automatically when you exit the program, and they display when you open the program.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Write notes in your choice of font and background colour</li>
      <li>Use drag and drop to email your notes</li>
      <li>Can be dragged into Calendar to book a time-slot</li>
      <li>Notes can be printed</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>KNotes es un programa que le permite escribir en el equipo el equivalente de notas adhesivas. Las notas se guardan automáticamente cuando usted sale del programa y se muestran cuando lo abre.</p>
    <p>Características:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Escriba notas en el tipo de letra y color de fondo de su elección</li>
      <li>Use arrastrar y soltar para enviar sus notas por correo</li>
      <li>Puede soltarse en el calendario para reservar una ranura de tiempo</li>
      <li>Las notas pueden imprimirse</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>KNotes on rakendus, mille abil saab arvutil kirjutada samasuguseid märkmeid, mida muidu kirjutatakse kleepuvate märkmepaberite peale. Sedelid salvestatakse automaatselt rakendusest väljudes ning seda taasavades näidatakse neid uuesti.</p>
    <p>Omadused:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Märkuste kirjutamine enda valitud kirja ja taustavärviga</li>
      <li>Märkuste lohistamise teel e-postiga saatmine</li>
      <li>Lohistamise võimalus kalendrisse mõne aja broneerimiseks</li>
      <li>Trükkimise võimalus</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>KNotes, ordenagailuan ohar itsaskorren parekoa idazten uzten dizun programa da. Oharrak automatikoki gordetzen dira programatik irteten zarenean, eta programa irekitzen duzunean agertzen dira.</p>
    <p>Ezaugarriak:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Sortu oharrak zuk aukeratutako letra-tipo eta atzeko planoko kolorearekin</li>
      <li>Erabili arrastatu eta jaregitea zure oharrak e-posta bidez bidaltzeko</li>
      <li>Egutegira arrastatu daiteke denbora-tarte bat gordetzeko</li>
      <li>Oharrak inprimatu daitezke</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>KNotes on ohjelma, jolla voit kirjoittaa tarralappujen tietokonevastineita. Laput tallennetaan automaattisesti ohjelmasta poistuessasi ja näytetään avatessasi ohjelman.</p>
    <p>Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Voit valita muistilappujen fontin ja taustavärin</li>
      <li>Voit lähettää muistilappusi sähköpostitse vetämällä ja pudottamalla</li>
      <li>Voit vetää muistilaput kalenteriin varataksesi tapahtumalle ajan</li>
      <li>Muistilaput voi tulostaa</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>KNotes est un programme qui vous permet d'avoir l'équivalent électronique des papillons autocollants (Post-it®). Les notes sont enregistrées automatiquement lorsque vous quittez le programme, et elles s'affichent lorsque vous l'ouvrez.</p>
    <p>Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Écrivez des notes avec la police de caractère et la couleur de fond de votre choix</li>
      <li>Utilisez le glisser-déposer pour envoyer vos notes par courriel</li>
      <li>Glissez les notes dans le calendrier pour réserver des créneaux horaires</li>
      <li>Imprimez les notes</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>KNotes é un programa que permite escribir o que sería un equivalente informático das notas pegañentas. As notas gárdanse automaticamente cando se sae do programa e móstranse cando se abre o programa.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Escriba notas usando a fonte e cor de fondo que prefira</li>
      <li>Use arrastrar e soltar para enviar as súas notas por correo electrónico.</li>
      <li>Pode arrastras as notas a un calendario para asocialas a un espazo de tempo.</li>
      <li>Pode imprimir as notas.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A KNotes program használatával kisebb jegyzeteket lehet készíteni. A jegyzetek a programból való kilépéskor automatikusan mentésre kerülnek, a program indulásakor pedig ismét megjelennek.</p>
    <p>Szolgáltatások:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Jegyzetek írása tetszőleges betűtípussal és háttérszínnel</li>
      <li>Jegyzetek elküldése e-mailben a fogd-és-vidd módszerrel</li>
      <li>Naptárba húzható egy időablak lefoglalásához</li>
      <li>A jegyzetek nyomtathatók</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ia">
    <p>KNotes es un programma que te permitte criber le equivalente per computator de notas collose. Le notas es salveguardate automaticamente quando tu exi le programma, e illos monstra quando tu aperi le programma.</p>
    <p>Characteristicas:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Scribe notas in tu selection de font e color de fundo</li>
      <li>Usa traher e poner per inviar via e-posta tu notas</li>
      <li>Pote esser trahite in Calendar per reservar un fissura de tempore</li>
      <li>Notas pote essser imprimite</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>KNotes adalah program yang memungkinkan kamu menulis komputer yang setara dengan catatan lekat. Catatan disimpan secara otomatis saat kamu keluar dari program, dan catatan itu ditampilkan saat kamu membuka program.</p>
    <p>Fitur:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Tulislah catatan dalam warna latarbelakang dan font pilihanmu</li>
      <li>Gunakanlah seret dan taruh untuk menyuratkan catatanmu</li>
      <li>Bisa diseret ke dalam Kalender untuk membukukan slot waktu</li>
      <li>Catatan bisa dicetak</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>KNotes è un programma che ti permette di scrivere nel computer l'equivalente delle note adesive (post-it). Le note vengono salvate automaticamente alla chiusura del programma, e visualizzate quando lo apri.</p>
    <p>Caratteristiche:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Scrivi le note scegliendo il carattere e lo sfondo</li>
      <li>Usa la funzione di trascinamento per inviare le note con la posta elettronica</li>
      <li>Possono essere trascinate e incollate nel Calendario per creare degli intervalli</li>
      <li>Le note possono essere stampate</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>KNotes는 메모를 남길 수 있는 프로그램입니다. 프로그램을 종료할 때 메모를 자동으로 저장하고, 다음 실행 때 보여 줍니다.</p>
    <p>기능:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>사용자 정의 글꼴 및 배경색 지원</li>
      <li>드래그 앤 드롭으로 바로 이메일 보내기</li>
      <li>달력에 드래그 앤 드롭으로 일정 추가</li>
      <li>인쇄 기능</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Ypatybės:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>KNotes er et program du kan bruke til å skrive «gule lapper» på datamaskinen.  Lappene lagres automatisk når du går ut av programmet, og vises igjen når du starter programmet.</p>
    <p>Egenskaper:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Skriv notater med den fargen du velger på skrift og bakgrunn</li>
      <li>Bruk dra og slipp til å sende notatene på e-øpost</li>
      <li>Kan dras inn i Kalendar for å holde av en tid</li>
      <li>Notater kan skrives ut</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nds">
    <p>Mit KNotes kannst Du so wat as Anback-Notizen för den Reekner maken. De Notizen warrt bi't Utmaken vun't Programm automaatsch sekert un wedder wiest, wenn Du dat Programm wedder opröppst.</p>
    <p>Markmalen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>De Notizen mit Dien Schriftoort un Achtergrundklöör schrieven</li>
      <li>Notizen över Trecken un Afleggen mit Nettpost loosstüern</li>
      <li>Laat sik na den Kalenner trecken, wat en Stoot Tiet reserveren deit</li>
      <li>Notizen laat sik drucken</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Knotes is de digitale variant van de gele zelfklevende notitieblaadjes. De notities worden bij het afsluiten automatisch bewaard en worden weer getoond wanneer het programma gestart wordt.</p>
    <p>Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Schrijf notities met uw keuze voor lettertype en achtergrondkleur</li>
      <li>Slepen en neerzetten gebruiken om uw notities te e-mailen</li>
      <li>Kan versleept worden in Agenda om een time-slot te boeken</li>
      <li>Notities kunnen worden afgedrukt</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>KNotes er eit program lèt deg skriva enkle notat – elektroniske «gule lappar». Notata vert automatisk lagra når du avsluttar programmet og vert viste når du opnar det.</p>
    <p>Funksjonar:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Skriv notat med sjølvvald skrift og bakgrunnsfarge</li>
      <li>Bruk dra-og-slepp for å senda notat via e-post</li>
      <li>Kan dragast til kalenderen for å reservera tid</li>
      <li>Notat kan skrivast ut</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>KNotatki jest programem, który umożliwia tworzenie w komputerze tzw. żółtych karteczek. Takie karteczki są samoczynnie zapisywane przy wyjściu z programu i pokazywane przy otwieraniu programu.</p>
    <p>Możliwości:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Pisanie notatek według własnego wyboru czcionki i koloru</li>
      <li>Używanie przeciągania i upuszczania do wysyłania pocztą swoich notatek</li>
      <li>Możliwość przeciągnięcia na kalendarz celem zaplanowania przedziału czasowego</li>
      <li>Możliwość drukowania notatek</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O KNotes é um programa que lhe permite escrever o equivalente para computadores das notas autocolantes. As notas são gravadas automaticamente quando sair do programa e as mesmas voltam a aparecer quando o abrir.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Escrever notas à sua escolha, com determinados tipos de letra e cores de fundo</li>
      <li>Arrastar as notas para as enviar por e-mail</li>
      <li>Pode ser arrastado para o Calendário para agendar um espaço de tempo</li>
      <li>As notas podem ser impressas</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>KNotes é um programa que lhe permite escrever no computador da mesma forma que usa notas autoadesivas. As notas são gravadas automaticamente quando você sai do programa e depois apresentadas quando você abre o programa.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Escrever notas com a fonte e cor de fundo de sua escolha</li>
      <li>Arrastar e soltar as notas para envio por e-mail</li>
      <li>Pode ser arrastado para o calendário para agendar um espaço de tempo</li>
      <li>As notas podem ser impressas</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Caracteristici:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Notele pot fi tipărite</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Программа KNotes имитирует клейкие записки на экране компьютера. При выходе из программы записки сохраняются и восстанавливаются при следующем запуске.</p>
    <p>Возможности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Выбор цвета шрифта и фона для заметок;</li>
      <li>Отправка заметок по электронной почте путём их перетаскивания;</li>
      <li>Добавление событий путём перетаскивания заметок на календарь;</li>
      <li>Заметки можно печатать.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>KNotes je program, ktorý vám umožní písať na počítači ekvivalent "sticky notes". Poznámky sa ukladajú automaticky keď ukončíte program a potom sa zobrazia pri otvorení programu.</p>
    <p>Funkcie:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Písanie poznámok podľa vášho výberu písma a farby pozadia</li>
      <li>Použitie drag and drop na poslanie vašich poznámok</li>
      <li>Je možné potiahnutie do kalendára na rezervovanie termínu</li>
      <li>Poznámky je možné tlačiť</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>KNotes je program, ki vam omogoča pisanje lepljivih sporočilc na računalniku. Sporočilca so samodejno shranjena ob izhodu iz programa in prikazana ob odprtju programa.</p>
    <p>Zmožnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Pisanje sporočilc s pisavo in barvo ozadja po meri</li>
      <li>Pošiljanje sporočilc preko e-pošte s pomočjo povleci/spusti</li>
      <li>Sporočilca lahko povlečete v koledar in rezervirate določen termin</li>
      <li>Sporočilca lahko natisnete</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Knotes är ett program som låter dig skriva datorns motsvarighet till klisterlappar. Anteckningarna sparas automatiskt när programmet avslutas, och visas när programmet startas.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Skriv anteckningar med eget val av teckensnitt och bakgrundsfärg</li>
      <li>Använd drag och släpp för att skicka anteckningar med e-post</li>
      <li>Kan dras till en kalender för att boka en tidslucka</li>
      <li>Anteckningar kan skrivas ut</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>KNotes yapışkan notların bilgisayar eşleniğini yazmanızı sağlayan bir programdır. Notlar programdan çıktığınızda otomatik olarak kaydedilir, ve açtığınızda görüntülenir.</p>
    <p>Özellikler:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Seçtiğiniz yazı tipi ve arka plan rengi ile notlarınız yazın</li>
      <li>Notlarınızı e-posta ile göndermek için sürükleyip bırakın</li>
      <li>Belli bir zaman yuvasını tutması için Takvim'e sürüklenebilir</li>
      <li>Notlar yazdırılabilir</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>KNotes — це програма, що дозволяє створювати комп'ютерний еквівалент липких листочків із нотатками. Нотатки автоматично зберігаються під час завершення роботи програми і показуються при її запуску.</p>
    <p>Можливості:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>запис нотаток бажаним для вас кольором і шрифтом на тлі бажаного кольору;</li>
      <li>використання перетягування зі скиданням для надсилання ваших нотаток електронною поштою;</li>
      <li>можливість перетягування нотаток до календаря для створення запису планування;</li>
      <li>можливість друку нотаток.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxKNotes is a program that lets you write the computer equivalent of sticky notes. The notes are saved automatically when you exit the program, and they display when you open the program.xx</p>
    <p>xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>xxWrite notes in your choice of font and background colorxx</li>
      <li>xxUse drag and drop to email your notesxx</li>
      <li>xxCan be dragged into Calendar to book a time-slotxx</li>
      <li>xxNotes can be printedxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>KNotes 是一个类似便签贴的计算机程序。在您退出程序后，便笺将被被自动保存，并且在下次打开程序时自动显示。</p>
    <p>功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>使用您选择的字体和背景色写便笺</li>
      <li>使用拖放来通过邮件发送便笺</li>
      <li>可以拖拽到日历，预订一个时间</li>
      <li>便笺可以被打印</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-TW">
    <p>KNotes 讓您可以在螢幕上貼便利貼。便條會在離開時自動儲存，開啟程式時再顯示。</p>
    <p>功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>可以選擇便條的字型與背景顏色</li>
      <li>可以用拖放的方式透過電子郵件傳送您的便條</li>
      <li>可以拖到行事曆中來預約時間</li>
      <li>可以列印便條</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.knotes</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.knotes.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" height="64" type="cached">knotes.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" height="128" width="128">knotes.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.knotes.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <developer_name>The KDE Community</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ar">مجتمع كدي</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">La comunitat KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca-valencia">La comunitat KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Komunita KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">KDE-fællesskabet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Die KDE-Gemeinschaft</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Η Κοινότητα του KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en-GB">The KDE Community</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">La comunidad de KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="et">KDE kogukond</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">KDE komunitatea</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">KDE-yhteisö</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">La communauté KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">A comunidade de KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ia">Le communitate de KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Komunitas KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">La Comunità KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">KDE 커뮤니티</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">De KDE gemeenschap</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nn">KDE-fellesskapet</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Społeczność KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">A Comunidade do KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt-BR">A Comunidade KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Сообщество KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">KDE Komunita</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Skupnost KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">KDE-gemenskapen</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">KDE Topluluğu</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Спільнота KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="x-test">xxThe KDE Communityxx</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh-CN">KDE 社区</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh-TW">KDE 社群</developer_name>
  <name>KNotes</name>
  <name lang="ar">ملاحظاتك</name>
  <name lang="bs">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="ca">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="cs">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="da">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="de">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="el">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="es">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="et">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="eu">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="fi">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="fr">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="gl">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="hu">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="ia">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="id">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="it">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="ko">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="lt">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="nb">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="nds">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="nl">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="nn">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="pl">KNotatki</name>
  <name lang="pt">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="ro">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="ru">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="sk">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="sl">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="sv">Knotes</name>
  <name lang="tr">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="uk">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxKNotesxx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">KNotes</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">螢幕便利貼_KNotes</name>
  <summary>Sticky notes application</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">تطبيق الملاحظات اللاصقة</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Aplicació de notes adhesives</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Aplicació de notes adhesives</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Aplikace s poznámkami na lepicím štítku</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Program til post-it-noter</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Haftnotizen</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Εφαρμογή επικολλημένων σημειωμάτων</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Sticky notes application</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Aplicación de notas adhesivas</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Kleepuvate sedelite rakendus</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Ohar itsaskorren aplikazioa</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Muistilappusovellus</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Application de notes autocollantes</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Aplicación de notas pegañentas</summary>
  <summary lang="ia">Application de notas collose</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Aplikasi catatan lekat</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Applicazione per le note adesive</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">찍찍이 노트 프로그램</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Toepassing voor plaknotities</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">«Gule lappar»-program</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Aplikacja źółtych karteczek</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Aplicação de notas autocolantes</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Aplicativo de notas adesivas</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Приложение для работы с заметками</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Aplikácia nalepovacích poznámok</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Program za lepljiva sporočilca</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Program för uppklistrade anteckningar</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Yapışkan notlar uygulaması</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Програма для роботи з нотатками</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxSticky notes applicationxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">便签笔记应用程序</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-TW">便利貼應用程式</summary>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=knotes</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=knotes</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://kontact.kde.org/components/knotes/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/knotes/knotes.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>knotes</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-07-07" version="5.20.3" />
    <release date="2022-06-09" version="5.20.2" />
    <release version="5.20.1" date="2022-05-12" />
    <release date="2022-04-21" version="5.20.0" />
  </releases>
</component>