<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <description>
    <p>Calindori is a touch friendly calendar application. It has been designed for mobile devices but it can also run on desktop environments. Users of Calindori are able to check previous and future dates and manage tasks and events.</p>
    <p>When executing the application for the first time, a new calendar file is created that follows the ical standard. Alternatively, users may create additional calendars or import existing ones.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Events</li>
      <li>Todos</li>
      <li>Multiple calendars</li>
      <li>Import calendar</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El Calindori és una aplicació de calendari tàctil. Està dissenyada per als dispositius mòbils, però també es pot executar als entorns d'escriptori. Els usuaris del Calindori poden revisar dates anteriors i futures i gestionar tasques i esdeveniments.</p>
    <p>En executar l'aplicació per primera vegada, es crea un fitxer nou de calendari que segueix l'estàndard «ical». Alternativament, els usuaris poden crear calendaris addicionals o importar-ne d'existents.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Esdeveniments</li>
      <li>Tasques pendents</li>
      <li>Calendaris múltiples</li>
      <li>Importa calendaris</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>Calindori és una aplicació de calendari tàctil. Està dissenyada per als dispositius mòbils, però també es pot executar en els entorns d'escriptori. Els usuaris de Calindori poden revisar dates anteriors i futures i gestionar tasques i esdeveniments.</p>
    <p>En executar l'aplicació per primera vegada, es crea un fitxer nou de calendari que seguix l'estàndard «ical». De manera alternativa, els usuaris poden crear calendaris addicionals o importar-ne d'existents.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Esdeveniments</li>
      <li>Tasques pendents</li>
      <li>Calendaris múltiples</li>
      <li>Importa calendaris</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Vlastnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Události</li>
      <li>Úlohy</li>
      <li>Importovat kalendář</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Calindori er et touch-venligt kalenderprogram. Det er designet til mobile enheder, men det kan også køre i skrivebordsmiljøer. Brugere af Calindori kan tjekke tidligere og fremtidige datoer og håndtere opgaver og begivenheder.</p>
    <p>Når programmet køres første gang oprettes en ny kalenderfil som følger ical-standarden. Alternativt kan brugere oprette yderligere kalendere eller importere eksisterende kalendere.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Begivenheder</li>
      <li>Gøremål</li>
      <li>Flere kalendere</li>
      <li>Importér kalender</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Calindori ist eine Kalenderanwendung für Touch-Geräte. Sie wurde für mobile Geräte entwickelt, kann aber auch auf Desktop-Umgebungen ausgeführt werden. Benutzer von Calindori sind in der Lage, frühere und zukünftige Termine zu überprüfen und Aufgaben bzw. Ereignisse zu verwalten.</p>
    <p>Beim ersten Start der Anwendung wird ein neuer Kalender nach dem ICal-Standard erstellt. Alternativ können zusätzliche Kalender erstellt oder vorhandene Kalender importiert werden.</p>
    <p>Funktionen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Ereignisse</li>
      <li>Aufgaben</li>
      <li>Mehrere Kalender</li>
      <li>Kalender importieren</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το Calindori είναι μια φιλική σε οθόνες αφής εφαρμογή ημερολογίου. Έχει σχεδιαστεί για κινητά αλλά εκτελείται και σε περιβάλλοντα υπολογιστών γραφείου. Οι χρήστες του Calindori μπορούν να ελέγχουν ημερομηνίες στο παρελθόν και στο μέλλον και να διαχειρίζονται εργασίες και γεγονότα.</p>
    <p>Όταν η εφαρμογή εκτελείται για πρώτη φορά, δημιουργείται ένα νέο αρχείο ημερολογίου το οποίο ακολουθεί το πρότυπο ical. Εναλλακτικά, οι χρήστες μπορούν να δημιουργούν νέα ημερολόγια ή να εισάγουν αυτά που υπάρχουν.</p>
    <p>Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ατζέντα</li>
      <li>Γεγονότα</li>
      <li>Εργασίες προς υλοποίηση</li>
      <li>Πολλαπλά ημερολόγια</li>
      <li>Εισαγωγή ημερολογίου</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>Calindori is a touch friendly calendar application. It has been designed for mobile devices but it can also run on desktop environments. Users of Calindori are able to check previous and future dates and manage tasks and events.</p>
    <p>When executing the application for the first time, a new calendar file is created that follows the ical standard. Alternatively, users may create additional calendars or import existing ones.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Events</li>
      <li>To-dos</li>
      <li>Multiple calendars</li>
      <li>Import calendar</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Calindori es una aplicación de calendarios táctil. Ha sido diseñada para dispositivos móviles, aunque también se puede ejecutar en entornos de escritorio. Los usuarios de Calindori pueden comprobar fechas anteriores y futuras, así como gestionar tareas y eventos.</p>
    <p>Al ejecutar la aplicación por primera vez, se crea un nuevo archivo de calendario conforme al estándar ical. De forma alternativa, los usuarios pueden crear calendarios adicionales o importar otros existentes.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Eventos</li>
      <li>Listas de tareas</li>
      <li>Múltiples calendarios</li>
      <li>Importar calendario</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Calindori on puutetundlik kalendrirakendus. See loodi eelkõige mobiilseadmetele, aga seda saab kasutada ka töölauaarvutites. Calindori kasutajatel on võimalik uurida möödunud ja tulevasi kuupäevi ning korraldada oma ülesandeid ja sündmusi.</p>
    <p>Rakenduse esmakäivitusel luuakse uus, iCali standardit järgiv kalender. Soovi korral võib kasutaja mõistagi luua lisakalendreid või importida juba olemasolevaid.</p>
    <p>Omadused:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Päevakava</li>
      <li>Sündmused</li>
      <li>Ülesanded</li>
      <li>Mitme kalendri kasutamise võimalus</li>
      <li>Kalendri importimine</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Calindori ukimena onartzen duen egutegiko aplikazio bat da. Gailu mugikorretarako diseinatu den arren, mahaigaineko inguruneetan ere ibili daiteke. Calindori-ren erabiltzaileek igarotako eta etorkizuneko datak arakatu eta eginkizunak eta gertakizunak kudeatu ditzakete.</p>
    <p>Aplikazioa aurreneko aldiz exekutatzean, egutegiko fitxategi berri bat sortzen da, «ical» estandarrari jarraitzen diona. Horrez gain, erabiltzaileek egutegi osagarriak sortu edo inportatu ditzakete.</p>
    <p>Ezaugarriak:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Gertakizunak</li>
      <li>Zereginak</li>
      <li>Egunkari anizkoitzak</li>
      <li>Inportatu egutegia</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Calindori on kosketusnäytölle sopiva kalenterisovellus, joka on suunniteltu mobiililaitteille mutta toimii myös työpöytäympäristössä. Calindorin käyttäjät voivat tarkistaa menneitä ja tulevia päivämääriä sekä hallita tehtäviä ja tapahtumia.</p>
    <p>Käynnistettäessä ohjelma ensi kertaa luodaan uusi iCal-standardia noudattava kalenteritiedosto. Käyttäjä voi myös luoda lisää kalentereja tai tuoda olemassa olevia.</p>
    <p>Ominaisuuksia:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Työsuunnitelma</li>
      <li>Tapahtumat</li>
      <li>Tehtävät</li>
      <li>Useammat kalenterit</li>
      <li>Kalenterin tuonti</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Calindori est une application d'agenda ergonomique pour les écrans tactiles. Elle a été conçue pour les appareils mobiles mais fonctionne également sur les environnements de bureau. Les utilisateurs de Calindori peuvent consulter les dates passées et futures et gérer les tâches et les évènements.</p>
    <p>Lors de sa première exécution, l'application crée un nouveau fichier agenda respectant la norme ical. Les utilisateurs peuvent également créer des agendas supplémentaires ou importer des agendas existants.</p>
    <p>Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Évènements</li>
      <li>Tâches</li>
      <li>Agendas multiples</li>
      <li>Importer un agenda</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Calindori é unha aplicación de calendario optimizada para uso táctil. Deseñouse para dispositivos móbiles pero tamén pode usarse en contornos de escritorio. Os usuarios de Calindori poden consultar datas pasadas e futuras e xestionar tarefas e eventos.</p>
    <p>Ao executar a aplicación por vez primeira, créase un novo ficheiro de calendario que segue o estándar de iCal. De maneira alternativa, os usuarios poden crear calendarios adicionais ou importar calendarios existentes.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Axenda</li>
      <li>Eventos</li>
      <li>Tarefas</li>
      <li>Varios calendarios</li>
      <li>Importar un calendario</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ia">
    <p>Calindori es un application de calendatio amicale de tocco. Illo ha essite designate per dispositivos mobile ma anque pote executar sur ambientes de scriptorio. Usators de Calindori es capace de verificar datas previe e future e gerer cargas e eventos.</p>
    <p>Quando executa le application per le prime vice, un nove file de calendario es create que seque le standard ical. Alternativemente, usatores pote crear calendarios additional o importar los que existe.</p>
    <p>Characteristicas:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Eventos</li>
      <li>Cosas de facer</li>
      <li>Calendarios multiple</li>
      <li>Importa calendario</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Calindori adalah sebuah aplikasi kalender sentuhan yang akrab. Ini sudah dirancang untuk perangkat genggam tetapi juga bisa berjalan pada lingkungan desktop. Penggunaan Calindori bisa untuk memeriksa sebelumnya dan  keakanan tanggal dan mengelola tugas dan peristiwa.</p>
    <p>Ketika pengeksekusian aplikasi saat pertama kali, sebuah file kalender baru telah diciptakan yang mengikuti standar ical. Selain itu, pengguna bisa menciptakan kalender tambahan atau mengimpor yang sudah ada.</p>
    <p>Fitur:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Peristiwa</li>
      <li>Kegiatan</li>
      <li>Multipel kalender</li>
      <li>Impor kalender</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Calindori è un'applicazione calendario amichevole. È stato progettato per i dispositivi mobili, ma può anche funzionare in ambienti desktop. Gli utenti di Calindori sono in grado di controllare date precedenti e future, e di gestire attività ed eventi.</p>
    <p>Quando si esegue l'applicazione per la prima volta viene creato un nuovo file di calendario che segue lo standard ical. In alternativa, gli utenti possono creare dei calendari aggiuntivi, oppure importare quelli esistenti.</p>
    <p>Funzionalità:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Eventi</li>
      <li>Cose da fare</li>
      <li>Calendari multipli</li>
      <li>Importa calendario</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>Calindort는 터치 친화적 캘린더 프로그램입니다. 모바일 장치뿐만 아니라 데스크톱 환경에서도 실행할 수 있습니다. Calindori를 사용하면 과거와 미래 날짜를 보고 작업과 이벤트를 관리할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p>프로그램을 처음으로 실행하면 iCal 표준을 따르는 캘린더 파일을 생성합니다. 추가 캘린더를 만들거나 기존 캘린더를 가져올 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p>기능:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>일정</li>
      <li>이벤트</li>
      <li>할 일</li>
      <li>다중 캘린더</li>
      <li>캘린더 가져오기</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Calindori is een agendatoepassing vriendelijk voor aanraken. Het is ontworpen voor mobiele apparaten maar het kan ook in een bureaubladomgeving werken. Gebruikers van Calindori kunnen eerdere en toekomstige datums controleren en taken en afspraken beheren.</p>
    <p>Bij het de eeerste keer uitvoeren van de toepassing, wordt een nieuw agendabestand aangemaakt die de ical-standaard gebruikt. Alternatief kunnen gebruikers extra agenda's aanmaken of bestaande importeren.</p>
    <p>Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Afspraken</li>
      <li>Taken</li>
      <li>Meerdere agenda's</li>
      <li>Agenda importeren </li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>Calindori er eit kalender­program eigna for trykk­skjermar. Det er laga for mobil­telefonar, men kan òg brukast på vanlege datamaskiner. Du kan bruka det som ein kalender og til å halda oversikt over gjeremål og hendingar.</p>
    <p>Når du startar programmet første gong, vert det automatisk laga ei ny kalenderfil som følgjer iCalendar-standarden. Men du kan òg oppretta fleire kalendrar eller importera nokon du har frå før.</p>
    <p>Funksjonar:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Timeplan</li>
      <li>Hendingar</li>
      <li>Gjeremål</li>
      <li>Fleire kalendrar</li>
      <li>Kalender­importering</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pa">
    <p>ਕੈਲਿੰਡੋਰੀ ਟੱਚ ਲਈ ਢੁੱਕਵੀਂ ਕੈਲੰਡਰ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਮੋਬਾਈਲ ਡਿਵਾਈਸਾਂ ਲਈ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਪਰ ਇਹ ਡੈਸਕਟਾਪ ਮਾਹੌਲ ਵਿੱਚ ਵੀ ਚੱਲ ਸਕਦੀ ਹੈ। ਕੈਲਿੰਡੋਰੀ ਦੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਪਿਛਲੀਆਂ ਤੇ ਭਵਿੱਖ ਦੀਆਂ ਤਾਰੀਖਾਂ ਵੇਖ ਅਤੇ ਕੰਮ ਤੇ ਸਮਾਗਮਾਂ ਦਾ ਇੰਤਾਜ਼ਮ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹਨ।</p>
    <p>ਜਦੋਂ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਨੂੰ ਪਹਿਲੀ ਵਾਰ ਚਲਾਇਆ ਜਾਂਦਾ ਹੈ ਤਾਂ ical ਮਿਆਰ ਦੀ ਵਰਤੋਂ ਕਰਕੇ ਨਵੀਂ ਕੈਲੰਡਰ ਫਾਇਲ ਬਣਾਈ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ। ਬਦਲਵੇਂ ਰੂਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਵਧੀਕ ਕੈਲੰਡਰ ਬਣਾ ਜਾਂ ਮੌਜੂਦਾ ਕੈਲੰਡਰ ਦਰਾਮਦ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹਨ।</p>
    <p>ਫੀਚਰ:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>ਏਜੰਡਾ</li>
      <li>ਸਮਾਗਮ</li>
      <li>ਕੰਮ-ਕਾਰ</li>
      <li>ਕਈ ਕੈਲੰਡਰ</li>
      <li>ਕੈਲੰਡਰ ਇੰਪੋਰਟ ਕਰੋ</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Calindori jest aplikacją kalendarza przystosowaną do dotyku. Została stworzona dla urządzeń przenośnych, lecz można ją także uruchomić na komputerach stacjonarnych. Użytkownicy Calindori mogą  sprawdzać poprzednie i przyszłe daty oraz zarządzać zadaniami i wydarzeniami.</p>
    <p>Przy wykonywaniu aplikacji po raz pierwszy, tworzony jest plik nowego kalendarza, który przestrzega standardu ical. Alternatywnie, użytkownicy mogą stworzyć dodatkowe kalendarz lub zaimportować już istniejące.</p>
    <p>Możliwości:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Rozkład zajęć</li>
      <li>Wydarzenia</li>
      <li>Zadania-do-zrobienia</li>
      <li>Wiele kalendarzy</li>
      <li>Importowanie kalendarzy</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Calindori é uma aplicação de calendário amigável para dispositivos tácteis. Foi desenhada para dispositivos móveis, mas também pode ser executada em computadores. Os utilizadores do Calindori poderão ver as datas anteriores e futuras, assim como gerir as tarefas e eventos.</p>
    <p>Ao executar a aplicação pela primeira vez, será criado um ficheiro de calendário novo que segue a norma iCal. Em alternativa, os utilizadores poderão criar calendários adicionais ou importar existentes.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Eventos</li>
      <li>Itens Por-Fazer</li>
      <li>Vários calendários</li>
      <li>Importar o calendário</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>O Calindori é um aplicativo de calendário amigável ao toque. Ele foi desenhado para dispositivos móveis mas também pode ser executado em ambientes de trabalho. Os usuários do Calindori podem verificar as datas anteriores e futuras e gerenciar tarefas e eventos.</p>
    <p>Ao executar o aplicativo pela primeira vez, um novo arquivo de calendário que segue o padrão ical é criado. Alternativamente, os usuários podem criar calendários adicionais ou importar os existentes.</p>
    <p>Recursos:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Eventos</li>
      <li>Tarefas</li>
      <li>Múltiplos calendários</li>
      <li>Importar calendário</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Calindori — программа-календарь для сенсорных интерфейсов. Она разработана для мобильных устройств, но ей можно пользоваться и на обычных рабочих станциях. Пользователи Calindori могут проверять записи для прошедших и будущих дат и управлять соответствующими задачами и событиями.</p>
    <p>При первом запуске программа создаёт файл календаря в формате ical. Кроме того, пользователь может создавать дополнительные календари или импортировать уже имеющиеся.</p>
    <p>Возможности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Расписание</li>
      <li>События</li>
      <li>Задачи</li>
      <li>Несколько календарей</li>
      <li>Импорт календарей</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Funkcie:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Udalosti</li>
      <li>Úlohy</li>
      <li>Viac kalendárov</li>
      <li>Import kalendára</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Calindori je dotikom prijazna aplikacija za koledar. Zasnovana je za mobilne naprave, vendar lahko deluje tudi v namiznih okoljih. Uporabniki Calindore lahko preverjajo prejšnje in prihodnje datume ter upravljajo z nalogami in dogodki.</p>
    <p>Ko poženete program prvič, se ustvari nova koledarska datoteka, po standardu ical. Sicer uporabniki lahko ustvarjajo dodatne koledarje ali uvozijo obstoječe.</p>
    <p>Možnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Dnevni red</li>
      <li>Dogodki</li>
      <li>Za narediti</li>
      <li>Več koledarjev</li>
      <li>Uvozi koledar</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Calindori är ett pekvänligt kalenderprogram. Det har konstruerats för mobilenheter men kan också köra på skrivbordsmiljöer. Användare av Calindori kan kontrollera tidigare och framtida datum, samt hantera uppgifter och händelser.</p>
    <p>När programmet körs för första gången skapas en ny kalenderfil som följer ical-standarden. Som alternativ kan användare skapa ytterligare kalendrar eller importera befintliga.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Agenda</li>
      <li>Händelser</li>
      <li>Uppgifter</li>
      <li>Flera kalendrar</li>
      <li>Importera kalender</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Calindori, dokunmatik ekran dostu bir takvim uygulamasıdır. Taşınabilir aygıtlar için tasarlanmıştır; ancak masaüstü ortamlarında da çalışabilir. Calindori kullanıcıları, geçmiş ve gelecek tarihleri denetleyebilir, görevleri ve etkinlikleri düzenleyebilir.</p>
    <p>Uygulama ilk kez çalıştırılırken, ical standartını izleyen bir takvim dosyası oluşturulur. Alternatif olarak, kullanıcılar ek takvimler oluşturabilir veya var olanları içe aktarabilir.</p>
    <p>Özellikler:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ajanda</li>
      <li>Etkinlikler</li>
      <li>Yapılacaklar</li>
      <li>Çoklu takvimler</li>
      <li>Takvim içe aktarma</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Calindori — програма-календар для сенсорних інтерфейсів. Її розроблено для мобільних пристроїв, але нею можна користуватися на звичайних комп'ютерних робочих станціях. Користувачі Calindori можуть читати записи попередніх і майбутніх подій і керувати записами завдань і подій.</p>
    <p>Під час першого запуску програма створить файл стандартного календаря у форматі ical. Крім того, користувач може створювати додаткові календарі або імпортувати вже створені.</p>
    <p>Можливості:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Порядок денний</li>
      <li>Події</li>
      <li>Завдання</li>
      <li>Користування декількома календарями</li>
      <li>Імпортування календарів</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxCalindori is a touch friendly calendar application. It has been designed for mobile devices but it can also run on desktop environments. Users of Calindori are able to check previous and future dates and manage tasks and events.xx</p>
    <p>xxWhen executing the application for the first time, a new calendar file is created that follows the ical standard. Alternatively, users may create additional calendars or import existing ones.xx</p>
    <p>xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>xxAgendaxx</li>
      <li>xxEventsxx</li>
      <li>xxTodosxx</li>
      <li>xxMultiple calendarsxx</li>
      <li>xxImport calendarxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>Calindori 是一款适合触控的日历应用程序。它针对移动设备设计，也可以运行在桌面环境上。用户可以使用 Calindori 查看指定的日期，并管理任务和活动。</p>
    <p>首次运行此程序时，它会自动按照 ical 标准创建一个新日历。用户也可以创建其他日历，或者导入已有日历。</p>
    <p>程序功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>日程表</li>
      <li>活动</li>
      <li>待办事项</li>
      <li>多日历</li>
      <li>导入日历</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-TW">
    <p>功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>活動</li>
      <li>待辦事項</li>
      <li>多行事曆</li>
      <li>匯入行事曆</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.calindori</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.calindori.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">calindori.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" height="128" type="cached">calindori.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.calindori.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <name>Calindori</name>
  <name lang="ca">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="cs">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="da">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="de">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="el">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="es">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="et">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="eu">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="fi">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="fr">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="gl">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="ia">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="id">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="it">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="ko">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="nl">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="nn">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਕੈਲਿੰਡੋਰੀ</name>
  <name lang="pl">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="pt">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="ru">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="sk">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="sl">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="sv">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="tr">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="uk">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxCalindorixx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">Calindori</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">Calindori</name>
  <summary>Calendar application</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Aplicació de calendari</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Aplicació de calendari</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Aplikace kalendáře</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Kalenderprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Kalenderprogramm</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Εφαρμογή ημερολογίου</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Calendar application</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Aplicación de calendarios</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Kalendrirakendus</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Egutegiko aplikazioa</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Kalenterisovellus</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Application d'agenda</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Aplicación de calendario</summary>
  <summary lang="ia">Application de calendario</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Aplikasi kalender</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Applicazione calendario</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">캘린더 프로그램</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Agendatoepassing</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Kalenderprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="pa">ਕੈਲੰਡਰ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Aplikacja kalendarza</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Aplicação de calendário</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Aplicativo de calendário</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Программа с функциями календаря</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Aplikácia Calendar</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Aplikacija koledar</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Kalenderprogram</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Takvim uygulaması</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Програма-календар</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxCalendar applicationxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">日历应用程序</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-TW">行事曆應用程式</summary>
  <recommends>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
  <categories>
    <category>Utility</category>
    <category>Calendar</category>
    <category>KDE</category>
  </categories>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Calindori on Mobile</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">El Calindori al mòbil</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Calindori al mòbil</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Calindori na mobilní zařízení</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Calindori på mobil</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Calindori auf einem Mobilgerät</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Calindori σε κινητό</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">Calindori on Mobile</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Calindori en el móvil</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Calindori mobiilis</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Calindori mugikorrean</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Mobiili-Calindori</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Calindori sur plate-forme mobile</caption>
      <caption lang="ia">Calindori sur Mobile</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Calindori di Ponsel</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Calindori su mobile</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">모바일 환경에서의 Calindori</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Calindori op mobiel</caption>
      <caption lang="nn">Calindori på mobil</caption>
      <caption lang="pa">ਮੋਬਾਈਲ ਉੱਤੇ ਕੈਲਿੰਡੋਰੀ</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Calindori przenośny</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Calindori no Telemóvel</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Calindori no celular</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Calindori на мобильном устройстве</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Calindori na mobilni napravi</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Calindori på mobil</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Taşınabilirde Calindori</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Calindori на мобільному телефоні</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxCalindori on Mobilexx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-CN">Calindori 移动版</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/calindori/mobile.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Calindori on Desktop</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">El Calindori a l'escriptori</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Calindori a l'escriptori</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Calindori na počítač</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Calindori på desktop</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Calindori auf einer Arbeitsfläche</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Calindori σε υπολογιστή γραφείου</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">Calindori on Desktop</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Calindori en el escritorio</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Calindori arvutis</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Calindori mahaigainean</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Työpöytä-Calindori</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Calindori sur ordinateur de bureau</caption>
      <caption lang="ia">Calindori sur scriptorio</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Calindori di Desktop</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Calindori su desktop</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">데스크톱 환경에서의 Calindori</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Calindori op bureaublad</caption>
      <caption lang="nn">Calindori på PC</caption>
      <caption lang="pa">ਡੈਸਕਟਾਪ ਉੱਤੇ ਕੈਲਿੰਡੋਰੀ</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Calindori biurkowy</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Calindori no PC</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Calindori na área de trabalho</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Calindori на компьютере</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Calindori na namizju</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Calindori på skrivbord</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Masaüstünde Calindori</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Calindori на комп'ютері</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxCalindori on Desktopxx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-CN">Calindori 桌面版</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/calindori/desktop.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://invent.kde.org/plasma-mobile/calindori</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/describecomponents.cgi?product=calindori</url>
  <releases>
    <release version="22.06" date="2022-06-24">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/06/28/plasma-mobile-gear-22-06/</url>
    </release>
    <release date="2022-04-26" version="22.04">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/04/26/plasma-mobile-gear-22-04/</url>
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>General user interface improvements and backend rework</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2022-02-09" version="22.02">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/02/09/plasma-mobile-gear-22-02/</url>
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>General user interface improvements and backend rework</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.12" date="2021-12-07">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2021/12/07/plasma-mobile-gear-21-12/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="21.08" date="2021-08-31">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2021/08/31/plasma-mobile-gear-21-08/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="21.07" date="2021-07-20">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2021/07/20/plasma-mobile-gear-21-07/</url>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-06-10" version="21.06">
      <description>
        <p>Improvements and fixes</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Ensure that the footer inline message is displayed on top of the content</li>
          <li>Show events by default only on wide screens</li>
          <li>On desktop, ensure that no more than two page columns are visible at the same time</li>
          <li>Update translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2021/06/10/plasma-mobile-update-june/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="21.05" date="2021-05-10" />
    <release date="2021-03-01" version="1.4.0">
      <description>
        <p>New features, improvements and fixes</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Show progress of month swipes</li>
          <li>Improve calendar month performance</li>
          <li>Directly open calendar files</li>
          <li>Show import notifications in the app footer</li>
          <li>Fix inline message display on desktop</li>
          <li>Introduce the import-calendar-data action</li>
          <li>Fix scheduling of repeating events</li>
          <li>Fix time picker display</li>
          <li>Add attendees support to events</li>
          <li>Refactor event and task editor pages</li>
          <li>Prevent accidental task or event deletion</li>
          <li>Offer attendee role editing</li>
          <li>Solve string puzzles</li>
          <li>Add a proper generic name for the application</li>
          <li>Offer export functionality</li>
          <li>Offer import on specific calendars</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>calindori</binary>
  </provides>
</component>