<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.kmousetool</pkgname>
  <id>org.kde.kmousetool</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="bg">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="ca">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="cs">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="da">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="de">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="el">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="es">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="et">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="eu">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="fi">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="fr">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="gl">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="ia">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="id">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="it">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="ko">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="nl">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="nn">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="pl">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="pt">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="ro">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="ru">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="sk">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="sl">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="sv">Kmousetool</name>
  <name lang="uk">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="vi">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxKMouseToolxx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">KMouseTool</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">KMouseTool</name>
  <summary>Automatic clicks to reduce the effects of repetitive strain injury</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Извършва автоматични щраквания с мишката, намалявайки уврежданията от повтарящи се механични действия</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Els clics automàtics redueixen els efectes la síndrome del canal carpià</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Els clics automàtics reduïxen els efectes la síndrome del canal carpià</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Klikker automatisk for at reducere skadevirkningerne ved ensidigt gentaget arbejde</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Automatische Mausklicks zur Vorbeugung gegen das RSI-Syndrom</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Αυτόματα κλικ για να μειωθούν οι συνέπειες των κακώσεων λόγω επαναλαμβανόμενης καταπόνησης</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Automatic clicks to reduce the effects of repetitive strain injury</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Clics automáticos para reducir el efecto de lesiones por esfuerzo repetitivo</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Automaatne klõpsamine ülekoormuskahjustuse mõjude vähendamiseks</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Esfortzu errepikakorraren ondoriozko lesioaren efektuak murrizteko klik automatikoak</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Hiiren automaattinapsautukset rasitusvammojen vaikutusten vähentämiseksi</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Clics automatiques pour réduire les effets des troubles musculo-squelettiques</summary>
  <summary lang="ia">Clicar automatic per reducer le effectos de damnos sporadic repetitive</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Klik otomatis untuk mengurangi efek cedera pegal</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Clic automatici per ridurre gli effetti del disturbo degli arti superiori da lavoro</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">자동 클릭으로 반복성 긴장 장애 예방</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Automatische klik om het effect van RSI (repetitive strain injury) te voorkomen</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Automatiske klikk hjelper deg å unngå musesjuke</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Samoczynne kliknięcia, aby ograniczyć efekt kontuzji spowodowanych powtarzaną czynnością</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">'Clicks' automáticos para reduzir os efeitos de lesões por movimentos repetitivos</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Cliques automáticos para reduzir os efeitos das lesões por esforço repetitivo</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Face clicuri automate pentru a reduce efectele leziunilor de încordare repetitivă</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Автоматический щелчок мышью для предупреждения хронического растяжения сухожилий</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Automatické kliknutia na zníženie účinkov opakovaného zranenia</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Samodejni kliki za zmanjšanje učinkov ponavljajočih se poškodb zaradi obremenitve</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Automatiska klick för att reducera effekten av belastningsskador</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Автоматично клацає для запобігання шкоді вашому здоров'ю від постійного напруження</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Bấm tự động để giảm tác động của chấn thương do căng lặp lại</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxAutomatic clicks to reduce the effects of repetitive strain injuryxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">自动点击功能，有助于降低重复性操作带来的劳损</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
     KMouseTool clicks the mouse for you, so you don't have to. KMouseTool works with any mouse or pointing device.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Извършва действия с мишката вместо вас. KMouseTool работи с всякакви устройства за посочване и мишки.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El KMouseTool fa el clic de ratolí per vós, així que no ho heu de fer. El KMouseTool funciona amb qualsevol ratolí o dispositiu apuntador.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>KMouseTool fa el clic de ratolí per vós, així que no ho heu de fer. KMouseTool funciona amb qualsevol ratolí o dispositiu apuntador.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>KMouseTool klikker med musen for dig, så du ikke behøver gøre det. KMouseTool virker med alle mus og pegeenheder.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>KMouseTool drückt die Maustaste für Sie und funktioniert mit jeder Maus und jedem Zeigergerät.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το KMouseTool κάνει κλικ το ποντίκι, έτσι εσείς δεν χρειάζεται να το κάνετε. Το KMouseTool λειτουργεί με κάθε ποντίκι ή συσκευή με δείκτη.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>KMouseTool clicks the mouse for you, so you don't have to. KMouseTool works with any mouse or pointing device.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>KMouseTool pulsa los botones del ratón por usted. KMouseTool funciona con cualquier ratón o dispositivo apuntador.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>KMouseTool teeb sinu eest hiireklõpsu, vabastades sind vaevast. KMouseTool töötab koos kõigi hiirte või osutusseadmetega.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>KMouseTool tresnak saguari klik egiten dio zure ordez, zuk egin behar ez dezazun. KMouseTool edozein sagu edo gailu erakuslerekin dabil.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>KMouseTool napsauttaa hiirtä puolestasi, jottei sinun tarvitse. KMouseTool toimii kaikilla hiirillä ja osoitinlaitteilla.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>KMouseTool clique sur la souris pour vous afin que vous n'ayez pas à le faire. KMouseTool fonctionne avec n'importe quelle souris ou dispositif de pointage.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>KMouseTool preme o rato por vostede. KMouseTool funciona con calquera rato ou dispositivo de punteiro.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ia">
    <p>KMouseTool cicca le mus per te, assi que tu non debe facer lo. KMouseTool functiona con ulle mus o dispositivo de punctar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>KMouseTool mengeklik mouse untuk kamu, jadi kamu tidak perlu melakukannya. KMouseTool bekerja dengan mouse atau perangkat penunjuk apa pun.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>KMouseTool fa clic col mouse per te, cosicché tu non debba farlo. Funziona con qualsiasi mouse o strumento di puntamento.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>KMouseTool은 여러분을 대신하여 마우스 단추를 클릭해 줍니다. 마우스 및 포인팅 장치에 관계 없이 동작합니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>KMouseTool klikt voor u de muis, dus hoeft u dat niet te doen. KMouseTool werkt met elke muis of aanwijzer.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>KMouseTool trykkjer med musa for deg, slik at du slepp. Det fungerer med alle typar mus og peikeverktøy.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>KMouseTool klika myszą za ciebie, abyś sam nie musiał ego robić. KMouseTool działa z każdą myszą lub urządzeniem wskazującym.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O KMouseTool carrega o botão do rato, para que não tenha de o fazer. O KMouseTool funciona com qualquer rato ou dispositivo de ponteiro.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>O KMouseTool clica o botão do mouse para você. Ele funciona com qualquer mouse ou dispositivo apontador.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>KMouseTool apasă butonul mausului pentru dumneavoastră, ca să nu o faceți singur. KMouseTool funcționează cu orice maus sau dispozitiv de indicare.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Программа KMouseTool выполняет щелчки мышью за пользователя. KMouseTool работает с любой мышью или указывающим устройством.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>KMouseTool za vás klikne myšou, takže vy nemusíte. KMouseTool spolupracuje s akoukoľvek myšou alebo ukazovacím zariadením.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>KMouseTool klikne miško namesto vas, da vam tega ni treba. KMouseTool deluje s katero koli miško ali kazalno napravo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Kmousetool klickar musen åt dig så att du inte behöver göra det. Kmousetool fungerar med vilken mus eller pekenhet som helst.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>KMouseTool «клацає» кнопками миші за вас. KMouseTool працює замість будь-якої миші або координатного пристрою.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="vi">
    <p>KMouseTool bấm chuột giúp bạn, để bạn không phải làm nữa. KMouseTool hoạt động với bất kì chuột hay thiết bị trỏ nào.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxKMouseTool clicks the mouse for you, so you don't have to. KMouseTool works with any mouse or pointing device.xx</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>KMouseTool 可以替您点击鼠标按钮，可用于任意鼠标或指针设备。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-TW">
    <p>KMouseTool 代你點擊滑鼠，你只需要看著就行。KMouseTool 支援任何滑鼠或指向裝置。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kmousetool</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kmousetool&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kmousetool</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org/applications/utilities/kmousetool/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.kde.org/images/screenshots/kmousetool.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kmousetool</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kmousetool.desktop</launchable>
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-07-07" version="22.04.3" />
    <release version="22.04.2" date="2022-06-09" />
    <release version="22.04.1" date="2022-05-12" />
    <release version="22.04.0" date="2022-04-21" />
  </releases>
</component>