<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.kamoso</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kamoso.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">kamoso.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" height="128" type="cached">kamoso.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.kamoso.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="ar">كاموسو</name>
  <name lang="ca">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="cs">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="da">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="de">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="el">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="es">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="et">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="eu">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="fi">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="fr">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="gl">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="ia">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="id">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="it">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="ko">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="lt">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="nl">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="nn">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="pl">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="pt">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="ro">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="ru">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="sk">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="sl">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="sv">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="tr">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="uk">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxKamosoxx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">Kamoso</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">Kamoso</name>
  <summary>Use your webcam to take pictures and make videos</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">استخدام كاميرا الوِبّ لديك لأخذ الصّور و تسجيل الفيديوهات.</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Useu la càmera web per a prendre fotografies o fer vídeos</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Utilitzeu la càmera web per a prendre fotografies o fer vídeos</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Používejte svou webkameru k pořizování snímků a videí</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Brug dit webkamera til at tage billeder eller lave videoer</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Mit Kamoso können Sie mit Ihrer Webcam Bilder und Videos aufnehmen</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Λήψη με web κάμερα φωτογραφιών ή βίντεο</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Use your webcam to take pictures and make videos</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Use su webcam para capturar imágenes y hacer vídeos</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Veebikaameraga piltide ja videode tegemine</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Erabili zure web-kamera argazkiak atera eta bideoak egiteko</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Ota kuvia ja tee videoita web-kamerallasi</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Utilisez votre webcam pour prendre des photos et enregistrer des vidéos</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Kamoso é un programa xenial para usar a súa cámara web para sacar fotos e gravar vídeos</summary>
  <summary lang="ia">Usa tu webcam per prender photos e facer videos.</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Gunakan untuk webcam-mu untuk mengambil gambar dan membuat video</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Utilizza la tua webcam per scattare foto o registrare video</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">웹캠으로 사진을 찍거나 동영상 녹화하기</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Naudokite savo kamerą norėdami fotografuoti ar filmuoti vaizdo įrašus</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Uw webcam te gebruiken om foto's of video's te maken</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Bruk nettkamera for å ta bilete og laga videoar</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Używaj swojej kamerki do robienia zdjęć i filmów</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Use a sua Webcam para tirar fotografias ou criar vídeos</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Use sua webcam para tirar fotos e gravar vídeos</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Folosiți-vă camera web pentru a face poze și filmulețe</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Приложение для получения и видео с веб-камеры.</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Použite vašu webkameru na tvorbu fotiek alebo natáčanie videa</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Uporabite spletno kamero za fotografiranje in video posnetke</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Använda din webbkamera för att ta bilder eller göra videor</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Kamoso, fotoğraf  veya video çekmek için web kameranızı kullanmanıza olanak sağlayan harika bir programdır.</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Kamoso — чудова програма для використання вашої вебкамери для створення знімків або запису відео</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxUse your webcam to take pictures and make videosxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">使用摄像头照相以及制作视频</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-TW">使用您的 Webcam 拍照或錄影</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Kamoso is a simple and friendly program to use your camera. Use it to take pictures and make videos to share.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>«كاموسو» برنامج رائع وبسيط لاستخدام كاميرا الوِبّ لديك لأخذ الصّور أو تسجيل الفيديوهات.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El Kamoso és un programa senzill i fàcil d'emprar per a usar la càmera web. Useu-lo per a prendre fotografies o fer vídeos per a compartir.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>Kamoso és un programa senzill i fàcil d'emprar per a utilitzar la càmera web. Utilitzeu-lo per a prendre fotografies o fer vídeos per a compartir.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Kamoso er et simpelt og brugervenligt program til at bruge dit webkamera. Du kan bruge det til at tage billeder eller lave videoer til at dele med andre.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Kamoso ist ein einfaches und benutzerfreundliches Programm für Ihre Kamera. Benutzen Sie es, um Bilder und Videos  aufzunehmen und freigeben.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το Kamoso είναι ένα απλό και φιλικό πρόγραμμα για τη χρήση της κάμερας. Χρησιμοποιήστε το για λήψη φωτογραφιών ή βίντεο για κοινή χρήση.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>Kamoso is a simple and friendly program to use your camera. Use it to take pictures and make videos to share.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Kamoso es un programa simple y amigable para usar su webcam. Úselo para capturar imágenes y hacer vídeos que compartir.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Kamoso on lihtne ja kasutajasõbralik rakendus oma kaamera kasutamiseks. Tee sellega pilte ja videoid, mida teistelegi jagada.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Kamoso zure kamera erabiltzeko programa erraz eta lagunkoia da. Erabili partekatuko diren argazkiak eta bideoak ateratzeko.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Kamoso on yksinkertainen ja helppo ohjelma kameran käyttöön. Voit ottaa sillä jaettavia kuvia ja videoita.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Kamoso est un programme simple et intuitif qui vous permettra d'utiliser votre caméra. Vous pouvez l'utiliser pour prendre des photos et enregistrer des vidéos afin de les partager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Kamoso é un programa simple para usar facilmente a súa cámara. Úseo para sacar fotos e gravar vídeos para compartir.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ia">
    <p>Kamoso es un simple e amicale programma per usar tu camera. Tu usa lo per prender photos e facer videos de compartir. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Kamoso adalah program yang mudah dan sederhana untuk penggunaan kameramu. Gunakan ini untuk mengambil gambar dan membuat video untuk dibagikan.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Kamoso è un programma semplice e amichevole per utilizzare la tua webcam. Utilizzalo per scattare foto o registrare video da condividere.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>Kamoso는 카메라를 사용하는 간단하고 편한 프로그램입니다. 사진과 동영상을 찍고 공유할 수 있습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Kamoso yra paprasta ir draugiška kamerai naudoti skirta programa. Naudokite ją norėdami fotografuoti ar filmuoti vaizdo įrašus, skirtus bendrinti.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Kamoso is een eenvoudig en vriendelijk programma om uw camera te gebruiken. Gebruik het om foto's en video's te maken en te delen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>Kamoso er eit brukarvennleg program der du kan bruka nettkameraet ditt til å ta bilete eller laga videoar for å dela med andre.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Kamoso jest prostym i przyjaznym użytkownikowi programem do używania kamerki internetowej. Używaj go do robienia zdjęć i filmów do udostępnienia w sieci.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Kamoso é um programa simples e amigável para usar a sua Webcam. Use-a para tirar fotografias ou criar vídeos para partilhar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>O Kamoso é um programa simples e amigável para usar sua webcam. Use-o para tirar fotos e gravar vídeos e compartilhá-los.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Kamoso e un program simplu și prietenos pentru folosirea camerei. Folosiți-l pentru a face poze și filmulețe de partajat.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Kamoso — простое приложение для захвата видео и изображений с веб-камеры с понятным интерфейсом. Может быть использовано для получения фотографий и видео для публикации.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Kamoso je jednoduchý program na použitie vašej webkamery na tvorbu fotiek alebo natáčanie videa.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Kamoso je preprost in prijazen program za uporabo foto naprave. Uporabite ga za zajem slik in videov za skupno rabo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Kamoso är ett enkelt och trevligt program för att använda din kamera. Använd det för att ta bilder eller göra videor att dela med dig av.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Kamoso, kameranızı kullanmanızı sağlayan yalın ve kullanımı kolay bir programdır. Paylaşılacak resimler veya videolar çekmek için kullanabilirsiniz.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Kamoso — проста і дружня до користувача програма для використання вашої вебкамери для створення знімків або запису відео.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxKamoso is a simple and friendly program to use your camera. Use it to take pictures and make videos to share.xx</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>Kamoso是一个简单方便的程序，可以使用您的相机拍照并制作视频分享。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-TW">
    <p>Kamoso 是一款使用您相機的友好簡單程式。使用它來拍照或錄影以分享。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://userbase.kde.org/Kamoso</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kamoso</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kamoso</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Kamoso main window</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">النافذة الرئيسة لكاموسو</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Finestra principal del Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Finestra principal de Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Hlavní okno Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Kamosos hovedvindue</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Hauptfenster von Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Kamoso κύριο παράθυρο</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">Kamoso main window</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Ventana principal de Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Kamoso peaaken</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Kamoso leiho nagusia</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Kamoson pääikkuna</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">La fenêtre principale de Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Xanela principal de Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="ia">Fenestra principal de Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Window utama Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La finestra principale di Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">Kamoso 주 창</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Kamoso pagrindinis langas</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Hoofdvenster van Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="nn">Hovudvindauge i Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Główne okno Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Janela principal do Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Janela principal do Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="ro">Fereastra principală Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Главное окно приложения Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Hlavné okno Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Glavno okno Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Huvudfönstret i Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Kamoso ana penceresi</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Головне вікно Kamoso</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxKamoso main windowxx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-CN">Kamoso 主窗口</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-TW">Kamoso 主視窗</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kamoso/kamoso.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kamoso</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="22.04.3" date="2022-07-07" />
    <release date="2022-06-09" version="22.04.2" />
    <release date="2022-05-12" version="22.04.1" />
    <release date="2022-04-21" version="22.04.0" />
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>