<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>libsForQt5.pix</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.pix.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="cached" height="64" width="64">pix.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" width="128" type="cached">pix.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.pix.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-3.0</project_license>
  <name>Pix</name>
  <name lang="ca">Pix</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">Pix</name>
  <name lang="cs">Pix</name>
  <name lang="de">Pix</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">Pix</name>
  <name lang="es">Pix</name>
  <name lang="et">Pix</name>
  <name lang="fi">Pix</name>
  <name lang="fr">Pix</name>
  <name lang="gl">Pix</name>
  <name lang="hi">पिक्स (Pix)</name>
  <name lang="hu">Pix</name>
  <name lang="id">Pix</name>
  <name lang="it">Pix</name>
  <name lang="ko">Pix</name>
  <name lang="lt">Pix</name>
  <name lang="my">ပစ်ဇ်</name>
  <name lang="nl">Pix</name>
  <name lang="nn">Pix</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਪਿਕਸ</name>
  <name lang="pl">Pix</name>
  <name lang="pt">Pix</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">Pix</name>
  <name lang="sk">Pix</name>
  <name lang="sl">Pix</name>
  <name lang="sv">Pix</name>
  <name lang="tr">Piks</name>
  <name lang="uk">Пікс</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxPixxx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">Pix</name>
  <name lang="zh-TW">Pix</name>
  <summary>Image Gallery</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Galeria d'imatges</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Galeria d'imatges</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Galerie obrázků</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Bildergalerie</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Image Gallery</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Galería de imágenes</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Kuvagalleria</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Galerie d'images</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Galleria d'immagini</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">그림 갤러리</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Paveikslų galerija</summary>
  <summary lang="my">ပုံရိပ်ခင်းကျင်းပြတိုက်</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Afbeeldingsgalerij</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Galeria obrazów</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Galeria de Imagens</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Galeria de imagens</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Galéria obrázkov</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Galerija slik</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Bildgalleri</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Görsel Galerisi</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Галерея зображень</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxImage Galleryxx</summary>
  <summary lang="zh-CN">图像库/相册程序</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Pix is an image gallery and image viewer. Pix can be used to open images with other applications like an image editor, add tags to the files, add annotations to pictures, rotate and share them.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El Pix és una galeria d'imatges i un visualitzador d'imatges. El Pix es pot usar per a obrir imatges amb altres aplicacions com un editor d'imatges, afegir etiquetes als fitxers, afegir anotacions a les imatges, girar-les i compartir-les.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>Pix és una galeria d'imatges i un visor d'imatges. Pix es pot utilitzar per a obrir imatges amb atres aplicacions com un editor d'imatges, afegir etiquetes als fitxers, afegir anotacions a les imatges, girar-les i compartir-les.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Pix ist eine Bildergalerie und ein Bildbetrachter. Pix kann verwendet werden, um Bilder mit anderen Anwendungen wie einem Bildbearbeitungsprogramm zu öffnen, Stichwörter zu Dateien hinzufügen, Bilder drehen und teilen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>Pix is an image gallery and image viewer. Pix can be used to open images with other applications like an image editor, add tags to the files, add annotations to pictures, rotate and share them.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Pix es una galería de imágenes y visor de imágenes. Se puede usar Pix para abrir imágenes con otras aplicaciones como editores de imágenes, añadir etiquetas a los archivos, añadir anotaciones a las imágenes, rotarlas y compartirlas.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Pix on kuvagalleria ja -katselin. Pixiä voi käyttää avaamaan toisten sovellusten kuten kuvankäsittelyohjelmien kuvat, lisäämään kuviin luokituksia ja merkintöjä sekä kääntämään ja jakamaan kuvia.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Pix est une galerie d'images et un afficheur d'images. Pix peut être utilisé pour ouvrir des images avec d'autres applications comme un éditeur d'images, ajouter des étiquettes aux fichiers, ajouter des annotations aux images, les faire pivoter et les partager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Pix è una galleria d'immagini e un visore d'immagini. Può essere utilizzato per aprire immagini con altre applicazioni come un'editor d'immagine, per aggiungere etichette ai file o le annotazioni alle immagini, per ruotarle o per condividerle.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>Pix는 그림 갤러리이자 뷰어입니다. Pix는 그림 편집기 등 다른 프로그램으로 그림 열기, 파일에 태그 추가, 그림에 주석 달기, 회전, 공유 등을 지원합니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Pix yra paveikslų galerija ir paveikslų žiūryklė. Pix gali būti naudojama, norint atverti paveikslus kitose programėlėse, tokiose kaip paveikslų redaktorius, pridėti žymes į failus, pridėti anotacijas paveikslams, pasukti juos ir bendrinti.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Pix is een afbeeldingsgalerij en afbeeldingsviewer. Pix kan gebruikt worden om afbeeldingen met andere toepassingen, zoals een afbeeldingsbewerker, te openen, tags aan de bestanden en annotaties aan afbeeldingen toe te voegen, ze te roteren en ze te delen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Pix jest galerią obrazów i ich przeglądarką. Pix można użyć do otwierania obrazów w innych aplikacjach takich jak edytory obrazów, dodawania znaczników do plików, opisywania obrazów, ich obrotu, a także udostępniania.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Pix é uma galeria de imagens e um visualizador das mesmas. O Pix pode ser usado para abrir imagens com outras aplicações como um editor de imagens, adicionar marcas aos ficheiros, anotações às imagens, rodá-las e partilhá-las.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>O Pix é uma galeria e um visualizador de imagens. O Pix pode ser usado para abrir imagens por meio de outros aplicativos como um editor de imagens, adicionar tags aos seus arquivos, inserir anotações, rotacionar e compartilhar suas imagens.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Pix je galerija slik in pregledovalnik slik. Pix lahko uporabite za odpiranje slik z drugimi aplikacijami kot npr. z urejevalniki slik, lahko dodajate oznake datotek, napise k slikam, jih lahko zavrtite in delite z drugimi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Pix är ett bildgalleri och bildvisare. Pix kan användas för att öppna bilder med andra program som en bildeditor, lägga till taggar i filerna och kommentarer i bilder, samt rotera och dela dem.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Piks, bir görsel galerisi ve görüntüleyicidir. Piks, bir görsel düzenleyici gibi diğer uygulamalarda görsel açmak için kullanılabilir, dosyalara etiketler, resimlere ek açıklamalar ekleyebilir, onları döndürebilir ve paylaşabilir.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Пікс — галерея зображень і програма для перегляду зображень. Пікс можна скористатися для відкриття зображень за допомогою інших програм, зокрема редактора зображень, додавання міток до файлів, додавання анотацій до зображень, обертання зображень та оприлюднення зображень.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxPix is an image gallery and image viewer. Pix can be used to open images with other applications like an image editor, add tags to the files, add annotations to pictures, rotate and share them.xx</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>Pix 是一款图像库/相册浏览器和图像查看器。它可以浏览和打开图像，也可以调用外部图像编辑器打开图像。它还可以为图像文件添加标签、标注，对图像进行旋转、分享等操作。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/pix</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=pix</url>
  <url type="donation">https://kde.org/community/donations</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/pix/pix.png</image>
      <caption>The Pix music player</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">El reproductor de música Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">El reproductor de música Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Přehrávač hudby Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Pix-Musikwiedergabe</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">The Pix music player</caption>
      <caption lang="es">El reproductor de música Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Muusikamängija Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Pix-musiikkisoitin</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Le lecteur de musique Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">O reprodutor de música Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="hi">पिक्स संगीत चालक</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">A Pix zenelejátszó</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Pemutar musik Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Il lettore musicale Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">Pix 음악 재생기</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Pix muzikos grotuvas</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">De muziekspeler Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="nn">Pix musikkspelar</caption>
      <caption lang="pa">ਪਿਕਸ ਸੰਗੀਤ ਪਲੇਅਰ</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Odtwarzacz muzyki Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">O leitor de música Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">O reprodutor de músicas Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Hudobný prehrávač Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Predvajalnik glasbe Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Musikspelaren Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Piks müzik çalar</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Музичний програвач Pix</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxThe Pix music playerxx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-CN">Pix 音乐播放器</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-TW">Pix 音樂播放器</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/pix/pix-2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/pix/pix-3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <recommends>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0" />
  <provides>
    <binary>pix</binary>
  </provides>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <releases>
    <release date="2021-05-11" version="1.2.2">
      <url>https://nxos.org/maui/maui-1-2-2-release/</url>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-09-06" version="0.1.0" />
  </releases>
</component>