<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>mate.mate-calc</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">mate-calc.desktop</launchable>
  <id>mate-calc.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>MATE Calc</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">MATE Calc</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">MATE 计算器</name>
  <name lang="uk">MATE Рахівник</name>
  <name lang="tr">MATE Hesaplayıcı</name>
  <name lang="sr">Мејтов дигитрон</name>
  <name lang="sl">Računalo MATE</name>
  <name lang="ru">Калькулятор MATE</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">MATE Calculadora</name>
  <name lang="pt">MATE Calc</name>
  <name lang="pl">Kalkulator MATE</name>
  <name lang="oc">MATE Calc</name>
  <name lang="nl">MATE Calc</name>
  <name lang="nb">MATE kalkulator</name>
  <name lang="ms">Kalkulator MATE</name>
  <name lang="lt">MATE Calc</name>
  <name lang="ko">MATE 계산기</name>
  <name lang="ja">MATE 電卓</name>
  <name lang="it">MATE Calc</name>
  <name lang="id">Kalkulator MATE</name>
  <name lang="he">מחשבון MATE</name>
  <name lang="gl">Calculadora do MATE</name>
  <name lang="fr">MATE Calc</name>
  <name lang="es">Calculadora de MATE</name>
  <name lang="de">MATE Taschenrechner</name>
  <name lang="da">MATE Calc</name>
  <name lang="cs">MATE Kalkulačka</name>
  <name lang="ca">Calculadora de MATE</name>
  <summary>MATE Desktop calculator</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">MATE 桌面計算機</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">MATE 计算器</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Рахівник стільниці MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">MATE Masaüstü hesap makinesi</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">MATE Desktop kalkylator</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Дигитрон за Мејтову радну површ</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Namizno računalo MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Kalkulačka prostredia MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Калькулятор MATE </summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Calculator MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Calculadora do MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Calculadora de Área de Trabalho MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Kalkulator środowiska MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Calculadoira de burèu MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">MATE Bureaublad-rekenmachine</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">MATE skrivebordskalkulator</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Kalkulator Desktop MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">MATE darbalaukio skaičiuotuvas</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">MATE 데스크톱 계산기 </summary>
  <summary lang="ja">MATE 卓上計算機</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Calcolatrice del Desktop MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="ie">Calculator de pupitre MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Kalkulator destop MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="hy">MATE Հաշվիչ</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">MATE asztali számológép </summary>
  <summary lang="he">מחשבון לשולחן העבודה MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Calculadora do Escritorio MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Calculatrice du bureau MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">MATE Työpöytä laskin</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">MATE mahaigaineko kalkulagailua</summary>
  <summary lang="et">MATE töölaua kalkulaator</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Calculadora del escritorio MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Kalkulilo de MATE Labortablo</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">MATE Desktop calculator</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Αριθμομηχανή Επιφάνεια εργασίας  ΜΑΤΕ</summary>
  <summary lang="de">MATE-Taschenrechner</summary>
  <summary lang="da">MATE Skrivebords lommeregner</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Kalkulačka prostředí MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Calculadora de l'escriptori MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Calculadora de l'escriptori MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">MATE Калкулатор</summary>
  <summary lang="am">የ ሜት ዴስክቶፕ መደመሪያ</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
   MATE Calc is a powerful graphical calculator with financial,
   logical and scientific modes. It uses a multiple precision package
   to do its arithmetic to give a high degree of accuracy.
  </p>
    <p>
   MATE Calc is a fork of GNOME Calc and part of the MATE Desktop Environment.
   If you would like to know more about MATE and MATE Calc, please visit the
   project's home page.
  </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>La calculadora de MATE és una calculadora gràfica potent amb mode financer, lògic i científic. Utilitza l'empaquetament de precisió múltiple per fer que la seva aritmètica doni un grau elevat de precisió.</p>
    <p>La calculadora de MATE és una bifurcació de la calculadora de GNOME, i part de l'entorn d'escriptori MATE. Si voleu saber més sobre MATE i la calculadora de MATE, visiteu la pàgina principal del projecte.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>MATE Kalkulačka je schopná grafická kalkulačka s finančními, logickými a vědeckými režimy. Používá pro svou atitmetiku multiple precision package, aby poskytla vysoký stupeň přesnosti.</p>
    <p>MATE Calc je novou větví GNOME Calc a je součástí pracovního prostředí MATE. Pokud byste se chtěli dozvědět více o MATE a MATE Calc, navštivte domovskou stránku projektu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>MATE Calc er en kraftfuld grafisk lommeregner med finansiel, logisk og videnskabelig tilstande. Det bruger en multipel præcisionspakke til at udføre aritmetik til en høj grad af nøjagtighed.</p>
    <p>MATE Calc er en forgrening af GNOME Calc og en del af MATE-skrivebordet. Hvis du ønsker at vide mere om MATE og MATE Calc, så besøg projektets hjemmeside.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>MATE-Calc ist ein leistungsfähiger grafischer Taschenrechner mit finanziellen, logischen und wissenschaftlichen Modi. Es verwendet ein Mehrfachpräzisionspaket für seine Arithmetik, um ein hohes Maß an Genauigkeit zu bieten.</p>
    <p>MATE-Calc ist eine Abspaltung von GNOME-Calc und ein Teil der MATE-Arbeitsumgebung. Wenn Sie mehr über MATE und MATE-Calc erfahren möchten, besuchen Sie bitte die Internetseite des Projektes.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Calculadora de MATE es una potente calculadora gráfica que incluye los modos financiero, lógico y científico. Utiliza un paquete de precisión múltiple para realizar los cálculos y ofrecer un alto grado de precisión.</p>
    <p>Calculadora de MATE es una bifurcación de Calculadora de GNOME y forma parte del entorno de escritorio MATE. Si quiere saber más sobre MATE y Calculadora de MATE, visite la página principal del proyecto.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>MATE Calc est une calculatrice graphique puissante dotée de modes financier, logique et scientifique. Elle utilise un paquet de précision multiple pour ses opérations arithmétiques afin d'obtenir un niveau élevé de précision.</p>
    <p>MATE Calc est un fork de GNOME Calc et fait partie de l'environnement de bureau MATE. Si vous désirez en savoir plus au sujet de MATE et de la calculatrice MATE, veuillez visiter la page d'accueil du projet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>A calculadora do MATE é unha potente calculadora gráfica con modo financeiro, lóxico e científico. Utiliza un paquete de precisión múltiple para levar a cabo súa aritmética cun alto nivel de precisión.</p>
    <p>A calculadora do MATE é unha bifurcación da Calculadora do GNOME é e parte do contorno de escritorio MATE. Se quere saber máis sobre MATE e a Calculadora do MATE, visite a páxina do proxecto.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>המחשבון של MATE הוא מחשבון גרפי רב עצמה עם מצבים פיננסי, לוגי ומדעי. המחשבון משתמש בחבילת דיוק בסיסית כדי לבצע את החישובים תוך אספקת רמת דיוק גבוהה.</p>
    <p>המחשבון שלMATE פוצל מתוך המחשבון של GNOME והוא חלק מסביבת שולחן העבודה של MATE. אם מעניין אותך לדעת עוד על MATE ועל המחשבון של MATE, נא לבקר בדף הבית של המיזם.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Kalkulator MATE adalah kalkulator grafis yang bertenaga dengan mode keuangan, logika, dan ilmiah. Menggunakan paket presisi ganda untuk melakukan aritmatika yang memberikan tingkat akurasi yang tinggi.</p>
    <p>Kalkulator MATE merupakan fork dari Kalkulator GNOME dan bagian dari Lingkungan Desktop MATE. Bila Anda ingin tahu lebih banyak tentang MATE dan Kalkulator MATE, silakan kunjungi laman beranda proyek.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>MATE Calc è una calcolatrice grafica con modalità finanziaria, avanzata e scientifica. Utilizza un pacchetto a precisione multipla per eseguire i calcoli e fornisce un alto livello di precisione.</p>
    <p>MATE Calc è un fork di GNOME Calc e parte dell'ambiente desktop MATE. Se desideri ulteriori informazioni su MATE e MATE Calc, visita il sito web del progetto.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>MATE 電卓は、金融、論理、科学の各モードを備えた強力なグラフィカルな電卓です。演算を行うために多数の正確なパッケージを使用し、高い精度を実現します。</p>
    <p>MATE 電卓は GNOME 電卓のフォークであり、MATE デスクトップ環境の一部です。もしあなたが MATE と MATE 電卓についてもっと知りたければ、プロジェクトのウェブサイトを参照してください。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>MATE 계산기는 재무, 논리 및 과학 모드를 갖춘 강력한 그래픽 계산기입니다. 다중 정밀도 패키지를 사용하여 높은 수준의 정확도를 제공합니다.</p>
    <p>GNOME 계산기는 GNOME 계산기의 포크이며 GNOME 데스크탑 환경의 일부입니다. GNOME와 GNOME 계산기에 대해 더 알고 싶다면 프로젝트 홈페이지를 방문하십시오.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>MATE skaičiuotuvas yra galingas grafinis skaičiuotuvas su finansine, logine ir moksline veiksena. Savo aritmetinių skaičiavimų atlikimui šis skaičiuotuvas naudoja kelis tikslumo paketus, kad tokiu būdu suteiktų jums aukštą tikslumo laipsnį.</p>
    <p>MATE skaičiuotuvas yra GNOME skaičiuotuvo atšaka ir MATE dabalaukio aplinkos dalis. Jei norite sužinoti daugiau apie MATE ir MATE skaičiuotuvą, prašome apsilankyti projekto tinklalapyje.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Kalkulator MATE ialah kalkultor bergrafik yang terbaik dengan mod kewangan, logikal dan saintifik. Ia menggunakan pakej kepersisan berbilang untuk melakukan aritmatiknya supaya dapat mempersembahkan ketepatan yang tinggi.</p>
    <p>Kalkulator MATE merupakan cabang dari GNOME Calc dan sebahagian dari Persekitaran Desktop MATE. Jika anda mahu ketahui lebih lanjut mengenai MATE dan Kalkulator MATE, sila lawati laman sesawang projek.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>MATE-kalkulatoren er en kraftig grafisk kalkulator med økonomisk, logisk og vitenskapelig modus. Den bruker stortallsaritmetikk for å kalkulere med høy nøyaktighet.</p>
    <p>MATE-kalkulatoren er avledet fra GNOME-kalkulatoren og er en del av skrivebordsmiljøet MATE. Besøk prosjektets hjemmeside hvis du vil vite mer om MATE og MATE-kalkulatoren.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>MATE Calc is een krachtige grafische rekenmachine met financiële, logische en wetenschappelijke standen. Hij gebruikt een meervoudig precisiepakket voor zijn berekeningen om een hoge mate van accuraatheid te bereiken.</p>
    <p>MATE Calc is een vork van GNOME Calc en maakt deel uit van de MATE-werkomgeving. Als u meer wilt weten over MATE en MATE Calc, bezoek dan de webpagina van het project.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>MATE Calc es una calculadoira potenta amb mòdes financièr, avançat e scientific. Emplega d’unes paquets de precisions per son aritmetica per dire de donar un naut grau d’exactitud.</p>
    <p>MATE Calc es una derivacion de GNOME Calc e fa part de l’environament de burèu MATE. Se volètz ne saber mai tocant MATE e MATE Calc, consultatz lo site del projècte.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Kalkulator MATE to potężny kalkulator graficzny o trybach finansowych, logicznych i naukowych. Wykorzystuje pakiet wielokrotnej precyzji, aby wykonać swoją arytmetykę, aby zapewnić wysoki stopień dokładności.</p>
    <p>Kalkulator MATE to odgałęzienie Kalkulatora GNOME i część środowiska MATE Desktop. Jeśli chcesz dowiedzieć się więcej o MATE i Kalkulatorze MATE, odwiedź stronę główną projektu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Mate Calc é uma calculador gráfica poderosa com modos para finanças, lógica e ciência. Utiliza um pacote de precisão múltipla no seu processo aritmético para obter um nível alto de precisão.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>MATE Calc é uma calculadora gráfica poderosa com modo financeiro, lógico e científico. Ela usa um pacote de precisão múltipla para fazer a aritmética e fornecer um alto grau de precisão.</p>
    <p>MATE Calculadora é um fork do GNOME Calc e parte do MATE Desktop Environment. Se você quiser saber mais sobre o MATE e o MATE Calc, visite a página inicial do projeto..</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Калькулятор MATE — это мощный графический калькулятор с денежным, логическим и научным режимами расчёта. Он использует пакет произвольной точности для высочайшей точности вычислений.</p>
    <p>Кальулятор MATE — это форк GNOME Calc и часть окружения рабочего стола MATE. Если вы хотите узнать больше о MATE и Калькуляторе MATE, пожалуйста, посетите домашнюю страницу проекта. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Računalo MATE je močan grafični kalkulator s finančnim, logičnim in znanstvenim načinom. Za izdelavo aritmetike uporablja več natančnih paketov, ki daje visoko stopnjo natančnosti.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Мејтов дигитрон је моћан графички дигитрон са финансијским, логичким и научним режимима. Користи пакет вишеструке тачности за своју аритметику како би дао висок степен тачности.</p>
    <p>Мејтов дигитрон је исцепак Гномовог дигитрона и део Мејтовог окружења радне површи. Ако желите да сазнате више о Мејту и Мејтовом дигитрону, посетите матичну страницу пројекта.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>MATE Hesaplayıcı; finansal, mantıksal ve bilimsel kipleri bulunan güçlü bir grafik hesap makinesidir. Yüksek bir doğruluk seviyesi sağlamak amacıyla, aritmetiği için çoklu hassasiyet paketi kullanır.</p>
    <p>MATE Hesaplayıcı, GNOME Hesaplayıcının çatallamasıdır ve MATE Masaüstü Ortamı'nın bir parçasıdır. MATE ve MATE Hesaplayıcı hakkında daha fazla bilgi edinmek isterseniz, lütfen projenin anasayfasını ziyaret ediniz.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>MATE Calc — це потужний графічний рахівник з економічним, логічним і науковим режимами. Він використовує пакунок повторюваних операцій, щоб додати розрахункам більшої точности.</p>
    <p>MATE Calc є відгалуженням(форком) GNOME Calc і частиною оточення стільниці MATE. Якщо ви хочете дізнатися більше про MATE, чи MATE Calc, будь ласка, відвідайте домашню сторінку проєкту.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>MATE Calc 是一款功能强大的图形计算器，有三种模式：财务，逻辑和科学。 为了提高精度，它使用多精度软件包进行数学运算。</p>
    <p>MATE Calc 为 MATE 桌面环境的一部分，是 GNOME Calc 的复刻。想了解更多 MATE 及 MATE Calc 的信息，请访问项目主页。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>MATE Calc 是一個強大的圖形化計算機，其包含了金融、邏輯與科學模式。它使用了多精度軟體來讓其算數有高度的精確度。</p>
    <p>MATE Calc 是一個 GNOME Calc 的分支以及 MATE 桌面環境的一部份。若您想要知道更多關於 MATE 與 MATE Calc 的資訊，請拜訪專案首頁。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="314" height="247">
    https://alexpl.fedorapeople.org/AppData/mate-calc/screens/mate-calc_01.png
   </image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image width="564" height="308">
    https://alexpl.fedorapeople.org/AppData/mate-calc/screens/mate-calc_02.png
   </image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image height="374" width="514">
    https://alexpl.fedorapeople.org/AppData/mate-calc/screens/mate-calc_03.png
   </image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.mate-desktop.org</url>
  <updatecontact>mate-dev@ml.mate-desktop.org</updatecontact>
  <project_group>MATE</project_group>
</component>