<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>mate.mate-system-monitor</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">mate-system-monitor.desktop</launchable>
  <id>mate-system-monitor.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>MATE System Monitor</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">MATE 系統監控程式</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">MATE 系统监视器</name>
  <name lang="uz">MATE Tizim Nazorati</name>
  <name lang="uk">Системний монітор MATE</name>
  <name lang="tr">MATE Sistem Gözlemcisi</name>
  <name lang="th">เครื่องมือเฝ้าสังเกตระบบของ MATE</name>
  <name lang="sv">Systemövervakare för MATE</name>
  <name lang="sr">Мејтов пратилац система</name>
  <name lang="sq">MATE Monitori i sistemit </name>
  <name lang="sl">MATE Sistemski Nadzornik</name>
  <name lang="sk">Monitor systému prostredia MATE</name>
  <name lang="ru">Системный монитор MATE</name>
  <name lang="ro">Monitor sistem MATE</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Monitor do sistema MATE</name>
  <name lang="pt">Monitor do Sistema MATE</name>
  <name lang="pl">Monitor systemu MATE</name>
  <name lang="oc">Monitor sistèma MATE</name>
  <name lang="nl">MATE Systeembewaking</name>
  <name lang="nds">MATE System-Uppasser</name>
  <name lang="nb">MATE Systemovervåking</name>
  <name lang="ms">Pemantau Sistem MATE</name>
  <name lang="lt">MATE sistemos monitorius</name>
  <name lang="ko">MATE 시스템 모니터</name>
  <name lang="kn">MATE ಗಣಕ ಮೇಲ್ವಿಚಾರಕ</name>
  <name lang="kk">MATE жүйелік бақылаушысы</name>
  <name lang="ja">MATE システムモニター</name>
  <name lang="it">Monitor di Sistema MATE</name>
  <name lang="ie">Monitor del sistema MATE</name>
  <name lang="id">Pemantau Sistem MATE</name>
  <name lang="hy">MATE Համակարգային Հսկում</name>
  <name lang="hu">MATE rendszerfigyelő</name>
  <name lang="hr">MATE nadzor sustava</name>
  <name lang="he">צג המערכת של MATE</name>
  <name lang="gl">Monitor do sistema do MATE</name>
  <name lang="fr">Moniteur système MATE</name>
  <name lang="fi">MATE Järjestelmän valvonta</name>
  <name lang="eu">MATE Sistemaren Monitorea</name>
  <name lang="et">MATE süsteemijälgija</name>
  <name lang="es_AR">Monitor del sistema de MATE</name>
  <name lang="es">Monitor del sistema de MATE</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">MATE System Monitor</name>
  <name lang="en_AU">MATE System Monitor</name>
  <name lang="el">Παρακολούθηση Συστήματος MATE</name>
  <name lang="de">MATE-Systemüberwachung</name>
  <name lang="da">MATE - systemovervågning</name>
  <name lang="cs">Sledování systému MATE</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">Monitor del sistema del MATE</name>
  <name lang="ca">Monitor del sistema de MATE</name>
  <name lang="bg">Наблюдение на системата на MATE</name>
  <name lang="be">Сістэмны назіральнік MATE</name>
  <name lang="ast">Monitor del sistema de MATE</name>
  <name lang="ar">مرقاب نظام متّة</name>
  <name lang="am">ሜት ስርአት መቆጣጠሪያ </name>
  <summary>A Process and resource monitor for MATE Desktop</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">適用於 MATE 桌面環境的處理程序及資源監視器</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">用于 MATE 桌面的进程与资源监视器</summary>
  <summary lang="uz">MATE Ish stoli uchun Jarayon va resurs nazorati</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Монітор процесів і ресурсів середовища MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">MATE masaüstü için süreç ve kaynak gözlemcisi</summary>
  <summary lang="th">เฝ้าสังเกตโพรเซสและทรัพยากรสำหรับเดสก์ท็อป MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">En process och resursövervakare för MATE-skrivbordet</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Пратилац процеса и ресурса за Мејтову радну површ</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Pregled procesov in sredstev za MATE Namizje</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Monitor procesov a prostriedkov prostredia MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="sc">Unu monitor de protzessos e resursas pro MATE Desktop</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Монитор процессов и ресурсов среды MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Un monitor de procese și resurse pentru desktopul MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Um monitor de processo e recurso para desktop MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Um processo e monitor de recursos do Ambiente de Trabalho MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Monitor procesów i zasobów dla środowiska MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Un monitor de processus e ressorsas pel burèu MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Een proces- en systeembelastingbewaker voor de MATE-werkomgeving</summary>
  <summary lang="nds">Een Uppasser över Prozessen un Resourcen för de MATE Schrievdisk</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Et prosess og ressursovervåknings-program for MATE-skrivebordsmiljøet</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Pemantau proses dan sumber untuk Desktop MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Procesų ir išteklių monitorius MATE darbalaukiui</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">MATE 데스크톱용 프로세스 및 자원 감시 프로그램</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">MATE デスクトップのプロセスとリソースを監視します。</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Un monitor di processi e risorse per l'ambiente desktop MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="ie">Un monitor de processus e ressurses por ambientie MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Pemantau proses dan sumber daya untuk Desktop MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="hy">Գործընթացի և ռեսուրսի վերահսկում MATE  Աշխատանքային սեղանի համար</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Egy folyamat és erőforrás figyelő a MATE asztali környezethez</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Nadzor prosesa i resursa za MATE radno okruženje</summary>
  <summary lang="he">צג התהליכים והמשאבים של שולחן העבודה MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Un monitor de procesos e recursos para o escritorio MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Un moniteur de processus et ressources pour le bureau MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Prosessien ja resurssien valvonta MATE-työpöydälle</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Prozesu eta baliabideen erabileraren monitorea MATE mahaigainerako</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Protsesside ja ressursside jälgimisprogramm MATE töölauale</summary>
  <summary lang="es_CO">Un monitor de recursos y procesos para el entorno de escritorio MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Un monitor de procesos y recursos para MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">A Process and resource monitor for MATE Desktop</summary>
  <summary lang="en_AU">A Process and resource monitor for MATE Desktop</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Ένα πρόγραμμα εποπτείας διεργασιών και πόρων για το MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Eine Prozess- und Ressourcenüberwachung für die MATE-Arbeitsumgebung</summary>
  <summary lang="da">En proces- og ressourceovervåger for MATE-skrivebordet</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Sledování procesů a systémových prostředků pro MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Un monitor de processos i de recursos per a l'escriptori MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Un monitor de processos i de recursos per a l'escriptori MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Програма за следене на процесите и ресурсите на MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Назіральнік працэсаў і рэсурсаў асяроддзя MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="ast">Un monitor de procesos y recursos pa MATE</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">مراقب للعمليات و الموارد في سطح مكتب متّة</summary>
  <summary lang="am">ለ ሜት ዴስክቶፕ ሂደቶች እና ምንጮችን መቆጣጠሪያ</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
   MATE System Monitor allows to graphically view and manipulate the running
   processes on your system. It also provides an overview of available resources,
   such as CPU and memory.
  </p>
    <p>
   MATE System Monitor is a fork of GNOME System Monitor and part of the MATE
   Desktop Environment. If you would like to know more about MATE and System Monitor,
   please visit the project's home page.
  </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El monitor del sistema de MATE permet visualitzar i manipular gràficament els processos en execució del vostre sistema. També proporciona una visió general dels recursos disponibles, com ara la CPU i la memòria.</p>
    <p>El monitor del sistema de MATE és una bifurcació del monitor del sistema de GNOME, i forma part de l'entorn d'escriptori MATE. Si voleu saber més sobre MATE i el monitor del sistema de MATE, visiteu la pàgina principal del projecte.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Sledování systému MATE umožňuje graficky prohlížet a manipulovat se spuštěnými procesy ve vašem systému. Poskytuje také přehled o dostupných systémových prostředcích, jako jsou např. procesor a paměť.</p>
    <p>Aplikace Sledování systému MATE je forkem aplikace GNOME System Monitor a je součástí prostředí MATE. Pokud se chcete dozvědět více o MATE a Sledování systému, navštivte domovskou stránku projektu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>MATE System Monitor giver mulighed for grafisk at vise og manipulere de kørende processer på dit system. Det giver også et overblik over de tilgængelige ressourcer, såsom CPU og hukommelse.</p>
    <p>MATE System Monitor er en forgrening af GNOME System Monitor og en del af skrivebordsmiljøet MATE. Hvis du ønsker at vide mere om MATE og System Monitor så besøg projektets hjemmeside.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>El monitor del sistema de MATE permite ver y manipular gráficamente los procesos en ejecución en el sistema. También proporciona una visión general de los recursos disponibles, como por ejemplo el procesador y la memoria.</p>
    <p>Monitor del sistema de MATE es una bifurcación de Monitor del sistema de GNOME y es parte del entorno de escritorio MATE. Si quiere saber más sobre MATE y Monitor del sistema, visite la página principal del proyecto.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>MATE SIstemaren Monitoreak zure sisteman exekutatzen ari diren prozesuak grafikoki ikusi eta aldatzeko aukera ematen dizu. Era berean, eskuragarri dauden baliabideen ikuspegi orokor bat erakusten du, hala nola CPU-a eta memoria.</p>
    <p>MATE Sistemaren Monitorea GNOME Sistemaren Monitorea aplikaziotik eratorria da eta MATE Mahaigain Ingurunearen partea da. MATE eta Sistemaren Monitoreari buruz gehiago jakiteko, mesedez ikusi proiektuaren webgunea.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Le Moniteur système MATE permet d'afficher et de manipuler graphiquement des processus en cours du système. Il fournit aussi un aperçu des ressources disponibles, tels le CPU et la mémoire.</p>
    <p>Le moniteur système MATE est un fork du moniteur système GNOME et fait partie de l'Environnement de bureau MATE. Si vous souhaitez en savoir plus sur MATE et le moniteur système MATE, veuillez visiter la page d'accueil du projet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>O Monitor do sistema do MATE permite ver e manipular graficamente os procesos que están a executarse no sistema. Tamén ofrece unha vista xeral dos recursos dispoñíbeis, como o procesador e a memoria do equipo.</p>
    <p>O Monitor do sistema do MATE é unha bifurcación do Monitor do sistema do GNOME é e parte do contorno de escritorio MATE. Se quere saber máis sobre MATE e o Monitor do sistema do MATE, visite a páxina do proxecto.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Pemantau Sistem MATE memiliki kemampuan untuk melihat dan memanipulasi proses yang berjalan pada sistem Anda secara visual. Aplikasi ini juga menyediakan gambaran tentang sumber daya yang tersedia, seperti CPU dan memori.</p>
    <p>Pemantau Sistem MATE adalah fork dari GNOME System Monitor dan merupakan bagian dari Lingkungan Desktop MATE. Jika Anda hendak mengetahui lebih lanjut tentang MATE dan System Monitor, harap mengunjungi halaman home page proyek.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Il Monitor di Sistema MATE permette di visualizzare graficamente e agire sui processi in esecuzione nel sistema. Fornisce inoltre una panoramica delle risorse disponibili, come CPU e memoria.</p>
    <p>l Monitor di Sistema MATE è un fork del Monitor di Sistema GNOME ed è parte dell'ambiente desktop MATE. Se vuoi conoscere di più su MATE e Monitor di Sistema, visita l'home page del progetto.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>MATE システムモニターは、システムで実行中のプロセスをグラフィカルに表示し、操作することができます。また、CPU やメモリなど利用可能なリソースの概要も表示します。</p>
    <p>MATE システムモニターは、GNOME システムモニターのフォークであり、 MATE デスクトップ環境の一部です。MATE とシステムモニターの詳細について知りたい場合は、プロジェクトのウェブページをご覧ください。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>GNOME 시스템 모니터는 GNOME 시스템 모니터의 포크이자 GNOME 데스크톱 환경의 일부입니다. GNOME 및 시스템 모니터에 대해 자세히 알고 싶으시면 프로젝트의 홈 페이지를 방문하십시오.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>MATE sistemos monitorius leidžia matyti ir valdyti jūsų sistemoje vykdomus procesus. Jis taip pat pateikia prieinamų išteklių, tokių kaip centrinis procesorius ir atmintis, apžvalgą. </p>
    <p> MATE sistemos monitorius yra GNOME sistemos monitoriaus atšaka ir MATE dabalaukio aplinkos dalis. Jei norite sužinoti daugiau apie MATE ir MATE sistemos monitorių, prašom apsilankyti projekto tinklalapyje. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Pemantau Sistem MATE membolehkan paparan bergrafik dan manipulasi proses yang berjalan dalam sistem anda. Ia juga menyediakan selayang pandang sumber yang tersedia, seperti CPU dan ingatan.</p>
    <p>Pemantau Sistem MATE merupakan cabang Pemantau Sistem GNOME dan sebahagian dari Persekitaran Desktop MATE. Jika anda mahu ketahui lebih lanjut mengenai MATE dan Pemantau Sistem, sila lawati laman sesawang projek.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>MATE Systemovervåkning lar deg vise og håndtere de prosessene som kjører på systemet. Programmet gir deg også et overblikk over tilgjengelige ressurser, som CPU og minne.</p>
    <p>MATE Systemovervåkning er avledet av GNOME Systemovervåkning og er den del av skrivebordsmiljøet MATE. Besøk prosjektets hjemmeside hvis du vil vite mer om MATE og MATE Systemovervåkning.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>MATE Systeembewaker stelt u in staat om grafisch de draaiende processen op uw systeem te zien en te bewerken. Hij biedt ook een overzicht van de beschikbare systeemhulpbronnen, zoals CPU en geheugen.</p>
    <p>MATE Systeembewaker is een vork van GNOME System Monitor en maakt deel uit van de werkomgeving MATE. Als u meer wilt weten over MATE en Systeembewaker, bezoek dan a.u.b. de thuispagina van het project.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>Lo Monitor sistèma MATE permet d'afichar e de manipular graficament de processús en cors del sistèma. Provesís tanben un apercebut de las ressorsas disponiblas, coma lo CPU e la memòria.</p>
    <p>Lo Monitor Sistèma de MATE es una derivacion de GNOME System Monitor e fa part de l’environament de burèu MATE. Se volètz ne saber mai a prepaus de MATE e del Monitor Sistèma MATE, consultatz lo site del projècte.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Monitor systemu MATE umożliwia graficzne przeglądanie i manipulowanie działającymi procesami w systemie. Zawiera również przegląd dostępnych zasobów, takich jak procesor i pamięć.</p>
    <p>Monitor systemu MATE jest forkiem Monitora systemu GNOME i częścią środowiska graficznego MATE. Jeśli chcesz dowiedzieć się więcej o MATE i Monitorze systemu, odwiedź stronę główną projektu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Monitor de Sistema do MATE permite a visualização gráfica e a manipulação dos processos em execução no sistema. Também dá uma panorâmica dos recursos de CPU e de memória disponíveis. </p>
    <p>O Monitor de Sistema do MATE é um derivado do Monitor de Sistema do GNOME e faz parte do Ambiente de Trabalho MATE. Para saber mais sobre o MATE e sobre o Monitor de Sistema, visitar o sítio web do projecto.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Системный монитор MATE позволяет графически просматривать и управлять запущенными процессами на вашей системе. Он также предоставляет обзор доступных ресурсов, таких как как процессор и память.</p>
    <p>MATE System Monitor – форк GNOME System Monitor и часть рабочей среды MATE. Если вы хотите узнать больше о MATE и системном мониторе, пожалуйста, посетите домашнюю страницу проекта.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>MATE nadzornik sistema omogoča grafični prikaz in spreminjanje izvajanih procesov sistema. Poleg tega ponuja pregled virov, ki so na voljo, kot so CPE in pomnilnik.</p>
    <p>MATE nadzornik sistema je predelava GNOME nadzornika sistema in del MATE namiznega okolja. Če bi radi izvedeli več o MATE in Nadzorniku sistema, obiščite spletno stran projekta.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Мејтов пратилац система омогућава да видите и да управљате покренутим процесима на вашем систему. Такође обезбеђује преглед доступних ресурса, као што је процесор и меморија.</p>
    <p>Мејтов пратилац система је исцепак Гномовог пратиоца система и део Мејтовог окружења радне површи. Ако желите да сазнате више о Мејту и о Пратиоцу система, посетите матичну страницу пројекта.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="th">
    <p>เครื่องมือเฝ้าสังเกตระบบของ MATE อนุญาตให้ดูแบบกราฟิกและจัดการโพรเซสที่กำลังทำงานในระบบของคุณ ยังให้ภาพรวมของทรัพยากรที่ใช้ได้ เช่น ซีพียูและหน่วยความจำ</p>
    <p>เครื่องมือเฝ้าสังเกตระบบของ MATE แตกแขนงมาจากเครื่องมือเฝ้าสังเกตระบบของ GNOME และเป็นส่วนหนึ่งของสภาพแวดล้อมเดสก์ท็อป MATE ถ้าคุณต้องการทราบข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับ MATE และเครื่องมือเฝ้าสังเกตระบบ กรุณาเยี่ยมชมโฮมเพจของโครงการ</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>MATE System Monitor дозволяє графічно переглядати та керувати запущеними процесами у вашій системі. Він також надає огляд доступних ресурсів, таких як центральний процесор і пам'ять.</p>
    <p>MATE System Monitor є відгалуженням системного монітора GNOME та частиною робочого середовища MATE. Якщо ви волієте дізнатися більше про MATE та System Monitor, відвідайте домашню сторінку проєкту.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p> MATE 系统监视器，以图形化的方式来让用户浏览或操作当前进程。还提供了可用资源的概览, 如 CPU 和 内存状况。</p>
    <p>MATE 系统监视器是 MATE 桌面环境的一部分，为 GNOME 系统监视器的复刻。想了解更多有关 MATE 及 MATE 系统监视器的信息，可访问项目主页。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>MATE 系統監控程式讓您可以圖形化檢視及管理執行中在您的系統上的處理程序。它也提供了可用資源的概覽，像是 CPU 及記憶體。</p>
    <p>MATE 系統監控程式是一個 GNOME 系統監控程式的分支，且為 MATE 桌面環境的一部份。如果您想要知道更多關於 MATE 及系統監控程式的詳細資訊，請參觀專案首頁。 </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="960" height="540">
    https://alexpl.fedorapeople.org/AppData/mate-system-monitor/screens/mate-system-monitor_01.png
   </image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image height="540" width="960">
    https://alexpl.fedorapeople.org/AppData/mate-system-monitor/screens/mate-system-monitor_02.png
   </image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image width="960" height="540">
    https://alexpl.fedorapeople.org/AppData/mate-system-monitor/screens/mate-system-monitor_03.png
   </image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://mate-desktop.org</url>
  <updatecontact>mate-dev@ml.mate-desktop.org</updatecontact>
  <project_group>MATE</project_group>
</component>