<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>networkmanagerapplet</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">nm-connection-editor.desktop</launchable>
  <id>nm-connection-editor.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">网络管理器</name>
  <name lang="uk">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="tr">Ağ Yöneticisi</name>
  <name lang="sv">Nätverkshanteraren</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Upravnik mreže</name>
  <name lang="sr">Управник мреже</name>
  <name lang="sk">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="ru">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="ro">Administrator de rețea</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="pt">Gestor de rede</name>
  <name lang="pl">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਨੈੱਟਵਰਕ-ਮੈਨੇਜਰ</name>
  <name lang="oc">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="nl">Netwerkbeheer</name>
  <name lang="nb">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="lv">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="lt">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="kk">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="ja">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="it">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="is">NetworkManager netstýring</name>
  <name lang="id">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="hu">Hálózatkezelő</name>
  <name lang="hr">Mrežni upravitelj</name>
  <name lang="gl">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="gd">Manaidsear lìonraidh</name>
  <name lang="fr">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="fi">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="eu">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="es">Gestor de la red</name>
  <name lang="de">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="da">Netværkshåndtering</name>
  <name lang="cs">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="ca">NetworkManager</name>
  <name lang="be">NetworkManager</name>
  <summary>NetworkManager connection editor</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">NetworkManager 連線編輯器</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">网络管理器连接编辑器</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Редактор з'єднань NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Ağ Yöneticisi bağlantı düzenleyici</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Nätverkshanteraren (anslutningsredigerare)</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Uređivač veza upravnika mreže</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Уређивач веза управника мреже</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Editor pripojení správcu siete NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Редактор подключений NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Editorul de conexiuni „Administrator de rețea”</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Editor de conexão NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Editor de ligação NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Edytor połączeń usługi NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary lang="pa">ਨੈੱਟਵਰਕ-ਮੈਨੇਜਰ ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਐਡੀਟਰ</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Editor de connexion NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Netwerkbeheer verbindingseditor</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">NetworkManager – redigering av tilkoblinger</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">NetworkManager savienojumu redaktors</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">NetworkManager ryšio redaktorius</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">NetworkManager байланыстар түзеткіші</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">NetworkManager 接続エディター</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Editor connessione NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary lang="is">NetworkManager tengingaritill</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Penyunting koneksi NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Hálózatkezelő kapcsolatszerkesztő</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Mrežni upravitelj - uređivač povezivanja</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Editor de conexións de NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary lang="gd">Deasaiche ceanglaichean Manaidsear lìonraidh</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Éditeur de connexion NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">NetworkManager-yhteysmuokkain</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">NetworkManager konexioen editorea</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Editor de conexiones Network Manager</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Netzwerkverwaltung-Verbindungseditor</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Netværkshåndtering — redigering af forbindelse</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Editor připojení NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Editor de connexions del NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Рэдактар злучэнняў NetworkManager</summary>
  <description>
    <p>NetworkManager is a system service for managing and configuring your
    network connections and devices.</p>
    <p>The nm-connection-editor program works with NetworkManager to create
    and edit existing connection profiles for NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>NetworkManager - сістэмная служба для кіравання і наладкі сеткавых злучэнняў і прылад.</p>
    <p>Праграма nm-connection-editor працуе з NetworkManager для стварэння і рэдагавання існых профіляў злучэнняў для NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El NetworkManager és un servei de sistema per a gestionar i configurar les vostres connexions de xarxa i els vostres dispositius.</p>
    <p>El programa nm-connection-editor funciona amb el NetworkManager per a crear i editar perfils existents de connexions per al NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>NetworkManager je systémová služba pro správu a nastavení vašich síťových připojení a zařízení.</p>
    <p>Program nm-connection-editor spolupracuje se službou NetworkManager při vytváření a změnách stávajících profilů připojení pro NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Netværkshåndtering er en systemtjeneste til håndtering og konfigurering af dine netværksforbindelser og -enheder.</p>
    <p>Programmet nm-connection-editor arbejder sammen med Netværkshåndtering om at oprette og redigere eksisterende forbindelsesprofiler til Netværkshåndtering.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>NetworkManager ist ein Systemdienst zur Verwaltung und Einrichtung Ihrer Netzwerkverbindungen und -geräte.</p>
    <p>nm-connection-editor arbeitet gemeinsam mit NetworkManager zum Anlegen und Bearbeiten von vorhandenen Verbindungsprofilen für NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>NetworkManager es un demonio del sistema para gestionar y configurar sus conexiones y sus dispositivos de red.</p>
    <p>El programa nm-connection-editor funciona con NetworkManager para crear y editar perfiles de NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>NetworkManager zure sareko konexioak eta gailuak kudeatzeko eta konfiguratzeko sistema-zerbitzua da.</p>
    <p>Nm-connection-editor programak NetworkManager programarekin funtzionatzen du NetworkMager-en konexio-profilak sortzeko eta editatzeko.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>NetworkManager on järjestelmäpalvelu, joka hallitsee ja määrittää verkkoyhteydet sekä -laitteet.</p>
    <p>Ohjelma nimeltä nm-connection-editor toimii NetworkManagerin kanssa; sillä luodaan ja muokataan yhteysprofiileja NetworkManagerin käyttöön.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>NetworkManager est un service système de gestion et de configuration de vos connexions et périphériques réseau.</p>
    <p>Le programme nm-connection-editor fonctionne avec NetworkManager pour créer et éditer les profils de connexions de NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gd">
    <p>'S e seirbheis an t-siostaim a th' ann am Manaidsear lìonraidh gus na ceanglaichean is uidheaman lìonraidh agad a stiùireadh 's a rèiteachadh.</p>
    <p>Obraichidh am prògram nm-connection-editor le Manaidsear lìonraidh gus pròifilean ceanglaidh a chruthachadh 's a dheasachadh airson Manaidsear lìonraidh.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>NetworkManager é un servizo do sistema para xestionar e configurar os dispositivos e conexións de rede.</p>
    <p>O programa nm-connection-editor traballa co NetworkManager para crear e editar os perfís das conexións existentes no NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Mrežni upravitelj je usluga sustava za upravljanje i podešavanje vaših mrežnih povezivanja i uređaja.</p>
    <p>nm-connection-editor program radi s Mrežnim upraviteljem kako bi stvorio i uredio postojeće profile povezivanja Mrežnog upravitelja.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Hálózatkezelő egy rendszerszolgáltatás hálózati kapcsolatok és eszközök kezelésére és beállítására.</p>
    <p>A Hálózati kapcsolatok program használható kapcsolati profilok létrehozására a Hálózatkezelőhöz, és a meglévők kezelésére.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>NetworkManager adalah sebuah layanan sistem untuk mengelola dan menata perangkat dan koneksi jaringan Anda.</p>
    <p>Program nm-connection-editor bekerja dengan NetworkManager untuk membuat dan menyunting profil koneksi yang ada untuk NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>NetworkManager er kerfisþjónusta sem gerir kleift að sýsla með og stilla nettengingar og nettæki.</p>
    <p>Forritið nm-connection-editor virkar með NetworkManager við að búa til ný tengisnið og breyta þeim sem þegar eru fyrir hendi í NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>NetworkManager è un servizio di sistema per gestire e configurare connessioni e dispositivi di rete.</p>
    <p>Il programma nm-connection-editor funziona con NetworkManager per creare e modificare profili di connessioni per NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>NetworkManager は、ネットワーク接続およびデバイスを管理、設定するためのシステムサービスです。</p>
    <p>nm-connection-editor プログラムは、NetworkManager と連携して NetworkManager 用の接続プロファイルを作成し、また既存の接続プロファイルを編集します。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <p>NetworkManager - бұл жүйелік байланыстарды және құрылғыларды басқару және баптауға арналған жүйелік қызмет.</p>
    <p>nm-connection-editor бағдарламасы NetworkManager-мен бірге NetworkManager үшін байланыс профильдерін жасауға және түзетуге жұмыс істейді.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>NetworkManager yra sisteminė tarnyba tinklo ryšių bei įrenginių valdymui bei konfigūravimui.</p>
    <p>nm-connection-editor programa dirba su NetworkManager ryšių profilių kūrimui bei redagavimui.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>NetworkManager ir sistēmas pakalpojums tīkla savienojumu un ierīču pārvaldībai un konfigurēšanai.</p>
    <p>nm-connection-editor strādā ar NetworkManager, lai izveidotu un rediģētu savienojumu profilus NetworkManager programmai.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>NetworkManager et en systemtjeneste som behandler og setter opp systemets nettverkstilkoblinger og enheter.</p>
    <p>Programmet nm-connection-editor virker med NetworkManager for å opprette og redigere eksisterende profiler til NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Netwerkbeheer is een systeemdienst voor het beheren en configureren van uw netwerkverbindingen en apparaten.</p>
    <p>Het programma nm-connection-editor werkt met Netwerkbeheer om bestaande verbindingsprofielen voor Netwerkbeheer aan te maken en te bewerken.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>NetwokrManager es un servici sistèma per gerir e configurar las connexions e periferics ret.</p>
    <p>Lo programa nm-connection-editor fonciona amb NetworkManager per crear e modificar de perfils de connexion existentas per NetwokrManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pa">
    <p>ਨੈੱਟਵਰਕ-ਮੈਨੇਜਰ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਨੈੱਟਵਰਕ ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਅਤੇ ਜੰਤਰ ਦੇ ਪਰਬੰਧ ਅਤੇ ਸੰਰਚਨਾ ਲਈ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੇਵਾ ਹੈ।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>NetworkManager jest usługą systemową do zarządzania i konfigurowania połączeń i urządzeń sieciowych.</p>
    <p>Program nm-connection-editor umożliwia tworzenie i modyfikowanie istniejących profilów połączeń za pomocą usługi NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Gestor de redes é um serviço do sistema para gerir e configurar os seus dispositivos e ligações de rede.</p>
    <p>O programa nm-connection-editor trabalha com o Gestor de redes para criar e editar perfis de ligação existentes.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>NetworkManager é um serviço de sistema para gerenciamento e configuração de seus dispositivos e conexões de rede.</p>
    <p>O programa nm-connection-editor funciona com NetworkManager para criar e editar perfis de conexão existentes para NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Administrator de rețea este un serviciu de sistem pentru gestionarea și configurarea conexiunilor de rețea și dispozitivelor.</p>
    <p>Programul nm-connection-editor funcționează cu Administrator de rețea pentru a creea și edita profile de conexiune pentru Administrator de rețea.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>NetworkManager — системная служба для управления и настройки сетевых подключений и устройств.</p>
    <p>Программа nm-connection-editor работает с NetworkManager для создания и редактирования существующих профилей подключений для NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>NetworkManager je systémová služba na správu a nastavenie vašich sieťových pripojení a zariadení.</p>
    <p>Program nm-connection-editor spolupracuje so správcom siete NetworkManager na vytváranie a úpravu sieťových profilov pre NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Управник мреже је системска услуга за управљање и подешавање мрежних веза и уређаја.</p>
    <p>Програм ум-уређивач-веза ради са Управником мреже да би направио и уредио постојеће профиле везе за Управника мреже.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Upravnik mreže je sistemska usluga za upravljanje i podešavanje mrežnih veza i uređaja.</p>
    <p>Program um-uređivač-veza radi sa Upravnikom mreže da bi napravio i uredio postojeće profile veze za Upravnika mreže.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Nätverkshanteraren är en systemtjänst för att hantera och konfigurera dina nätverksanslutningar och nätverksenheter.</p>
    <p>Programmet nm-connection-editor arbetar med Nätverkshanteraren för att skapa och redigera befintliga profiler för Nätverkshanteraren.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Ağ Yöneticisi; ağ bağlantılarınızı ve aygıtlarınızı yönetmek, yapılandırmak için bir sistem hizmetidir.</p>
    <p>nm-connection-editor programı, Ağ Yöneticisi için bağlantı profilleri oluşturmak ve var olanları düzenlemek için Ağ Yöneticisi ile birlikte çalışır.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>NetworkManager — загальносистемна служба для керування та налаштовування роботи ваших з'єднань із мережею та пристроїв для роботи у мережі.</p>
    <p>Програма nm-connection-editor працює із NetworkManager з метою створення та редагування профілів з'єднань NetworkManager.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>网络管理器（NetworkManager）是一项系统服务，用于管理和配置您的网络连接和设备。</p>
    <p>程序 nm-connection-editor 与网络管理器（NetworkManager）交互来为网络管理器创建和编辑已有的连接配置。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>NetworkManager 是一個用於管理和設定網路連線和裝置的系統服務。</p>
    <p>nm-connection-editor 程式與 NetworkManager 一起使用，以建立和編輯 NetworkManager 的現有連線設定檔。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="772" height="548">https://git.gnome.org/browse/network-manager-applet/plain/nm-connection-editor.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://networkmanager.dev</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/network-manager-applet/issues</url>
  <update_contact>networkmanager-maint@gnome.bugs</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">nm-applet</translation>
  <developer_name>The NetworkManager Developers</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">NetworkManager 開發者</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">网络管理器开发者</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Розробники NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">Ağ Yöneticisi Geliştiricileri</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">Utvecklarna av Nätverkshanteraren</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr@latin">Programeri upravnika mreže</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Програмери управника мреже</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Vývojári správcu siete NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Разработчики NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ro">Dezvoltatorii Administrator de rețea</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">Os desenvolvedores do NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Os programadores do NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Programiści projektu NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pa">ਨੈੱਟਵਰਕ-ਮੈਨੇਜਰ ਡਿਵੈਲਪਰ</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="oc">Los desvolopaires de NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">De Netwerkbeheer-ontwikkelaars</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb">NetworkManagers utviklere</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lv">NetworkManager izstrādātāji</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">NetworkManager kūrėjai</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="kk">NetworkManager жасағандар</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">NetworkManager 開発者</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Gli sviluppatori di NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="is">Þróunarteymi NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Para Pengembang NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">A Hálózatkezelő fejlesztői</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">Razvijatelji mrežnog upravitelja</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">Os desenvolvedores de NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gd">Luchd-leasachaidh na h-aplaid Manaidsear lìonraidh</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Les développeurs de NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">NetworkManager-kehittäjät</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">NetworkManager-en garatzaileak</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Los desarrolladores de NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Die NetworkManager-Entwickler</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="da">Udviklerne af Netværkshåndtering</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Vývojáři aplikace NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">Els desenvolupadors del NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="be">Распрацоўшчыкі NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0" />
  <releases>
    <release date="2019-10-09" version="1.8.24" />
    <release version="1.8.22" date="2019-05-29" />
    <release version="1.8.20" date="2019-02-07" />
    <release version="1.8.18" date="2018-09-07" />
    <release version="1.8.16" date="2018-08-07" />
    <release version="1.8.14" date="2018-06-25" />
    <release date="2018-05-28" version="1.8.12" />
    <release date="2017-12-19" version="1.8.10" />
    <release date="2017-12-18" version="1.8.8" />
    <release version="1.8.6" date="2017-11-07" />
    <release version="1.8.4" date="2017-09-20" />
    <release version="1.8.2" date="2017-06-13" />
    <release version="1.8.0" date="2017-05-10" />
    <release date="2017-03-06" version="1.4.6" />
    <release version="1.4.4" date="2017-01-25" />
    <release version="1.4.2" date="2016-09-30" />
    <release date="2016-08-24" version="1.4.0" />
    <release date="2016-08-03" version="1.2.4" />
    <release version="1.2.2" date="2016-05-11" />
    <release version="1.2.0" date="2016-04-20" />
    <release version="1.0.10" date="2015-12-23" />
    <release date="2015-11-20" version="1.0.8" />
    <release date="2015-08-27" version="1.0.6" />
    <release date="2015-07-14" version="1.0.4" />
    <release date="2015-05-05" version="1.0.2" />
    <release date="2014-12-18" version="1.0.0" />
    <release date="2014-07-03" version="0.9.10" />
    <release version="0.9.8.10" date="2014-04-24" />
    <release version="0.9.8.9" date="2014-04-02" />
    <release version="0.9.8.8" date="2013-11-11" />
    <release date="2013-09-13" version="0.9.8.4" />
    <release version="0.9.8.2" date="2013-06-07" />
    <release version="0.9.8.0" date="2013-02-20" />
    <release date="2012-10-26" version="0.9.6.4" />
    <release version="0.9.6.2" date="2012-08-09" />
    <release version="0.9.6.0" date="2012-08-07" />
    <release date="2012-03-23" version="0.9.4.1" />
    <release date="2012-03-23" version="0.9.4.0" />
    <release date="2011-11-09" version="0.9.2" />
    <release version="0.9.0" date="2011-08-22" />
    <release date="2011-04-20" version="0.8.4" />
    <release version="0.8.2" date="2010-11-03" />
    <release version="0.8.1" date="2010-07-21" />
    <release date="2010-02-18" version="0.8" />
    <release version="0.7.2" date="2009-11-23" />
    <release version="0.7.1" date="2009-04-13" />
    <release date="2008-11-27" version="0.7.0" />
    <release version="0.6.6" date="2008-03-06" />
    <release version="0.6.5" date="2007-04-11" />
  </releases>
</component>