<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <description>
    <p>Whether you're writing in Markdown or managing a complex app codebase, Code is the lightweight but full-featured editor for you. It auto-saves your files to ensure they're always up-to-date, and it remembers your tabs so you never lose your spot—even between sessions.</p>
    <p>Designed around a project-based workflow, Code knows about your separate codebases. It comes with helpful Git integration to create and switch between branches and show changed files and lines within your projects.</p>
    <p>Work with your language: whether you're crafting code in Vala, scripting with PHP, or marking things up in HTML, Code has you covered. Experience full syntax highlighting with nearly all programming, scripting, and markup languages.</p>
    <p>Find anything in your current file, specific folders, or your whole project with options for case-sensitivity and regular expressions.</p>
    <p>Smart features throughout: automatic indentation, smart cut/copy behavior, visible whitespace for selected text and at the end of lines by default, and optional extensions for Markdown actions, spell checking, whitespace trimming, word completion, and more.</p>
    <p>Adapt Code to your workflow: you can tweak the behavior and interface as needed with a handful of useful and well-considered extensions and preferences.</p>
    <p>There's a ton more:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Solarized Light, Solarized Dark, and High Contrast color schemes that affect the whole UI</li>
      <li>Togglable sidebar to fit your workflow</li>
      <li>Smart indentation and .editorconfig support</li>
      <li>Browser-class tabs with drag-and-drop, duplication, undo closing, and tab history</li>
      <li>Display the current line and character—and quickly jump to a new line</li>
      <li>Scroll past the end of the file so you can keep the current line where it's comfortable</li>
      <li>Optional mini-map to make navigating large files easier</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Tant si escriviu a Markdown com si gestioneu una base de codis d’aplicacions complexa, el Code és l’editor lleuger però amb totes les funcions. Desa automàticament els fitxers per assegurar-se que estiguin sempre actualitzats i recorda les pestanyes perquè mai no perdeu el punt, fins i tot entre sessions.</p>
    <p>Dissenyat al voltant d’un flux de treball basat en projectes, el Code coneix les vostres bases de codis separades. Inclou una integració útil amb Git per crear i canviar entre branques i mostrar fitxers i línies canviats als projectes.</p>
    <p>Funciona amb la vostre llenguatge. Tant si elaboreu codi en Vala, feu scripts amb PHP o marqueu coses en HTML, el Codi us té cobert. Experimenteu el realçament complet de sintaxi amb gairebé tota la programació, seqüències d'ordres i llenguatges de marcatge.</p>
    <p>Cerqueu qualsevol cosa al fitxer actual, a carpetes específiques o a tot el projecte amb les opcions per distingir entre majúscules i minúscules i expressions regulars.</p>
    <p>Funcions intel·ligents: sagnat automàtic, comportament de retall / còpia intel·ligent, espai en blanc visible per al text seleccionat i al final de les línies de manera predeterminada, i extensions opcionals per a accions del Markdown, correcció ortogràfica, retall d’espais en blanc, acabament de paraules i molt més.</p>
    <p>Adapteu el Codi al vostre flux de treball: podeu modificar-ne el comportament i la interfície segons sigui necessari amb un grapat d’extensions i preferències útils i ben considerades.</p>
    <p>Hi ha moltes més coses:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Esquemes de colors Solarized Light, Solarized Dark i High Contrast que afecten tota la interfície d’usuari</li>
      <li>Barra lateral commutable per adaptar-se al flux de treball</li>
      <li>Sagnat intel·ligent i suport per a .editorconfig</li>
      <li>Pestanyes de la classe del navegador amb arrossegar i deixar anar, duplicació, desfer el tancament i historial de pestanyes</li>
      <li>Es mostra la línia i el caràcter actuals i se salta ràpidament a una línia nova.</li>
      <li>Desplaceu-vos fins al final del fitxer per mantenir la línia actual on sigui còmode.</li>
      <li>Minimapa opcional per facilitar la navegació per fitxers grans</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ckb">
    <p>تۆ ئەم ئەپە بۆ نووسینێکی سادە بەکار بهێنیت یان پڕۆگرامینگی پڕۆژەیەکی گەورەی پێ بکەیت، ئەوا هیچ کێشەت بۆ دروست نابێت. کۆد ئەپێکی زۆر سادە و سوکەڵەیە بەڵام پڕە لە تایبتەمەندی. خۆکارە پەڕگەکانت پاشەکەوت دەکات ( Auto-save) و تابەکان لە یاد نەکات کە کردبووتنەوە، تەنانەت ئەگەر سێشنیش کۆتایی پێ بهێنیت.</p>
    <p>کۆد، لەسەر بنەمای پڕۆژە دیزاین کراوە. ئەم ئەپە دەزانێت کە دەکرێت تۆ بنکەکۆدی جیاوازت هەبن. یەکێکی تر لە تایبەتمەندییەکانی بریتییە لە گیت بۆ دروستکردنی و هاتووچۆکردن لە نێوان بڕانچەکاندا، هەروەها دێر و پەڕگە دەستکاریکراوەکانت لەناو پڕۆژەکەتدا پشان دەدات.</p>
    <p>بەو زمانە بنووسە کە خۆت دەتەوێت: گرنگ نییە کە تۆ کار بە ڤالا بکەیت، یان خەریکی نووسینی سکریپت بیت بە PHP یان پێشەوەی وێبێک دابڕێژیت بە HTML، کۆد خەمی لێت خواردووە، بەنزیکەیی پاڵپشتی سینتاکسی تەواوی زمانەکانی بەرنامەنووسین، سکریپکردن و مارکەپ کردن دەکات و یەرمەتی هایلایتینگ دەدات.</p>
    <p>بۆ هەر چییەک دەگەڕێت بگەڕێ لەناو پەڕگە کراوەکەی ئێستاتدا، یان لە ناو تەواوی پڕۆژەکەتدا بە بەکارهێنانی بژاردەکانی هەستیارەکەیس (case-sensitivity) و دەستەواژە باوەکان.</p>
    <p>تایبەتمەندیە زیرەکەکان: بۆشایی خۆکاری سەرەتای دێڕ، ڕەفتاری زیرەکی بڕین/لەبەرگرتنەوە، بۆشایی سپی بینراو بۆ دەقی هەڵبژێردراو و لە کۆتایی هێڵەکان بە شێوەی سەرەکی، و پێوەکراوی ئارەزوومەندانە بۆ کردارەکانی مارکداون، هەڵەچنی، کورتکردنەوەی بۆشایی سپی، تەواوکردنی ووشەکان، و زیاتر.</p>
    <p>کۆد بۆ ژینگەی کارەکەت بگونجێنە: دەتوانیت بە ئارەزووی خۆت دەستکاری ڕەفتار و ڕووکاری کۆد بکەیت لە ڕێکخستنەکان و زیادکراوە سوودبەخشەکان.</p>
    <p>یەک تەن تایبەتمەندی تر ماوە:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>ڕووکاری ڕەنگ هەتاوی، و تاریک و سکیمەکانی ڕەنگی کۆنتراست بەرز کە تەواوی دیزاینی ئەپەکە دەگرێتەوە</li>
      <li>سایدباڕێک کە دەتوانیت بیشاریتەوە یان وەکو خۆی بیهێڵییەوە، واتا ڕەوتکراوە</li>
      <li>دانانی بۆشایی سەرەتای دێڕ بە شێوەیەکی زیرەکانە و پاڵپشتی کردنی .editorconfig</li>
      <li>تابەکان لەناو ئەم ئەپەدا، وەکو تابەکانی وێبگەڕ (بڕاوزەر) وایە، دەتوانیت ڕاکێشان بە تابەکان بکەیت یان بە دوویان بکەیت. هەر وەکو وێبگەڕ، دەتوانیت تابێكی داخراو دوبارە بگەڕێنییە یان سەیری مێژووی تابە کراوەکانت بکەیت</li>
      <li>پشاندانی کارێکتەر و دێڕی ئێستا و بەخێرای بازدان بۆ دێڕی تازە</li>
      <li>سکرۆڵکردن لە کۆتایی فایلەکە بۆ ئەوەی بتوانیت هێڵی ئێستا لەو شوێنەی کە ئاسوودەیە بهێڵیتەوە</li>
      <li>نەخشۆچکەیەکی ئارەزوومەندانە بۆ ئاسانکردنی هاتووچۆکردن بەناو فایلە گەورەکان</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Automaticky ukládá soubory, aby byli vždy aktuální. Pamatuji si také otevřené panely, abyste se už nikdy neztratili, ani při přepínání několika sezení. Automaticky ukládá soubory, aby bylo zajištěno, že jsou aktuální a pamatuje si otevřené panely, takže nikdy neztratíte své soustředění – ani mezi relacemi.</p>
    <p>Navrženo kolem projektového způsobu práce, Code ví o oddělených zdrojových kódech. Přichází s nápomocným napojením na Git pro vytváření a přepínání mezi větvemi a zobrazuje změněné soubory a řádky v rámci projektů.</p>
    <p>Umí pracovat s vaším jazykem: ať už vytváříte kód ve Vale, skriptujete v PHP, nebo značkujete pomocí HTML, Code je tu pro vás. Jistě oceníte plné zvýrazňování syntaxe s téměř všemi programovacími, skriptovacími a značkovacími jazyky.</p>
    <p>Najděte cokoli v právě otevřeném souboru, konkrétních složkách nebo v celém projektu pomocí voleb pro (ne)rozlišování mezi malými/VELKÝMI písmeny a regulárních výrazů.</p>
    <p>Přehlídka chytrých funkcí: automatické odsazování, inteligentní chování vyjmutí/zkopírování, ve výchozím stavu viditelné prázdné znaky (whitespace) pro označený text a na konci řádku a volitelná rozšíření pro akce ohledně Markdown, kontrola překlepů, ořezávání prázdných znaků, dokončování slov a další.</p>
    <p>Upravte si Code podle stylu své práce: je možné vyladit chování rozhraní dle potřeby pomocí mnoha užitečných a promyšlených rozšíření a předvoleb.</p>
    <p>A je toho mnohem více:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Schémata barev Solarized Light, Solarized Dark, a Vysoký kontrast, která se týkají celého uživatelského rozhraní</li>
      <li>Volitelný postranní panel, který zapadá do vašeho způsobu práce</li>
      <li>Chytré odsazování a podpora standardu .editorconfig</li>
      <li>Panely jako ve webovém prohlížeči, které je možné přesouvat, duplikovat, brát zpět zavření a také jejich historie</li>
      <li>Zobrazit stávající řádek jako znak – a rychle skočit na nový řádek</li>
      <li>Posunování za konec souboru, takže je možné ponechat stávající řádek tam, kde je to pohodlné</li>
      <li>Volitelná minimapa, která usnadňuje pohyb po větších souborech</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Ob Sie in Markdown schreiben oder eine komplexe Anwednungs-Codebasis managen - Code ist der schlanke und dennoch funktionsreiche Editor für Sie. Er speichert Ihre Dateien ganz automatisch, so dass diese immer auf dem aktuellen Stand sind. Außerdem merkt sich Code, welche Tabs Sie geöffnet hatten, sodass Sie nie den Faden verlieren. Sogar über mehrere Sitzungen hinweg.</p>
    <p>Da er um einen projektbasierten Workflow herum designt ist, weiß Code um Ihre separierten Codebases. Er beinhaltet hilfreiche Git-Integration um Branches zu erstellen und zwischen ihnen zu wechseln. Er zeigt ausserdem geänderte Dateien und Zeilen innerhalb ihrer Projekte an.</p>
    <p>Arbeiten Sie mit der Programmiersprache Ihrer Wahl: Ob Sie in Vala programmieren, PHP-Code schreiben oder Text in HTML verfassen – Code deckt all Ihre Anforderungen ab. Erleben Sie, wie Code in fast allen Programmier-, Skript- und Markup-Sprachen die perfekte Syntax-Hervorhebung beherrscht.</p>
    <p>Finden Sie alles in Ihrer aktuellen Datei, Ordnern oder Ihrem ganzen Projekt mit Optionen für Groß/Kleinschreibung und reguläre Ausdrücke.</p>
    <p>Smarte Funktionen durch und durch: Automatisches Einrücken, smartes Ausschneiden/Kopieren, standardmäßig sichtbare Leerstellen für markierten Text und am Ende von Zeilen und optionale Erweiterungen für Markdown-Aktionen, Rechtschreibprüfung, Leerstellen-Trimmen, Wortkomplettierungen und vieles mehr.</p>
    <p>Passen Sie Code an Ihren Workflow an: Sie können das Verhalten und die Oberfläche mit einer Handvoll nützlichen und speziell designten Erweiterungen ganz nach Ihren Bedürfnissen anpassen.</p>
    <p>Und es gibt noch eine Menge mehr:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Solarized Light, Solarized Dark und High Contrast Farbschemata, die die komplette Oberfläche beeinflussen</li>
      <li>An- und ausschaltbare Seitenleiste um Ihrem Workflow zu entsprechen</li>
      <li>Smartes Einrücken und .editorconfig Unterstützung</li>
      <li>Browserartiges Tabverhalten mit Drag &amp; Drop, Duplizieren, Schließen-rückgängig-Funktion und Tab-Verlaufsfunktion</li>
      <li>Anzeigen der aktuellen Zeile und Zeichen — und schnelles Springen zu einer neuen Zeile</li>
      <li>Über das Ende der Datei hinaus scrollen, um die aktuelle Zeile dort zu sehen, wo es bequem ist</li>
      <li>Optionale Mini-Map um das Navigieren in großen Dateien zu vereinfachen</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Whether you're writing in Markdown or managing a complex app codebase, Code is the lightweight but full-featured editor for you. It auto-saves your files to ensure they're always up-to-date, and it remembers your tabs so you never lose your spot—even between sessions.</p>
    <p>Designed around a project-based workflow, Code knows about your separate codebases. It comes with helpful Git integration to create and switch between branches and show changed files and lines within your projects.</p>
    <p>Work with your language: whether you're crafting code in Vala, scripting with PHP, or marking things up in HTML, Code has you covered. Experience full syntax highlighting with nearly all programming, scripting, and markup languages.</p>
    <p>Find anything in your current file, specific folders, or your whole project with options for case-sensitivity and regular expressions.</p>
    <p>Smart features throughout: automatic indentation, smart cut/copy behavior, visible whitespace for selected text and at the end of lines by default, and optional extensions for Markdown actions, spell checking, whitespace trimming, word completion, and more.</p>
    <p>Adapt Code to your workflow: you can tweak the behaviour and interface as needed with a handful of useful and well-considered extensions and preferences.</p>
    <p>There's a ton more:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Solarised Light, Solarised Dark, and High Contrast colour schemes that affect the whole UI</li>
      <li>Togglable sidebar to fit your workflow</li>
      <li>Smart indentation and .editorconfig support</li>
      <li>Browser-class tabs with drag-and-drop, duplication, undo closing, and tab history</li>
      <li>Display the current line and character—and quickly jump to a new line</li>
      <li>Scroll past the end of the file so you can keep the current line where it's comfortable</li>
      <li>Optional mini-map to make navigating large files easier</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Ya sea que esté escribiendo en Markdown o administrando una código de una aplicación compleja, Code es el editor liviano pero con todas las funciones para usted. Guarda automáticamente sus archivos para asegurarse de que estén siempre actualizados y recuerda sus pestañas para que nunca pierda su trabajo incluso entre sesiones.</p>
    <p>Diseñado en torno a un flujo de trabajo basado en proyectos, Code conoce tus código de forma independiente. Viene con una útil integración de Git para crear y cambiar entre ramas y mostrar archivos y líneas modificados dentro de sus proyectos.</p>
    <p>Trabaje con su lenguaje: ya sea creando código en Vala, creando scripts con PHP o maquetando en HTML, Code lo tiene todo cubierto. Experimenta el resaltado de sintaxis completo con casi todos los lenguajes de programación, secuencias de comandos y marcas.</p>
    <p>Encuentra cualquier cosa en tu archivo actual, carpetas específicas o todo tu proyecto con opciones para la distinción entre mayúsculas y minúsculas y expresiones regulares.</p>
    <p>Funciones inteligentes en todas partes: sangría automática, comportamiento inteligente de cortar/copiar, espacios en blanco visibles para el texto seleccionado y al final de las líneas de forma predeterminada, y extensiones opcionales para acciones de Markdown, revisión ortográfica, recorte de espacios en blanco, finalización de palabras y más.</p>
    <p>Adapte Code a su flujo de trabajo: puede modificar el comportamiento y la interfaz según sea necesario con un puñado de extensiones y preferencias útiles y bien consideradas.</p>
    <p>Hay mucho más:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Esquemas de color Solarized Light, Solarized Dark y Alto Contraste que afectan a toda la interfaz de usuario</li>
      <li>Barra lateral conmutable para adaptarse a tu flujo de trabajo</li>
      <li>Compatibilidad con sangría inteligente y .editorconfig</li>
      <li>Pestañas tipo navegador con función de arrastrar y soltar, duplicar, deshacer cierre e historial de pestañas</li>
      <li>Muestra la línea y el carácter actuales y salta rápidamente a una nueva línea</li>
      <li>Desplácese más allá del final del archivo para que pueda mantener la línea actual donde le resulte más cómodo</li>
      <li>Minimapa opcional para facilitar la navegación en archivos grandes</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Que vous écriviez en Markdown ou que vous gériez le code d'une application complexe, Code est l'éditeur léger mais complet qu'il vous faut. Il enregistre automatiquement vos fichiers pour qu'ils soient toujours à jour et mémorise vos onglets pour que vous ne vous perdiez jamais, même entre deux sessions.</p>
    <p>Conçu pour fonctionner par projet, Code reconnaît vos bases de code distinctes. Il est livré avec une intégration Git utile pour créer et passer d'une branche à l'autre et afficher les fichiers et lignes modifiés dans vos projets.</p>
    <p>Il fonctionne avec votre langage. Que vous élaboriez du code en Vala, des scripts PHP, ou des pages HTML, Code est là pour vous. Profitez d’une coloration syntaxique complète avec presque tous les langages de programmation, des scripts ou de balisage.</p>
    <p>Trouvez n'importe quoi dans votre fichier actuel, dans des dossiers spécifiques ou dans l'ensemble de votre projet grâce aux options de sensibilité à la casse et aux expressions régulières.</p>
    <p>De nombreuses fonctionnalités intelligentes : indentation automatique, comportement intelligent en matière de couper/copier, espaces blancs visibles pour le texte sélectionné et à la fin des lignes par défaut, et extensions disponibles en option pour les actions Markdown, la vérification orthographique, le découpage des espaces blancs, l'auto-complétion, et plus encore.</p>
    <p>Adaptez Code à votre flux de travail : vous pouvez modifier le comportement et l'interface selon vos besoins grâce à une poignée d'extensions et de préférences utiles et bien pensées.</p>
    <p>Et bien plus encore :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Thèmes de couleurs Solarized Light, Solarized Dark et Contraste élevé qui affectent l'ensemble de l'interface utilisateur</li>
      <li>Barre latérale amovible pour s'adapter à votre flux de travail</li>
      <li>Indentation intelligente et prise en charge des fichiers .editorconfig</li>
      <li>Onglets comme dans un navigateur, avec glisser-déposer, duplication, annulation de la fermeture et historique des onglets</li>
      <li>Affichage de la ligne et du caractère courants, et saut rapide à une nouvelle ligne</li>
      <li>Faites défiler le fichier jusqu'à la fin pour garder la ligne en cours là où c'est confortable</li>
      <li>Mini-carte en option pour faciliter la navigation dans les gros fichiers</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>בין אם בכתיבת Markdown או בניהול מאגר קוד מורכב של יישום, קוד הוא עורך קליל אך עשיר ביכולות עבורך. הוא שומר את הקבצים שלך אוטומטית כדי לוודא שהם תמיד עדכניים והוא זוכר את הלשוניות שלך כדי לאפשר חזרה מאיפה שהפסקת, אפילו לאחר הפוגה ממושכת.</p>
    <p>תוכנן סביב תהליכי עבודה מבוססי מיזמים, Code יודע על מאגרי הקוד הנפרדים שלך. בכלי יש יכולות שילוב מול Git כדי ליצור ולהחליף בין ענפים ולהציג קבצים ושורות שהשתנו בתוך המיזמים שלך.</p>
    <p>עובד בשפה שלך: בין אם בחרישת קוד ב־Vala, כתיבת סקריפטים עם PHP או תיוג דברים ב־HTML, קוד מגבה אותך. ניתן להתנסות בהדגשת תחביר מלאה כמעט בכל שפות התכנות, הסקריפטים והתגיות.</p>
    <p>ניתן למצוא כל דבר, בין אם בקובץ הנוכחי, בתיקיות מסוימות או בכל המיזם שלך אם אפשרויות לרגישות רישיות וביטויים רגולריים.</p>
    <p>יכולות חכמות מעל ומעבר: הזחה אוטומטית, התנהות חכמה לגזירה/העתקה, רווח גלוי לטקסט נבחר ובסופי שורות כבררת מחדל והרחבה כרשות לפעולות Markdown, בדיקת איות, קיצוץ רווחים, השלמת מילים ועוד.</p>
    <p>התאמת קוד לתהליך העבודה שלך: אפשר לשפצר את ההתנהגות והמנשקים כראות עיניך עם מגוון הרחבות והעדפות שימושיות וראויות.</p>
    <p>ויש עוד המון:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>זריחה בהירה, זריחה כהה וערכות צבע עם ניגודיות גבוהה שמשפיעות על כל מנשק המשתמש</li>
      <li>לוח צד גמיש שמתאים לאופן העבודה שלך</li>
      <li>הזחה חכמה ותמיכה ב־‎.editorconfig</li>
      <li>לשוניות ברמת דפדפן עם גרירה ושחרור, שכפול, ביטול סגירה והיסטוריית לשוניות</li>
      <li>הצגת השורה והתו הנוכחיים לצד האפשרות לקפוץ לשורה חדשה</li>
      <li>גלילה מעבר לסוף הקובץ כדי לשמור על השורה הנוכחית במקום נוח</li>
      <li>מפה ממוזערת כרשות כדי להקל על הניווט בקבצים גדולים</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>Akár Markdown-fájlokat szerkeszt, akár összetett kódbázist kezel, a Kód a megfelelő szerkesztő az ön számára. Automatikusan menti a fájlokat, hogy mindig aktuálisak legyenek, illetve megjegyzi a megnyitott lapokat — még munkamenetek közt is — így ön mindig tudni fogja, hol tart a munkájában.</p>
    <p>Dolgozzon a kedvenc nyelvén: akár Vala kódolással, PHP szkripteléssel vagy HTML szerkesztéssel foglalkozik, a Kód alkalmas a feladatra. Tapasztalja meg a teljes szintaxiskiemelést szinte minden programozási, szkript- és jelölőnyelven.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>Markdown で文書を作成するときも、複雑なアプリのソースコードを管理するときも、軽量ながら高機能な“コード”はぴったりです。ファイルを自動保存して、常に最新の状態を維持します。また、タブを保存し次回起動時に復元するので、時間が経っても最後に編集した箇所を見失うことはありません。</p>
    <p>“コード”はプロジェクト単位のワークフロー向けにデザインされているので、コードベースごとに認識されるようになっています。便利な Git との統合機能が搭載されており、ブランチを作成したり変更したり、プロジェクト内のファイルや行の差分を表示したりできます。</p>
    <p>あの言語にも、この言語にも、対応。Vala でコーディングしていても、PHP でスクリプティングしていても、HTML でマークアップしていても、“コード”はあなたをサポートします。完璧なシンタックスハイライトが、ほぼすべてのプログラミング言語・スクリプティング言語・マークアップ言語で利用可能です。</p>
    <p>表示中のファイルや特定のフォルダー、プロジェクト全体を対象に自由自在に検索できます。大文字・小文字の区別や正規表現を使った検索も可能です。</p>
    <p>便利な機能がこんなにも。自動インデント、“便利な行の切り取り／コピー”機能、デフォルトで選択中のテキストと行末の空白を表示する機能、オプションで Markdown アクション・スペルチェック・余分な空白の削除・単語補完などの機能も。</p>
    <p>“コード”を自身のワークフローに導入しましょう。厳選された便利な拡張機能と設定を使って、挙動とインターフェースを必要に応じて調整できます。</p>
    <p>そのほかの機能:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>UI 全体に反映される、Solarized Light、Solarized Dark、ハイコントラストカラースキーム</li>
      <li>ワークフローに応じて表示・非表示が可能なサイドバー</li>
      <li>便利なインデント機能と .editorconfig への対応</li>
      <li>ドラッグアンドドロップ、タブの複製、閉じたタブの復元、タブ履歴など、ブラウザー並みの機能を持つタブ</li>
      <li>現在カーソルのある行と列を表示します。そして、別の行に瞬時に移動できます</li>
      <li>ファイルの最終行より先にもスクロールできるので、編集中の行をお好きな位置に表示できます</li>
      <li>行数の多いファイルでも移動が簡単になるミニマップ機能もオプションで用意</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Of je nou in Markdown schrijft of een complexe codebase beheert, Code is een lichtgewicht maar volwaardige editor. Het slaat automatische je bestanden op zodat je altijd up-to-date bent, en het herinnert je tabbladen zodat je nooit je plaats verliest—zelfs tussen sessies in.</p>
    <p>Ontworpen rondom een project gebaseerde workflow, Code is bekkend met je verschillende codebases. Het komt met behulpzame Git-integratie om Git-takken aan te maken, te schakelen tussen takken en om veranderingen in bestanden en individuele lijnen te tonen binnen u projecten.</p>
    <p>Werkt met uw taal: Of u nu in Vala code schrijft, een script maakt in PHP of opmaak bouwt in HTML, Code is er voor u. Benut volledige syntax-markering met bijna alle programmeer-, script-, en markuptalen.</p>
    <p>Vind alles in u huidige bestand, specifieke folders, of u hele project met opties voor hoofdlettergevoeligheid en reguliere uitdrukkingen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Nieważne czy piszesz dokument w Markdownie czy zarządzasz skomplikowanym kodem aplikacji, Kod jest lekkim, lecz w pełni funkcjonalnym edytorem dla Ciebie. Automatycznie zapisuje Twoje pliki by zapewnić, że zawsze są aktualne, oraz zapamiętuje Twoje zakładki, więc nigdy nie tracisz miejsca, w którym skończyłeś – nawet pomiędzy sesjami.</p>
    <p>Zaprojektowany z myślą o pracy z projektami, Kod wie o twoich osobnych repozytoriach kodu. Jest wyposażony w pomocną integrację z Gitem, by tworzyć i zmieniać branch'e oraz pokazywać zmienione pliki i linie kodu w twoich projektach.</p>
    <p>Działa w Twoim języku, niezależnie czy piszesz kod w Vala, skrypt PHP, czy markery w HTML-u, Kod Ci w tym pomoże. Doświadcz pełnego kolorowania składni w prawie wszystkich językach programowania, skryptowych i markupowych.</p>
    <p>Znajdź cokolwiek w aktualnym pliku, konkretnych folderach lub w całym twoim projekcie z opcjami rozróżnienia małych i wielkich liter oraz wyrażeniami regularnymi.</p>
    <p>Inteligentne funkcje wszędzie tam gdzie to możliwe: automatyczne wcięcia, inteligentne zachowanie przy wycinaniu/kopiowaniu, widoczne białe znaki dla zaznaczonego tekstu oraz na końcach linii domyślnie oraz opcjonalne rozszerzenia dla akcji Markdown, sprawdzanie pisowni, przycinanie białych znaków, dokańczanie słów i więcej.</p>
    <p>Przystosuj Kod do twojego stylu pracy: możesz dostosować zachowania oraz interfejs do twoich potrzeb przy użyciu kilku użytecznych oraz przemyślanych wtyczek i ustawień.</p>
    <p>To wciąż nie wszystko:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Motywy słoneczny jasny, słoneczny ciemny oraz wysoki kontrast wpływające na cały interfejs</li>
      <li>Przełączalny panel boczny by pracować tak jak chesz</li>
      <li>Inteligentne wcięcia i wsparcie dla .editorconfig</li>
      <li>Karty w stylu przeglądarek z przeciąganiem, duplikacją, cofnięciem zamknięcia oraz historią kart</li>
      <li>Wyświetl aktualną linię oraz znak oraz szybko przejdź do nowej linii</li>
      <li>Przejdź do końca pliku by przechować aktualną linię tam gdzie jest wygodnie</li>
      <li>Opcjonalna mini-mapa by łatwiej nawigować w dużych plikach</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Пишете ли вы используя Markdown или редактируете код сложного проекта, Код — это лёгкий, но полнофункциональный редактор для Вас. Он автоматически сохраняет ваши файлы, а также запоминает открытые вкладки. Вы никогда не потеряете место, на котором остановились, даже в перерывах между сессиями.</p>
    <p>Разработан для работы с различными проектами, Код знает о ваших отдельных кодовых базах. Он поставляется с интеграцией Git для создания и переключения между ветками, а также для отображения измененных файлов и строк в ваших проектах.</p>
    <p>Работайте со своим языком: создаете ли вы код на Vala, пишите скрипты на PHP или делаете разметку на HTML, Код поможет вам. Вы можете воспользоваться полной подсветкой синтаксиса почти во всех языках программирования, скриптов и разметки.</p>
    <p>Находите всё что угодно в текущем файле, определённых папках, или целом проекте с опцией выбора регистра и регулярных выражений.</p>
    <p>Умные функции: автоматический отступ, умное вырезание/копирование, отображение пробелов выбранного текста и в конце строк по умолчанию, а также дополнительные расширения для работы с Markdown, проверка орфографии, обрезка пробельных символов, завершения слов и многое другое.</p>
    <p>Приспособте Код к своему рабочему процессу: при необходимости можно настроить поведение и интерфейс с помощью нескольких полезных и хорошо продуманных расширений и настроек.</p>
    <p>И еще много чего:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Цветовые схемы Solarized Light, Solarized Dark и High Contrast, которые влияют на весь интерфейс</li>
      <li>Динамичная панель сбоку подходящая вам</li>
      <li>Умный отступ и поддержка .editorconfig</li>
      <li>Вкладки браузерного качества с возможностью перетаскивания в другое окно, дублированием, отменой закрытия и историей вкладок</li>
      <li>Отображает текущую строку и символ — и быстро переходит к новой строке</li>
      <li>Прокрутите файл до конца, чтобы сохранить текущую строку там, где это удобно</li>
      <li>Мини-карта для упрощения навигации по большим файлам</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Či už píšete v Markdown alebo spravujete komplexnú aplikačnú databázu, Kód je nenáročný, ale plne funkčný editor pre vás. Automaticky ukladá vaše súbory, aby boli vždy aktuálne. Pamätá si tiež otvorené karty, aby ste sa nikdy nestratili, dokonca ani pri prepínaní niekoľkých relácií.</p>
    <p>Navrhnutý okolo projektového spôsobu práce, Kód vie o vašich oddelených zdrojových kódoch. Prichádza s nápomocným napojením na Git pre vytváranie a prepínanie medzi vetvami a zobrazovanie zmien v súboroch a riadkoch v rámci vašich projektov.</p>
    <p>Pracujte s vaším jazykom: či už zostrojujete kód vo Vale, skriptujete s PHP alebo pracujete v HTML, Kód je tu pre vás. Určite oceníte úplné zvýrazňovanie syntaxe s takmer všetkými programovacími, skriptovacími a značkovacími jazykmi.</p>
    <p>Nájdite čokoľvek v práve otvorenom súbore, v konkrétnych priečinkoch alebo v celom projekte s možnosťami pre rozlišovanie medzi malými a veľkými písmenami a bežnými výrazmi.</p>
    <p>Inteligentné funkcie skrz na skrz: automatické odsadzovanie, inteligentné správanie vystrihovania/kopírovania, prepínanie viditeľnosti prázdnych znakov pre označený text a na konci riadkov a voliteľné rozšírenia pre Markdown akcie, kontrolu preklepov, orezávanie prázdnych znakov, dokončovanie slov a viac.</p>
    <p>Upravte si Kód podľa štýlu vašej práce: môžete si upraviť správanie a vzhľad rozhrania podľa potreby pomocou množstva užitočných a premyslených rozšírení a predvolieb.</p>
    <p>A je toho omnoho viac:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Schémy farieb Solarizovaná svetlá, Solarizovaná tmavá a Vysoký kontrast, ktoré sa týkajú celého používateľského rozhrania</li>
      <li>Voliteľný bočný panel, ktorý zapadá do vášho spôsobu práce</li>
      <li>Inteligentné odsadzovanie a podpora štandardu .editorconfig</li>
      <li>Karty ako vo webovom prehliadači, ktoré je možné presúvať, duplikovať, znova zobraziť po zatvorení a prezrieť si ich históriu</li>
      <li>Zobrazte si aktuálny riadok a znak – a rýchlo preskočte na nový riadok</li>
      <li>Posúvajte sa až za koniec súboru, takže môžete ponechať aktuálny riadok v takej výške, v akej je to pohodlné</li>
      <li>Voliteľná minimapa, ktorá zjednodušuje pohyb po väčších súboroch</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>İster Markdown formatında yazıyor, ister karmaşık bir uygulama kod tabanını yönetiyor olun, Kod sizin için hafif ama tam özellikli bir düzenleyicidir. Her zaman güncel olduklarından emin olmak için dosyalarınızı otomatik olarak kaydeder ve sekmelerinizi hatırlar, böylece oturumlar arasında bile yerinizi asla kaybetmezsiniz.</p>
    <p>Proje tabanlı bir iş akışı için tasarlanan Kode, ayrı kod tabanlarınızı bilir. Dallar oluşturma, bunlar arasında geçiş yapmak ve projelerinizdeki değişen dosya ve satırları göstermek için yararlı Git entegrasyonuyla birlikte gelir.</p>
    <p>Kendi dilinizle çalışın: ister Vala ile kodluyor olun, ister PHP ile script yazıyor veya HTML dosyası düzenliyor olun, Kod her zaman yanınızda. Tam sözdizimi vurgulaması ile neredeyse bütün programlama dilleri ile uyumun tecrübesini yaşayın.</p>
    <p>Büyük/küçük harf duyarlılığı ve normal ifadeler arama seçenekleriyle mevcut dosyanızda, belirli klasörlerde veya tüm projenizdeki herhangi bir şeyi bulun.</p>
    <p>Baştan sona akıllı özellikler: otomatik girinti, akıllı kesme/kopyalama davranışı, varsayılan olarak seçilen metin için ve satırların sonundaki boşlukları gösterir, isteğe bağlı olarak Markdown eylemleri, yazım denetimi, boşluk düzeltme, sözcük tamamlama ve daha fazlası için uzantılar.</p>
    <p>Kod uygulamasını iş akışınıza uyarlayın: Bir avuç kullanışlı ve iyi düşünülmüş uzantı ve tercihle davranışı ve arayüzü gerektiği gibi değiştirebilirsiniz.</p>
    <p>Bir ton daha özellik var:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Tüm kullanıcı arayüzünü etkileyen Açık Renk Tema, Koyu Renk Tema ve Yüksek karşıtlık renk şemaları</li>
      <li>İş akışınıza uyacak şekilde değiştirilebilir kenar çubuğu</li>
      <li>Akıllı girintili yazma ve .editorconfig desteği</li>
      <li>Sürükle ve bırak, çoğaltma, kapatmayı geri alma ve sekme geçmişine sahip tarayıcı sınıfı sekmeler</li>
      <li>Geçerli satırı ve karakteri görüntüleyin ve hızla yeni bir satıra geçin</li>
      <li>Dosyanın son satırını istediğiniz yere kaydırın, böylece geçerli satırı rahat olduğu yerde tutabilirsiniz</li>
      <li>Büyük dosyalarda gezinmeyi kolaylaştırmak için isteğe bağlı mini harita</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Незалежно від того, чи пишете ви в Markdown або керуєте складною кодовою базою застосунків, Код — це легкий, але повнофункціональний редактор для вас. Він автоматично зберігає ваші файли, щоб вони завжди були актуальними й запам'ятовує ваші вкладки, щоб ви ніколи не втратите місце, на якому зупинилися, навіть в перервах між сеансами.</p>
    <p>Розроблений для роботи з різними проєктами, Код знає про ваші окремі кодові бази. Він поставляється з інтеграцією Git для створення та перемикання між гілками та показу змінених файлів та рядків у ваших проєктах.</p>
    <p>Працюйте зі своєю мовою: чи пишете ви код на Vala, чи скрипти на PHP або робите щось з HTML, Код прикриє вас. Підсвічування синтаксису багатьох мов програмування, скриптів і розмітки.</p>
    <p>Пошук у поточному файлі, конкретних теках або у всьому проєкті будь-чого з параметрами регістрозалежності та регулярних виразів.</p>
    <p>Розумні функції: автовідступ, поведінка розумного копіювання/вирізання, показ пробілів вибраного тексту та в кінці рядків прямо з коробки та додаткові розширення для роботи з Markdown, перевірки правопису, обтинання пробілів, автозавершення слів та багато іншого.</p>
    <p>Пристосуйте код до свого робочого процесу: за необхідності можна налаштувати поведінку та інтерфейс за допомогою кількох корисних та добре продуманих розширень та налаштувань.</p>
    <p>А також:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Solarized світла, Solarized темна, а також висококонтрастна кольорові схеми, які впливають на весь інтерфейс</li>
      <li>Перемикання бічної панелі для зручності роботи</li>
      <li>Розумні автовідступи та підтримка .editorconfig</li>
      <li>Вкладки, як у переглядачі з перетягуванням, дублюванням, скасуванням закриття й історією вкладки</li>
      <li>Знайдіть поточний рядок чи символ і швидко перейдіть до нового рядка</li>
      <li>Прокрутіть у кінець файлу, щоб зберегти поточний рядок там, де зручно</li>
      <li>Опційна міні-карта для полегшення навігації у великих файлах</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>无论您是使用 Markdown 编写还是管理复杂的应用程序代码库，Code 都是适合您的轻量级但功能齐全的编辑器。 它会自动保存您的文件以确保它们始终是最新的，并且它会记住您的选项卡，因此您永远不会丢失您的位置 - 即使在会话之间也是如此。</p>
    <p>围绕基于项目的工作流程设计，Code 了解您单独的代码库。 它带有有用的 Git 集成，可以在分支之间创建和切换，并在项目中显示更改的文件和行。</p>
    <p>海纳百川！无论您是 Vala 老手、PHP 专家还是 HTML 大师，Code 都能满足您的需求。语法高亮功能支持几乎所有编程语言、脚本语言和标记语言。</p>
    <p>使用区分大小写和正则表达式的选项，在当前文件、特定文件夹或整个项目中查找任何内容。</p>
    <p>智能功能贯穿始终：自动缩进、智能剪切/复制行为、默认情况下所选文本和行尾的可见空白，以及 Markdown 操作的可选扩展、拼写检查、空白修剪、单词完成等。</p>
    <p>使 Code 适应您的工作流程：您可以根据需要使用一些有用且经过深思熟虑的扩展和首选项来调整行为和界面。</p>
    <p>更多:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>影响整个 UI 的 Solarized Light、Solarized Dark 和 High Contrast 配色方案</li>
      <li>可切换的侧边栏以适合您的工作流程</li>
      <li>智能缩进和 .editorconfig 支持</li>
      <li>具有拖放、复制、撤消关闭和选项卡历史记录的浏览器类选项卡</li>
      <li>显示当前行和字符——并快速跳转到新行</li>
      <li>滚动到文件的末尾，以便您可以将当前行保持在舒适的位置</li>
      <li>可选的缩略图，使浏览大文件更容易</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>pantheon.elementary-code</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.elementary.code.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" type="cached" height="64">io.elementary.code.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" height="128" type="cached">io.elementary.code.png</icon>
  <id>io.elementary.code</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_group>elementary</project_group>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Code</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">Code</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">代码</name>
  <name lang="uz">Code</name>
  <name lang="uk">Код</name>
  <name lang="tr">Kod</name>
  <name lang="szl">Kod</name>
  <name lang="sv">Kod</name>
  <name lang="sr">Код</name>
  <name lang="sl">Koda</name>
  <name lang="sk">Kód</name>
  <name lang="si">කේතය</name>
  <name lang="ru">Код</name>
  <name lang="ro">Code</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Code</name>
  <name lang="pt">Code</name>
  <name lang="pl">Kod</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਕੋਡ</name>
  <name lang="oc">Còdi</name>
  <name lang="nn">Code</name>
  <name lang="nl">Code</name>
  <name lang="nb">Kode</name>
  <name lang="ms">Code</name>
  <name lang="mr">कोड</name>
  <name lang="lt">Kodas</name>
  <name lang="ko">코드</name>
  <name lang="ja">コード</name>
  <name lang="it">Codice</name>
  <name lang="id">Code</name>
  <name lang="hu">Kód</name>
  <name lang="hi">कोड</name>
  <name lang="he">קוד</name>
  <name lang="gl">Code</name>
  <name lang="fr_CA">Code</name>
  <name lang="fr">Code</name>
  <name lang="fi">Koodi</name>
  <name lang="fa">کد</name>
  <name lang="es">Code</name>
  <name lang="eo">Kodo</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Code</name>
  <name lang="en_CA">Code</name>
  <name lang="en_AU">Code</name>
  <name lang="el">Κώδικας</name>
  <name lang="de">Code</name>
  <name lang="da">Code</name>
  <name lang="cs">Code</name>
  <name lang="ckb">كۆد</name>
  <name lang="ca">Codi</name>
  <name lang="bs">Kod</name>
  <name lang="bo">Code</name>
  <name lang="ar">كود</name>
  <summary>The editor that works for you</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">适合您的编辑器</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Редактор, який працює для вас</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Sizin için çalışan metin editörü</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Editor, ktorý pracuje pre vás</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Редактор, который работает для Вас</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">O editor que funciona para si</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Edytor, który działa dla ciebie</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">De tekstverwerker die het werk voor jou doet</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">便利なエディター</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">A megfelelő szerkesztő ön számára</summary>
  <summary lang="he">עורך הטקסט שעובד בשבילך</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">L'éditeur qui travaille pour vous</summary>
  <summary lang="es">El editor que trabaja para ti</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">The editor that works for you</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Der Editor, der für Sie arbeitet</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Editor, který pracuje pro vás</summary>
  <summary lang="ckb">ئەو دەستکاریکەرەی کە بۆ تۆ کار دەکات</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">L'editor que us funciona</summary>
  <releases>
    <release version="6.2.0" urgency="medium" date="2022-04-01">
      <description>
        <p>Improvements:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">改进：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Удосконалення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">İyileştirmeler:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Vylepšenia:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Улучшения:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ulepszenia:</p>
        <p lang="ja">改善点:</p>
        <p lang="he">שיפורים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Améliorations :</p>
        <p lang="es">Mejoras:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Improvements:</p>
        <p lang="de">Verbesserungen:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Vylepšení:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">پێشکەوتنەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Millores:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>The current document filename is now shown as the window title in multitasking view</li>
          <li lang="uk">Назва поточного файлу документів тепер показуватиметься назвою вікна у багатозадачному огляді</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nazwa pliku aktualnego dokumentu jest teraz pokazywana jako tytuł okna w widoku wielozadaniowym</li>
          <li lang="he">שם הקובץ של המסמך הנוכחי לא מופיע כיוון שכותרת החלון היא בתצוגת ריבוי משימות</li>
          <li lang="fr">Le nom du document courant est désormais affiché comme titre de fenêtre dans la vue multitâche</li>
          <li lang="es">El nombre de archivo del documento actual ahora se muestra como el título de la ventana en la vista multitarea</li>
          <li lang="ckb">لە کاتی مەڵتی تاسکینگدا، ناوی پەڕگەی کراوە وەکو لە تایتڵی پەنجەرەدا دەردەکەوێت</li>
          <li lang="ca">El nom del fitxer del document actual es mostra ara com a títol de la finestra a la vista de multitasca.</li>
          <li>Hidden folders are now shown in the project sidebar</li>
          <li lang="uk">Сховані теки відтепер показуються на бічній панелі проєкту</li>
          <li lang="pl">Ukryte folder są teraz pokazywane w panelu bocznym projektu</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקיות מוסתרות מופיעות בסרגל הצד של המיזם</li>
          <li lang="fr">Les dossiers cachés sont désormais affichés dans la barre latérale du projet</li>
          <li lang="es">Las carpetas ocultas ahora se muestran en la barra lateral del proyecto</li>
          <li lang="ckb">بوخچە شاراوەکان لە سایدباڕی پڕۆژەکدا دەردەکەون</li>
          <li lang="ca">Les carpetes ocultes ara es mostren a la barra lateral del projecte.</li>
          <li>The currently selected result and the number of results is displayed while searching</li>
          <li lang="uk">Під час пошуку показується поточний вибраний результат і кількість результатів</li>
          <li lang="pl">Aktualnie zaznaczony wynik i liczba wyników jest teraz pokazywane podczas wyszukiwania</li>
          <li lang="he">התוצאה הנבחרת ומספר התוצאות מופיעים בזמן החיפוש</li>
          <li lang="fr">Le résultat sélectionné et le nombre de résultats est affiché lors de la recherche</li>
          <li lang="es">El resultado seleccionado actualmente y el número de resultados se muestran durante la búsqueda</li>
          <li lang="ckb">ئەنجامە دیاریکراوەکانی ئێستا و ژمارەی ئەنجامەکان پیشان دەدرێن لەکاتی گەڕان</li>
          <li lang="ca">Durant la cerca es mostren el resultat seleccionat actualment i el nombre de resultats.</li>
          <li>The search bar now has a regular expression mode</li>
          <li lang="uk">Панель пошуку тепер має режим регулярних виразів</li>
          <li lang="pl">Pasek wyszukiwania posiada teraz tryb wyrażeń regularnych</li>
          <li lang="he">לסרגל החיפוש יש מעכשיו מצב ביטויים רגולריים</li>
          <li lang="fr">La barre de recherche possède désormais un mode expression régulière</li>
          <li lang="es">La barra de búsqueda ahora tiene un modo de expresión regular</li>
          <li lang="ckb">شریتی گەڕان ئێستا دۆخی دەربڕینی ئاسایی هەیە</li>
          <li lang="ca">La barra de cerca ara té un mode d'expressió regular.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Fixes:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">修复：</p>
        <p lang="uz">To'g'rilashlar:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Виправлення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Düzeltmeler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Поправке:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Opravy:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Исправления:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Correções:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Correções:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Poprawki:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Opgelost:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Fikser:</p>
        <p lang="mr">निराकारणे:</p>
        <p lang="ja">修正点:</p>
        <p lang="it">Correzioni:</p>
        <p lang="hu">Javítások:</p>
        <p lang="he">תיקונים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Corrections :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Korjaukset:</p>
        <p lang="es">Correcciones:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Fixes:</p>
        <p lang="de">Fehlerbehebungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Rettelser:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Opravuje:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">چاککردنەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Correccions:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>It is now possible to change Git branch with untracked files present in a project</li>
          <li lang="uk">Тепер можна змінити гілку Git з не відстежуваними файлами, присутніми в проєкті</li>
          <li lang="pl">Możliwe stała się zmiana gałęzi Git z nieśledzonymi plikami obecnymi w projekcie</li>
          <li lang="he">מעתה ניתן לשנות את ענף ה־Git כשיש קבצים שאינם במעקב במיזם</li>
          <li lang="fr">Il est désormais possible de changer de branche Git lorsque des fichiers non suivi sont présent dans un projet</li>
          <li lang="es">Ahora es posible cambiar la rama de Git con archivos sin seguimiento presentes en un proyecto</li>
          <li lang="ckb">ئێستا دەتوانرێ برانچی گیت بگۆڕیت لەگەڵ فایلە نەدۆزراوەکان کە لە پرۆژەکەدا هەیە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Ara és possible canviar la branca de Git amb fitxers sense seguiment presents en un projecte.</li>
          <li>Crashes are prevented while searching in large projects</li>
          <li lang="uk">Усунуто збої під час пошуку у великих проєктах</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zapobiegnięto błędom krytycznym podczas szukania w dużych projektach</li>
          <li lang="he">נמנעה קריסה כשמחפשים במיזמים גדולים</li>
          <li lang="fr">Prévention des risques de plantage lors de la recherche dans des projets conséquents</li>
          <li lang="es">Se evitan bloqueos durante la búsqueda en proyectos grandes</li>
          <li lang="ckb">ڕێگری لە تێکچوونی کۆد کراوە لەکاتی گەڕان لە پڕۆژە گەورەکاندا</li>
          <li lang="ca">Les fallades s'eviten durant la cerca en projectes grossos.</li>
          <li>The correct document is now focused after opening Code from an external program</li>
          <li lang="uk">Тепер фокусування відбувається на правильному документі після відкриття коду із зовнішнього застосунку</li>
          <li lang="pl">Poprawny dokument jest teraz sfokusowany po otwarciu Kodu przez zewnętrzny program</li>
          <li lang="he">המסמך הנכון ממוקד מעתה לאחר פתיחת קוד מתוכנית חיצונית</li>
          <li lang="fr">Le bon document est désormais sélectionné après l'ouverture de Code depuis un autre programme</li>
          <li lang="es">El documento correcto ahora se enfoca después de abrir Code desde un programa externo</li>
          <li lang="ckb">دۆکیومێنتە دروستەکە ئێستا سەرنجدراوە دوای کردنەوەی کۆد لە بەرنامەیەکی دەرەکی</li>
          <li lang="ca">Ara es focalitza el document correcte després d'obrir el Codi des d'un programa extern.</li>
          <li>Line duplication is now actioned correctly if there is no selection present</li>
          <li lang="uk">Дублювання рядка тепер працює правильно, якщо нічого не вибрано</li>
          <li lang="pl">Duplikowanie linii jest teraz obsługiwane poprawnie gdy nic nie jest zaznaczone</li>
          <li lang="he">שכפול שורות מטופל כראוי אם אין בחירה</li>
          <li lang="fr">La duplication des lignes est maintenant effectuée correctement si aucune sélection n'est présente</li>
          <li lang="ckb">بە دووکردنی دێڕ ئێستا بە دروستی کارپێکراوە ئەگەر هیچ دیاریکردنێک بوونی نەبێت</li>
          <li lang="ca">La duplicació de línies ara actua correctament si no hi ha cap selecció.</li>
          <li>Code no longer crashes when asked to open an unknown URI format</li>
          <li lang="uk">Усунуто збої Коду під час запиту відкриття URI невідомого формату</li>
          <li lang="pl">Otwieranie nieznanych formatów URI w Kodzie nie powoduje już błędu krytycznego</li>
          <li lang="he">קוד לא קורס יותר כשמתקבלת בקשה לפתוח תצורת כתובת לא מוכרת</li>
          <li lang="fr">Code ne plante plus lorsqu'il est demandé d'ouvrir un format d'URI inconnu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">ئەپەکە لەکار ناکەوێت ئەگەر داوای لێ بکرێت فۆڕماتێکی نەزانرای URI بکاتەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">El Codi ja no es bloqueja quan se li demana que obri un format d'URI desconegut.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Minor updates:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">小幅更新：</p>
        <p lang="uz">Kichik yangilanishlar:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Незначні оновлення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Küçük güncellemeler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Мања освежења:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Menšie aktualizácie:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Незначительные обновления:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Pequenas atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Pequenas atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Mniejsze aktualizacje:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Kleine updates:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Små oppdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="mr">किरकोळ अद्यतने:</p>
        <p lang="ja">軽微なアップデート:</p>
        <p lang="it">Aggiornamenti minori:</p>
        <p lang="he">עדכונים משניים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Mises à jour mineures :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Pienet päivitykset:</p>
        <p lang="es">Actualizaciones menores:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Minor updates:</p>
        <p lang="de">Weitere Aktualisierungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Mindre opdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Drobné aktualizace:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">وردە نوێکارییەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Actualitzacions menors:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">翻译更新</li>
          <li lang="uz">Yangilangan tarjimalar</li>
          <li lang="uk">Оновлено переклади</li>
          <li lang="tr">Çeviriler güncellendi</li>
          <li lang="sr">Освежени преводи</li>
          <li lang="sl">Posodobljeni prevodi</li>
          <li lang="sk">Aktualizované preklady</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обновлены переводы</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zaktualizowano tłumaczenia</li>
          <li lang="nl">Bijgewerkte vertalingen</li>
          <li lang="nb">Oppdaterte oversettelser</li>
          <li lang="mr">अद्ययावत अनुवाद</li>
          <li lang="lt">Atnaujinti vertimai</li>
          <li lang="ko">번역 업데이트</li>
          <li lang="ja">翻訳の更新</li>
          <li lang="it">Traduzioni aggiornate</li>
          <li lang="he">עדכוני תרגומים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Traducións actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="fr">Mise à jour des traductions</li>
          <li lang="fi">Päivitetyt käännökset</li>
          <li lang="es">Traducciones actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝisdatigitaj tradukoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="de">Aktualisierte Übersetzungen</li>
          <li lang="da">Opdaterede oversættelser</li>
          <li lang="cs">Aktualizovány překlady</li>
          <li lang="ckb">وەرگێڕانەکان نوێکراونەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Traduccions actualitzades</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-11-23" urgency="medium" version="6.1.0">
      <description>
        <p>Improvements:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">改进：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Удосконалення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">İyileştirmeler:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Vylepšenia:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Улучшения:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ulepszenia:</p>
        <p lang="ja">改善点:</p>
        <p lang="he">שיפורים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Améliorations :</p>
        <p lang="es">Mejoras:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Improvements:</p>
        <p lang="de">Verbesserungen:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Vylepšení:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">پێشکەوتنەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Millores:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Projects with the same name now include their parent folder name as well</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">具有相同名称的项目现在也包括其父文件夹名称</li>
          <li lang="uk">Проєкти з однаковою назвою тепер містять і назву батьківської теки</li>
          <li lang="sk">Projekty s rovnakým názvom odteraz zahŕňajú aj názov svojho nadradeného priečinku</li>
          <li lang="ru">Проекты с одинаковыми именами теперь включают названия своих родительских папок</li>
          <li lang="pl">Projekty o tej samej nazwie zawierają teraz również nazwę swojego folderu nadrzędnego</li>
          <li lang="ja">プロジェクト名が同じ場合は親フォルダーの名前も表示するように修正</li>
          <li lang="he">מיזמים עם אותו השם מעתה כוללים את שם תיקיית ההורה בנוסף</li>
          <li lang="fr">Les projets de même nom incluent désormais également le nom du dossier parent</li>
          <li lang="es">Los proyectos con el mismo nombre ahora también incluyen el nombre de su carpeta principal</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Projects with the same name now include their parent folder name as well</li>
          <li lang="cs">Projekty, které jsou nazvané stejně, jsou nyní rozlišovány pomocí své nadřazené složky</li>
          <li lang="ckb">ئێستا ئەو پڕۆژانەی کە هەمان ناویان هەیە، ناوی باوانیشیان پشان دەدرێت</li>
          <li lang="ca">Els projectes amb el mateix nom ara també inclouen el nom de la carpeta principal.</li>
          <li>When scrolling to search results, overshoot slightly for better visibility</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">滚动到搜索结果时，稍微过冲以获得更好的可见性</li>
          <li lang="uk">Під час прокрутки результатів пошуку, вони трохи перевищують зону видимості для кращого перегляду</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zlepšená viditeľnosť pri posúvaní k výsledkom vyhľadávania</li>
          <li lang="ru">При прокрутке результатов поиска, они немного превышают зону видимости для лучшего просмотра</li>
          <li lang="pl">Przy przewijaniu do wyników wyszukiwania, przewijane jest nieco dalej dla lepszej widoczności</li>
          <li lang="ja">検索結果にスクロールする際に、見やすくなるように余分にスクロールするように変更</li>
          <li lang="he">בעת גלילת לתוצאות החיפוש, יש לגלוש קצת מעבר לשיפור המראה</li>
          <li lang="fr">Lors du défilement des résultats de recherche, ajout d'un léger débordement pour une meilleure visibilité</li>
          <li lang="es">Cuando te desplazas en los resultados de búsqueda, se resalta ligeramente para una mejor visibilidad</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">When scrolling to search results, overshoot slightly for better visibility</li>
          <li lang="cs">Při posouvání k výsledkům hledání, je zlepšena jejich viditelnost</li>
          <li lang="ckb">کاتێك سكڕۆڵ دەکەیت بۆ ئەنجامەکانی گەڕان، کەمێك زیاتر بڕۆ خوارەوە بۆ بینینێکی باشتر</li>
          <li lang="ca">Quan us desplaceu als resultats de la cerca, aneu una mica més enllà per obtenir una millor visibilitat.</li>
          <li>Use the FileChooser portal instead of the one from GTK</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">使用 FileChooser 门户而不是来自 GTK</li>
          <li lang="uk">Використовується портал FileChooser, а не з GTK</li>
          <li lang="sk">Použiť portál FileChooser namiesto toho z GTK</li>
          <li lang="ru">Используется портал FileChooser, а не GTK</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zmieniono wybieranie plików by korzystało z portalu FileChooser zamiast z GTK</li>
          <li lang="ja">GTK が提供するファイル選択ダイアログではなく、ファイル選択ポータルを使用するように修正</li>
          <li lang="he">נעשה שימוש בשער FileChooser במקום בזה שמגיע מ־GTK</li>
          <li lang="fr">Utilisation du portail pour le sélecteur de fichiers à la place de celui fourni par GTK</li>
          <li lang="es">Utilice el portal FileChooser en lugar del de GTK</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Use the FileChooser portal instead of the one from GTK</li>
          <li lang="cs">Použit portál FileChooser namísto toho z GTK</li>
          <li lang="ckb">بەکارهێنانی دەرچەی FileChooser لە جێگەی دانەکەی GTK</li>
          <li lang="ca">Ús del portal FileChooser en comptes del de GTK</li>
          <li>Center the global search dialog over the main Code window</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">将全局搜索对话框在主代码窗口居中显示</li>
          <li lang="uk">Центрування діалогового вікна глобального пошуку над основним вікном Коду</li>
          <li lang="sk">Dialóg globálneho vyhľadávania je teraz zarovnaný na stred hlavného okna Kódu</li>
          <li lang="ru">Центр диалогового окна глобального поиска над основным окном Кода</li>
          <li lang="pl">Okno dialogowe globalnego wyszukiwania jest teraz wyśrodkowane nad głównym oknem aplikacji</li>
          <li lang="ja">プロジェクト全体の検索ダイアログを“コード”の主ウィンドウに対して中央に表示するように修正</li>
          <li lang="he">חלונית החיפוש הגלובלית ממורכזת על פני חלון הראשי של קוד</li>
          <li lang="fr">La boîte de dialogue de recherche gobale est désormais centrée par dessus la fenêtre de Code</li>
          <li lang="es">Centra el cuadro de dialogo de búsqueda global sobre la ventana principal de Code</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Center the global search dialog over the main Code window</li>
          <li lang="cs">Vystředěn dialog globálního vyhledávání nad hlavním oknem s Code</li>
          <li lang="ckb">دایەلۆگی گەڕانی گشتی خراوەتە ناوەڕاست، بەسەر پەنجەرەی سەرەکی کۆددا</li>
          <li lang="ca">Centrat el diàleg de cerca global a la finestra principal del Codi</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Fixes:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">修复：</p>
        <p lang="uz">To'g'rilashlar:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Виправлення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Düzeltmeler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Поправке:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Opravy:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Исправления:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Correções:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Correções:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Poprawki:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Opgelost:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Fikser:</p>
        <p lang="mr">निराकारणे:</p>
        <p lang="ja">修正点:</p>
        <p lang="it">Correzioni:</p>
        <p lang="hu">Javítások:</p>
        <p lang="he">תיקונים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Corrections :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Korjaukset:</p>
        <p lang="es">Correcciones:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Fixes:</p>
        <p lang="de">Fehlerbehebungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Rettelser:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Opravuje:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">چاککردنەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Correccions:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix visibility of Terminal button on Welcome page</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">修复欢迎页面上终端按钮的可见性</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено видимість кнопки терміналу на сторінці привітання</li>
          <li lang="sk">Opravená viditeľnosť tlačidla Terminálu na uvítacej stránke</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлена видимость кнопки терминала на странице приветствия</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawiono widoczność przycisku Terminala na stronie powitalnej</li>
          <li lang="ja">ようこそ画面の“ターミナル”ボタンが消える不具合を修正</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון מראה כפתור המסוף בעמוד קבלת הפנים</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction de la visibilité du bouton Terminal sur la page d'accueil</li>
          <li lang="es">Corrección de la visibilidad del botón Terminal en la página de bienvenida</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix visibility of Terminal button on Welcome page</li>
          <li lang="de">Sichtbarkeit des Terminal-Buttons auf der Willkommensseite sicherstellen</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opravena viditelnost tlačítka terminálu na uvítací stránce</li>
          <li lang="ckb">چارەسەرکردنی دەرکەوتنی دوگمەی تێرمیناڵ لە پەنجەرەی بەخێرهاتندا</li>
          <li lang="ca">Correcció de la visibilitat del botó del terminal a la pàgina de benvinguda</li>
          <li>Fix some keyboard shortcuts affecting unfocused Document instead of focused Terminal</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">修复一些键盘快捷键影响未聚焦的文档而不是聚焦的终端</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено деякі комбінації клавіш, що впливають на нефокусований документ, а не на термінал у фокусі</li>
          <li lang="sk">Opravené niektoré klávesové skratky týkajúce sa nezameraného dokumentu namiesto zameraného Terminálu</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлено задействование некоторых клавиш на документе при фокусе на терминале</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawiono niektóre skróty klawiszowe działające na niezfokusowanych dokumentach zamiast zfokusowanym terminalu</li>
          <li lang="ja">キーボードショートカットがフォーカス状態のターミナルではなく、フォーカスされていないテキストビューに適用される不具合を修正</li>
          <li lang="he">תוקנו קיצורי מקלדת שמשפיעים על מסמך שאינו במיקוד במקום מסוף שעליו המיקוד</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction de certains raccourcis clavier affectant le Document non focalisé au lieu du Terminal focalisé</li>
          <li lang="es">Corregidos algunos atajos de teclado que afectan al Documento desenfocado en lugar de la Terminal enfocada</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix some keyboard shortcuts affecting unfocused Document instead of focused Terminal</li>
          <li lang="de">Behebt einen Fehler, bei dem einige Tastenkürzel ihren Effekt auf ein nicht ausgewähltes Dokument statt des gewählten hatten</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opraveny některé klávesové zkratky týkající se nezaměřeného dokumentu namísto zaměřeného terminálu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">چاککردنی هەندێک کورتەڕێی تەختەکلیل کە کاردەکاتە سەر ئەو دۆکیومێنتەی کە سەرنجی نەخراوەتەوە سەر بەجێگەی تێرمیناڵی سەرنج دراو</li>
          <li lang="ca">Correcció d'algunes dreceres de teclat que afecten el document desenfocat en lloc del terminal enfocat</li>
          <li>Close Terminal if shell exited and create new Terminal if re-opened with no shell</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">如果 shell 退出，请关闭终端，如果在没有 shell 的情况下重新打开，则创建新终端</li>
          <li lang="uk">Термінал закривається, якщо виконано вихід з оболонки, і створюються новий термінал, якщо виконано повторне відкриття без оболонки</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zatvoriť Terminál po skončení aktivity shellu a otvoriť nový Terminál ak bol znovu otvorený bez shellu</li>
          <li lang="ru">Терминал закрывается, если выполнен выход из оболочки, и создаётся новый терминал, если было повторное открытие без оболочки</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zamknij terminal gdy shell zostanie zamknięty i otwórz terminal gdy otwarty bez shella</li>
          <li lang="ja">シェルが終了した場合はターミナルを閉じ、シェルなしでターミナルが開かれた場合は新しいターミナルを作成するように修正</li>
          <li lang="he">לסגור את המסוף אם המעטפת נסגרת וליצור מסוף חדש אם נפתח מחדש ללא מעטפת</li>
          <li lang="fr">Fermeture du Terminal si le shell est fermé et création d'un nouveau Terminal si réouvert sans le shell</li>
          <li lang="es">Cierre la Terminal si se salió del shell y cree una nueva Terminal si se vuelve a abrir sin shell</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Close Terminal if shell exited and create new Terminal if re-opened with no shell</li>
          <li lang="cs">Pokud shell skončil, terminál je zavřen a při opětovném otevření také znovu otevřen</li>
          <li lang="ckb">داخستنی تێرمیناڵ ئەگەر شێڵ بوونی هەبوو و دروستکردنی تێرمیناڵێکی نوێ ئەگەر دوبارە بەبێ شێڵ کرایەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Tanqueu el terminal si s'ha sortit de l'intèrpret d'ordres i creeu-ne un de nou si es torna a obrir sense.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Minor updates:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">小幅更新：</p>
        <p lang="uz">Kichik yangilanishlar:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Незначні оновлення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Küçük güncellemeler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Мања освежења:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Menšie aktualizácie:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Незначительные обновления:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Pequenas atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Pequenas atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Mniejsze aktualizacje:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Kleine updates:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Små oppdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="mr">किरकोळ अद्यतने:</p>
        <p lang="ja">軽微なアップデート:</p>
        <p lang="it">Aggiornamenti minori:</p>
        <p lang="he">עדכונים משניים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Mises à jour mineures :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Pienet päivitykset:</p>
        <p lang="es">Actualizaciones menores:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Minor updates:</p>
        <p lang="de">Weitere Aktualisierungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Mindre opdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Drobné aktualizace:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">وردە نوێکارییەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Actualitzacions menors:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>"Visible whitespace" combobox is now a switch</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">“可见空白”组合框现在是一个开关</li>
          <li lang="uk">Поле «Видимі пробіли» стало перемикачем</li>
          <li lang="sk">Kombinovaná ponuka „Viditeľné prázdne znaky“ je teraz prepínač</li>
          <li lang="ru">Выпадающий список «Видимые пробелы» стал переключателем</li>
          <li lang="pl">Znacznik „Widoczne białe znaki” jest teraz przełącznikiem</li>
          <li lang="ja">“空白を表示”コンボボックスをスイッチに変更</li>
          <li lang="he">תיבת הבחירה „רווח גלוי” היא מעתה מתג</li>
          <li lang="fr">« Espaces blancs visibles » est désormais un bouton d'activation/désactivation</li>
          <li lang="es">El cuadro combinado "Espacio en blanco visible" ahora es un interruptor</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">"Visible whitespace" combobox is now a switch</li>
          <li lang="cs">Kombinovaná nabídka „Viditelné prázdné znaky“ je nyní přepínač</li>
          <li lang="ckb">کۆمبۆبۆکسی "بۆشایی سپی دیار" ئێستا بووە بە سویچ</li>
          <li lang="ca">El quadre combinat "Espai en blanc visible" ara és un interruptor.</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">翻译更新</li>
          <li lang="uz">Yangilangan tarjimalar</li>
          <li lang="uk">Оновлено переклади</li>
          <li lang="tr">Çeviriler güncellendi</li>
          <li lang="sr">Освежени преводи</li>
          <li lang="sl">Posodobljeni prevodi</li>
          <li lang="sk">Aktualizované preklady</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обновлены переводы</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zaktualizowano tłumaczenia</li>
          <li lang="nl">Bijgewerkte vertalingen</li>
          <li lang="nb">Oppdaterte oversettelser</li>
          <li lang="mr">अद्ययावत अनुवाद</li>
          <li lang="lt">Atnaujinti vertimai</li>
          <li lang="ko">번역 업데이트</li>
          <li lang="ja">翻訳の更新</li>
          <li lang="it">Traduzioni aggiornate</li>
          <li lang="he">עדכוני תרגומים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Traducións actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="fr">Mise à jour des traductions</li>
          <li lang="fi">Päivitetyt käännökset</li>
          <li lang="es">Traducciones actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝisdatigitaj tradukoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="de">Aktualisierte Übersetzungen</li>
          <li lang="da">Opdaterede oversættelser</li>
          <li lang="cs">Aktualizovány překlady</li>
          <li lang="ckb">وەرگێڕانەکان نوێکراونەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Traduccions actualitzades</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="6.0.1" urgency="medium" date="2021-08-28">
      <description>
        <p>Fixes:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">修复：</p>
        <p lang="uz">To'g'rilashlar:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Виправлення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Düzeltmeler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Поправке:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Opravy:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Исправления:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Correções:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Correções:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Poprawki:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Opgelost:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Fikser:</p>
        <p lang="mr">निराकारणे:</p>
        <p lang="ja">修正点:</p>
        <p lang="it">Correzioni:</p>
        <p lang="hu">Javítások:</p>
        <p lang="he">תיקונים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Corrections :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Korjaukset:</p>
        <p lang="es">Correcciones:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Fixes:</p>
        <p lang="de">Fehlerbehebungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Rettelser:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Opravuje:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">چاککردنەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Correccions:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix crash when creating new window from tab drop</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">修复从选项卡下拉创建新窗口时崩溃</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено збій під час створення нового вікна зі спадного меню вкладок</li>
          <li lang="tr">Sekme düşüşünden yeni pencere oluştururken kilitlenme düzeltildi</li>
          <li lang="sk">Opravený pád pri vytváraní nového okna z rozbaľovacej ponuky karty</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлен сбой при создании нового окна из выпадающего меню вкладкок</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawiono błąd przy otwieraniu nowego okna przez upuszczenie karty</li>
          <li lang="ja">タブをドロップして新しいウィンドウを開こうとするとクラッシュする不具合を修正</li>
          <li lang="he">תוקנה קריסה בעת יצירת חלון חדש מתפריט לשונית</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction d'un plantage lors de la création d'une nouvelle fenêtre au moment de la suppression d'un onglet</li>
          <li lang="es">Se corrigió el error al crear una nueva ventana desde la pestaña desplegable</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix crash when creating new window from tab drop</li>
          <li lang="de">Behebt einen Fehler beim Öffnen neuer Fenster durch das Ablegen eines Tabs</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opraven pád při vytváření nového okna z rozbalovací nabídky karty</li>
          <li lang="ckb">چارەسەرکردنی تێکچوون کاتێک پەنجەرەیەکی نوێ لە تاب درۆپەوە دەکەیەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Correcció del bloqueig en crear una finestra nova des de la pestanya</li>
          <li>Ensure files created from the sidebar are automatically opened</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">确保从侧边栏创建的文件自动打开</li>
          <li lang="uk">Тепер створені з бічної панелі файли відкриваються автоматично</li>
          <li lang="tr">Kenar çubuğundan oluşturulan dosyaların otomatik olarak açıldığından emin olundu</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zaistené, že súbory vytvorené z bočného panelu sa automaticky otvoria</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлено автоматическое открытие создаваемых файлов в панели сбоку</li>
          <li lang="pl">Upewniono się, że pliki utworzone przez panel boczny są automatycznie otwierane</li>
          <li lang="ja">サイドバーで作成したファイルを自動的に開くように修正</li>
          <li lang="he">וידוא שקבצים שנוצרו מחלונית הצד נפתחים אוטומטית</li>
          <li lang="fr">Nous nous sommes assurés que les fichiers créés depuis la barre latérale soient automatiquement ouverts</li>
          <li lang="es">Asegúrese de que los archivos creados desde la barra lateral se abran automáticamente</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Ensure files created from the sidebar are automatically opened</li>
          <li lang="de">Sicherstellen, dass über die Seitenleiste erstellte Dateien automatisch geöffnet werden</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zajištěno že soubory vytvořené z postranního panelu jsou automaticky otevřeny</li>
          <li lang="ckb">دڵنیابوونەوە لە بوونەوەی خۆکارانەی ئەو پەڕگانەی کە لە سایدباڕدا دروست دەکرێن</li>
          <li lang="ca">S'assegura que els fitxers creats des de la barra lateral s’obrin automàticament.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Improvements:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">改进：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Удосконалення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">İyileştirmeler:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Vylepšenia:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Улучшения:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ulepszenia:</p>
        <p lang="ja">改善点:</p>
        <p lang="he">שיפורים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Améliorations :</p>
        <p lang="es">Mejoras:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Improvements:</p>
        <p lang="de">Verbesserungen:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Vylepšení:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">پێشکەوتنەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Millores:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Hide project chooser button when hiding sidebar</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">隐藏侧边栏时不显示项目选择器按钮</li>
          <li lang="uk">Меню вибору проєктів ховається разом з бічною панеллю</li>
          <li lang="tr">Kenar çubuğunu gizlerken proje seçici düğmesini gizle</li>
          <li lang="sk">Skryť tlačidlo výberu projektu pri skrytí bočného panelu</li>
          <li lang="ru">Меню выбора проектов скрывается вместе с боковой панелью</li>
          <li lang="pl">Schowano przycisk wyboru projektu przy chowaniu panelu bocznego</li>
          <li lang="ja">サイドバーを表示していない場合はプロジェクト選択ボタンも表示しないように修正</li>
          <li lang="he">הסתרת כפתור בוחר המיזמים בעת הסתרת סרגל הצד</li>
          <li lang="fr">Le bouton de sélection de projet est désormais masqué lorsque la barre latérale est masquée</li>
          <li lang="es">Ocultar el botón del selector de proyectos al ocultar la barra lateral</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Hide project chooser button when hiding sidebar</li>
          <li lang="de">Projekt-Wahlbutton verstecken, wenn die Seitenleiste versteckt wird</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidáno tlačítko skrytí voliče projektu při skrytí postranního panelu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">شاردنەوەی دوگمەی هەڵبژێرەری پڕۆژە کاتێک سایدباڕ دەشارییەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Amaga el botó de selecció de projectes quan s'amaga la barra lateral.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Minor updates:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">小幅更新：</p>
        <p lang="uz">Kichik yangilanishlar:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Незначні оновлення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Küçük güncellemeler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Мања освежења:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Menšie aktualizácie:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Незначительные обновления:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Pequenas atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Pequenas atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Mniejsze aktualizacje:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Kleine updates:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Små oppdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="mr">किरकोळ अद्यतने:</p>
        <p lang="ja">軽微なアップデート:</p>
        <p lang="it">Aggiornamenti minori:</p>
        <p lang="he">עדכונים משניים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Mises à jour mineures :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Pienet päivitykset:</p>
        <p lang="es">Actualizaciones menores:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Minor updates:</p>
        <p lang="de">Weitere Aktualisierungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Mindre opdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Drobné aktualizace:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">وردە نوێکارییەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Actualitzacions menors:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Ensure all copy is translatable</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">确保所有副本都是可翻译的</li>
          <li lang="uk">Усі копії придатні для перетворення</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zaistené, že všetky kópie sú prekladateľné</li>
          <li lang="ru">Все копии пригодны для преобразования</li>
          <li lang="pl">Upewniono się, że kopiuj jest tłumaczone</li>
          <li lang="ja">すべてのテキストが翻訳できるように修正</li>
          <li lang="he">וידוא שכל ההעתקה ניתנת לתרגום</li>
          <li lang="fr">Nous nous sommes assurés que tout soit traduisible</li>
          <li lang="es">Asegúrese de que toda la copia sea traducible</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Ensure all copy is translatable</li>
          <li lang="de">Sicherstellen, dass Copytext übersetzbar ist</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zajištěno že jsou překladatelné veškeré kopie</li>
          <li lang="ckb">دڵنیابوونەوە لەوەی کە هەموو لەبەرگیراوەکان وەردەگێڕدرێن</li>
          <li lang="ca">S'assegura que tota la còpia sigui traduïble.</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">翻译更新</li>
          <li lang="uz">Yangilangan tarjimalar</li>
          <li lang="uk">Оновлено переклади</li>
          <li lang="tr">Çeviriler güncellendi</li>
          <li lang="sr">Освежени преводи</li>
          <li lang="sl">Posodobljeni prevodi</li>
          <li lang="sk">Aktualizované preklady</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обновлены переводы</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zaktualizowano tłumaczenia</li>
          <li lang="nl">Bijgewerkte vertalingen</li>
          <li lang="nb">Oppdaterte oversettelser</li>
          <li lang="mr">अद्ययावत अनुवाद</li>
          <li lang="lt">Atnaujinti vertimai</li>
          <li lang="ko">번역 업데이트</li>
          <li lang="ja">翻訳の更新</li>
          <li lang="it">Traduzioni aggiornate</li>
          <li lang="he">עדכוני תרגומים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Traducións actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="fr">Mise à jour des traductions</li>
          <li lang="fi">Päivitetyt käännökset</li>
          <li lang="es">Traducciones actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝisdatigitaj tradukoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="de">Aktualisierte Übersetzungen</li>
          <li lang="da">Opdaterede oversættelser</li>
          <li lang="cs">Aktualizovány překlady</li>
          <li lang="ckb">وەرگێڕانەکان نوێکراونەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Traduccions actualitzades</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release urgency="medium" version="6.0.0" date="2021-07-15">
      <description>
        <p>New features:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">新特性：</p>
        <p lang="uz">Yangi imkoniyatlar:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Нові функції:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Yeni özellikler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Нове функције:</p>
        <p lang="sl">Nove zmožnosti:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Nové funkcie:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Новые возможности:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Novas funcionalidades:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Novas funcionalidades:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Nowe funkcje:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Nieuwe functies:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Nye funksjoner:</p>
        <p lang="mr">नवीन वैशिष्ट्य:</p>
        <p lang="ja">新機能:</p>
        <p lang="it">Nuove funzionalità:</p>
        <p lang="he">תכונות חדשות:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Nouvelles fonctionnalités :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Uudet ominaisuudet:</p>
        <p lang="es">Funcionalidades nuevas:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Novaj funkcioj:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">New features:</p>
        <p lang="de">Neue Funktionen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Nye funktioner:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Nové funkce:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">تایبەتمەندییە تازەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Funcions noves:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>New Markdown plugin for WYSIWYG-like editing.</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">为 WYSIWYG-like 编辑提供新 Markdown 插件。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Новий плагін розмітки для WYSIWYG-подібного редагування.</li>
          <li lang="tr">WYSIWYG gibi düzenleme yapmak için yeni Markdown eklentisi.</li>
          <li lang="sr">Нови прикључак означавања за ОШВЈОШД-слично уређивање.</li>
          <li lang="sk">Nový zásuvný modul Markdown pre úpravy podobné WYSIWYG.</li>
          <li lang="ru">Новый плагин разметки для WYSIWYG-подобного редактирования.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Novo plugin Markdown para edição no estilo WYSIWYG.</li>
          <li lang="pt">Novo plugin Markdown para edição tipo WYSIWYG.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nowy plugin do Markdowna z edycją w stylu WYSWIG.</li>
          <li lang="mr">WYSIWYG सारख्या संपादनासाठी नवीन मार्कडाउन प्लगइन.</li>
          <li lang="ja">WYSIWYG 風に編集できる Markdown プラグインを追加しました。</li>
          <li lang="he">תוסף Markdown לעריכה חזותית.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Nouveau plugin Markdown pour une édition en mode WYSIWYG.</li>
          <li lang="es">Complemento nuevo para Markdown, para una edición tipo WYSIWYG.</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">New Markdown plugin for WYSIWYG-like editing.</li>
          <li lang="de">Neues Markdown-Plugin für WYSIWYG-ähnliche Textbearbeitung.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Nový zásuvný modul Markdown pro interaktivní (WYSIWYG) upravování.</li>
          <li lang="ckb">پێوەکراوی نوێی مارک داون بۆ دەستکاریکردنی وەک WYSIWYG.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Connector nou de Markdown per a l'edició semblant a WYSIWYG.</li>
          <li>Switch Git branches or create new ones in project folder context menus</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">切换Git分支或在项目文件夹上下文菜单中创建新的分支</li>
          <li lang="uk">Перемикання гілок Git або створення нових з контекстного меню теки проєкту</li>
          <li lang="sk">Prepínajte Git vetvy alebo vytvárajte nové v kontextových menu priečinkov projektu</li>
          <li lang="ru">Переключение веток Git или создание новых в контекстном меню папки проекта</li>
          <li lang="pt">Trocar de ramos Git ou criar novos ramos nos menus de contexto de pastas de projetos</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zmieniaj branche Gita lub twórz nowe w menu kontekstowym folderu projektu</li>
          <li lang="ja">プロジェクトフォルダーのコンテキストメニューから、Git ブランチを切り替えたり新しいブランチを作成したりできる機能を追加</li>
          <li lang="he">ניתן לעבור בין ענפים של Git או ליצור חדשים בתפריטי ההקשר של תיקיית המיזם</li>
          <li lang="fr">Changez de branche Git ou créez en de nouvelles dans le menu contextuel du dossier du projet</li>
          <li lang="es">Cambie las ramas de Git o cree nuevas en los menús contextuales de la carpeta del proyecto</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Switch Git branches or create new ones in project folder context menus</li>
          <li lang="de">Git Zweige direkt im Projektordner-Kontextmenü wechseln oder erstellen</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přepínejte mezi větvemi v git nebo vytvářejte nové v kontextových nabídkách složky projektu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">گۆڕین یان دروستکردنی بڕانچی نوێی گیت لە لیستی دەقی بوخچەی پڕۆژە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Canvieu les branques de Git o creeu-ne de noves als menús contextuals de la carpeta del projecte.</li>
          <li>Show Git diff status in source view gutters</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">在源视图中显示Git diff状态</li>
          <li lang="uk">Показ стану Git diff у проміжних поданнях джерела</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zobrazujte Git diff status v okrajoch zdrojového zobrazenia</li>
          <li lang="ru">Показывать статус Git diff в желобах представления источника</li>
          <li lang="pt">Mostra o estado do Git diff nas calhas da visualização do código-fonte</li>
          <li lang="pl">Pokaż status różnic Gita w podglądzie plików źródłowych</li>
          <li lang="ja">ソースビューの左端に Git の差分を表示する機能を追加</li>
          <li lang="he">הצגת מצב ההבדלים ב־Git במרזבי תצוגת המקור</li>
          <li lang="fr">Affichage du statut diff de Git dans les volets de la vue source</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Show Git diff status in source view gutters</li>
          <li lang="de">Zeige Git diff status in der Quellcodeansicht-Seitenleiste</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zobrazujte stav git diff v gutters zobrazení zdroje</li>
          <li lang="ckb">پشاندانی دۆخی گیت دیف</li>
          <li lang="ca">Es mostra l'estat de Git diff als espais en blanc de la vista del codi.</li>
          <li>Full text search within project folder.</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">在项目文件夹中进行全文搜索。</li>
          <li lang="uk">Повнотекстовий пошук у теці проєкту.</li>
          <li lang="sk">Úplné textové vyhľadávanie v priečinku projektu</li>
          <li lang="ru">Полнотекстовый поиск в папке проекта.</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Pesquisa de texto completa na pasta do projeto.</li>
          <li lang="pt">Pesquisa de texto completo na pasta do projeto.</li>
          <li lang="pl">Pełnoprawne wyszukiwanie tekstu w folderze projektu.</li>
          <li lang="ja">プロジェクトフォルダー内での全文検索に対応しました。</li>
          <li lang="he">חיפוש טקסט מלא בתוך תיקיית המיזם.</li>
          <li lang="fr">Recherche de texte complète à l'intérieur du dossier d'un projet.</li>
          <li lang="es">Búsqueda de texto completo dentro de la carpeta del proyecto.</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Full text search within project folder.</li>
          <li lang="de">Volltextsuche im Projektordner.</li>
          <li lang="cs">Plnotextové vyhledávání v rámci složky projektu.</li>
          <li lang="ckb">گەڕانی دەقی تەواو لە بوخچەی پڕۆژەدا.</li>
          <li lang="ca">Cerca de text complet a la carpeta del projecte.</li>
          <li>Save and restore cursor position between sessions</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">在会话之间保存和恢复光标位置</li>
          <li lang="uk">Збереження та відновлення позиції курсора між сеансами</li>
          <li lang="sk">Uložte a obnovte polohu kurzora medzi rôznymi reláciami</li>
          <li lang="ru">Сохранение и восстановление положения курсора между сеансами</li>
          <li lang="pt">Guardar e restaurar a posição do cursor entre as sessões</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zapisywanie i przywracanie pozycji kursora pomiędzy sesjami</li>
          <li lang="ja">セッションの最後のカーソル位置を保存し復元する機能を追加</li>
          <li lang="he">לשמור ולשחזר את מיקום הסמן בין הפעלות</li>
          <li lang="fr">Enregistrement et restauration de la position du curseur entre les sessions</li>
          <li lang="es">Guardar y restaurar la posición del cursor entre sesiones</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Save and restore cursor position between sessions</li>
          <li lang="de">Sichern und Wiederherstellen der Cursorposition zwischen Sessions</li>
          <li lang="cs">Ukládána a obnovována pozice kurzoru z minulé relace</li>
          <li lang="ckb">پاشەکەوتکردن و هێنانەوەی نیشاندەری دەق لە نێوان سێشنەکاندا</li>
          <li lang="ca">Es desa i es restaura la posició del cursor entre sessions.</li>
          <li>Close files from a project when that project is closed</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">关闭项目时关闭项目中的文件</li>
          <li lang="uk">Закриття файлів з проєкту, коли цей проєкт закрито</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zatvárajte súbory z projektu pri zatvorení daného projektu</li>
          <li lang="ru">Закрытие файлов проекта при завершении работы с проектом</li>
          <li lang="pt">Fechar ficheiros cujo projecto foi fechado</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zamykanie plików projektu gdy projekt jest zamykany</li>
          <li lang="ja">プロジェクトが閉じた場合にそのプロジェクト内のファイルも閉じるように修正</li>
          <li lang="he">לסגור קבצים של מיזם בעת סגירתו</li>
          <li lang="fr">Fermeture des fichiers d'un projet lorsque ce projet est fermé</li>
          <li lang="es">Cerrar archivos de un proyecto cuando ese proyecto está cerrado</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Close files from a project when that project is closed</li>
          <li lang="de">Projektdaten schliessen wenn das Projekt geschlossen wird</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zavírání souborů z projektu když je takový projekt zavřen</li>
          <li lang="ckb">داخستنی پەڕگەکانی پڕۆژەیەک کاتێک پڕۆژەکە دادەخەیت</li>
          <li lang="ca">Tanqueu fitxers d’un projecte quan es tanca el projecte.</li>
          <li>Show full file path in tab tooltips</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">在选项卡工具提示中显示完整的文档路径</li>
          <li lang="uk">Показ повного шляху до файлу у підказках вкладки</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zobrazte úplnú cestu súboru v popisoch kariet</li>
          <li lang="ru">Отображение полного пути к файлу в подсказке вкладки</li>
          <li lang="pt">Mostrar o caminho completo do ficheiro nas dicas do separador</li>
          <li lang="pl">Pokazywanie pełnej ścieżki pliku w tooltipach kart</li>
          <li lang="ja">タブのツールチップにファイルのフルパスを表示するように変更</li>
          <li lang="he">הצגת הנתיב המלא לקובץ בחלוניות העצה של הלשוניות</li>
          <li lang="fr">Affichage du chemin complet du fichier dans l'infobulle des onglets</li>
          <li lang="es">Mostrar la ruta completa del archivo en la información de herramientas de la pestaña</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Show full file path in tab tooltips</li>
          <li lang="de">Zeige vollständigen Dateipfad in den Tab Tooltips</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zobrazován úplný popis umístění souboru v bublinové nápovědě panelu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">پشاندانی شوێنی تەواوی پەڕگە لە توڵتیپسی تابدا</li>
          <li lang="ca">Es mostra el camí complet del fitxer a les descripcions emergents de la pestanya.</li>
          <li>Clear lines with Ctrl + K</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">用 Ctrl + K 清除线条</li>
          <li lang="uk">Очищення рядка за допомогою Ctrl + K</li>
          <li lang="sk">Vymazávajte riadky pomocou Ctrl + K</li>
          <li lang="ru">Очистка линий с помощью Ctrl + K</li>
          <li lang="pt">Limpar linhas com Ctrl + K</li>
          <li lang="pl">Usuń linię przy użyciu Ctrl + K</li>
          <li lang="ja">Ctrl + K で行の文字を消去する機能を追加</li>
          <li lang="he">ניתן למחוק שורות עם Ctrl + K</li>
          <li lang="fr">Effacer les lignes avec Ctrl + K</li>
          <li lang="es">Borrar líneas con Ctrl + K</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Clear lines with Ctrl + K</li>
          <li lang="de">Zeilen löschen mit Strg + K</li>
          <li lang="cs">Vymazání řádek pomocí Ctrl+K</li>
          <li lang="ckb">پاککردەوەی دێڕەکان بە کۆنتڕۆڵ و K</li>
          <li lang="ca">Esborreu línies amb Ctrl + K.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Minor updates:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">小幅更新：</p>
        <p lang="uz">Kichik yangilanishlar:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Незначні оновлення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Küçük güncellemeler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Мања освежења:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Menšie aktualizácie:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Незначительные обновления:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Pequenas atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Pequenas atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Mniejsze aktualizacje:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Kleine updates:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Små oppdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="mr">किरकोळ अद्यतने:</p>
        <p lang="ja">軽微なアップデート:</p>
        <p lang="it">Aggiornamenti minori:</p>
        <p lang="he">עדכונים משניים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Mises à jour mineures :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Pienet päivitykset:</p>
        <p lang="es">Actualizaciones menores:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Minor updates:</p>
        <p lang="de">Weitere Aktualisierungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Mindre opdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Drobné aktualizace:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">وردە نوێکارییەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Actualitzacions menors:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Allow Spell Checker extension in Markdown files</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">在 Markdown 文件里可以使用拼写检查插件</li>
          <li lang="uz">Markdown fayllarida avtomatik so'zlarni imloga tekshirish qo'shimchasini yoqish</li>
          <li lang="uk">Дозволити розширення перевірки правопису у файлах Markdown</li>
          <li lang="tr">Markdown dosyalarında Yazım Denetleyicisi uzantısına izin ver</li>
          <li lang="sr">Допушта проширење провере правописа у датотекама обележавања</li>
          <li lang="sk">Povoliť rozšírenie Kontrola pravopisu v súboroch Markdown</li>
          <li lang="ru">Разрешить расширение проверки орфографии в файлах Markdown</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Permitir extensão do corretor ortográfico nos arquivos Markdown</li>
          <li lang="pt">Permitir a extensão do corretor ortográfico nos ficheiros Markdown</li>
          <li lang="pl">Rozszerzenie do sprawdzania pisowni w plikach Markdown</li>
          <li lang="nl">De spellingscontrole extensie is toegestaan in Markdown bestanden</li>
          <li lang="nb">Tillat stavekontrollutvidelse i Markdown-filer</li>
          <li lang="mr">मार्कडाउन फायलींमध्ये शब्दलेखन तपासक विस्तारास अनुमती द्या</li>
          <li lang="ja">Markdown ファイルでスペルチェッカー拡張機能を利用できるように変更</li>
          <li lang="it">Abilita l'estensione Controllo Ortografico nei documenti Markdown</li>
          <li lang="he">לאפשר את הרחבת בדיקת האיות בקובצי Markdown</li>
          <li lang="fr">Autorisation de la correction orthographique dans les fichiers Markdown</li>
          <li lang="es">Se permite la extensión de revisión ortográfica en los archivos Markdown</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Allow Spell Checker extension in Markdown files</li>
          <li lang="de">Erweiterung der Rechtschreibprüfung in Markdown-Dateien erlauben</li>
          <li lang="cs">Umožnit rozšíření pro kontrolu překlepů v souborech Markdown</li>
          <li lang="ckb">ڕێگەدان بە کارکردنی پێوەکراوی هەڵەچنین لە پەڕگە مارکداونەکاندا</li>
          <li lang="ca">Es permet l'extensió del corrector ortogràfic als fitxers de Markdown.</li>
          <li>Improve multi-line duplication</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">改善多行重复</li>
          <li lang="uk">Вдосконалено багаторядкових дублювань</li>
          <li lang="sk">Vylepšená duplikácia viacerých riadkov naraz</li>
          <li lang="ru">Улучшение многострочного дублирования</li>
          <li lang="pt">Melhorar duplicação multi-linha</li>
          <li lang="pl">Poprawienie działania duplikacji wielu linii</li>
          <li lang="ja">複数行の複製を改善</li>
          <li lang="he">שיפור שכפול של קבוצת שורות</li>
          <li lang="fr">Amélioration de la duplication multi-lignes</li>
          <li lang="es">Mejorar la duplicación de varias líneas</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Improve multi-line duplication</li>
          <li lang="de">Duplizieren von mehreren Zeilen verbessert</li>
          <li lang="cs">Vylepšeno zdvojování vícero řádků</li>
          <li lang="ckb">گەشەدان بە بەدووکردنی جوت هێڵ</li>
          <li lang="ca">Millora de la duplicació de línies múltiples</li>
          <li>Remember whether the sidebar is open</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">记忆侧边栏开关状态</li>
          <li lang="uz">Yon panelda qaysi joylar ochilganini eslab qolish</li>
          <li lang="uk">Пам'ятати чи відкрито бічну панель</li>
          <li lang="tr">Kenar çubuğunun açık olup olmadığını hatırla</li>
          <li lang="sr">Памти да ли је бочна површ отворена</li>
          <li lang="sk">Pamätať si, či je bočný panel otvorený</li>
          <li lang="ru">Запоминать, открыта ли боковая панель</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Lembre-se se a barra lateral está aberta</li>
          <li lang="pt">Lembra-se se a barra lateral está aberta</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zapamiętywanie statusu otwarcia panelu bocznego</li>
          <li lang="nl">Onthoud of de zijbalk opengeklapt is</li>
          <li lang="nb">Husk hvorvidt sidepanelet er åpent</li>
          <li lang="mr">साइडबार खुले आहे की नाही ते लक्षात ठेवा</li>
          <li lang="ja">サイドバーの表示／非表示の状態を保存するように変更</li>
          <li lang="it">Ricorda se la barra laterale é aperta</li>
          <li lang="he">לזכור האם סרגל הצד פתוח</li>
          <li lang="fr">Nous avons fait en sorte de sauvegarder l'état de la barre latérale</li>
          <li lang="es">Se recuerda si la barra lateral estaba abierta</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Remember whether the sidebar is open</li>
          <li lang="de">Merken, ob die Seitenleiste geöffnet ist</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zapamatováno, zda je postranní panel otevřen</li>
          <li lang="ckb">بیریبێت کە سایدباڕ کراوەیە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Es recorda quan la barra lateral està oberta.</li>
          <li>Set window title to the focused file</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">设置窗口标题为聚焦文件</li>
          <li lang="uk">Установлення заголовків вікна сфокусованому файлу</li>
          <li lang="sk">Nastavovať názov okna ako práve vybraný súbor</li>
          <li lang="ru">Установка заголовков окна на сфокусированном файле</li>
          <li lang="pt">Usar título de ficheiro em foco como título da janela</li>
          <li lang="pl">Ustaw tytuł okna na otwarty plik</li>
          <li lang="ja">現在表示中のファイル名をウィンドウのタイトルとして設定するように修正</li>
          <li lang="he">הגדרת כותרת החלון לקובץ שבמיקוד</li>
          <li lang="fr">Le titre de la fenêtre reflète le fichier en cours d'édition</li>
          <li lang="es">Establecer el título de la ventana basándose en el archivo que se encuentra abierto</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Set window title to the focused file</li>
          <li lang="de">Namen der aktiven Datei als Fenstertitel setzen</li>
          <li lang="cs">Titulek okna nastavován na zaměřený soubor</li>
          <li lang="ckb">گۆڕینی تایتڵی پەنجەرە بۆ فایلی کارا و سەرنج دراو</li>
          <li lang="ca">Establiment del títol de la finestra segons el fitxer amb el focus</li>
          <li>Add keyboard shortcuts for next and previous documents</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">为下一个和上一个文档添加键盘快捷键</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано комбінації клавіш переходу до наступного та попереднього документів</li>
          <li lang="tr">Önceki ve sonraki belgeler için klavye kısayolları atandı</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додаје пречице тастатуре за следеће и претходне документе</li>
          <li lang="sk">Pridané klávesové skratky pre nasledujúce a predchádzajúce dokumenty</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлены сочетания клавиш для следующих и предыдущих документов</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionar atalhos de teclado para os documentos anteriores e seguintes</li>
          <li lang="pt">Adicionar teclas de atalho para os documentos seguintes e anteriores</li>
          <li lang="pl">Dodanie skrótów klawiszowych dla następnego i poprzedniego dokumentu</li>
          <li lang="mr">पुढील आणि मागील दस्तऐवजांसाठी कीबोर्ड शॉर्टकट जोडा</li>
          <li lang="ja">タブを切り替えるキーボードショートカットを追加</li>
          <li lang="he">הוספת קיצור מקלדת למסמכים הבא והקודם</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout des raccourcis claviers pour les documents précédent et suivant</li>
          <li lang="es">Añadir atajos de teclado para los documentos anteriores y siguientes</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Add keyboard shortcuts for next and previous documents</li>
          <li lang="de">Hinzufügen von Tastaturkürzeln für nächste und vorhergegangene Dokumente</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidány klávesové zkratky pro následující a předchozí dokumenty</li>
          <li lang="ckb">زیادکردنی کورتەڕێی تەختەکلیل بۆ دۆکیومێنتەکانی دواتر و پێشتر</li>
          <li lang="ca">Addició de dreceres de teclat per als documents següents i anteriors</li>
          <li>Show full document path in tab tooltip</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">在选项卡工具提示中显示完整的文档路径</li>
          <li lang="uk">Показ повного шляху до документа у підказці вкладки</li>
          <li lang="tr">İpucu sekmesinde tam belge yolunu göster</li>
          <li lang="sr">Прикажи пуну путању документа у облачићу језичка</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zobraziť úplnú cestu k dokumentu v popise karty</li>
          <li lang="ru">Отображение полного пути к документу в подсказке вкладки</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Mostrar o caminho completo do documento na dica de ferramenta da guia</li>
          <li lang="pt">Mostrar o caminho completo do documento na dica de ferramenta do separador</li>
          <li lang="pl">Pokazywanie pełnej ścieżki dokumentu w tooltipie</li>
          <li lang="mr">टॅब टूलटिपमध्ये दस्तऐवजाचा पूर्ण पाथ दाखवा</li>
          <li lang="ja">タブのツールチップにドキュメントのフルパスを表示するように変更</li>
          <li lang="he">הצגת הנתיב המלא למסמך בחלונית העצה של הלשונית</li>
          <li lang="fr">Affichage du chemin complet du document dans l'infobulle des onglets</li>
          <li lang="es">Se muestra la ruta completa del documento en la descripción emergente de la pestaña</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Show full document path in tab tooltip</li>
          <li lang="de">Vollen Dokumentenpfad im Tab Tooltip anzeigen</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zobrazen úplný popis umístění dokumentu v bublinové nápovědě panelu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">پشاندانی شوێنی تەواوی دۆکیومێنت لە توڵتیپی تابدا</li>
          <li lang="ca">Es mostra el camí complet del document a la descripció emergent de la pestanya.</li>
          <li>Update Pastebin plugin</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">更新Pastebin插件</li>
          <li lang="uk">Оновлено плагін Pastebin</li>
          <li lang="sk">Aktualizovaný doplnok Pastebin</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обновлен плагин Pastebin</li>
          <li lang="pt">Atualizar extensão Pastebin</li>
          <li lang="pl">Aktualizacja wtyczki Pastebin</li>
          <li lang="ja">Pastebin プラグインをアップデート</li>
          <li lang="he">עדכון תוסף Patebin</li>
          <li lang="fr">Mise à jour du module Pastebin</li>
          <li lang="es">Actualizar el complemento Pastebin</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Update Pastebin plugin</li>
          <li lang="de">Aktualisieren des Pastebin-Plugins</li>
          <li lang="cs">Aktualizován zásuvný modul pro Pastebin</li>
          <li lang="ckb">نوێکردنەوەی پێوەکراوی پەیست بین (Pastebin)</li>
          <li lang="ca">Actualització del connector de Pastebin</li>
          <li>Correctly indent last line when using the preserve whitespace plugin</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">使用保留空格插件时正确缩进最后一行</li>
          <li lang="uk">Правильний відступ останнього рядка коли застосовується плагін прибирання пробілів</li>
          <li lang="sk">Správne odsadzovať posledný riadok pri použití doplnku Zachovať mezdery</li>
          <li lang="ru">Правильный отступ последней строки при использовании плагина убирания пробелов</li>
          <li lang="pt">Indentar a última linha corretamente quando a extensão de preservar espaço em branco estiver em uso</li>
          <li lang="pl">Poprawnie wcinanie ostatniej linii podczas używania wtyczki do przechowywania białych znaków</li>
          <li lang="ja">“ファイル末尾の空白を削除”プラグインを使用時、最終行が適切にインデントするように修正</li>
          <li lang="he">הזחה נכונה של השורה האחרונה בעת שימוש בתוסף שימור הרווחים</li>
          <li lang="fr">Indentation correcte de la dernière ligne lors de l'utilisation de l'extension de conservation des espaces blancs</li>
          <li lang="es">Corregir sangrado en la última línea cuando se utiliza el complemento de conservación de espacios en blanco</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Correctly indent last line when using the preserve whitespace plugin</li>
          <li lang="de">Letzte Zeile korrekt Einrücken, wenn das preserve whitespace-Plugin benutzt wird</li>
          <li lang="cs">Správné odsazování posledního řádku při použití zásuvného modulu pro zachovávání prázdných znaků</li>
          <li lang="ckb">زیادکردنی بۆشایی سەرەتای دێڕ بۆ کۆتا دێڕ بەشێوەیەکی دروست کاتێک پێوەکراوی بۆشایی سپی بەکار دەهێنیت</li>
          <li lang="ca">Sagnat correcte de l’última línia quan s’usa el connector de conservació d’espai en blanc</li>
          <li>Keep syntax highlighting when duplicating a file</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">复制文件时保持语法高亮</li>
          <li lang="uk">Збереження підсвічування синтаксису коли дублюється файл</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zachovať zvýrazňovanie syntaxe pri duplikovaní súboru</li>
          <li lang="ru">Сохранение подсветки синтаксиса при дублировании файла</li>
          <li lang="pt">Manter o realce da sintaxe ao duplicar um ficheiro</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zachowaj podświetlanie składni podczas duplikowania pliku</li>
          <li lang="ja">複製したファイルに複製元と同じシンタックスハイライトを適用するように修正</li>
          <li lang="hu">Szintaxiskiemelés megőrzése fájl megkettőzésekor</li>
          <li lang="he">לשמור על הדגשת התחביר בעת שכפול קובץ</li>
          <li lang="fr">Garde la coloration syntaxique originale lors de la duplication d'un fichier</li>
          <li lang="es">Se mantiene la coloración sintáctica al duplicar un archivo</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Keep syntax highlighting when duplicating a file</li>
          <li lang="de">Syntax-Hervorhebung beibehalten wenn eine Datei dupliziert wird</li>
          <li lang="cs">Při zduplikování souboru ponecháno zvýraznění syntaxe</li>
          <li lang="ckb">هێشتنەوەی هایلایتکردنی سینتاکسلە کاتی بەدووکردنی پەڕگەیەک</li>
          <li lang="ca">Es continua ressaltant la sintaxi en duplicar un fitxer.</li>
          <li>Expand a collapsed folder if you attempt to open it twice</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">如果试图打开折叠的文件夹两次，则展开它</li>
          <li lang="uk">Розгортання згорнутої теки після другої спроби відкрити її</li>
          <li lang="sk">Rozbaliť zatvorený priečinok, ak sa ho pokúsite otvoriť dvakrát</li>
          <li lang="ru">Развертание свернутой папки, если вы пытаетесь открыть её дважды</li>
          <li lang="pt">Expandir uma pasta recolhida ao tentar abri-la duas vezes</li>
          <li lang="pl">Rozwinięcie zwiniętego folderu przy dwukrotnej próbie otworzenia</li>
          <li lang="ja">折りたたまれたフォルダーを2回開いてしまった場合に、フォルダーを展開するように変更</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקייה מצומצמת מתרחבת אם מנסים לפתוח אותה פעמיים</li>
          <li lang="fr">Développement d'un dossier réduit si vous tentez de l'ouvrir deux fois</li>
          <li lang="es">Se expande una carpeta contraída si se intenta abrir dos veces</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Expand a collapsed folder if you attempt to open it twice</li>
          <li lang="de">Zugeklappten Ordner aufklappen wenn zweimal versucht wird ihn zu öffnen</li>
          <li lang="cs">Rozbalení sbalené složky při pokusu o její otevření dvakrát</li>
          <li lang="ckb">کردنەوەی بوخچەیەکی کۆکراوە ئەگەر هەوڵ بدەیت دوو جار بیکەیتەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Ampliació d'una carpeta reduïda si s'intenta obrir-la dues vegades</li>
          <li>Fix an issue where searches are lost when Code loses focus</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">修复当代码失去焦点时搜索丢失的问题</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено проблему втрати результатів пошуку після перенесення фокусу з Коду</li>
          <li lang="sk">Opravený problém straty vyhľadávaných výrazov pri prepnutí z okna Kód na iné okno</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлена проблема, при которой исчезал поиск, когда Код терял фокус</li>
          <li lang="pt">Corrige um problema onde pesquisas em curso são perdidas quando o Code perde o foco</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawienie problemu z utraconymi wyszukiwaniami gdy Kod przestaje być w fokusie</li>
          <li lang="ja">“コード”のウィンドウが非アクティブになった場合に検索文字列がリセットされてしまう不具合を修正</li>
          <li lang="he">תוקנה תקלה שחיפושים אבדו בעת אובדן מיקוד על היישום</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction d'un problème où les recherches sont perdues lorsque Code n'était plus au premier plan</li>
          <li lang="es">Solucionado un problema por el cual las búsquedas se pierden cuando Code pierde el foco</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix an issue where searches are lost when Code loses focus</li>
          <li lang="de">Behebt einen Fehler, bei dem Suchvorgänge verloren gehen wenn Code nicht mehr das aktive Fenster ist</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opraven problém se ztrácením výsledků když okno Code ztratí zaměření</li>
          <li lang="ckb">چارەسەرکردنی کێشەیەک کە گەڕانەکان بزر دەبون کاتێک سەرنج لەسەر پەنجەری کۆد نە دەما</li>
          <li lang="ca">Solució d'un problema en què es perdien les cerques quan el Codi perdia el focus</li>
          <li>Start Vim plugin in command mode</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">在命令模式下启动Vim插件</li>
          <li lang="uk">Запуск плагіну Vim у командному режимі</li>
          <li lang="sk">Spúšťať doplnok Vim v príkazovom režime</li>
          <li lang="ru">Запуск плагина Vim в командном режиме</li>
          <li lang="pt">Iniciar a extensão Vim em modo comando</li>
          <li lang="pl">Uruchamianie wtyczki Vim w trybie komend</li>
          <li lang="ja">Vim プラグインをコマンドラインモードで開始するように変更</li>
          <li lang="he">הפעלת תוסף Vim במצב פקודות</li>
          <li lang="fr">Lancez le plugin Vim en mode commande</li>
          <li lang="es">Se inicia el complemento Vim en modo de órdenes</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Start Vim plugin in command mode</li>
          <li lang="de">Starte Vim plugin im Command-Mode</li>
          <li lang="cs">Spouštění zásuvného modulu Vim v příkazovém režimu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">دەستپێکردنی پێوەکراوی ڤیم (Vim) لە دۆخی فەرماندا</li>
          <li lang="ca">Inicieu el connector Vim en mode de línia d'ordres.</li>
          <li>Fix and add new Vim commands</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">修复并添加新的Vim命令</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено та додано нові команди Vim</li>
          <li lang="sk">Opravené a pridané nové Vim príkazy</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлены и добавлены новые команды Vim</li>
          <li lang="pt">Corrigir e adicionar novos comandos Vim</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawa i dodanie nowych komend Vima</li>
          <li lang="ja">Vim コマンドの修正と追加</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון והוספת פקודות Vim חדשות</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction et ajout de nouvelles commandes Vim</li>
          <li lang="es">Se arreglan y añaden nuevas órdenes de Vim</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix and add new Vim commands</li>
          <li lang="de">Neue Vim Kommandos hinzugefügt und Fehler behoben</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opraveny stávající a přidány nové Vim příkazy</li>
          <li lang="ckb">چاککردن و زیادکردنی فەرمانی نوێی ڤیم (Vim)</li>
          <li lang="ca">Correcció i addició d'ordres noves de Vim</li>
          <li>Show project folders with a hidden root folder</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">显示带有隐藏根文件夹的项目文件夹</li>
          <li lang="uk">Показ тек проєкту з прихованою кореневою текою</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zobrazovať projektové súbory so skrytým priečinkom root</li>
          <li lang="ru">Отображение папок проекта со скрытой корневой папкой</li>
          <li lang="pt">Mostrar pastas de projetos com a pasta de root ocultada</li>
          <li lang="pl">Pokaż foldery projektów z ukrytym folderem źródłowym</li>
          <li lang="ja">ルートフォルダーが隠しフォルダーになっているプロジェクトのフォルダーを表示するように修正</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקיות מיזם עם תיקיית מקור מוסתרת מוצגות</li>
          <li lang="fr">Affichage des dossiers de projets dont le dossier racine est caché</li>
          <li lang="es">Mostrar carpetas de proyectos con una carpeta raíz oculta</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Show project folders with a hidden root folder</li>
          <li lang="de">Zeige Projektordner bei verstecktem Root-Ordner</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zobrazeny složky projektů se skrytou kořenovou složkou</li>
          <li lang="ckb">پشاندانی بوخچەکانی پڕۆژە لە بوخچەی ڕوتی شاراوەدا</li>
          <li lang="ca">Es mostren les carpetes del projecte amb una carpeta d'arrel oculta.</li>
          <li>Allow launching with pkexec and disallow launching with sudo</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">允许使用 pkexec 启动并禁止使用 sudo 启动</li>
          <li lang="uk">Дозволено запуск з pkexec і заборонено запуск з sudo</li>
          <li lang="sk">Povolené spúšťanie s pkexec a zakázané spúšťanie so sudo</li>
          <li lang="ru">Разрешен запуск с помощью pkexec и запрещен запуск с помощью sudo</li>
          <li lang="pt">Permitir execução com pkexec e bloquear execução com sudo</li>
          <li lang="pl">Umożliwienie uruchamiania z pkexec i uniemożliwienie uruchamiania z sudo</li>
          <li lang="ja">pkexec での起動を可能にし、sudo での起動ができないように修正</li>
          <li lang="he">אפשר לטעון עם pkexec ואי אפשר לטעון עם sudo</li>
          <li lang="fr">Autorisation de l'exécution avec pkexec et interdiction de l'exécution avec sudo</li>
          <li lang="es">Permitir el lanzamiento con pkexec y no permitir el lanzamiento con sudo</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Allow launching with pkexec and disallow launching with sudo</li>
          <li lang="de">Gestatte den Start mit pkexec und verbiete den Start mit sudo</li>
          <li lang="cs">Umožněno spouštění prostřednictvím pkexec a znemožněno spouštění prostřednictvím sudo</li>
          <li lang="ckb">ڕێگەدان بە کردنەوە لەگەڵ pkexec و ڕێگە نەدان بە کردنەوە لەگەڵ sudo</li>
          <li lang="ca">Es permet el llançament amb pkexec i no es permet el llançament amb sudo.</li>
          <li>Remove split view</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">删除拆分视图</li>
          <li lang="uk">Вилучено розділене подання</li>
          <li lang="sk">Odstránené rozdelené zobrazenie</li>
          <li lang="ru">Удален раздельный вид</li>
          <li lang="pt">Remover vista dividida</li>
          <li lang="pl">Usunięcie dzielenia widoku</li>
          <li lang="ja">分割ビューを削除</li>
          <li lang="he">הסרת תצוגה מפוצלת</li>
          <li lang="fr">Suppression de la vue scindée</li>
          <li lang="es">Se elimina la vista dividida</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Remove split view</li>
          <li lang="de">Split View entfernt</li>
          <li lang="cs">Odebráno rozdělené zobrazení</li>
          <li lang="ckb">رەشکردنی دیمەنی جیاکردنەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Supressió de la visualització dividida</li>
          <li>Remove browser preview</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">移除浏览器预览</li>
          <li lang="uk">Вилучено попередній перегляд браузера</li>
          <li lang="sk">Odstránená ukážka v prehliadači</li>
          <li lang="ru">Убран предварительный просмотр браузера</li>
          <li lang="pt">Remover pré-visualização no navegador</li>
          <li lang="pl">Usunięcie podglądu przeglądarki</li>
          <li lang="ja">ブラウザープレビューを削除</li>
          <li lang="he">הסרת דפדפן תצוגה מקדימה</li>
          <li lang="fr">Suppression de l'aperçu dans le navigateur</li>
          <li lang="es">Desaparece la previsualización en el navegador</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Remove browser preview</li>
          <li lang="de">Browservorschau entfernt</li>
          <li lang="cs">Odebrán náhled prohlížeče</li>
          <li lang="ckb">رەشکردنەوەی پێشبینینی وێبگەڕ</li>
          <li lang="ca">Supressió de la previsualització del navegador</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">翻译更新</li>
          <li lang="uz">Yangilangan tarjimalar</li>
          <li lang="uk">Оновлено переклади</li>
          <li lang="tr">Çeviriler güncellendi</li>
          <li lang="sr">Освежени преводи</li>
          <li lang="sl">Posodobljeni prevodi</li>
          <li lang="sk">Aktualizované preklady</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обновлены переводы</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zaktualizowano tłumaczenia</li>
          <li lang="nl">Bijgewerkte vertalingen</li>
          <li lang="nb">Oppdaterte oversettelser</li>
          <li lang="mr">अद्ययावत अनुवाद</li>
          <li lang="lt">Atnaujinti vertimai</li>
          <li lang="ko">번역 업데이트</li>
          <li lang="ja">翻訳の更新</li>
          <li lang="it">Traduzioni aggiornate</li>
          <li lang="he">עדכוני תרגומים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Traducións actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="fr">Mise à jour des traductions</li>
          <li lang="fi">Päivitetyt käännökset</li>
          <li lang="es">Traducciones actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝisdatigitaj tradukoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="de">Aktualisierte Übersetzungen</li>
          <li lang="da">Opdaterede oversættelser</li>
          <li lang="cs">Aktualizovány překlady</li>
          <li lang="ckb">وەرگێڕانەکان نوێکراونەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Traduccions actualitzades</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-06-09" version="3.4.1">
      <description>
        <p>Fixes:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">修复：</p>
        <p lang="uz">To'g'rilashlar:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Виправлення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Düzeltmeler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Поправке:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Opravy:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Исправления:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Correções:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Correções:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Poprawki:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Opgelost:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Fikser:</p>
        <p lang="mr">निराकारणे:</p>
        <p lang="ja">修正点:</p>
        <p lang="it">Correzioni:</p>
        <p lang="hu">Javítások:</p>
        <p lang="he">תיקונים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Corrections :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Korjaukset:</p>
        <p lang="es">Correcciones:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Fixes:</p>
        <p lang="de">Fehlerbehebungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Rettelser:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Opravuje:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">چاککردنەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Correccions:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix empty sidebar layout, ensuring folders can always be added</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">修正了空的侧边栏布局, 确保文件夹可以随时添加</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено вигляд порожньої бічної панелі, забезпечивши можливість завжди додавати теки</li>
          <li lang="tr">Kenar çubuğu düzeltilerek her zaman klasör eklenebilmesi sağlandı</li>
          <li lang="sr">Поправља празан распоред бочне површи, осигуравајући да се фасцикле увек могу додати</li>
          <li lang="sk">Opravené prázdne rozloženie bočného panelu, čo zaistí, že priečinky je možné vždy pridať</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлен вид пустой боковой панели, обеспечив возможность всегда добавлять папки</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Corrija o layout da barra lateral vazia, garantindo que as pastas sempre possam ser adicionadas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Corrige a disposição de barra lateral vazia, assegurando que as pastas podem sempre ser adicionadas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawiono wygląd pustego panelu bocznego, zapewniając, że foldery zawsze mogą być dodane</li>
          <li lang="nl">Een probleem met de zijbalk opgelost, waardoor mappen altijd kunnen worden toegevoegd</li>
          <li lang="mr">रिक्त साइडबार लेआउट निश्चित करा, फोल्डर नेहमीच जोडले जाऊ शकतात याची खात्री करा</li>
          <li lang="ja">フォルダーが常に追加されるようにすることで、サイドバーのレイアウトに何も表示されない不具合を修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Corretta la barra laterale vuota, assicurando che le cartelle possano sempre essere aggiunte</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון פריסת חלונית צד ריקה, כדי לוודא שתמיד ניתן יהיה להוסיף תיקיות</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction de la disposition de la barre latérale lorsqu'elle est vide, en s'assurant que les dossiers puissent toujours être ajoutés</li>
          <li lang="es">Se solucionó el problema de la barra lateral vacía, lo que garantiza que siempre puedan añadirse carpetas</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix empty sidebar layout, ensuring folders can always be added</li>
          <li lang="de">Korrektur des leeren Layouts der Seitenleiste, um sicherzustellen, dass Ordner jederzeit hinzugefügt werden können</li>
          <li lang="da">Ret tomt sidepanellayout, så der altid kan tilføjes mapper</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opraveno prázdné rozvržení postranního panelu, což zajišťuje že složky je možné vždy přidat</li>
          <li lang="ckb">چاککردنی لەیئاوتی سایدباڕی بەتاڵ، دڵنیابوونەوە لەوەی کە هەمیشە بوخچەکان زیاد دەبن</li>
          <li lang="ca">El disseny buit de la barra lateral garanteix que sempre es puguin afegir carpetes.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Minor updates:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">小幅更新：</p>
        <p lang="uz">Kichik yangilanishlar:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Незначні оновлення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Küçük güncellemeler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Мања освежења:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Menšie aktualizácie:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Незначительные обновления:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Pequenas atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Pequenas atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Mniejsze aktualizacje:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Kleine updates:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Små oppdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="mr">किरकोळ अद्यतने:</p>
        <p lang="ja">軽微なアップデート:</p>
        <p lang="it">Aggiornamenti minori:</p>
        <p lang="he">עדכונים משניים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Mises à jour mineures :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Pienet päivitykset:</p>
        <p lang="es">Actualizaciones menores:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Minor updates:</p>
        <p lang="de">Weitere Aktualisierungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Mindre opdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Drobné aktualizace:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">وردە نوێکارییەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Actualitzacions menors:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Scroll past the end of a file</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">滚动到文件的末尾</li>
          <li lang="uz">Faylni oxiriga o'tish</li>
          <li lang="uk">Тепер можна гортати далі кінця файлу</li>
          <li lang="tr">Dosyanın sonundan öteye kaydırma</li>
          <li lang="sr">Премиче преко краја датотеке</li>
          <li lang="sk">Umožnené posúvanie až za koniec súboru</li>
          <li lang="ru">Теперь можно листать дальше конца файла</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Rolar até o final de um arquivo</li>
          <li lang="pt">Rolar até ao fim de um ficheiro</li>
          <li lang="pl">Możliwość przewijania poza koniec pliku</li>
          <li lang="nl">Scrollen voorbij het einde van een bestand</li>
          <li lang="nb">Rull forbi filens slutt</li>
          <li lang="mr">फाईलच्या शेवटी स्क्रोल करा</li>
          <li lang="ja">ファイルの最終行よりもさらにスクロールできるように変更</li>
          <li lang="it">Scorri oltre la fine di un file</li>
          <li lang="he">גלילה מעבר לסוף הקובץ</li>
          <li lang="fr">Faire défiler la fin d'un fichier</li>
          <li lang="es">Desplazamiento que sobrepasa el final de un archivo</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Scroll past the end of a file</li>
          <li lang="de">Bildlauf über das Ende einer Datei hinaus</li>
          <li lang="da">Rul forbi slutningen af en fil</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opraveno posouvání za konec souboru</li>
          <li lang="ckb">سکڕۆڵ کردن بۆ کۆتایی پەڕگەیەک</li>
          <li lang="ca">Desplaçament més enllà del final del fitxer</li>
          <li>More efficiently save and restore window position</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">更有效地保存和恢复窗口位置</li>
          <li lang="uk">Ефективніше збереження та відновлення положення вікна</li>
          <li lang="tr">Pencere konumunun daha verimli şekilde kaydedilmesi ve geri getirilmesi sağlandı</li>
          <li lang="sr">Делотворније чува и враћа положај прозора</li>
          <li lang="sk">Efektívnejšie ukladanie a obnovovanie polohy okna</li>
          <li lang="ru">Более эффективное сохранение и восстановление положения окна</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Salve e restaure com mais eficiência a posição da janela</li>
          <li lang="pt">Guarda e restaura a posição da janela de forma mais eficiente</li>
          <li lang="pl">Bardziej efektywne zapisywanie i przywracanie pozycji okna</li>
          <li lang="nl">Het onthouden en herstellen van de positie van het venster is efficiënter</li>
          <li lang="mr">अधिक कार्यक्षमतेने विंडो स्थिती जतन आणि पुनर्संचयित करा</li>
          <li lang="ja">ウィンドウの位置を、より効率的に保存・復元するように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Salva e ripristina in modo più efficiente la posizione della finestra</li>
          <li lang="he">לשמור ולשחזר מיקומי חלונות בצורה יעילה יותר</li>
          <li lang="fr">Sauvegarde et restauration plus efficace de la position de la fenêtre</li>
          <li lang="es">Guardado y restauración más eficientes de la posición de la ventana</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">More efficiently save and restore window position</li>
          <li lang="de">Effizienteres Speichern und Wiederherstellen der Fensterposition</li>
          <li lang="da">Gemme og gendanne vinduesposition mere effektivt</li>
          <li lang="cs">Efektivnější ukládání a obnovování pozice okna</li>
          <li lang="ckb">پاشەکەوتکردن و گەڕاندنەوەی شوێنی پەنجەرەیەک بە شێوەیەکی باشتر</li>
          <li lang="ca">Deseu i restaureu de manera més eficient la posició de la finestra.</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">翻译更新</li>
          <li lang="uz">Yangilangan tarjimalar</li>
          <li lang="uk">Оновлено переклади</li>
          <li lang="tr">Çeviriler güncellendi</li>
          <li lang="sr">Освежени преводи</li>
          <li lang="sl">Posodobljeni prevodi</li>
          <li lang="sk">Aktualizované preklady</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обновлены переводы</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zaktualizowano tłumaczenia</li>
          <li lang="nl">Bijgewerkte vertalingen</li>
          <li lang="nb">Oppdaterte oversettelser</li>
          <li lang="mr">अद्ययावत अनुवाद</li>
          <li lang="lt">Atnaujinti vertimai</li>
          <li lang="ko">번역 업데이트</li>
          <li lang="ja">翻訳の更新</li>
          <li lang="it">Traduzioni aggiornate</li>
          <li lang="he">עדכוני תרגומים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Traducións actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="fr">Mise à jour des traductions</li>
          <li lang="fi">Päivitetyt käännökset</li>
          <li lang="es">Traducciones actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝisdatigitaj tradukoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="de">Aktualisierte Übersetzungen</li>
          <li lang="da">Opdaterede oversættelser</li>
          <li lang="cs">Aktualizovány překlady</li>
          <li lang="ckb">وەرگێڕانەکان نوێکراونەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Traduccions actualitzades</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-04-01" version="3.4.0">
      <description>
        <p>New features:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">新特性：</p>
        <p lang="uz">Yangi imkoniyatlar:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Нові функції:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Yeni özellikler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Нове функције:</p>
        <p lang="sl">Nove zmožnosti:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Nové funkcie:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Новые возможности:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Novas funcionalidades:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Novas funcionalidades:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Nowe funkcje:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Nieuwe functies:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Nye funksjoner:</p>
        <p lang="mr">नवीन वैशिष्ट्य:</p>
        <p lang="ja">新機能:</p>
        <p lang="it">Nuove funzionalità:</p>
        <p lang="he">תכונות חדשות:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Nouvelles fonctionnalités :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Uudet ominaisuudet:</p>
        <p lang="es">Funcionalidades nuevas:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Novaj funkcioj:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">New features:</p>
        <p lang="de">Neue Funktionen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Nye funktioner:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Nové funkce:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">تایبەتمەندییە تازەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Funcions noves:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Include Git status in file tooltips</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">在文件提示中包含 Git 状态</li>
          <li lang="uk">Стан Git включено до підказок для файлів</li>
          <li lang="tr">Dosya ipuçlarına Git durumu dahil edildi</li>
          <li lang="sr">Укључује стање Гита у облачићима датотеке</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zahrnúť stav Git do popisu súborov</li>
          <li lang="ru">Включен статус Git во всплывающие подсказки файлов</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Incluir status Git nas dicas de ferramentas de arquivo</li>
          <li lang="pt">Incluir o estado do Git nas dicas de ferramentas do ficheiro</li>
          <li lang="pl">Umieszczenie statusu Gita w tooltipach pliku</li>
          <li lang="nl">Toon Git status in de knopinfo</li>
          <li lang="mr">फाईल टूलटिपमध्ये गिट स्थिती समाविष्ट करा</li>
          <li lang="ja">ファイルのツールチップに Git の状態を表示</li>
          <li lang="it">Include lo stato di Git nei nomi dei file</li>
          <li lang="he">הוספת מצב Git בחלוניות עצה של קבצים</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout du statut GIT dans l'infobulle des fichiers</li>
          <li lang="es">Se incluye el estado de Git en las descripciones emergentes de los archivos</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Include Git status in file tooltips</li>
          <li lang="de">Git-Status in Datei-Tooltips anzeigen lassen</li>
          <li lang="da">Inkluder Git-status i filværktøjstips</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zahrnout Git stav v nástrojových tipech souborů</li>
          <li lang="ckb">تێخزاندنی دۆخی گیت لە توڵتیپسی پەڕگە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Inclusió de l'estat de GIt a les descripcions emergents dels fitxers</li>
          <li>Option for explicit case-sensitive Find</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">严谨区分大小写的查找选项</li>
          <li lang="uk">Можливість явного пошуку з урахуванням регістру</li>
          <li lang="tr">Büyük-küçük harfe duyarlı Bul seçeneği eklendi</li>
          <li lang="sr">Опција за изричито налажење осетљивости на величину слова</li>
          <li lang="sk">Možnosť explicitného vyhľadávania s rozlišovaním veľkých a malých písmen</li>
          <li lang="ru">Опция для явного поиска с учетом регистра</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Opção para localização explícita que diferencia maiúsculas de minúsculas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Opção para localização explícita que diferencia maiúsculas de minúsculas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Możliwość wyszukiwania z uwzględnieniem wielkości liter</li>
          <li lang="nl">Optie voor hoofdletter gevoelig Zoeken</li>
          <li lang="mr">सुस्पष्ट केस-सेन्सेटिव्ह शोधासाठी पर्याय</li>
          <li lang="ja">大文字と小文字を区別する検索オプションを追加</li>
          <li lang="it">Opzione per la ricerca con distinzione esplicita tra maiuscole e minuscole</li>
          <li lang="he">אפשרות לאיתור תלוי רישיות מפורש</li>
          <li lang="fr">Option pour la recherche sensible à la casse</li>
          <li lang="es">Opción para buscar explícitamente con distinción de mayúsculas y minúsculas</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Option for explicit case-sensitive Find</li>
          <li lang="de">Option für explizite Suche unter Berücksichtigung der Groß-/Kleinschreibung</li>
          <li lang="da">Mulighed for eksplicit versalfølsomhed i Find</li>
          <li lang="cs">Volba pro výslovné rozlišování malých/VELKÝCH písmen při hledání</li>
          <li lang="ckb">بژاردە بۆ دۆزینەوەی هەستیاری کەیسی ڕوون</li>
          <li lang="ca">Opció per a la cerca explícita amb distinció de majúscules</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Other updates:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">其它更新：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Інші оновлення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Diğer güncellemeler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Остала освежења:</p>
        <p lang="sl">Druge posodobitve:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Ďalšie aktualizácie:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Остальные обновления:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Outras atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Outras atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Inne aktualizacje:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Andere updates:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Andre oppdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="mr">इतर अद्यतने:</p>
        <p lang="ja">そのほかのアップデート:</p>
        <p lang="it">Altri aggiornamenti:</p>
        <p lang="he">עדכונים נוספים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Autres mises à jour :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Muut päivitykset:</p>
        <p lang="es">Otras actualizaciones:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Aliaj ĝisdatigoj:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Other updates:</p>
        <p lang="de">weitere Aktualisierungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Andre opdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Ostatní aktualizace:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">نوێکردنەوەکانی تر:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Altres actualitzacions:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Correctly show Toggle Comment menu item when no text is selected</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">当没有选择文本时正确地显示切换注释菜单项</li>
          <li lang="uk">Правильний показ пункту меню «Перемкнути коментар», якщо не вибрано текст</li>
          <li lang="sr">Исправно приказује ставку изборника окидања напомене када није изабран текст</li>
          <li lang="sk">Ak nie je vybraný žiadny text, správne zobraziť položku ponuky Prepnúť komentár</li>
          <li lang="ru">Правильное отображение меню «Закомментировать/Раскомментировать», если текст не выделен</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Exibir corretamente o item de menu Alternar comentário quando nenhum texto for selecionado</li>
          <li lang="pt">Mostrar correctamente o item do menu Alternar comentário quando nenhum texto é selecionado</li>
          <li lang="pl">Poprawnie wyświetlanie menu Za-/Odkomentuj gdy nie zaznaczono żadnego tekstu</li>
          <li lang="nl">Toon het Opmerkingen menu item op correcte wijze als geen tekst geselecteerd is</li>
          <li lang="mr">कोणताही मजकूर निवडला नसताना टॉगल टिप्पणी मेनू आयटम योग्यरित्या दर्शवा</li>
          <li lang="ja">テキストが選択されていない場合にも、メニュー項目"コメントを切り替え"を適切に表示するように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Corretta la visualizzazione della voce di menu "Attiva o disattiva il commento" quando nessun testo è selezionato</li>
          <li lang="he">הצגה נכונה של פריט התפריט החלפת מצב הערה כאשר לא נבחר טקסט כלל</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction de l'affichage de l'élément commenter/décommenter du menu quand aucun texte n'est sélectionné</li>
          <li lang="es">Se muestra correctamente el elemento del menú «Conmutar comentario» cuando no se ha seleccionado texto</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Correctly show Toggle Comment menu item when no text is selected</li>
          <li lang="de">Menüpunkt "Kommentar umschalten" korrekt anzeigen, wenn kein Text ausgewählt ist</li>
          <li lang="da">Korrekt visning af Vis/Skjul-Kommentar menu når ingen tekst er valgt</li>
          <li lang="cs">Správné zobrazování položky nabídky přepnout komentář když není označen žádný text</li>
          <li lang="ckb">بە دروستی پیشاندانی لیستی تۆگڵ کۆمێنت کاتێک هیچ دەقێک دیاری نەکراوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Es mostra correctament al menú la commutació de comentari quan no hi ha text seleccionat.</li>
          <li>Fixed font switch alignment</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">固定对齐字体</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено вирівнювання перемикача шрифтів</li>
          <li lang="sr">Поправљено поравнање пребацивања словног лика</li>
          <li lang="sk">Opravené zarovnanie prepínača typu písma</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлено выравнивание переключателя шрифтов</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Corrigido o alinhamento de fonte</li>
          <li lang="pt">Alinhamento do interruptor da fonte corrigido</li>
          <li lang="pl">Poprawiono wyrównanie zmiany czcionek</li>
          <li lang="nl">Een probleem opgelost met het inspringen bij het wisselen van lettertype</li>
          <li lang="mr">फॉन्ट स्विच संरेखन निश्चित केले</li>
          <li lang="ja">"カスタムフォント"スイッチの配置を修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Risolto il problema con l'allineamento dell'interruttore del tipo di caratteri</li>
          <li lang="he">תוקן יישור מתג הגופנים</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction de l'alignement de la police des boutons</li>
          <li lang="es">Se corrigió la alineación del conmutador de tipos de letra</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fixed font switch alignment</li>
          <li lang="de">Ausrichtung des Schriftartenschalters korrigiert</li>
          <li lang="da">Rettede font skifte justering</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opraveno zarovnání přepínání fontů</li>
          <li lang="ckb">چاککردنی لاگرتنی گۆڕینی فۆنت</li>
          <li lang="ca">Correcció de l'alineament del canvi de lletra</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">翻译更新</li>
          <li lang="uz">Yangilangan tarjimalar</li>
          <li lang="uk">Оновлено переклади</li>
          <li lang="tr">Çeviriler güncellendi</li>
          <li lang="sr">Освежени преводи</li>
          <li lang="sl">Posodobljeni prevodi</li>
          <li lang="sk">Aktualizované preklady</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обновлены переводы</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zaktualizowano tłumaczenia</li>
          <li lang="nl">Bijgewerkte vertalingen</li>
          <li lang="nb">Oppdaterte oversettelser</li>
          <li lang="mr">अद्ययावत अनुवाद</li>
          <li lang="lt">Atnaujinti vertimai</li>
          <li lang="ko">번역 업데이트</li>
          <li lang="ja">翻訳の更新</li>
          <li lang="it">Traduzioni aggiornate</li>
          <li lang="he">עדכוני תרגומים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Traducións actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="fr">Mise à jour des traductions</li>
          <li lang="fi">Päivitetyt käännökset</li>
          <li lang="es">Traducciones actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝisdatigitaj tradukoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="de">Aktualisierte Übersetzungen</li>
          <li lang="da">Opdaterede oversættelser</li>
          <li lang="cs">Aktualizovány překlady</li>
          <li lang="ckb">وەرگێڕانەکان نوێکراونەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Traduccions actualitzades</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2020-02-29" version="3.3.0">
      <description>
        <p>New features:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">新特性：</p>
        <p lang="uz">Yangi imkoniyatlar:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Нові функції:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Yeni özellikler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Нове функције:</p>
        <p lang="sl">Nove zmožnosti:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Nové funkcie:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Новые возможности:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Novas funcionalidades:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Novas funcionalidades:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Nowe funkcje:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Nieuwe functies:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Nye funksjoner:</p>
        <p lang="mr">नवीन वैशिष्ट्य:</p>
        <p lang="ja">新機能:</p>
        <p lang="it">Nuove funzionalità:</p>
        <p lang="he">תכונות חדשות:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Nouvelles fonctionnalités :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Uudet ominaisuudet:</p>
        <p lang="es">Funcionalidades nuevas:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Novaj funkcioj:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">New features:</p>
        <p lang="de">Neue Funktionen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Nye funktioner:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Nové funkce:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">تایبەتمەندییە تازەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Funcions noves:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>New "Close Other Folders" menu item to help clean up your sidebar</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">新建 "关闭其他文件夹" 菜单项，以帮助清理你的工具条</li>
          <li lang="uk">Новий пункт меню «Закрити інші теки», який допоможе очистити бічну панель</li>
          <li lang="sr">Нова ставка изборника „Затвори друге фасцикле“ која помаже чишћењу ваше бочне површи</li>
          <li lang="sl">Nova menijska vrstica "Zapri ostale mape" za pomoč pri čiščenju stranske vrstice</li>
          <li lang="sk">Nová položka ponuky „Zatvoriť ďalšie priečinky“, ktorá vám pomôže vyčistiť bočný panel</li>
          <li lang="ru">Новый пункт меню «Закрыть остальные папки», который поможет очистить боковую панель</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Novo item de menu "Fechar outras pastas" para ajudar a limpar sua barra lateral</li>
          <li lang="pt">Novo item do menu "Fechar outras pastas" para ajudar a limpar a sua barra lateral</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nowe opcja w menu, „Zamknij inne foldery”, przydatna do czyszczenia panelu bocznego</li>
          <li lang="nl">Een nieuw “sluit andere mappen” menu item om te helpen bij het opruimen van de zijbalk</li>
          <li lang="nb">Nytt «Lukk andre mapper»-menyelement for å rydde opp i sidefeltet</li>
          <li lang="mr">आपला साइडबार साफ करण्यास मदत करण्यासाठी नवीन "इतर फोल्डर्स बंद करा" मेनू आयटम</li>
          <li lang="ja">サイドバーを整理できるように、新しいメニュー項目"ほかのフォルダーを閉じる"を追加</li>
          <li lang="it">Nuova voce del menu "Chiudi le altre cartelle" per aiutarti a mantenere in ordine la barra laterale</li>
          <li lang="he">פריט חדש „לסגור תיקיות אחרות” בתפריט כדי לסייע בפינוי סרגל הצד שלך</li>
          <li lang="fr">Nouvelle option « Fermer les autres dossiers » pour aider à nettoyer la barre latérale</li>
          <li lang="es">Nuevo elemento de menú «Cerrar otras carpetas» para ayudar a limpiar su barra lateral</li>
          <li lang="eo">Nova menua elektaĵo "Fermi Aliajn Dosierujojn" helpos malembarasi la flankbreton</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">New "Close Other Folders" menu item to help clean up your sidebar</li>
          <li lang="de">Neuer Menüpunkt "Andere Ordner schließen", um Ihre Seitenleiste übersichtlicher zu gestalten</li>
          <li lang="da">Ny "Luk andre mapper"-menu til at hjælpe med at rydde op i dit sidepanel</li>
          <li lang="cs">Nová položka nabídky „Zavřít ostatní složky“ pro uklízení postranního panelu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">دانەیەکی تر بۆ لیستەکە زیادکراوە بە ناوی "داخستنی بوخچەکانی تر" بۆ ئاسانکاری لە پاککردنەوەی سایدباڕەکەتدا</li>
          <li lang="ca">Nova opció "Tanca altres finestres" al menú per ajudar a netejar la barra lateral</li>
          <li>Save and restore cyclic search setting</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">保存和恢复循环搜索设置</li>
          <li lang="uk">Збереження та відновлення налаштувань циклічного пошуку</li>
          <li lang="sr">Чува и враћа поставке цикличне претраге</li>
          <li lang="sl">Shrani in obnovi nastavitve krožnega iskanja</li>
          <li lang="sk">Ukladanie a obnovovanie nastavenia cyklického vyhľadávania</li>
          <li lang="ru">Сохранение и восстановление параметров циклического поиска</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Salvar e restaurar a configuração de pesquisa cíclica</li>
          <li lang="pt">Guardar e restaurar a definição de pesquisa cíclica</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zapisywanie i przywracanie ustawień cyklicznych wyszukiwań</li>
          <li lang="nl">Bewaar en herstel cyclische zoek instelling</li>
          <li lang="nb">Lagre og gjenopprett syklisk søkeinnstilling</li>
          <li lang="mr">चक्रीय शोध सेटिंग जतन आणि पुनर्संचयित करा</li>
          <li lang="ja">循環検索の設定を保存し復元するように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Salva e ripristina il settaggio di ricerca ciclico</li>
          <li lang="he">שמירה ושחזור של הגדרות חיפוש מעגליות</li>
          <li lang="fr">Sauvegarde et restauration du paramètre de recherche cyclique</li>
          <li lang="es">Se guarda y restaura la configuración de búsqueda cíclica</li>
          <li lang="eo">Savi kaj restaŭri cicklan serĉan agordon</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Save and restore cyclic search setting</li>
          <li lang="de">Speichern und Wiederherstellen der zyklischen Sucheinstellung</li>
          <li lang="da">Gem og gendan cyklisk søgeindstilling</li>
          <li lang="cs">Ukládání a obnovování nastavení cyklického hledání</li>
          <li lang="ckb">پاشەکەوتکردن و گەڕاندنەوەی ڕێکخستنی گەڕانی بازنەیی</li>
          <li lang="ca">Paràmetre de cerca cíclica per desar i restaurar</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Other updates:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">其它更新：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Інші оновлення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Diğer güncellemeler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Остала освежења:</p>
        <p lang="sl">Druge posodobitve:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Ďalšie aktualizácie:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Остальные обновления:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Outras atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Outras atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Inne aktualizacje:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Andere updates:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Andre oppdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="mr">इतर अद्यतने:</p>
        <p lang="ja">そのほかのアップデート:</p>
        <p lang="it">Altri aggiornamenti:</p>
        <p lang="he">עדכונים נוספים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Autres mises à jour :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Muut päivitykset:</p>
        <p lang="es">Otras actualizaciones:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Aliaj ĝisdatigoj:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Other updates:</p>
        <p lang="de">weitere Aktualisierungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Andre opdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Ostatní aktualizace:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">نوێکردنەوەکانی تر:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Altres actualitzacions:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add keyboard shortcuts to menu items</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">为菜单项添加键盘快捷键</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано комбінації клавіш до пунктів меню</li>
          <li lang="tr">Menü öğelerine klavye kısayolları atandı</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додаје пречице тастатуре ставкама изборника</li>
          <li lang="sl">Dodaj bližnjice za tipkovnico v meni</li>
          <li lang="sk">Pridané klávesové skratky k položkám ponuky</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлены сочетания клавиш к пунктам меню</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionar atalhos de teclado aos itens de menu</li>
          <li lang="pt">Adicionar atalhos de teclado aos itens do menu</li>
          <li lang="pl">Dodaj skróty klawiszowe do opcji menu</li>
          <li lang="nl">Toetsenbord sneltoetsen toegevoegd aan menu items</li>
          <li lang="nb">Tillagte tastatursnarveier i menyelementer</li>
          <li lang="mr">मेनू आयटममध्ये कीबोर्ड शॉर्टकट जोडा</li>
          <li lang="ja">メニュー項目にキーボードショートカットを表示するように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunte scorciatoie da tastiera alle voci del menu</li>
          <li lang="he">הוספת קיצור מקלדת לפריטי התפריט</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout des raccourcis claviers aux éléments de menu</li>
          <li lang="es">Se añadieron atajos de teclado a los elementos de menú</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni fulmklavojn al menuaĵoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Add keyboard shortcuts to menu items</li>
          <li lang="de">Hinzufügen von Tastaturkürzeln zu Menüelementen</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj tastaturgenveje til menupunkter</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidány klávesové zkratky k položkám nabídek</li>
          <li lang="ckb">زیادکردنی کورتەڕێ بۆ دانەکانی لیست</li>
          <li lang="ca">Addició de dreceres de teclat als menús</li>
          <li>Make sidebar folder items not selectable</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">使侧边栏文件夹项不可选择</li>
          <li lang="uk">Унеможливлено вибір елементів теки на бічній панелі</li>
          <li lang="sr">Чини да се ставке фасцикле бочне површи не могу изабрати</li>
          <li lang="sl">Mape v stranski vrstici ne morejo biti več izbrane</li>
          <li lang="sk">Možnosť zrušiť označovanie priečinkov v bočnom paneli</li>
          <li lang="ru">Выбор элементов папки на боковой панели были сделаны недоступными для выбора</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Tornar itens da pasta da barra lateral não selecionáveis</li>
          <li lang="pt">Tornar os itens da pasta lateral não selecionáveis</li>
          <li lang="pl">Ustawienie folderów w panelu bocznym jako niezaznaczalne</li>
          <li lang="nl">Maak zijbalk map items niet selecteerbaar</li>
          <li lang="mr">साइडबार फोल्डर आयटम निवडण्यायोग्य नसतात</li>
          <li lang="ja">サイドバーのフォルダー項目を選択できないように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Le cartelle nella barra laterale non possono essere selezionate</li>
          <li lang="he">הפיכת הפריטים בתיקיית סרגל הצד לבלתי ניתנים לבחירה</li>
          <li lang="fr">Les éléments du dossier de la barre latérale ne sont désormais plus sélectionnables</li>
          <li lang="es">Ya no se pueden seleccionar los elementos de carpeta en la barra lateral</li>
          <li lang="eo">Malebligi elekteblecon de doseriaj elementoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Make sidebar folder items not selectable</li>
          <li lang="de">Sidebar-Ordner-Elemente nicht auswählbar machen</li>
          <li lang="da">Gør sidepanelets mappeemner ikke valgbare</li>
          <li lang="cs">Odstranění možnosti výběru položek složky v postranním panelu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">وا لێکردنی دانەکانی بوخچەی سایدباڕ دیاری نەکرێن</li>
          <li lang="ca">Fer que els elements de carpeta de la barra lateral no siguin seleccionables</li>
          <li>Center new windows</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">居中新建的窗口</li>
          <li lang="uk">Центрування нових вікон</li>
          <li lang="sr">Нове прозоре поставља у средиште</li>
          <li lang="sl">Centriraj nova okna</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zarovnávať nové okná na stred</li>
          <li lang="ru">Центрирование новых окон</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Centralizar novas janelas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Centrar novas janelas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Wyśrodkowanie nowych okien</li>
          <li lang="nl">Centreer nieuwe vensters</li>
          <li lang="nb">Sentrering av nye vinduer</li>
          <li lang="mr">नवीन विंडो मध्यभागी ठेवा</li>
          <li lang="ja">新しいウィンドウを画面の中央に表示するように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Centra le nuove finestre</li>
          <li lang="he">מרכוז חלונות חדשים</li>
          <li lang="fr">Les nouvelles fenêtres sont désormais centrées</li>
          <li lang="fi">Keskitä uudet ikkunat</li>
          <li lang="es">Las ventanas nuevas se centran</li>
          <li lang="eo">Centrigi novajn fenestrojn</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Centre new windows</li>
          <li lang="de">Neue Fenster zentrieren</li>
          <li lang="da">Centrer nye vinduer</li>
          <li lang="cs">Nová okna jsou vystřeďována</li>
          <li lang="ckb">سەنتەرکردنی پەنجەرە تازەکان</li>
          <li lang="ca">Finestres noves centrades</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">翻译更新</li>
          <li lang="uz">Yangilangan tarjimalar</li>
          <li lang="uk">Оновлено переклади</li>
          <li lang="tr">Çeviriler güncellendi</li>
          <li lang="sr">Освежени преводи</li>
          <li lang="sl">Posodobljeni prevodi</li>
          <li lang="sk">Aktualizované preklady</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обновлены переводы</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zaktualizowano tłumaczenia</li>
          <li lang="nl">Bijgewerkte vertalingen</li>
          <li lang="nb">Oppdaterte oversettelser</li>
          <li lang="mr">अद्ययावत अनुवाद</li>
          <li lang="lt">Atnaujinti vertimai</li>
          <li lang="ko">번역 업데이트</li>
          <li lang="ja">翻訳の更新</li>
          <li lang="it">Traduzioni aggiornate</li>
          <li lang="he">עדכוני תרגומים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Traducións actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="fr">Mise à jour des traductions</li>
          <li lang="fi">Päivitetyt käännökset</li>
          <li lang="es">Traducciones actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝisdatigitaj tradukoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="de">Aktualisierte Übersetzungen</li>
          <li lang="da">Opdaterede oversættelser</li>
          <li lang="cs">Aktualizovány překlady</li>
          <li lang="ckb">وەرگێڕانەکان نوێکراونەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Traduccions actualitzades</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.2.0" date="2020-01-09">
      <description>
        <p>New features:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">新特性：</p>
        <p lang="uz">Yangi imkoniyatlar:</p>
        <p lang="uk">Нові функції:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Yeni özellikler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Нове функције:</p>
        <p lang="sl">Nove zmožnosti:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Nové funkcie:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Новые возможности:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Novas funcionalidades:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Novas funcionalidades:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Nowe funkcje:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Nieuwe functies:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Nye funksjoner:</p>
        <p lang="mr">नवीन वैशिष्ट्य:</p>
        <p lang="ja">新機能:</p>
        <p lang="it">Nuove funzionalità:</p>
        <p lang="he">תכונות חדשות:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Nouvelles fonctionnalités :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Uudet ominaisuudet:</p>
        <p lang="es">Funcionalidades nuevas:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Novaj funkcioj:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">New features:</p>
        <p lang="de">Neue Funktionen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Nye funktioner:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Nové funkce:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">تایبەتمەندییە تازەکان:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Funcions noves:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Visually deprioritize .gitignored files in project sidebar</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">优先可视化侧边栏中的 .gitignored 文件</li>
          <li lang="uk">Візуально знецінено .gitignored у файлах на бічній панелі проєкту</li>
          <li lang="sr">Видно поништава хитност „.gitignored“ датотека у бочној траци пројекта</li>
          <li lang="sl">Manjša vidna prednost za .gitignore datoteke v projektni stranski vrstici</li>
          <li lang="sk">Vizuálne znížená priorita súborov .gitignore v bočnom paneli projektu</li>
          <li lang="ru">Визуально обесценены .gitignored файлы на боковой панели проекта</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Despriorizar visualmente os arquivos .gitignored na barra lateral do projeto</li>
          <li lang="pt">Ignora visualmente ficheiros .gitignorados na barra lateral do projeto</li>
          <li lang="pl">Wizualnie oznacz pliki z .gigitnore jako mniej istotne w panelu bocznym</li>
          <li lang="nl">Maak .gitignored bestanden visueel minder belangrijk in de projecten balk</li>
          <li lang="mr">प्रोजेक्ट साइडबारमधील .gitignored फायली दृश्यमानपणे वंचित करा</li>
          <li lang="ja">.gitignore ファイルに記述されたファイルの名前をプロジェクトサイドバーに薄く表示するように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Mette in secondo piano tutti i files presenti nel file .gitignored nella barra laterale del progetto</li>
          <li lang="he">להוריד את העדיפות של קבצים ב־‎.gitignored בסרגל הצד של המיזם</li>
          <li lang="fr">Dé-prioriser visuellement dans la barre latérale les fichiers .gitignorés</li>
          <li lang="es">Se desenfatizan los archivos en .gitignore en la barra lateral del proyecto</li>
          <li lang="eo">Vide malprioritatigi .gitignored-dosierojn ĉe la projekta flankobreto</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Visually deprioritise .gitignored files in project sidebar</li>
          <li lang="de">Visuelle Depriorisierung von .gitignored Dateien in der Projekt-Sidebar</li>
          <li lang="da">Afprioriter visuelt .gitignored filer i projektets sidepanelet</li>
          <li lang="cs">Vizuálně snížena priorita souborů, označených v .gitignore v postranním panelu projektu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">بە شێوەیەکی بینراو پەڕگە .gitignoredەکان پاشبخە لە سایدباڕی پرۆژە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Despriorització visual de fitxers .gitignored a la barra lateral del projecte</li>
          <li>Smart cut/copy lines with no active selection</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">智能剪切/复制行</li>
          <li lang="uk">Розумні лінії вирізання/копіювання без активного виділення</li>
          <li lang="sr">Паметни исеци/умножи редови без активног избора</li>
          <li lang="sl">Pameten izrez in kopiranje vrstic brez aktivne izbire</li>
          <li lang="sk">Inteligentné vystrihovanie/kopírovanie riadkov bez aktívneho výberu</li>
          <li lang="ru">Умные линии вырезания/копирования без активного выделения</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Linhas inteligentes de corte/cópia sem seleção ativa</li>
          <li lang="pt">Forma inteligente de cortar/copiar linhas sem seleção</li>
          <li lang="pl">Inteligentne wycinanie/kopiowanie linii bez aktywnego zaznaczenia</li>
          <li lang="nl">Slimme knip/kopieer functie zonder selectie van tekst</li>
          <li lang="mr">कोणत्याही सक्रिय निवडीशिवाय ओळी स्मार्ट कट / कॉपी करा</li>
          <li lang="ja">行を選択していなくても切り取り／コピーできるように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Taglia/copia linee intelligente senza selezione attiva</li>
          <li lang="he">גזירה/העתקה חכמה של שורות ללא בחירה פעילה</li>
          <li lang="fr">Copier/coller intelligent sans sélection</li>
          <li lang="es">Cortado/copiado inteligente de renglones sin ninguna selección activa</li>
          <li lang="eo">Inteligenta tondo/kopio sen aktiva elektaĵo</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Smart cut/copy lines with no active selection</li>
          <li lang="de">Intelligentes Ausschneiden/Kopieren von Zeilen ohne aktive Auswahl</li>
          <li lang="da">Smart klip / kopier linjer uden aktivt valg</li>
          <li lang="cs">Inteligentní vyjímání/kopírování řádků bez aktivního výběru</li>
          <li lang="ckb">کۆپی/کەتی زیرەک بەبێ دیارکردنی چالاک</li>
          <li lang="ca">Línies de retall / còpia intel·ligents sense selecció activa</li>
          <li>Add a confirmation dialog to the "Restore" action</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">为“恢复”操作添加一个确认对话框</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано діалогове вікно підтвердження дії «Відновити»</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додаје прозорче потврђивања радњи враћања</li>
          <li lang="sl">Dodaj potrditveni dialog za "Obnovi" akcijo</li>
          <li lang="sk">Pridaný potvrdzovací dialóg do akcie „Obnoviť“</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлено диалоговое окно для подтверждения действия «Восстановить»</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicione um diálogo de confirmação à ação "Restaurar"</li>
          <li lang="pt">Adicionar uma mensagem de confirmação à ação "Restaurar"</li>
          <li lang="pl">Dodaj okno potwierdzenia dla akcji „Przywróć”</li>
          <li lang="nl">Er wordt nu bevestiging gevraagd bij het herstellen van bestanden</li>
          <li lang="mr">"पुनर्संचयित" क्रियेमध्ये पुष्टीकरण संवाद जोडा</li>
          <li lang="ja">"復元"アクションの実行時に確認ダイアログを表示するように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunge una finestra di conferma all'azione "Ripristina"</li>
          <li lang="he">הוספת דו־שיח אישור לפעולה „שחזור”</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout d'une boîte de configuration pour l'action de restauration</li>
          <li lang="es">Se añadió un diálogo de confirmación a la acción «Restaurar»</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni konfirman dialogon al ago „Restaŭri“</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Add a confirmation dialog to the "Restore" action</li>
          <li lang="de">Bestätigungsdialog für die "Zurücksetzen"-Funktion</li>
          <li lang="da">Føj en bekræftelsesdialog til "Gendan" -handlingen</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána potvrzovací dialog do akce „Obnovit“</li>
          <li lang="ckb">زیادکردنی دایەلۆگی دڵنیابوونەوە بۆ کرداری "گەڕاندنەوە"</li>
          <li lang="ca">Addició d'un diàleg de confirmació a l’acció "Restaura"</li>
          <li>Add "Open In" menu to the top-level folder in the folder manager</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">在文件夹管理器的根文件夹中添加“打开”菜单</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано меню «Відкрити у» до теки верхнього рівня в менеджері тек</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додаје изборник „Отвори у“ у фасциклу највишег нивоа у управнику фасцикли</li>
          <li lang="sl">V glavni meni upravitelja map dodan "Odpri v"</li>
          <li lang="sk">Pridaná ponuka „Otvoriť v“ do priečinka najvyššej úrovne v správcovi priečinkov</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлено меню «Открыть в» для папки верхнего уровня в менеджере папок</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionado menu "Abrir em" na pasta raiz no gerenciador de pastas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Adicionar o menu "Abrir em" à pasta de nível superior no gestor de pastas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Dodanie menu „Otwórz w” do najwyższego folderu w menedżerze folderów</li>
          <li lang="nl">Een “openen in” menu is toegevoegd aan het mappen beheerscherm</li>
          <li lang="mr">फोल्डर व्यवस्थापकात उच्च स्तरीय फोल्डरमध्ये "ओपन इन" मेनू जोडा</li>
          <li lang="ja">フォルダーマネージャーで最上位のフォルダーに"指定した方法で開く"メニューを追加</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunge il menu "Apri in" alla cartella di primo livello nel gestore delle cartelle</li>
          <li lang="he">הוספת תפריט „פתיחה עם” לתיקייה העליונה במנהל התיקיות</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout du menu « Ouvrir dans » au niveau supérieur du dossier dans le gestionnaire de dossiers</li>
          <li lang="es">Se añadió el menú «Abrir en» a la carpeta de nivel superior en el gestor de carpetas</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni „Malfermi per“-menuon al la plej supra dosiera nivelo de la dosiermastrumilo</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Add "Open In" menu to the top-level folder in the folder manager</li>
          <li lang="de">"Öffnen in"-Menü zum obersten Ordner im Ordnermanager hinzugefügt</li>
          <li lang="da">Føj "Åbn i" -menuen til øverste mappe i mappeadministratoren</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána nabídka „Otevřít v“ ve složce nejvyšší úrovně ve správě složek</li>
          <li lang="ckb">زیادکردنی لیستی "کردنەوە لە" بۆ ئاستی بەرزی بوخچە لە بەڕێوەبەری بوخچەدا</li>
          <li lang="ca">Addició del menú "Obrir a" a la carpeta de primer nivell del gestor de carpetes</li>
          <li>Don't show temporary files in the folder manager</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">不要在文件夹管理器中显示临时文件</li>
          <li lang="uk">Не показувати тимчасові файли в менеджері тек</li>
          <li lang="tr">Geçici dosyaları dizin yöneticisinde gösterme</li>
          <li lang="sr">Не приказује привремене датотеке у управнику фасцикли</li>
          <li lang="sl">Ne pokaži začasnih datotek v upravitelju map</li>
          <li lang="sk">Nezobrazovať dočasné súbory v správcovi súborov</li>
          <li lang="ru">Не отображать временные файлы в менеджере папок</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Não mostrar arquivos temporários no gerenciador de pastas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Não mostrar ficheiros temporários no gestor de pastas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nie pokazuj plików tymczasowych w menedżerze folderów</li>
          <li lang="nl">Verberg tijdelijke bestanden in het mappen beheerscherm</li>
          <li lang="mr">फोल्डर व्यवस्थापकात तात्पुरत्या फाइल्स दाखवू नका</li>
          <li lang="ja">フォルダーマネージャーで一時ファイルを表示しないように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Non mostrare i file temporanei nel gestore delle cartelle</li>
          <li lang="he">לא יוצגו קבצים זמניים במנהל התיקיות</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ne pas afficher de fichiers temporaires dans le gestionnaire de dossiers</li>
          <li lang="es">No se muestran los archivos temporales en el gestor de carpetas</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ne montri portempajn dosierojn en la dosiermastrumilo</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Don't show temporary files in the folder manager</li>
          <li lang="de">Temporäre Dateien im Ordnermanager nicht mehr anzeigen</li>
          <li lang="da">Vis ikke midlertidige filer i mappeadministratoren</li>
          <li lang="cs">Nezobrazování dočasných souborů ve správě složek</li>
          <li lang="ckb">پەڕگە کاتییەکان پشان مەدە لە بەڕێوەبەری بوخچەدا</li>
          <li lang="ca">No es mostren els fitxers temporals al gestor de carpetes</li>
          <li>Add brackets completion and auto-indent by default</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">默认情况下添加括号补全和自动缩进</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано типові завершення дужок та автоматичний відступ</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додаје допуњавање заграда и самоувлачење по основи</li>
          <li lang="sl">Dodaj zaključevanje oklepajev in samodejno zamikanje kot privzeto</li>
          <li lang="sk">Pridaná predvolene zapnutá funkcia doplňovania zátvoriek a automatického odsadzovania</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлены типичные завершения скобок и автоматический отступ</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionado indentação e completação de parênteses automáticos por padrão</li>
          <li lang="pt">Adiciona parênteses de conclusão e recuo automático por predefinição</li>
          <li lang="pl">Domyślne dodanie kończenia nawiasów i automatycznych wcięć</li>
          <li lang="nl">Het automatisch aanvullen van haakjes en automatisch inspringen zijn standaard ingeschakeld</li>
          <li lang="mr">डीफॉल्टनुसार कंस पूर्ण आणि ऑटो-इंडेंट जोडा</li>
          <li lang="ja">閉じカッコの補完と自動インデント機能をデフォルトで有効化</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunge il completamento delle parentesi e il rientro automatico per impostazione predefinita</li>
          <li lang="he">הוספת השלמת סוגריים והזחה אוטומטית כבררת מחדל</li>
          <li lang="fr">Activation par défaut de la complétion des accolades et de l'indentation automatique</li>
          <li lang="es">Se añadió compleción de paréntesis y se activó de manera predeterminada la sangría automática</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni apriorajn krampan plenigon kaj aŭtomatan marĝenigon</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Add brackets completion and auto-indent by default</li>
          <li lang="de">Klammervervollständigung und automatische Einrückung standardmäßig hinzufügen</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj komplettering af parenteser og automatisk indrykket som standard</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidání doplňování závorek a automatického odsazování ve výchozím stavu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">کاراکردنی تەواوکردنی کەوانە و زیادکردنی بۆشایی سەرەتای دێر بە شێوەیەکی خۆکارانە بە شێوەیەکی سەرەکی</li>
          <li lang="ca">Addició dels parèntesis d’acabament i sagnat automàtic de manera predeterminada</li>
          <li>Zoom terminal plugin with keyboard</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">使用键盘缩放终端插件</li>
          <li lang="uk">Плагін масштабування терміналу за допомогою клавіатури</li>
          <li lang="sr">Зумира прикључак терминала тастатуром</li>
          <li lang="sl">Spreminjanje velikosti terminala s tipkovnico</li>
          <li lang="sk">Približovanie a oddiaľovanie pomocou klávesnice v zásuvnom module terminálu</li>
          <li lang="ru">Плагин масштабирования терминала с помощью клавиатуры</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Zoom plugin de terminal com teclado</li>
          <li lang="pt">Plugin de terminal de zoom com teclado</li>
          <li lang="pl">Wtyczka terminala Zoom z klawiaturą</li>
          <li lang="nl">Zoom terminal plug-in met toetsenbord</li>
          <li lang="mr">कीबोर्ड वापरून टर्मिनल प्लगइन झूम करा</li>
          <li lang="ja">ターミナルプラグインをキーボードで拡大・縮小できるように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Zoom del plugin Terminale con la tastiera</li>
          <li lang="he">תוסף התמקדות במסוף עם מקלדת</li>
          <li lang="fr">Plugin de zoom du terminal avec le clavier</li>
          <li lang="es">Es posible ampliar y reducir el complemento de la terminal con el teclado</li>
          <li lang="eo">Kromprogramo por terminala zomo  per klavaro</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Zoom terminal plugin with keyboard</li>
          <li lang="de">Terminal-Plugin mit Tastatur vergrößern</li>
          <li lang="da">Zoom terminal plugin med tastatur</li>
          <li lang="cs">Změna velikost zásuvného modulu terminálu pomocí klávesnice</li>
          <li lang="ckb">زومکردنی پێوەکراوی تێرمیناڵ بە تەختەکلیل</li>
          <li lang="ca">Ampliació del connector del terminal amb teclat</li>
          <li>Honor global privacy setting when saving and restoring</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">保存与恢复遵从全局隐私设置</li>
          <li lang="uk">Підпорядкування загальним налаштуванням приватності під час збереження та відновлення</li>
          <li lang="sr">Поштује опште подешавање приватности приликом чувања и враћања</li>
          <li lang="sl">Spoštuj globalne nastavitve zasebnosti pri shranjevanju in obnovitvi</li>
          <li lang="sk">Rešpektovať globálne nastavenie ochrany súkromia pri ukladaní a obnovovaní</li>
          <li lang="ru">Соблюдение глобальных настроек конфиденциальности при сохранении и восстановлении</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Respeita a configuração de privacidade global ao salvar e restaurar</li>
          <li lang="pt">Honra a definição global de privacidade ao guardar e restaurar</li>
          <li lang="pl">Respektowanie globalnych ustawień prywatności podczas zapisywania i przywracania</li>
          <li lang="nl">Houd rekening met de algemene privacy instelling bij het opslaan en herstellen</li>
          <li lang="mr">जतन आणि पुनर्संचयित करताना जागतिक गोपनीयता सेटिंगचा सन्मान करा</li>
          <li lang="ja">保存・復元時にシステムのプライバシー設定を反映するように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Rispetta l'impostazione della privacy globale durante il salvataggio e il ripristino</li>
          <li lang="he">כיבוד הגדרות פרטיות גלובליות בעת שמירה ושחזור</li>
          <li lang="fr">Respect des paramètres de confidentialité généraux lors de la sauvegarde et de la restauration</li>
          <li lang="es">Se acata la configuración global de privacidad al guardar y restaurar</li>
          <li lang="eo">Respekti ĝeneralajn privatecajn agordojn dum savo kaj restaŭro</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Honour global privacy setting when saving and restoring</li>
          <li lang="de">Die globalen Datenschutzeinstellungen beim Speichern und Wiederherstellen beachten</li>
          <li lang="da">Overhold global indstilling for privatlivets fred, når du gemmer og gendanner</li>
          <li lang="cs">Respektování globálního nastavení ochrany soukromí při ukládání a obnovování</li>
          <li lang="ckb">ڕێزگرتن لە ڕێکخستنەکانی تایبەتمەندی جیهانی لەکاتی پاشەکەوتکردن و گەڕاندنەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Es satisfà la privacitat global quan es desa i es restaura.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Other updates:</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">其它更新：</p>
        <p lang="uk">Інші оновлення:</p>
        <p lang="tr">Diğer güncellemeler:</p>
        <p lang="sr">Остала освежења:</p>
        <p lang="sl">Druge posodobitve:</p>
        <p lang="sk">Ďalšie aktualizácie:</p>
        <p lang="ru">Остальные обновления:</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Outras atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pt">Outras atualizações:</p>
        <p lang="pl">Inne aktualizacje:</p>
        <p lang="nl">Andere updates:</p>
        <p lang="nb">Andre oppdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="mr">इतर अद्यतने:</p>
        <p lang="ja">そのほかのアップデート:</p>
        <p lang="it">Altri aggiornamenti:</p>
        <p lang="he">עדכונים נוספים:</p>
        <p lang="fr">Autres mises à jour :</p>
        <p lang="fi">Muut päivitykset:</p>
        <p lang="es">Otras actualizaciones:</p>
        <p lang="eo">Aliaj ĝisdatigoj:</p>
        <p lang="en_GB">Other updates:</p>
        <p lang="de">weitere Aktualisierungen:</p>
        <p lang="da">Andre opdateringer:</p>
        <p lang="cs">Ostatní aktualizace:</p>
        <p lang="ckb">نوێکردنەوەکانی تر:</p>
        <p lang="ca">Altres actualitzacions:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Simplify "Draw spaces" preference</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">简化“绘制空间”首选项</li>
          <li lang="uk">Спрощено налаштування «Малювати пробіли»</li>
          <li lang="sr">Поједностављује поставке исцртавања размака</li>
          <li lang="sl">Poenostavitev nastavitve za prikaz presledkov</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zjednodušenie predvoľby „Vykresľovať medzery“</li>
          <li lang="ru">Упрощена настройка «Рисовать пробелы»</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Simplificar a configuração de "Desenhar espaços"</li>
          <li lang="pt">Simplifica a preferência "Desenhar espaços"</li>
          <li lang="pl">Uproszczenie preferencji "Rysuj spacje"</li>
          <li lang="nl">De “teken ruimte” instelling is simpeler geworden</li>
          <li lang="mr">"स्पेस ड्रॉ करा" प्राधान्य सुलभ करा</li>
          <li lang="ja">"空白を表示"設定を簡易化</li>
          <li lang="it">Semplifica la preferenza "Mostra gli spazi"</li>
          <li lang="he">פישוט ההעדפה „ציור רווחים”</li>
          <li lang="fr">Simplification du paramètre « Afficher les espaces »</li>
          <li lang="es">Se simplificó la preferencia «Hacer espacios visibles»</li>
          <li lang="eo">Simpligi agordon de „Afiŝo de spacoj“</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Simplify "Draw spaces" preference</li>
          <li lang="de">Einstellung "Leerzeichen erzeugen" vereinfacht</li>
          <li lang="da">Forenkl præference for "Draw space"</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zjednodušení předvolby „Vykreslovat mezery“</li>
          <li lang="ckb">سادەکردنی ڕێکخستنی "Draw spaces"</li>
          <li lang="ca">Simplificació de la preferència "Dibuixa espais"</li>
          <li>Fix the keyboard shortcut for going backwards in search results</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">修复了在搜索结果中后退的键盘快捷键问题</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено комбінацію клавіш для повернення назад у результатах пошуку</li>
          <li lang="sr">Поправља пречицу тастатуре за кретање уназад у резултатима претраге</li>
          <li lang="sl">Popravi tipkovnično bližnjico za vrnitev na prejšnji iskalni rezultat</li>
          <li lang="sk">Opravená klávesová skratka pre posun späť vo výsledkoch vyhľadávania</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлено сочетание клавиш для перехода назад в результатах поиска</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Corrigido o atalho de teclado para voltar nos resultados de busca</li>
          <li lang="pt">Corrigir o atalho do teclado para ir atrás nos resultados da pesquisa</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawienie skrótu klawiszowego dla cofania się w rezultatach wyszukiwania</li>
          <li lang="nl">Een probleem met de sneltoets om terug te gaan in zoekresultaten is verholpen</li>
          <li lang="mr">शोध परिणामांमध्ये मागे जाण्यासाठी कीबोर्ड शॉर्टकट निश्चित करा</li>
          <li lang="ja">前の検索結果を表示するキーボードショートカットを修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Corretta la scorciatoia da tastiera per tornare indietro nei risultati di ricerca</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון קיצור המקלדת לחזרה אחורה בתוצאות החיפוש</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction du raccourci clavier pour revenir en arrière dans les résultats de recherche</li>
          <li lang="es">Corrección del atajo de teclado para retroceder en los resultados de búsqueda</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ripari la fulmklavon por retroiri inter serĉaj rezultatoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix the keyboard shortcut for going backwards in search results</li>
          <li lang="de">Die Tastenkombination für den Rückwärtslauf in den Suchergebnissen wurde korrigiert</li>
          <li lang="da">Ret tastaturgenvejen for at gå baglæns i søgeresultaterne</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opravena klávesová zkrátka pro hledání směrem zpět</li>
          <li lang="ckb">چارەسەکردنی کورتەڕێی تەختەکلیل بۆ گەڕانەوە بۆ دواوە لە ئەنجامەکانی گەڕاندا</li>
          <li lang="ca">Correcció de la drecera del teclat per tornar enrere en els resultats de la cerca</li>
          <li>Fix opening files from relative paths in Terminal</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">修复了终端中从对应路径打开文件的问题</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено відкриття файлів із відносних шляхів у Терміналі</li>
          <li lang="sr">Поправља отварање датотека из односних путања у терминалу</li>
          <li lang="sl">Popravljeno odpiranje datotek z relativnimi potmi iz terminala</li>
          <li lang="sk">Opravené otváranie súborov z relatívnych popisov umiestnenia v Terminále</li>
          <li lang="ru">Зафиксировать открытие файлов из относящихся путей в Терминале</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Corrigido o abrimento de arquivos de caminhos relativos no Terminal</li>
          <li lang="pt">Corrige os ficheiros abertos a partir dos mesmos caminhos no Terminal</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawiono otwieranie plików z względnymi ścieżkami w Terminalu</li>
          <li lang="nl">Een probleem met het openen van bestanden via relatieve paden in Terminal is verholpen</li>
          <li lang="mr">टर्मिनलमधील सापेक्ष मार्गांमधून फायली उघडण्याशी संबंधित समस्यांचे निराकरण करा</li>
          <li lang="ja">ターミナルから相対パスを使用してファイルを開く際の不具合を修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Risolta l'apertura di file da percorsi relativi nel Terminale</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון פתיחת קבצים מנתיבים יחסיים במסוף</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction de l'ouverture de fichiers à partir de chemins relatifs dans Terminal</li>
          <li lang="es">Apertura correcta de archivos con rutas relativas en la terminal</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ripari malfermon de dosieroj el relativaj indikoj en la Terminalo</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix opening files from relative paths in Terminal</li>
          <li lang="de">Korrektur beim Öffnen von Dateien aus relativen Pfaden im Terminal</li>
          <li lang="da">Ret åbning af filer fra relative stier i Terminal</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opraveno otevírání souborů z relativních popisů umístění v Terminálu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">چاککردنی کردنەوەی پەڕگەکان لە شوێنەکانیانەوە لە تێرمیناڵەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Correcció de l'obertura de fitxes des dels camins relatius al Terminal</li>
          <li>Fix null file dialog when opening a new window via the dock</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">修复通过程序坞打开新窗口时空文件对话框的问题</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено діалогове вікно файлу під час відкриття нового вікна через док</li>
          <li lang="sr">Поправља ништавно прозорче датотеке када отвара нови прозор путем луке</li>
          <li lang="sl">Popravljen prazen dialog, ko se odpre novo okno preko sidrišča</li>
          <li lang="sk">Opravený prázdny dialóg súboru pri otváraní nového okna z doku</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлено неработающее диалоговое окно файла при открытии нового окна в доке</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Corrigido dialogo de arquivo nulo quando abrindo uma nova janela pela doca</li>
          <li lang="pt">Corrige a mensagem de ficheiro nulo ao abrir uma nova janela através da doca</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawiono okno pliku null przy otwieraniu nowego okna przez dok</li>
          <li lang="nl">Een probleem met het Bestanden scherm bij het openen van een nieuw venster via het dock is verholpen</li>
          <li lang="mr">डॉकद्वारे नवीन विंडो उघडताना नल फाइल संवाद निश्चित करा</li>
          <li lang="ja">ドックのコンテキストメニューから新しいウィンドウを開いた際に「ファイル (null) を開けません」というダイアログが表示される不具合を修正</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון דו־שיח קבצים ריקים בעת פתיחת חלון חדש דרך המעגן</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction de la boîte de dialogue de fichier vide lors de l'ouverture d'une nouvelle fenêtre via le dock</li>
          <li lang="es">Se solucionó el mensaje de archivo vacío cuando se abre una nueva ventana por medio del dock</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ripari malplenan dialogon ĉe malfermo de nova fenestro per la butonbreto</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix null file dialog when opening a new window via the dock</li>
          <li lang="de">Korrektur des Nulldatei-Dialogs beim Öffnen eines neuen Fensters über das Dock</li>
          <li lang="da">Ret dialogboksen null file, når du åbner et nyt vindue via dokken</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opraven prázdný dialog souboru při otevírání nového okna z doku</li>
          <li lang="ckb">چاککردنی دایەلۆگی پەڕگەی نەڵ لە کاتی کردنەوەی پەنجەرەیەکی تازە لە دۆکەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Correcció del diàleg de fitxer nul quan s'obre una finestra nova a través de l'acoblador</li>
          <li>Add "=" as a zoom key</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加 "=" 键作为缩放键</li>
          <li lang="uk">«=» додано до клавіш масштабування</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додаје = као тастер увеличања</li>
          <li lang="sl">Dodana tipka "=" za povečavo</li>
          <li lang="sk">Pridané „=“ ako kláves pre priblíženie</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлен «=» в качестве клавиши масштабирования</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionado "=" como uma tecla de ampliação</li>
          <li lang="pt">Adicionar "=" como uma tecla de zoom</li>
          <li lang="pl">Dodano "=" jako przycisk przybliżania</li>
          <li lang="nl">De toets "=" kan nu worden gebruikt om te zoemen</li>
          <li lang="mr">झूम की म्हणून "=" जोडा</li>
          <li lang="ja">拡大に使用するキーボードショートカットに "=" を追加</li>
          <li lang="he">הוספת „=” כמקש תקריב</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout de « = » comme raccourci de zoom</li>
          <li lang="es">Se añadió «=» como tecla de escala</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni zoman „=“-klavon</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Add "=" as a zoom key</li>
          <li lang="de">Hinzufügen von "=" als zusätzliche Zoomtaste</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj "=" som forstørrelses tast</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidáno „=“ jako klávesa pro přiblížení</li>
          <li lang="ckb">زیادکردنی "=" وەکو کلیلی زووم کردن</li>
          <li lang="ca">Addició de "=" com a tecla de zoom</li>
          <li>Change search entry icon when results aren't found</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">当没有找到结果时，更改搜索条目图标</li>
          <li lang="uk">Змінено піктограму поля пошуку, коли результатів не знайдено</li>
          <li lang="sr">Мења иконицу уноса претраге када не нађе резултате</li>
          <li lang="sl">Sprememba ikone za iskanje, ko rezultat ni najden</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zmeniť ikonu políčka vyhľadávania, keď nie sú nájdené výsledky</li>
          <li lang="ru">Изменен значок поля поиска, когда результаты не найдены</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Altera o ícone da barra de pesquisa quando nenhum resultado for encontrado</li>
          <li lang="pt">Alterar o ícone de pesquisa quando os resultados não são encontrados</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zmieniono ikonę wyszukiwania gdy nie znaleziono żadnych wyników</li>
          <li lang="nl">Het zoek invoer icoon verandert als er geen resultaten zijn gevonden</li>
          <li lang="mr">परिणाम आढळले नाहीत तेव्हा शोध प्रविष्टी चिन्ह बदला</li>
          <li lang="ja">検索結果が見つからなかった場合に検索欄のアイコンを変更するように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Cambia l'icona della voce di ricerca quando i risultati non vengono trovati</li>
          <li lang="he">סמל רשומת החיפוש מוחלף כאשר לא נמצאות תוצאות</li>
          <li lang="fr">Modification de l'icône du champ de recherche quand aucun résultat n'est trouvé</li>
          <li lang="es">El icono del cuadro de búsqueda cambia cuando no se encuentran resultados</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ŝanĝi serĉo-enigan bildeton kaze de nenia trovo</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Change search entry icon when results aren't found</li>
          <li lang="de">Sucheingabe-Symbol wird verändert, wenn keine Ergebnisse gefunden werden</li>
          <li lang="da">Skift ikonet for søgning, når resultater ikke findes</li>
          <li lang="cs">Změna ikony zadávání vyhledávání když nejsou nalezeny výsledky</li>
          <li lang="ckb">گۆڕینی ئایکۆنی سێرچ کاتێک ئەنجامەکان نەدۆزرانەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Canvi de la icona d’entrada de cerca quan no es troben resultats</li>
          <li>Enter name of new file before creating it</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">在创建新文件之前输入文件名</li>
          <li lang="uk">Введення назви нового файлу до його створення</li>
          <li lang="sr">Уноси назив нове датотеке пре њеног стварања</li>
          <li lang="sl">Vnos imena nove datoteke preden je ustvarjena</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zadanie názvu nového súboru pred jeho vytvorením</li>
          <li lang="ru">Введение имени нового файла перед тем, как создавать его</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Digite o nome do novo arquivo antes de criá-lo</li>
          <li lang="pt">Introduza o nome do novo ficheiro antes de o criar</li>
          <li lang="pl">Nowym plikom będą teraz nadawane nazwy przed ich utworzeniem</li>
          <li lang="nl">Voer de naam in van een nieuw bestand voordat het gecreëerd wordt</li>
          <li lang="mr">नवीन फाईल तयार करण्यापूर्वी तिचे नाव प्रविष्ट करा</li>
          <li lang="ja">新しいファイルの名前をファイルの作成前に入力できるように修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Immettere il nome del nuovo file prima di crearlo</li>
          <li lang="he">הקלדת שם של קובץ חדש בטרם יצירתו</li>
          <li lang="fr">Entrez le nom d'un nouveau fichier avant de le créer</li>
          <li lang="es">Puede introducir el nombre del archivo nuevo antes de crearlo</li>
          <li lang="eo">Enigi nomon de nova dosiero antaŭ kreado</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Enter name of new file before creating it</li>
          <li lang="de">Den Namen einer neuen Datei vor dem Erstellen eingeben</li>
          <li lang="da">Indtast navnet på en ny fil før den oprettes</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zadání názvu souboru před jeho vytvářením</li>
          <li lang="ckb">نووسینی ناوی پەڕگە پێش دروستکردنی</li>
          <li lang="ca">S'introdueix el nom del fitxer nou abans de crear-lo.</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">翻译更新</li>
          <li lang="uz">Yangilangan tarjimalar</li>
          <li lang="uk">Оновлено переклади</li>
          <li lang="tr">Çeviriler güncellendi</li>
          <li lang="sr">Освежени преводи</li>
          <li lang="sl">Posodobljeni prevodi</li>
          <li lang="sk">Aktualizované preklady</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обновлены переводы</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zaktualizowano tłumaczenia</li>
          <li lang="nl">Bijgewerkte vertalingen</li>
          <li lang="nb">Oppdaterte oversettelser</li>
          <li lang="mr">अद्ययावत अनुवाद</li>
          <li lang="lt">Atnaujinti vertimai</li>
          <li lang="ko">번역 업데이트</li>
          <li lang="ja">翻訳の更新</li>
          <li lang="it">Traduzioni aggiornate</li>
          <li lang="he">עדכוני תרגומים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Traducións actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="fr">Mise à jour des traductions</li>
          <li lang="fi">Päivitetyt käännökset</li>
          <li lang="es">Traducciones actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝisdatigitaj tradukoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="de">Aktualisierte Übersetzungen</li>
          <li lang="da">Opdaterede oversættelser</li>
          <li lang="cs">Aktualizovány překlady</li>
          <li lang="ckb">وەرگێڕانەکان نوێکراونەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Traduccions actualitzades</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.1.1" date="2019-03-06">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Use Granite.MessageDialog throughout</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">始终使用 Granite.MessageDialog 对话框</li>
          <li lang="uk">Повсюдне використання Granite.MessageDialog</li>
          <li lang="sr">Користи „Granite.MessageDialog“ пролаз</li>
          <li lang="sl">Granite.MessageDialog uporabljen vsepovsod</li>
          <li lang="sk">Všade používať Granite.MessageDialog</li>
          <li lang="ru">Повсеместное использование Granite.MessageDialog</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Utilizar Granite.MessageDialog inteiramente</li>
          <li lang="pt">Use Granite.MessageDialog ao longo</li>
          <li lang="pl">Użyto wszędzie Granite.MessageDialog</li>
          <li lang="nl">Granite.MessageDialog wordt nu overal gebruikt</li>
          <li lang="nb">Bruk Granite.MessageDialog hele tiden</li>
          <li lang="mr">Granite.MessageDialog संपूर्ण वापरा</li>
          <li lang="lt">Naudoti visur Granite.MessageDialog</li>
          <li lang="ko">Granite.MessageDialog 전체 사용</li>
          <li lang="ja">一貫的な Granite.MessageDialog の利用</li>
          <li lang="it">Usa Granite.MessageDialog dappertutto</li>
          <li lang="hu">Használja a Granite.MessageDialogot mindenhol</li>
          <li lang="he">להשתמש ב־Granite.MessageDialog בכל מקום שנדרש</li>
          <li lang="gl">Use Granite.MessageDialog durante</li>
          <li lang="fr">Utilisation de Granite.MessageDialog</li>
          <li lang="es">Uso exhaustivo de Granite.MessageDialog</li>
          <li lang="eo">Uzi entute Granite.MessageDialog</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Use Granite.MessageDialog throughout</li>
          <li lang="de">Verwendet Granite.MessageDialog durchgängig</li>
          <li lang="da">Brug Granite.MessageDialog over det hele</li>
          <li lang="cs">Použití Granite.MessageDialog po celou dobu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">بەکارهێنانی Granite.MessageDialog</li>
          <li lang="ca">Ús complet de Granite.MessageDialog</li>
          <li>Include non-text files in sidebar</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">在侧边栏中包含非文本文件</li>
          <li lang="uk">Включено не текстові файли на бічну панель</li>
          <li lang="sr">Укључује нетекстуалне датотеке у бочној површи</li>
          <li lang="sl">Prikaži ne-besedilne datoteke v stranski vrstici</li>
          <li lang="sk">Zahrnúť súbory s iným ako textovým obsahom v bočnom paneli</li>
          <li lang="ru">Включены не текстовые файлы на боковую панель</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Incluir arquivos que não são de texto na barra lateral</li>
          <li lang="pt">Incluir ficheiros que não são de texto na barra lateral</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zawarto pliki nietekstowe w panelu bocznym</li>
          <li lang="nl">Ook niet tekstbestanden worden toegevoegd aan de zijbalk</li>
          <li lang="mr">साइडबारमध्ये नॉन-मजकूर फायली समाविष्ट करा</li>
          <li lang="lt">Įtraukti į šoninę juostą netekstinius failus</li>
          <li lang="ko">사이드 바에 비 텍스트 파일 포함</li>
          <li lang="ja">サイドバーにテキストファイル以外のファイルも表示するように変更</li>
          <li lang="it">Includi file non di testo nella barra laterale</li>
          <li lang="he">לכלול קבצים שאינם טקסטואליים בחלונית הצד</li>
          <li lang="gl">Incluír ficheiros que non sexan de texto na barra lateral</li>
          <li lang="fr">Inclusion des fichiers non textuels dans la barre latérale</li>
          <li lang="es">Se incluyen archivos binarios en la barra lateral</li>
          <li lang="eo">Inkluzivi netekstajn dosierojn en flankobreton</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Include non-text files in sidebar</li>
          <li lang="de">Einbeziehung von Nicht-Text-Dateien in die Seitenleiste</li>
          <li lang="da">Inkluder ikke-tekst filer i sidebaren</li>
          <li lang="cs">Zahrnutí souborů s jiným než textovým obsahem do postranního panelu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">تێخزاندنی پەڕگە نادەقییەکان لە سایدباڕدا</li>
          <li lang="ca">Inclusió de fitxers que no siguin de text a la barra lateral</li>
          <li>Fix Remove Current View</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">修复移除当前视图的问题</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено вилучення поточного подання</li>
          <li lang="sr">Поправља уклањање текућег прегледа</li>
          <li lang="sl">Popravljeno odstranjevanje trenutnega pogleda</li>
          <li lang="sk">Opravené odstraňovanie aktuálneho zobrazenia</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлено удаление текущего представления</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Corrigir Remoção de Visualização Atual</li>
          <li lang="pt">Corrigir Remover vista atual</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawiono usunięcie bieżącego widoku</li>
          <li lang="nl">Een probleem met het verwijderen van de huidige schermindeling is opgelost</li>
          <li lang="mr">वर्तमान दृश्य काढा दुरुस्ती</li>
          <li lang="lt">Pataisyti dabartinio rodinio šalinimą</li>
          <li lang="ko">현재 보기 제거 수정</li>
          <li lang="ja">"現在のビューを削除"の機能を修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Corretto "Rimuovi vista corrente"</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון הסרת התצוגה הנוכחית</li>
          <li lang="gl">Corrixir a eliminación da vista actual</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction de la suppression de la vue courante</li>
          <li lang="es">Corregir la eliminación de la vista actual</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ripari forigon el aktiva vido</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix Remove Current View</li>
          <li lang="de">Fix "Aktuelle Ansicht entfernen"</li>
          <li lang="da">Rettelse af Fjern Nuværende Visning</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opraveno odebrání stávajícího pohledu</li>
          <li lang="ckb">چارەکردنی ڕەشکردنەوەی دیمەنی ئێسا</li>
          <li lang="ca">Correcció la vista actual de la supressió</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.1.0" date="2019-03-06">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix New Window desktop action behavior</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">修复“新窗口”桌面操作行为</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено поведінку дії на робочому столі Нове вікно</li>
          <li lang="sr">Поправља понашање радње радне површи новог прозора</li>
          <li lang="sl">Popravljeno vedenje namizne akcije za ustvarjanje novega okna</li>
          <li lang="sk">Opravené správanie akcie pracovnej plochy Nové okno</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлено поведение действия «Новое окно» на рабочем столе</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Corrigir comportamento de ação de área de trabalho da Nova Janela</li>
          <li lang="pt">Corrigir comportamento de ação de nova janela do ambiente de trabalho</li>
          <li lang="pl">Naprawiono zachowanie czynności pulpitu nowego okna</li>
          <li lang="nl">Een probleem met de functie ‘nieuw venster’ vanaf de desktop is opgelost</li>
          <li lang="mr">नवीन विंडो डेस्कटॉप क्रिया वर्तन दुरुस्त करा</li>
          <li lang="lt">Pataisyti naujo lango darbalaukio veiksmo elgseną</li>
          <li lang="ko">새 창 바탕 화면 동작 기능 수정</li>
          <li lang="ja">デスクトップアクションの“新しいウィンドウ”の挙動を修正</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון התנהגות פעולת חלון חדש בשולחן העבודה</li>
          <li lang="gl">Corrixir comportamento da acción de escritorio Nova Xanela</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction du comportement de l'option « Nouvelle fenêtre » du lanceur</li>
          <li lang="es">Corregir comportamiento de la acción de escritorio Nueva Ventana</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ripari la konduton de la labortabla ago por nova fenestro</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Fix New Window desktop action behaviour</li>
          <li lang="de">Fix für das Verhalten der Desktop-Aktion *Neues Fenster"</li>
          <li lang="da">Ret Nyt Vindue skrivebords opførsel</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opraveno chování akce desktopu Nové okno</li>
          <li lang="ckb">چاککردنی ڕەفتاری کرداری ڕوومێزی پەنجەرەی تازە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Correcció del comportament d’escriptori de la finestra nova</li>
          <li>Properly synchronize Ctrl+N key presses with number of new documents spawned</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">按下 Ctrl+N 组合键次数与生成的新文档数量现已正确同步</li>
          <li lang="uk">Правильна синхронізація натискання клавіш Ctrl+N із кількістю створених нових документів</li>
          <li lang="sr">Исправно усаглашава притиске тастера Ктрл+N са бројем нових изрођених докумената</li>
          <li lang="sl">Pravilno uskladi pritiske tipk Ctrl+N s številom novo ustvarjenih dokumentov</li>
          <li lang="sk">Správna synchronizácia stlačení Ctrl+N s počtom novo vytvorených dokumentov</li>
          <li lang="ru">Правильная синхронизация нажатия сочетания клавиш Ctrl+N с количеством созданных новых документов</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Sincronizar corretamente as teclas Ctrl+N com o número de novos documentos gerados</li>
          <li lang="pt">Sincronizar corretamente as teclas Ctrl+N com o número de novos documentos gerados</li>
          <li lang="pl">Poprawnie zsynchronizuj przyciśnięcia Ctrl+N z liczbą stworzonych dokumentów</li>
          <li lang="nl">Het aantal nieuwe documenten loopt weer gelijk met het aantal keer dat de sneltoetsen Ctrl+N wordt gebruikt</li>
          <li lang="mr">तयार केलेल्या नवीन दस्तऐवजांची संख्या आणि Ctrl + N की दाबणे योग्यरित्या सिंक्रोनाइझ करा</li>
          <li lang="lt">Tinkamai sinchronizuoti Vald(Ctrl)+N klavišų paspaudimus su kuriamų naujų dokumentų skaičiumi</li>
          <li lang="ko">Ctrl + N 키를 눌러서 새로 만들어진 문서 수 적절히 동기화하기</li>
          <li lang="ja">Ctrl+N キーの押下を新規作成されたドキュメントの数と適切に同期</li>
          <li lang="he">סנכרון תקין של לחיצות על הצירוף Ctrl+N עם כמות המסמכים שנוצרים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Sincronizar correctamente as teclas Ctrl+N premidas co número de novos documentos</li>
          <li lang="fr">Synchronisation correcte du raccourci Ctrl+N avec le nombre de nouveaux documents générés</li>
          <li lang="es">Sincronizar correctamente las teclas Ctrl+N pulsadas con el número de nuevos documentos</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝuste sinkronigi la nombron da klavadoj de Stir.+N kaj la nombron da generitaj dosieroj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Properly synchronise Ctrl+N key presses with number of new documents spawned</li>
          <li lang="de">Richtige Synchronisierung bei der Eingabe von Strg+N mit der Anzahl der neu erstellten Dokumente</li>
          <li lang="da">Korrekt synkronisering af Ctrl + N-tastetryk med antallet af nye dokumenter, der er skabt</li>
          <li lang="cs">Správná synchronizace stisků Ctrl+N a počtu nových vytvořených dokumentů</li>
          <li lang="ckb">هاوکاتکردنی داگرتنی‏ کلیلی Ctrl+N لەگەڵ ژمارە دۆکیومێنتە تازەکان</li>
          <li lang="ca">Sincronització correcta de les tecles Ctrl + N amb el nombre de documents nous generats</li>
          <li>Build system fix for editorconfig dependency</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">为 editorconfig 依赖构建系统修复</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлено залежність editorconfig для збирання системи</li>
          <li lang="sr">Поправка градње система за зависност уређивача подешавања</li>
          <li lang="sl">Popravljena editorconfig soodvisnost v sistemu za izgradnjo programa</li>
          <li lang="sk">Oprava systému zostavovania pre závislosť editorconfig</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправлена зависимость editorconfig для сборки системы</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Correção do sistema de compilação para dependência do editorconfig</li>
          <li lang="pt">Correção do sistema de compilação para dependência do editorconfig</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zbudowano poprawkę systemu dla zależności editorconfig'a</li>
          <li lang="nl">Een probleem verholpen met het editorconfig pakket tijdens het installeren</li>
          <li lang="mr">Editorconfig अवलंबनासाठी सिस्टम फिक्स तयार करा</li>
          <li lang="lt">Darinių sistemos pataisymas, skirtas editorconfig priklausomybei</li>
          <li lang="ko">editorconfig 디페던시를 위한 빌드 시스템 수정</li>
          <li lang="ja">EditorConfig の依存関係に対するビルドシステムの修正</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון מערכת הבנייה לתלות ב־editorconfig</li>
          <li lang="gl">Construír a corrección do sistema para a dependencia editorconfig</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction d'une dépendance d'editorconfig pour le système de compilation</li>
          <li lang="es">Corrección del sistema de compilación para la dependencia con editorconfig</li>
          <li lang="eo">Sistemversia riparo de dependeco de editorconfig</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Build system fix for editorconfig dependency</li>
          <li lang="de">Erstellung eines System-Fixes für die Abhängigkeit von editorconfig</li>
          <li lang="da">Byg system rettelse til editorconfig afhængighed</li>
          <li lang="cs">Oprava systému pro sestavování pro závisení na editorconfig</li>
          <li lang="ckb">دروستکردنی چارەکردنی سیستەم بۆ پێبەندی editorconfig</li>
          <li lang="ca">Construcció de la correcció de sistema per a la dependència d'editorconfig</li>
          <li>Add Change Branch context menu item</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加“更改分支”上下文菜单项</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано пункт контекстного меню «Змінити гілку»</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додаје ставку приручног изборника промене гране</li>
          <li lang="sl">Dodaj zmožnost za zamenjavo veje v kontekstni meni</li>
          <li lang="sk">Pridaná položka kontextového menu Zmeniť vetvu</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлен элемент контекстного меню «Сменить ветку»</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionar item de menu de contexto Alterar Ramo</li>
          <li lang="pt">Adicionar item de menu Alterar contexto de ramificação</li>
          <li lang="pl">Dodano opcję w menu kontekstowym Zmień branch</li>
          <li lang="nl">Het context menu-item ‘Verander Branch’ toegevoegd</li>
          <li lang="mr">शाखा बदल संदर्भ मेनू आयटम जोडा</li>
          <li lang="lt">Pridėti kontekstinio meniu įrašą keisti šaką</li>
          <li lang="ko">변경 지점 컨텍스트 메뉴 항목 추가</li>
          <li lang="ja">コンテキストメニューの項目に“ブランチを変更”を追加</li>
          <li lang="it">Aggiunta voce di menu contestuale per cambiare ramo di sviluppo</li>
          <li lang="he">הוספת פריט החלפת ענף לתפריט ההקשר</li>
          <li lang="gl">Engade o elemento de menú de contexto de Change Branch</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout d'un élément de menu contextuel « Changer de branche »</li>
          <li lang="es">Se añadió el elemento «Cambiar rama» en el menú contextual</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni kuntekstan menuan elementon pri ŝanĝo de branĉo</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Add Change Branch context menu item</li>
          <li lang="de">Kontextmenüeintrag "Branch ändern" hinzugefügt</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj menupunkt for Skift Gren</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidána položka kontextové nabídky Změnit větev</li>
          <li lang="ckb">زیادکردنی دانەی گۆڕینی بڕانچ بۆ لیست</li>
          <li lang="ca">Addició de l'element del menú contextual «Canvia la branca»</li>
          <li>Avoid possible startup crash related to how plugins load</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">避免与插件加载方式相关的启动崩溃</li>
          <li lang="uk">Уникання можливого збою запуску, пов’язаного із завантаженням плагінів</li>
          <li lang="sr">Избегава могуће урушавање покретања односно на начин учитавања прикључака</li>
          <li lang="sl">Izogni se morebitnem sesutju ob zagonu zaradi načina nalaganja vtičnikov</li>
          <li lang="sk">Vyhnutie sa možnému pádu pri spustení v súvislosti s tým, ako sú načítavané zásuvné moduly</li>
          <li lang="ru">Избегание возможного сбоя при запуске, связанного с загрузкой плагинов</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Evite possíveis falhas de inicialização relacionadas a como os plugins são carregados</li>
          <li lang="pt">Evite possíveis falhas de arranque relacionadas a como os plugins são carregados</li>
          <li lang="pl">Uniknięto możliwego błędu przy uruchamianiu związanego z ładowaniem pluginów</li>
          <li lang="nl">Een mogelijke crash bij het opstarten verholpen die ontstond door de manier waarop plug-ins geladen werden</li>
          <li lang="mr">प्लगइन लोड करण्याशी संबंधित संभाव्य स्टार्टअप क्रॅश टाळा</li>
          <li lang="lt">Vengti galimų paleidimo strigčių, susijusių su tuo, kaip yra įkeliami įskiepiai</li>
          <li lang="ko">플러그인 로드 방식과 관련된 충돌 가능한 시작 방지</li>
          <li lang="ja">プラグインの読み込み方法に関連して起こる可能性のある起動時のクラッシュを防止</li>
          <li lang="he">הימנעות מקריסה אפשרית בעת ההפעלה בהקשר לאופן הפעלת התוספים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Evite os posibles fallos de inicio relacionados coa carga de complementos</li>
          <li lang="fr">Élimination d'un éventuel plantage au démarrage lié à la façon dont les plugins se chargent</li>
          <li lang="es">Se evitan los posibles fallos de inicio relacionados con la carga de complementos</li>
          <li lang="eo">Eviti eblan startan kraŝon rilate la ŝargan manieron de kromaĵoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Avoid possible startup crash related to how plugins load</li>
          <li lang="de">Vermeidung eines möglichen Absturzes beim Start in Verbindung mit dem Laden von Plugins</li>
          <li lang="da">Undgå muligt opstarts nedbrud relateret til hvordan plug-ins indlæser</li>
          <li lang="cs">Vyhnutí se možnému pádu při spouštění souvisejícího s tím, jak jsou načítány zásuvné moduly</li>
          <li lang="ckb">خۆپارێزی لە تێکچوونەکانی دەستپێک کە پەیوەندی بە چۆنیەتی لۆد کردنی پێوەکراوەکانەوە هەبوو</li>
          <li lang="ca">Evitar possibles errors d'inici relacionats amb com es carreguen dels connectors</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">翻译更新</li>
          <li lang="uz">Yangilangan tarjimalar</li>
          <li lang="uk">Оновлено переклади</li>
          <li lang="tr">Çeviriler güncellendi</li>
          <li lang="sr">Освежени преводи</li>
          <li lang="sl">Posodobljeni prevodi</li>
          <li lang="sk">Aktualizované preklady</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обновлены переводы</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zaktualizowano tłumaczenia</li>
          <li lang="nl">Bijgewerkte vertalingen</li>
          <li lang="nb">Oppdaterte oversettelser</li>
          <li lang="mr">अद्ययावत अनुवाद</li>
          <li lang="lt">Atnaujinti vertimai</li>
          <li lang="ko">번역 업데이트</li>
          <li lang="ja">翻訳の更新</li>
          <li lang="it">Traduzioni aggiornate</li>
          <li lang="he">עדכוני תרגומים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Traducións actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="fr">Mise à jour des traductions</li>
          <li lang="fi">Päivitetyt käännökset</li>
          <li lang="es">Traducciones actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝisdatigitaj tradukoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="de">Aktualisierte Übersetzungen</li>
          <li lang="da">Opdaterede oversættelser</li>
          <li lang="cs">Aktualizovány překlady</li>
          <li lang="ckb">وەرگێڕانەکان نوێکراونەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Traduccions actualitzades</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-01-03" version="3.0.2">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Smarter file saving behavior</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">更智能的文件保存行为</li>
          <li lang="uk">Розумніша поведінка збереження файлів</li>
          <li lang="sr">Паметније понашање чувања датотека</li>
          <li lang="sl">Pametnejše vedenje pri shranjevanju datotek</li>
          <li lang="sk">Inteligentnejšie správanie ukladania súborov</li>
          <li lang="ru">Более умное поведение сохранения файлов</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Comportamento de salvamento de arquivos mais inteligente</li>
          <li lang="pt">Comportamento de a guardar ficheiros mais inteligente</li>
          <li lang="pl">Inteligentniejsze zapisywanie plików</li>
          <li lang="nl">Bestanden worden slimmer opgeslagen</li>
          <li lang="mr">स्मार्ट फाईल सेव्हिंग वर्तन</li>
          <li lang="lt">Išmanesnė failų įrašymo elgsena</li>
          <li lang="ko">더 영리해진 저장 방식</li>
          <li lang="ja">ファイル保存の挙動を改善</li>
          <li lang="hu">Okosabb fájlmentési eljárás</li>
          <li lang="he">התנהגות חכמה יותר בשמירת קבצים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Comportamento de gardado de ficheiros máis intelixente</li>
          <li lang="fr">Meilleur comportement d'enregistrement des fichiers</li>
          <li lang="es">Comportamiento de guardado de archivos más inteligente</li>
          <li lang="eo">Inteligentigi la konduton pri dosiera registrado</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Smarter file saving behaviour</li>
          <li lang="de">Intelligenteres Verhalten beim Speichern von Dateien</li>
          <li lang="da">Smartere filgemmelses opførsel</li>
          <li lang="cs">Inteligentnější chování ukládání souborů</li>
          <li lang="ckb">پاشەکەوتکردنی پەڕگە بە شێوەیەکی زیرەکانەتر</li>
          <li lang="ca">Comportament més intel·ligent per desar fitxers</li>
          <li>File saving fixes</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">修复文件保存相关问题</li>
          <li lang="uk">Виправлення збереження файлів</li>
          <li lang="sr">Исправке чувања датотеке</li>
          <li lang="sl">Popravki pri shranjevanju datotek</li>
          <li lang="sk">Opravy ukladania súborov</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправления сохранения файлов</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Correções de salvamento de arquivo</li>
          <li lang="pt">Correções de a guardar ficheiro</li>
          <li lang="pl">Poprawki zapisywania plików</li>
          <li lang="nl">Problemen met het opslaan van bestanden verholpen</li>
          <li lang="mr">फाइल जतन फिक्स</li>
          <li lang="lt">Failų įrašymo pataisymai</li>
          <li lang="ko">파일 저장 문제 수정</li>
          <li lang="ja">ファイルの保存に関する修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Correzioni nel salvataggio dei file</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקון בשמירת קבצים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Correccións de gardado de ficheiros</li>
          <li lang="fr">Correction de l'enregistrement des fichiers</li>
          <li lang="es">Correcciones de guardado de archivos</li>
          <li lang="eo">Riparoj de dosieraj registradoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">File saving fixes</li>
          <li lang="de">Fehlerbehebungen beim Speichern von Dateien</li>
          <li lang="da">Rettelser til fil gemmelse</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opravy ukládání souborů</li>
          <li lang="ckb">چارەسەرکردنی پاشەکەوتکردنی پەڕگە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Correccions per desar fitxers</li>
          <li>Don't add temporary files to tab restore</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">不再将临时文件添加到还原选项卡</li>
          <li lang="uk">Тимчасові файли більше не додаються для відновлення вкладки</li>
          <li lang="sr">Не додаје привремене датотеке у враћање језичка</li>
          <li lang="sl">Ne dodajaj začasnih datotek h obnovitvi zavihkov</li>
          <li lang="sk">Nepridávať dočasné súbory do obnovenia kariet</li>
          <li lang="ru">Временные файлы больше не добавляются для восстановления вкладки</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Não adicione arquivos temporários a guia restauração</li>
          <li lang="pt">Não adicione ficheiros temporários ao restaurar separador</li>
          <li lang="pl">Tymczasowe pliki nie są dodawane do przywracania kart</li>
          <li lang="nl">Tijdelijke bestanden worden niet meer toegevoegd aan de Herstellen tab</li>
          <li lang="nb">Ikke legg til midlertidige filer i fanegjenoppretting</li>
          <li lang="mr">टॅब रिस्टोअर मध्ये तात्पुराट्या फायली जोडू नका</li>
          <li lang="lt">Nepridėti laikinųjų failų į kortelių atkūrimą</li>
          <li lang="ko">탭 복원에 임시 파일을 추가하지 마세요</li>
          <li lang="ja">タブの復元に一時ファイルを追加しないように修正</li>
          <li lang="he">קבצים זמניים לא יתווספו ללשונית השחזור</li>
          <li lang="gl">Non engada ficheiros temporais á restauración de pestanas</li>
          <li lang="fr">Pas de fichiers temporaires ajoutés à la restauration des onglets</li>
          <li lang="es">No añadir archivos temporales a la restauración de pestañas</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ne aldoni portempajn dosierojn al langeta restaŭro</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Don't add temporary files to tab restore</li>
          <li lang="de">Temporären Dateien werden nicht mehr zur Wiederherstellung von Tabs zugelassen</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføje ikke midlertidige filer til fane gendannelse</li>
          <li lang="cs">Nepřidávat dočasné soubory do obnovení karty</li>
          <li lang="ckb">پەڕگە کاتییەکان بۆ گەڕاندنەوەی تاب زیاد مەکە</li>
          <li lang="ca">No afegir fitxers temporals a la restauració de pestanyes</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">翻译更新</li>
          <li lang="uz">Yangilangan tarjimalar</li>
          <li lang="uk">Оновлено переклади</li>
          <li lang="tr">Çeviriler güncellendi</li>
          <li lang="sr">Освежени преводи</li>
          <li lang="sl">Posodobljeni prevodi</li>
          <li lang="sk">Aktualizované preklady</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обновлены переводы</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zaktualizowano tłumaczenia</li>
          <li lang="nl">Bijgewerkte vertalingen</li>
          <li lang="nb">Oppdaterte oversettelser</li>
          <li lang="mr">अद्ययावत अनुवाद</li>
          <li lang="lt">Atnaujinti vertimai</li>
          <li lang="ko">번역 업데이트</li>
          <li lang="ja">翻訳の更新</li>
          <li lang="it">Traduzioni aggiornate</li>
          <li lang="he">עדכוני תרגומים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Traducións actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="fr">Mise à jour des traductions</li>
          <li lang="fi">Päivitetyt käännökset</li>
          <li lang="es">Traducciones actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝisdatigitaj tradukoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="de">Aktualisierte Übersetzungen</li>
          <li lang="da">Opdaterede oversættelser</li>
          <li lang="cs">Aktualizovány překlady</li>
          <li lang="ckb">وەرگێڕانەکان نوێکراونەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Traduccions actualitzades</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-11-30" version="3.0.1">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Don't recreate deleted files when restoring session</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">还原会话时不重新创建已删除的文件</li>
          <li lang="uk">Видалені файли більше не створюються знову під час відновлення сеансу</li>
          <li lang="sr">Поново не прави обрисане датотеке приликом враћања сесије</li>
          <li lang="sl">Ne poustvarjaj izbrisanih datotek pri obnovitvi seje</li>
          <li lang="sk">Znovu nevytvárať odstránené súbory pri obnovovaní relácie</li>
          <li lang="ru">Удалённые файлы не воссоздаются при восстановлении сессии</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Não recriar arquivos apagados ao restaurar a sessão</li>
          <li lang="pt">Não recriar ficheiros eliminados ao restaurar a sessão</li>
          <li lang="pl">Usunięte pliki nie będą odtwarzane przy przywracaniu sesji</li>
          <li lang="nl">Verwijderde bestanden worden niet opnieuw aangemaakt bij het herstellen van een sessie</li>
          <li lang="nb">Ikke gjenopprett slettede filer ved gjenoppretting av økt</li>
          <li lang="mr">सत्र पुनर्संचयित करताना हटविलेल्या फायली पुन्हा तयार करू नका</li>
          <li lang="lt">Nekurti iš naujo failų atkuriant seansą</li>
          <li lang="ko">세션을 복원할 때 삭제된 파일을 다시 만들지 말아 주세요</li>
          <li lang="ja">セッションの復元時に削除したファイルを再作成しないように修正</li>
          <li lang="he">קבצים שנמחקו לא ייווצרו מחדש בעת שחזור הפעלה</li>
          <li lang="gl">Non recrear ficheiros eliminados ao restaurar a sesión</li>
          <li lang="fr">Pas de recréation des fichiers supprimés lors de la restauration d'une session</li>
          <li lang="es">No recrear archivos eliminados al restaurar la sesión</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ne rekrei forigitajn dosierojn ĉe seanca restaŭro</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Don't recreate deleted files when restoring session</li>
          <li lang="de">Gelöschte Dateien werden bei Wiederherstellen der Sitzung nicht neu erstellt</li>
          <li lang="da">Genskab ikke slettede filer når sessionen genskabes</li>
          <li lang="cs">Nevytvářet znovu smazané soubory při obnovování relace</li>
          <li lang="ckb">پەڕگە ڕەشکراوەکان دروست مەکەوە کاتێک سێشن دەگەڕێنییەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">No es recreen els fitxers suprimits en restaurar la sessió.</li>
          <li>Restore line wrap preference</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">恢复换行首选项</li>
          <li lang="uk">Відновлення налаштувань перенесення рядків</li>
          <li lang="sr">Враћа поставке прелома реда</li>
          <li lang="sl">Obnovitev nastavitve preloma vrstice</li>
          <li lang="sk">Obnovenie predvoľby zalamovania riadkov</li>
          <li lang="ru">Восстановлена настройка «перенос строки»</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Restaurar preferência de quebra de linha</li>
          <li lang="pt">Restaurar preferência de quebra de linha</li>
          <li lang="pl">Przywrócono preferencję zawijania linii</li>
          <li lang="nl">De voorkeur voor tekstterugloop is hersteld</li>
          <li lang="nb">Gjenopprett foretrukken linjebrytingsinnstilling</li>
          <li lang="mr">लाइन ओघ प्राधान्य पुनर्संचयित करा</li>
          <li lang="lt">Atkurti eilutės skaidymo nuostatą</li>
          <li lang="ko">줄 바꿈 환경 설정 복원</li>
          <li lang="ja">行の折り返しの設定を復活</li>
          <li lang="he">שחזור העדפת גלישת שורות</li>
          <li lang="gl">Restaurar a preferencia do envoltorio de liña</li>
          <li lang="fr">Restauration des préférences d'alignement</li>
          <li lang="es">Se restaura la preferencia de ajuste de renglones</li>
          <li lang="eo">Restaŭri linifaldajn agordojn</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Restore line wrap preference</li>
          <li lang="de">Einstellung für Zeilenumbruch wiederhergestellt</li>
          <li lang="da">Gendan præference for linieindpakning</li>
          <li lang="cs">Obnovení předvoleb zalamování řádek</li>
          <li lang="ckb">گەڕاندنەوەی ڕێکخستنی کۆکردنەوەی دێڕ</li>
          <li lang="ca">Restauració de la preferència d’ajust de línia</li>
          <li>Add accel tooltips</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">添加 accel 工具提示</li>
          <li lang="uk">Додано підказки Accel</li>
          <li lang="sr">Додаје облачиће убрзања</li>
          <li lang="sl">Dodani namigi za bližnjice</li>
          <li lang="sk">Pridanie popisu pre accel</li>
          <li lang="ru">Добавлены подсказки Accel</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Adicionar dicas de ferramentas de aceleração</li>
          <li lang="pt">Adicionar dicas de ferramentas de aceleração</li>
          <li lang="pl">Dodano tooltipy accel</li>
          <li lang="nl">Accel helpteksten toegevoegd</li>
          <li lang="mr">एक्सेल टूलटिप जोडा</li>
          <li lang="lt">Pridėti prieinamumo paaiškinimai</li>
          <li lang="ko">가속 툴팁 추가</li>
          <li lang="ja">アクセラレーターツールチップの追加</li>
          <li lang="he">הוספת עצות לסימוני האצה</li>
          <li lang="gl">Engadir indicadores de acceso directo</li>
          <li lang="fr">Ajout des indicateurs de raccourcis</li>
          <li lang="es">Se añadieron descripciones emergentes de los aceleradores</li>
          <li lang="eo">Aldoni fulmklavajn konsilojn</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Add accel tooltips</li>
          <li lang="de">Tooltips hinzugefügt</li>
          <li lang="da">Tilføj accel-værktøjstip</li>
          <li lang="cs">Přidání nástrojových tipu accel</li>
          <li lang="ckb">زیادکردنی توڵتیپسی ئەکسێل</li>
          <li lang="ca">Addició de consells d’accel</li>
          <li>Minor bug fixes</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">次要问题修复</li>
          <li lang="uk">Незначні виправлення</li>
          <li lang="tr">Küçük hata düzeltmeleri</li>
          <li lang="sr">Мање исправке грешака</li>
          <li lang="sl">Manjši popravki</li>
          <li lang="sk">Opravy menších chýb</li>
          <li lang="ru">Исправления незначительных ошибок</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Pequenas correções de bugs</li>
          <li lang="pt">Pequenas correções de problemas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Mniejsze poprawki błędów</li>
          <li lang="nl">Kleine bugfixes</li>
          <li lang="nb">Små feilfikser</li>
          <li lang="mr">किरकोळ दोष निराकरण</li>
          <li lang="lt">Nežymių klaidų pataisymai</li>
          <li lang="ko">자잘한 버그 수정</li>
          <li lang="ja">軽微なバグの修正</li>
          <li lang="it">Correzione di problemi minori</li>
          <li lang="he">תיקונים מזעריים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Pequenas correccións de erros</li>
          <li lang="fr">Corrections de bugs mineures</li>
          <li lang="es">Pequeñas correcciones de errores</li>
          <li lang="eo">Malgravaj sencimigoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Minor bug fixes</li>
          <li lang="de">Kleinere Fehlerbehebungen</li>
          <li lang="da">Mindre rettelser</li>
          <li lang="cs">Opravy drobných chyb</li>
          <li lang="ckb">چارەسەرکردنی چەند کێشەیەکی چکۆڵە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Correccions d'errors menors</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="zh_CN">翻译更新</li>
          <li lang="uz">Yangilangan tarjimalar</li>
          <li lang="uk">Оновлено переклади</li>
          <li lang="tr">Çeviriler güncellendi</li>
          <li lang="sr">Освежени преводи</li>
          <li lang="sl">Posodobljeni prevodi</li>
          <li lang="sk">Aktualizované preklady</li>
          <li lang="ru">Обновлены переводы</li>
          <li lang="pt_BR">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pt">Traduções atualizadas</li>
          <li lang="pl">Zaktualizowano tłumaczenia</li>
          <li lang="nl">Bijgewerkte vertalingen</li>
          <li lang="nb">Oppdaterte oversettelser</li>
          <li lang="mr">अद्ययावत अनुवाद</li>
          <li lang="lt">Atnaujinti vertimai</li>
          <li lang="ko">번역 업데이트</li>
          <li lang="ja">翻訳の更新</li>
          <li lang="it">Traduzioni aggiornate</li>
          <li lang="he">עדכוני תרגומים</li>
          <li lang="gl">Traducións actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="fr">Mise à jour des traductions</li>
          <li lang="fi">Päivitetyt käännökset</li>
          <li lang="es">Traducciones actualizadas</li>
          <li lang="eo">Ĝisdatigitaj tradukoj</li>
          <li lang="en_GB">Updated translations</li>
          <li lang="de">Aktualisierte Übersetzungen</li>
          <li lang="da">Opdaterede oversættelser</li>
          <li lang="cs">Aktualizovány překlady</li>
          <li lang="ckb">وەرگێڕانەکان نوێکراونەوە</li>
          <li lang="ca">Traduccions actualitzades</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.0" date="2018-10-16" />
    <release date="2017-02-20" version="2.4.1" />
  </releases>
  <provides>
    <binary>io.elementary.code</binary>
  </provides>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-desecration">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-slavery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-worship">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-homosexuality">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-prostitution">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-adultery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-appearance">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <developer_name>elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hu">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="he">elementary בע״מ.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en_GB">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ckb">کۆمپانیای ئێلەمێنتەری هاوپشک.</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <url type="homepage">https://elementary.io/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/elementary/code/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://elementary.io/get-involved#funding</url>
  <url type="help">https://github.com/elementary/code/discussions/categories/q-a</url>
  <url type="translate">https://l10n.elementary.io/projects/code</url>
  <update_contact>contact_AT_elementary.io</update_contact>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elementary/code/master/data/screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elementary/code/master/data/screenshot-dark.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>