<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <description>
    <p>
      Peek makes it easy to create short screencasts of a screen area. It was
      built for the specific use case of recording screen areas, e.g. for
      easily showing UI features of your own apps or for showing a bug in bug
      reports. With Peek you simply place the Peek window over the area you
      want to record and press "Record". Peek is optimized for generating
      animated GIFs, but you can also directly record to WebM or MP4 if you
      prefer.
    </p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Select a screen region to record</li>
      <li>Save recorded video as an optimized animated GIF</li>
      <li>Record directly to WebM or MP4 format</li>
      <li>Simple user interface optimized for the task</li>
      <li>Automatically downscale recorded videos</li>
      <li>Support for HiDPI screens</li>
      <li>Works inside a GNOME Shell Wayland session (using XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      Peek is not a general purpose screencast app with extended features but
      rather focuses on the single task of creating small, silent screencasts of
      an area of the screen for creating GIF animations or silent WebM or MP4
      videos.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>يجعل Peek مهمة إنشاء تسجيل لمنطقة من الشاشة أمرا سهلا.فقد تم تصميمه خصيصاً لتسجيل أجزاء من الشاشة، مثلا لإظهار ميزات من واجهة المستخدم لتطبيقاتك أو لإظهار علة في تقرير للإبلاغ عن العلل. مع Peek تقوم ببساطة باختيار جزء من الشاشة لتسجيله وتضغط على زر "سجّل". لقد تم تهيئة Peek لإنشاء التسجيل على شكل صور متحركة بامتداد GIF، لكن يمكنك أيضا التسجيل بصيغة WebM أو MP4 إن أردت ذلك.</p>
    <p>ميزات:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>اختر منطقة من الشاشة لتسجيلها</li>
      <li>احفظ الفيديو المسجل كصورة متحركة بامتداد GIF</li>
      <li>سجل مباشرة بصيغة WebM أو MP4</li>
      <li>واجهة مستخدم بسيطة لتسهيل إنجاز مهمتك</li>
      <li>تعديل قياسات الفيديو المسجل تلقائيا</li>
      <li>دعم الشاشات عالية الدقة</li>
      <li>يشتغل داخل جنوم شل بجلسة وايلاند (باستخدام XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek ليس بتطبيق عام لتسجيل الشاشة بميزات كثيرة، بل هو تطبيق يركز على مهمة واحدة تتمثل في إنشاء تسجيل صغير وصامت لجزء من الشاشة ليكون كصورة متحركة بامتداد GIF أو كفيديو صامت بامتداد WebM أو MP4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Peek umí jednoduše vytvářet krátké nahrávky části obrazovky. Byl vytvořen např. pro jednoduchou prezentaci možností rozhraní vaší aplikace nebo zobrazení chyby při jejím hlášení. Okno programu Peek jednoduše umístíte na oblast, kterou chcete nahrát a stisknete tlačítko „Nahrávat“. Peek je optimalizován pro generaci animovaných GIF souborů, ale můžete také nahrávat přímo do formátu WebM nebo MP4.</p>
    <p>Funkce:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Vyberte oblast obrazovky pro nahrávání</li>
      <li>Uložit nahrané video jako optimalizovaný animovaný GIF</li>
      <li>Nahrávat přímo do formátu WebM nebo MP4</li>
      <li>Jednoduché uživatelské rozhraní optimalizované pro daný úkol</li>
      <li>Automaticky podvzorkovat nahraná videa</li>
      <li>Podpora pro HiDPI obrazovky</li>
      <li>Pracuje uvnitř sezení GNOME Shell Wayland (s použitím XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek není komplexní aplikace pro nahrávání obrazovky, ale raději se zaměřuje na vytváření malých nahrávek zvolené části obrazovky do formátů GIF, WebM nebo MP4 bez zvuku.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Mit Peek können ganz einfach Bildschirmaufzeichnungen von einem Bildschirmbereich gemacht werden. Es wurde speziell für die Aufnahme von Bildschirmbereichen entwickelt, z. B. um schnell und einfach die Benutzeroberfläche eigener Anwendungen zu präsentieren oder um Fehler für Fehlerberichte zu dokumentieren. Mit Peek platzieren Sie einfach das Peek-Fenster über dem Bereich, den Sie aufnehmen wollen, und klicken auf »Aufnehmen«. Peek wurde für das Erzeugen von animierten GIFs optimiert, kann aber auch direkt im WebM- oder MP4-Format aufnehmen.</p>
    <p>Merkmale:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ein Bildschirmbereich zum Aufnehmen wählen</li>
      <li>Das aufgenommene Video als optimiertes animiertes GIF speichern</li>
      <li>Direkt im WebM- oder MP4-Format aufnehmen</li>
      <li>Eine Benutzeroberfläche, die für den Anwendungsfall optimiert ist</li>
      <li>Aufgenommene Videos automatisch skalieren</li>
      <li>Unterstützung für hochauflösende Bildschirme</li>
      <li>Funktioniert in GNOME Shell mit Wayland (mit XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek ist keine Allzweck-Anwendung zur Bildschirmaufzeichnung, sondern fokussiert sich stattdessen auf die Aufnahme von kleinen, stummen Bildschirmaufzeichnungen eines Bildschirmbereichs, um daraus GIF-Animationen oder stumme WebM- bzw. MP4-Videos zu erstellen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eo">
    <p>Peek faciligas kreadon de mallongaj registraĵoj de la ekrano. Ĝi estas farita por registrado de partoj de la ekrano; tio ebligas por vi facile montri funkciojn de viaj propraj programoj, aŭ registri problemojn por raportoj. Simple metu la fenestron de Peek sur la registrotan areon kaj klaku al «Registri». Peek estis kreita por GIF-movbildoj, sed ankaŭ eblas registri en la formojn WebM aŭ MP4, laŭ prefero.</p>
    <p>Funkcioj:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Elektu registrotan areon</li>
      <li>Konservi registritan filmon kiel optimumigitan GIF-movbildon</li>
      <li>Registri senpere en la formon WebM aŭ MP4</li>
      <li>Simpla fasado ĝustigita por la tasko</li>
      <li>Aŭtomate malpligrandigi registritajn filmojn</li>
      <li>Subteno por ekranoj kun multaj punktoj cole</li>
      <li>Funkcias en seanco de GNOME Shell kun Wayland (per XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek ne estas ĝenerala ekranregistilo kun multaj funkcioj, sed celas ebligi simplan kreadon de malgrandaj, silentaj registraĵoj de partoj de la ekrano por GIF-movbildoj, aŭ filmoj en la formoj WebM aŭ MP4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Peek hace que sea fácil crear screencasts cortos de un área de pantalla. Fue construido para el caso de uso específico de grabación de áreas de pantalla, p.ej. para mostrar fácilmente las características de interfaz de usuario de sus propias aplicaciones o para mostrar un error en los informes de errores. Con Peek simplemente coloque la ventana de Peek sobre el área que quiere grabar y pulse "Grabar". Peek está optimizado para generar GIFs animados, pero también puede grabar directamente en WebM o MP4 si lo prefiere.</p>
    <p>Características:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Seleccione una región de pantalla para grabar</li>
      <li>Guardar vídeo grabado como un GIF animado optimizado</li>
      <li>Grabar directamente en formato WebM o MP4</li>
      <li>Interfaz de usuario sencilla optimizada para la tarea</li>
      <li>Reducir automáticamente la escala de los vídeos grabados</li>
      <li>Compatibilidad con pantallas HiDPI</li>
      <li>Funciona dentro de una sesión de GNOME Shell en Wayland (mediante XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek no es una aplicación de screencast de propósito general de características ampliadas, sino que se centra en la única tarea de crear screencasts pequeños y silenciosos de un área de la pantalla para crear animaciones GIF o vídeos silenciosos en formato WebM o MP4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Peek aplikazioaren bidez erraz egin daitezke pantailaren area baten bideo grabazio txikiak.  Diseinatuta dago pantaila areak grabatzeko, esate baterako interfazeen erabilera erakusteko edo aplikazioen akatsen txostenak ilustratzeko. Peek-en leihatila grabatu nahi duzun arearen gainean kokatu eta sakatu "Grabatu". Optimizatuta dago GIF animatuak egiteko baina Webm edo MP4 formatuetan ere grabatu daiteke zuzenean.</p>
    <p>Eginbideak:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Hautatu pantaila area bat grabatzeko</li>
      <li>Gorde grabatutako bideoa optimizatutako GIF animatu moduan</li>
      <li>Grabatu zuzenean WebM edo MP4 formatuan</li>
      <li>Ataza egiteko optimizatutako erabiltzaile interfaze sinplea</li>
      <li>Txikiagotu automatikoki grabatutako bideoak</li>
      <li>HiDPI motako pantailak onartzen ditu</li>
      <li>GNOME Shell Wayland saioan bertan lan egiten du (XWayland-en bidez)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek ez da erabilera anitzeko eta eginbide zabaleko pantailako bideoen kapturak egiten dituen aplikazioa, bere helburua da sortzea pantailaren area baten bideo kaptura txiki eta mutuak GIF animatuen bidez edo WebM edo MP4 bideo mutuen bidez.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Valitse nauhoitettava alue näytöltä</li>
      <li>Tallenna nauhoitettu video optimoituna GIF-animaationa</li>
      <li>Nauhoita suoraan WebM- tai MP4-muotoihin</li>
      <li>Tuki HiDPI-näytöille</li>
      <li>Toimii Gnome Shell Wayland -istunnossa (käyttäen XWaylandia)</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Peek facilite la création de courtes captures vidéo d'une zone d'écran. Il a été conçu pour le cas spécifique d'enregistrement de zones d'écran, par exemple pour afficher facilement les fonctionnalités  UI de vos applications ou pour montrer un bug dans des rapports. Avec Peek, vous placez simplement la fenêtre de Peek sur la zone que vous souhaitez enregistrer et cliquez sur "Enregistrer". Peek est optimisé pour générer des GIF animés, mais vous pouvez également enregistrer directement en WebM ou MP4 si vous préférez.</p>
    <p>Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Sélectionnez une zone d'écran à enregistrer</li>
      <li>Sauvegarder la vidéo enregistrée en un GIF animé optimisé</li>
      <li>Enregistrer directement au format WebM ou MP4</li>
      <li>Simple interface utilisateur optimisée pour la tâche</li>
      <li>Vidéos enregistrées automatiquement en réduction d'échelle</li>
      <li>Prise en charge des écrans HiDPI</li>
      <li>Fonctionne dans une session GNOME Shell Wayland (en utilisant XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek n'est pas une application de capture vidéo d'écran d'usage général avec des fonctionnalités étendues, mais se concentre plutôt sur la simple tâche de créer de courtes vidéos silencieuses d'une zone d'écran pour créer des animations GIF, des vidéos WebM ou MP4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>Peek מאפשר לך ליצור הקלטות קצרות של איזור נבחר במסך. הוא נבנה באופן ייעודי להקלטה של איזורים במסך. לדוגמא, בשביל הצגה של תכונות ממשק משתמש של תוכנות שיצרת או להדגמה של תקלה בדיווח על שגיאות. עם Peek, פשוט שמים את החלון של Peek מעל האיזור אותו ברצונך להקליט במסך ולוחצים "הקלט". Peek מותאם בעיקר ליצירה של GIF'ים מונפשים, אבל ניתן להשתמש בו גם להקליט WebM או MP4, לפי הצורך.</p>
    <p>תכונות:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>הקלטה של איזור נבחר במסך</li>
      <li>שמירה של הוידאו שהוקלט כ-GIF מונפש</li>
      <li>הקלט ישירות לפורמט WebM או MP4</li>
      <li>ממשק משתמש פשוט שהותאם במיוחד עבור הקלטה של איזור נבחר במסך</li>
      <li>אפשרות להקטנה אוטומטית של וידאו מוקלט</li>
      <li>תמיכה במסכי HiDPI (צפיפות גבוהה)</li>
      <li>עובד בתוך סשן של Gnome Shell Wayland (באמצעות XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek אינה תוכנת הקלטת מסך לשימוש כללי עם המון תכונות, אלא תוכנה ששמה דגש על הפעולה של יצירת הקלטות קטנות, שקטות של איזור במסך בשביל יצירת קבצי GIF מונפשים, או סרטוני WebM או MP4 שקטים.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Peek olakšava stvaranje kratkih videa za područja ekrana. Izgrađen je baš za snimanje područja ekrana, primjerice za jednostavno prikazivanje funkcija korisničkog sučelja vlastitih programa ili za prikazivanje greške u izvještajima o greškama. S Peekom jednostavno stavi Peek prozor preko područja koje želiš snimiti i pritisni „Snimi”. Peek je optimiran za generiranje animiranih GIF-ova, ali ako ti je draže, možeš snimati i izravno u WebM ili MP4 format.</p>
    <p>Funkcije:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Odaberi područje ekrana koje želiš snimiti</li>
      <li>Spremi snimljeni video kao optimiran animirani GIF</li>
      <li>Snimaj direktno u WebM ili MP4 format</li>
      <li>Jednostavno sučelje optimirano za ovaj posao</li>
      <li>Automatski smanji veličinu snimljenih videa</li>
      <li>Podrška za HiDPI ekrane</li>
      <li>Radi unutar GNOME Shell Wayland sesije (koristi XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek nije program opće namjene za generiranje kratkih videa s proširenim funkcijama, već se jedino fokusira na stvaranja malih bezvučnih videa odabranih područja ekrana, u obliku GIF animacija ili bezvučnih WebM/MP4 video zapisa.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Peek membuatnya mudah untuk membuat layar pendek dari area layar. Itu tadidibuat untuk kasus penggunaan khusus area layar perekaman, mis. untuk mudahMenampilkan fitur UI aplikasi Anda sendiri atau untuk menampilkan bug dalam laporan bug.Dengan Peek kamu cukup letakkan jendela Peek di atas area yang ingin kamu rekamdan tekan "Rekam". Peek dioptimalkan untuk menghasilkan animasi GIF, tetapiAnda juga dapat langsung merekam ke WebM atau MP4 jika Anda mau.</p>
    <p>Fitur-fitur:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Pilih area layar untuk direkam</li>
      <li>Simpan video terekam sebagai sebuah animasi GIF yang teroptimasi</li>
      <li>Rekam langsung menjadi format WebM or MP4</li>
      <li>Antarmuka pengguna sederhana yang dioptimalkan untuk tugas</li>
      <li>Automatis menurunkan skala rekaman video</li>
      <li>Dukungan untuk layar HiDPI</li>
      <li>Bekerja di dalam sesi GNOME Shell Wayland (menggunakan XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek bukan aplikasi screencast yang umum dengan fitur yang diperluas tetapiAgak fokus pada satu tugas untuk menciptakan screencasts kecil dan sunyiarea layar untuk membuat animasi GIF atau WebM atau MP4video.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Peek rende facile creare brevi registrazioni di un'area dello schermo. E stato  creato per essere usato per registrare aree di schermo, es. per mostrare facilmente le UI delle app o per riportare dei bug nei bug report. Con Peek è sufficiente collocare la finestra Peek sull'area che si desidera registrare e premere "Registra". Peek è ottimizzato per creare delle GIF animate, ma puoi anche registrare in WebM o MP4 se preferisci.</p>
    <p>Funzionalità:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Seleziona una porzione di schermo da registrare</li>
      <li>Salva il video registrato come una GIF ottimizzata</li>
      <li>Registra direttamente nel formato WebM o MP4</li>
      <li>Semplice interfaccia ottimizzata per l'obiettivo</li>
      <li>Downscala automaticamente i video registrati</li>
      <li>Supporto per gli schermi HiDPI</li>
      <li>Funziona in una sessione GNOME Shell Wayland (usando Xwayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek non è un'applicazione di screencast per uso generale con funzioni estese ma si concentra su piccoli processi per creare, piccole registrazioni di un area dello schermo per creare una GIF animata,video WebM o MP4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>Peek は、指定した画面領域の短いスクリーンキャストを簡単に作成することができます。特定の用途（アプリの UI や機能に関する説明、バグ報告など）で画面領域を録画するために Peek は作成されました。Peek の使い方はシンプルで、録画したい領域に Peek のウィンドウを移動させて「録画」を押すだけです。Peek はアニメーション GIF を生成するのに最適化されていますが、WebM や MP4 で直接録画することもできます。</p>
    <p>機能:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>録画する画面領域を選択します</li>
      <li>録画されたビデオを最適化されたアニメーション GIF として保存します</li>
      <li>WebM や MP4 形式に直接録画します</li>
      <li>タスクに最適化されたシンプルなユーザーインターフェース</li>
      <li>録画されたビデオを自動的にダウンスケールします</li>
      <li>HiDPI スクリーンをサポート</li>
      <li>XWayland を使用して GNOME Shell Wayland セッション内で動作します</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek は拡張された機能を持った汎用目的のスクリーンキャストアプリではなく、むしろ GIF アニメーションや無音の WebM/MP4 ビデオを作成するという目的で画面領域の小さくて無音のスクリーンキャストを作成するという単一のタスクに焦点を当てています。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Peek palengvina ekrano srities trumpų ekrano įrašų kūrimą. Ši programa buvo sukurta specialiai ekrano sričių įrašymui, pvz., norint lengvai parodyti savo programos naudotojo sąsajos ypatybes arba, siekiant parodyti klaidą klaidų pranešimuose. Naudodami Peek, jūs tiesiog patalpinate Peek langą virš srities, kurią norite įrašyti ir paspaudžiate "Įrašinėti". Peek yra optimizuota animuotų GIF kūrimui, tačiau jei pageidaujate, galite tiesiogiai įrašinėti į WebM ar MP4.</p>
    <p>Ypatybės:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Pasirinkti norimą įrašinėti ekrano sritį</li>
      <li>Įrašyti įrašinėtą vaizdo įrašą kaip optimizuotą animuotą GIF</li>
      <li>Įrašinėti tiesiogiai į WebM ar MP4 formatą</li>
      <li>Paprasta, užduočiai optimizuota, naudotojo sąsaja</li>
      <li>Automatinis įrašinėtų vaizdo įrašų mažinimas pagal skalę</li>
      <li>HiDPI ekranų palaikymas</li>
      <li>Veikia GNOME apvalkalo Wayland seanso viduje (naudojant XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek nėra bendrosios paskirties ekrano įrašų programa su išplėstinėmis ypatybėmis, tačiau ji labiau susitelkia ties viena užduotimi - tylių ekrano srities ekrano įrašų kūrimu, kuriant GIF animacijas arba tylius WebM ar MP4 vaizdo įrašus.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Peek gjør det enkelt å opprette korte skjermopptak av skjermområde. Det ble bygg med den hensikt å ta opp skjermområder. F.eks. for å enkelt vise grensesnittsfunksjoner av programmer, eller for å vise en feil i en feilrapport. Med Peek kan du med letthet plassere Peek-vinduet over området du ønsker å ta opp og trykke "Ta opp". Peek er optimisert for å generere animerte GIF-filer, men du kan også ta opp direkte til WebM eller MP4 hvis du foretrekker det.</p>
    <p>Funksjoner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Velg et skjermområde å ta opp</li>
      <li>Lagre innspilt video som optimisert animert GIF-fil</li>
      <li>Ta opp direkte i WebM- eller MP4-format</li>
      <li>Enkelt brukergrensesnitt optimalisert for oppgaven</li>
      <li>Automatisk nedskalering av innspilte videoer</li>
      <li>Støtte for HiDPI-skjermer</li>
      <li>Fungerer inne i en GNOME-skall- Wayland-økt (ved bruk av XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek er ikke en generisk skjermdelingsapp med utvidede funksjoner, men snarere et fokus på enkle oppgaver som å lage små, tause skjermopptak av et område på skjermen for opprettelse av GIF-animasjoner eller stumme WebM- eller MP4-videoer.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Peek maakt het opnemen van korte screencasts van een deel van het scherm gemakkelijk. Het is gebouwd om delen van schermen op te nemen, bijv. om de werking van je apps te tonen of om een opname te maken voor een bugmelding. Plaats simpelweg het Peek-venster over het op te nemen gebied en drukt op "Opnemen". Peek is geoptimaliseerd voor het genereren van geanimeerde GIF's, maar je kunt ook, indien gewenst, direct opnemen naar WebM of MP4.</p>
    <p>Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Selecteer een op te nemen schermgebied</li>
      <li>Sla een opgenomen video op als een geoptimaliseerd, bewegend GIF-bestand</li>
      <li>Neem direct op naar WebM- of MP4-formaat</li>
      <li>Eenvoudig uiterlijk, geoptimaliseerd voor de taak</li>
      <li>Opgenomen video's automatisch bijsnijden</li>
      <li>Ondersteuning voor HiDPI-schermen</li>
      <li>Werkt in GNOME Shell op Wayland (met behulp van XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek is geen algemene screencast-app met uitgebreide mogelijkheden. Peek focust op het creëren van kleine, stille screencasts van een gedeelte van het scherm voor het creëren van GIF-animaties of stille WebM- of MP4-video's.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Peek ułatwia tworzenie krótkich nagrań  wybranego obszaru ekranu. Został zbudowany w celu nagrywania obszarów ekranu, na przykład aby łatwo pokazywać funkcje UI twojego programu lub pokazywać błędy w raportach. Po prostu umieść okno Peek nad obszarem, który chcesz nagrać i naciśnij "Nagraj". Peek jest zoptymalizowany do generowania animowanych plików GIF, ale istnieje także możliwość bezpośredniego zapisu do WebM lub MP4, wedle uznania.</p>
    <p>Funkcje:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Wybierz region ekranu do nagrywania</li>
      <li>Zapisz nagrane wideo jako zoptymalizowany, animowany GIF</li>
      <li>Nagraj bezpośrednio do formatu WebM lub MP4</li>
      <li>Prosty interfejs użytkownika zoptymalizowany do zadania</li>
      <li>Automatyczne skalowanie w dół nagranych materiałów</li>
      <li>Wsparcie dla ekranów HiDPI</li>
      <li>Działa wewnątrz sesji GNOME Shell Wayland (używanie XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek nie jest ogólnym rejestratorem z rozbudowanymi funkcjami, bardziej skupia się na pojedynczym zadaniu tworzenia małych, cichych nagrań obszaru ekranu zapisywanych jako animacje GIF lub ciche filmy WebM oraz MP4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>O Peek facilita a criação de screencasts curtos de uma área de tela. Ele foi construído para o caso de uso específico de gravação de áreas da tela, por exemplo, para facilmente mostrar os recursos de UI de seus próprios aplicativos ou para mostrar um erro no relatório de erros. Com o Peek você simplesmente coloca a janela Peek sobre a área que deseja gravar e pressiona "Gravar". O Peek é otimizado para gerar GIFs animadas, mas se você preferir, também pode gravar diretamente para WebM ou MP4.</p>
    <p>Características:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Selecione uma área da tela para gravar</li>
      <li>Salvar vídeo gravado como uma GIF animada otimizada</li>
      <li>Gravar diretamente para o formato WebM ou MP4</li>
      <li>Interface simples do usuário otimizada para a tarefa</li>
      <li>Reduzir automaticamente os vídeos gravados</li>
      <li>Suporte para telas HiDPI</li>
      <li>Trabalha dentro de uma sessão Wayland do GNOME Shell (Utilizando o XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>O Peek não é um aplicativo de gravação de tela de uso geral com recursos estendidos, mas tem o foco na simples tarefa de criar pequenas e silenciosas gravações de uma área da tela para criação de GIF animadas ou vídeos sem sons, WebM ou MP4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_PT">
    <p>O Peek facilita a criação de screencasts curtos de uma área do ecrã. Ele foi construído para o uso específico de gravação de áreas do ecrã, por exemplo, para facilmente mostrar os recursos da interface das suas próprias aplicações ou para mostrar um erro no relatório de erros. Com o Peek basta colocar a janela Peek sobre a área que quer gravar e pressionar o botão "Gravar". O Peek está otimizado para gerar GIFs animados, mas se preferir, também pode gravar diretamente nos formatos WebM ou MP4.</p>
    <p>Características:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Selecione uma região do ecrã para gravar</li>
      <li>Guardar o vídeo gravado como uma animação GIF otimizada</li>
      <li>Gravar diretamente para o formato WebM ou MP4</li>
      <li>Interface simples de utilizador otimizado para a tarefa</li>
      <li>Reduzir automaticamente os vídeos gravados</li>
      <li>Suporte a ecrãs de alta definição</li>
      <li>Funciona dentro de uma sessão GNOME Shell Wayland (usando XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>O Peek não é uma aplicação de gravação de ecrã de uso geral com recursos avançados. É antes focado na simples tarefa de criar gravações pequenas e sem som, de uma área do ecrã para criação de GIF animados ou vídeos WebM ou MP4 sem som.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Peek облегчает создание скринкастов областей экрана. Он был создан специально для записи частей экрана, например, для демонстрации возможностей ваших собственных приложений или создания сообщений об ошибках. Просто поместите окно Peek над той областью, которую хотите записать, и нажмите «Запись». Peek лучше всего записывает анимированные GIF, но также может записывать напрямую в WebM или MP4.</p>
    <p>Возможности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Выберите область экрана для записи</li>
      <li>Сохраните записанное видео в формате анимированного GIF</li>
      <li>Записывайте напрямую в формат WebM или MP4</li>
      <li>Простой пользовательский интерфейс, оптимизированный для этой задачи</li>
      <li>Автоматически уменьшать разрешение записанного видео</li>
      <li>Поддержка экранов высокой чёткости</li>
      <li>Работает в GNOME Shell на Wayland (при помощи XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek не является многофункциональным приложением для записи скринкастов, а помогает решить единственную задачу записи GIF-анимации или беззвучных видео WebM или MP4.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Виркало чини снимање одређених делова екрана веома лаким. Направљен је за прецизно снимање одређених делова екрана као што је то потребно приликом снимања графичких делова сопственог програма или за потребе пријаве грешке у неком програму. Са Виркалом је само потребно да поставите прозор Виркала над површином коју желите да снимите и да кликнте на „Снимај“. Виркало је оптимизовано за стварање анимираних GIF-ова али такође можете директно снимати у WebM видео или MP4, ако желите.</p>
    <p>Могућности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Бирање области за снимање</li>
      <li>Чување снимљеног видеа као оптимизовани анимирани GIF</li>
      <li>Директно снимање у WebM или MP4 формат</li>
      <li>Једноставан кориснички интерфејс направљен сходно задатку</li>
      <li>Аутоматско смањивање величине снимљених видео материјала</li>
      <li>Подршка за екране високе резолуције</li>
      <li>Ради унудар Вејленд сесије Гномове шкољке (преко XWayland-a)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Виркало није опште наменско решење за снимање радне површине, са напредним могућностима, већ се усредсређује на одређени циљ а то је стварање малих, тихих снимака одређених делова екрана зарад стварања GIF анимација или тихих WebM или MP4 видео записа.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Peek gör det enkelt att skapa korta inspelningar av ett område på skärmen. Det byggdes specifikt för att enkelt visa funktioner i dina egna program, eller för att spela in underlag till felrapporter. Med Peek kan du enkelt placera Peek-fönstret över det område du vill spela in och trycka på "Spela in". Peek är optimerad för att generera animerade GIF-filer, men du kan också spela in direkt till WebM eller MP4, om du föredrar det.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Välj ett skärmområde för inspelning</li>
      <li>Spara videon som optimerad, animerad GIF-fil</li>
      <li>Spela in direkt i WebM- eller MP4-formatet</li>
      <li>Enkelt användargränssnitt, optimerat för uppgiften</li>
      <li>Automatisk nedskalning av inspelad video</li>
      <li>Stöd för HiDPI-skärmar</li>
      <li>Fungerar i en GNOME Wayland-session (med hjälp av XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek är inte ett generellt skärminspelningsprogram med utökade funktioner, utan fokuserar snarare på den enda uppgiften att skapa små, tysta inspelningar av ett område på skärmen, för att sedan skapa GIF-animeringar eller tysta WebM- eller MP4-videor.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Peek, ekranın belirli bir bölümü için kayıt oluşturmayı kolaylaştırıyor. Arayüz özellikleri veya hata bildirimi yaparken kolayca ekranı kaydetme üzerine tasarlandı ve özel bir hamaca hizmet ediyor. Peek penceresini kaydetmek istediğiniz yere sürükleyip ve kolayca kayıt yapabilirsiniz. Peek animasyonlu GIFler için özel olarak optimize edildi fakat direkt olarak WebM veya MP4 formatında da kayıtta yapabilirsiniz.</p>
    <p>Özellikler:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Kayıt için bir ekran alanı seçiniz</li>
      <li>Oluşturulmuş videoyu optimize edilmiş GIF olarak kaydet</li>
      <li>Direkt olarak WeBM ya da MP4 formatında kayıt</li>
      <li>Tam bu iş için hazırlanmış kolay kullanımlı kullanıcı arayüzü</li>
      <li>Otomatik video optimizasyonu</li>
      <li>HiDPI ekran desteği</li>
      <li>GNOME Shell Wayland oturumu içerisinde çalışır (XWayland kullanarak)</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk_UA">
    <p>Властивості:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Позначення довільних ділянок екрану для запису</li>
      <li>Збереження відео у форматі оптимізованого оживленого GIF</li>
      <li>Запис напряму у форматі WebM або MP4</li>
      <li>Простий і оптимізований інтерфейс користувача</li>
      <li>Автоматичне пониження роздільної здатності записуваних відео</li>
      <li>Підтримка екранів високої роздільної здатності (HiDPI)</li>
      <li>Працює у GNOME Shell на Wayland (за допомогою XWayland)</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>Peek 使得在屏幕上指定区域录制短视频变得简单。例如，你可以简单地把 Peek 窗口移动到你想要录制的区域，然后按下“录制”，这样就可以方便的展示自己应用程序用户界面的功能或是在错误报告中展示错误。Peek 对制作 GIF 动画有优化；但如果你喜欢的话，你也可以直接录制 MP4 或者 WebM。</p>
    <p>特色：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>选择要录制的屏幕区域</li>
      <li>将录制的视频保存为优化过的 GIF 动画</li>
      <li>直接录制为 WebM 或 MP4 格式</li>
      <li>为任务优化的简单用户界面</li>
      <li>自动缩放录制的视频</li>
      <li>支持 HiDPI 屏幕</li>
      <li>可以在 GNOME Shell Wayland 会话内使用（使用 XWayland）</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek 不是一个拥有扩展功能的通用屏幕录制程序，它仅仅专注于在屏幕上录制小型、无声的 GIF、MP4 或 WebM 视频。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>Peek 讓錄製一部分的螢幕截取變得更加容易。這是專門被設計來錄製部分螢幕區塊的，例如在示範軟體操作或者重現 bug 狀況時就能派上用場。有了 Peek，您只要把 Peek 的視窗放置在您想錄影的區塊，然後按下「錄影」即可。Peek 已針對產生 GIF 動畫進行優化，不過需要的話也能直接錄製 WebM 或者 MP4 格式。</p>
    <p>功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>可選取欲錄製的螢幕區塊</li>
      <li>可將錄製的影片儲存為經最佳化的 GIF 動畫</li>
      <li>可直接錄製成 WebM 或 MP4 格式</li>
      <li>簡單易用的介面</li>
      <li>可自動縮小影片的解析度</li>
      <li>支援 HiDPI 螢幕</li>
      <li>支援 GNOME Shell Wayland 模式（透過 XWayland）</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Peek 並不是專門用來錄影的應用程式，Peek 專注在錄製螢幕區塊並輸出成 GIF 動畫或無聲的 WebM、MP4 影片。</p>
  </description>
  <pkgname>peek</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.uploadedlobster.peek.desktop</launchable>
  <icon height="64" width="64" type="cached">com.uploadedlobster.peek.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">com.uploadedlobster.peek.png</icon>
  <id>com.uploadedlobster.peek.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Peek</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">Peek</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">Peek</name>
  <name lang="uk_UA">Peek</name>
  <name lang="sv">Peek</name>
  <name lang="sr">Виркало</name>
  <name lang="ru">Peek</name>
  <name lang="pt_PT">Peek</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Peek</name>
  <name lang="pl">Peek</name>
  <name lang="nl">Peek</name>
  <name lang="nb">Peek</name>
  <name lang="lt">Peek</name>
  <name lang="ja">Peek</name>
  <name lang="it">Peek</name>
  <name lang="id">Peek</name>
  <name lang="hr">Peek</name>
  <name lang="he">Peek</name>
  <name lang="fr">Peek</name>
  <name lang="fi">Peek</name>
  <name lang="eu">Peek</name>
  <name lang="es">Peek</name>
  <name lang="eo">Peek</name>
  <name lang="el">Peek</name>
  <name lang="de">Peek</name>
  <name lang="cs">Peek</name>
  <name lang="ca">Peek</name>
  <name lang="ar">Peek</name>
  <summary>Simple screen recorder with an easy to use interface</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">簡單易用的螢幕錄影軟體</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">简单易用的屏幕录制器</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Kullanımı kolay bir arayüze sahip basit ekran kaydedici</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Enkel skärminspelare med ett användarvänligt gränssnitt</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Једноставан снимач екрана са лако употребљивим интерфејсом</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Простой рекордер экрана с удобным интерфейсом</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_PT">Gravador simples de animações GIF com uma interface fácil de usar</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Simples gravador de tela com uma interface fácil de usar</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Prosty rejestrator ekranu z łatwym w użyciu interfejsem</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Simpele, eenvoudig te bedienen schermopname-applicatie</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Enkel skjermopptaker med enkelt brukergrensesnitt</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Paprastas ekrano rašytuvas su lengva naudoti sąsaja</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">使いやすいインターフェースを備えたシンプルなスクリーンレコーダー</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Semplice registratore di schermo con un interfaccia facile da usare</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Perekam layar sederhana dengan antarmuka yang mudah digunakan</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Program za snimanje ekrana s jednostavnim sučeljem</summary>
  <summary lang="he">תוכנה פשוטה להקלטת המסך עם ממשק משתמש קל לשימוש</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Enregistreur d'écran simple avec une interface facile d'utilisation</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Yksinkertainen näyttönauhoitin helppokäyttöisellä käyttöliittymällä</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Pantailaren  grabagailu erabilerraza</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Grabador de pantalla sencillo con una interfaz fácil de usar</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Simpla ekran-registrilo kun facile uzebla fasado</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Einfacher Bildschirmrekorder mit einer einfach zu bedienenden Oberfläche</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Program pro nahrávání dění na obrazovce se snadno použitelným rozhraním</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">مسجل شاشة بسيط بواجهة سهلة الاستخدام</summary>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/phw/peek/master/data/screenshots/peek-main-window.png</image>
      <caption>The main window to select the recording area</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">選擇錄影區塊的主要視窗</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">用主窗口来选择录制区域</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Huvudfönster för att välja inspelningsområde</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Главни прозор за бирање површине која ће се снимати</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Главное окно для выбора записываемой области</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_PT">A janela principal para selecionar a área de gravação</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">A janela principal para selecionar a área de gravação</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Główne okno do wyboru obszaru nagrywania</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Het hoofdvenster om het op te nemen gebied te selecteren</caption>
      <caption lang="nb">Hovedvinduet for å velge opptaksområde</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Pagrindinis langas, skirtas pasirinkti įrašinėjimo sritį</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">録画範囲を選択するメインウィンドウ</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La finestra principale per selezionare l'area di registrazione</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Jendela utama untuk memilih area perekaman</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Glavni prozor za odabir područja snimanja</caption>
      <caption lang="he">החלון הראשי לבחירת איזור ההקלטה</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">La fenêtre principale pour sélectionner la zone d'enregistrement</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Grabatzeko area duen leiho nagusia</caption>
      <caption lang="es">La ventana principal para seleccionar el área de grabación</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">La ĉefa fenestro por elekti la registrotan areon</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Aufnahmebereich mit dem Hauptfenster wählen</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Hlavní okno pro výběr oblasti nahrávání</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">النافذة الرئيسية لاختيار منطقة التسجيل</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/phw/peek/master/data/screenshots/peek-preferences.png</image>
      <caption>Peek's preferences dialog</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">Peek 偏好設定</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">Peek 偏好设置</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Peek-inställningar</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Прозорче поставки Виркала</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Диалог настроек Peek</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_PT">Janela das preferências do Peek</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Janela de preferências do Peek</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Okno preferencji Peek</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Peek-voorkeurenvenster</caption>
      <caption lang="nb">Peek sitt innstillingsdialogvindu</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Peek nuostatų dialogas</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">Peek の設定ダイアログ</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Dialog pengaturan Peek</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Dijalog Peek postavki</caption>
      <caption lang="he">חלון ההגדרות של Peek</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Préférences de Peek</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Peekin asetusikkuna</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Peek-en hobespenen elkarrizketa-koadroa</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Diálogo de preferencias de Peek</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">Agorda fenestro de Peek</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Einstellungsdialog von Peek</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Předvolby programu Peek</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/phw/peek/master/data/screenshots/peek-recording-itself.gif</image>
      <caption>Peek is recording itself</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">Peek 正在錄製自己</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">Peek 正在录制自身</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Peek spelar in sig självt</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Виркало снима само себе</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Peek записывает сам себя</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_PT">Peek está a gravar-se a si próprio</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">O Peek está se gravando</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Peek nagrywa sam siebie</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Peek is bezig zichzelf op te nemen</caption>
      <caption lang="nb">Peek tar opp seg selv</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Peek įrašinėja pati save</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">Peek が Peek 自身を録画しています</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Peek si sta registrando da solo</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Peek sedang merekam sendiri</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Peek snima samog sebe</caption>
      <caption lang="he">Peek מקליט את עצמו</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Peek en train de s'enregistrer</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Peek nauhoittaa itseään</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Peek bere burua grabatzen ari da</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Peek se está grabando a sí mismo</caption>
      <caption lang="eo">Peek registras sin mem</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Peek nimmt sich selbst auf</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Peek nahrává sám sebe</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">Peek يُسجِل نفسه</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <categories>
    <category>Graphics</category>
    <category>Utility</category>
    <category>GNOME</category>
    <category>GTK</category>
  </categories>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>AppMenu</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>Notifications</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <url type="homepage">http://peek.uploadedlobster.com</url>
  <!-- <url type="help">http://peek.uploadedlobster.com</url> -->
  <url type="faq">https://github.com/phw/peek#frequently-asked-questions</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/phw/peek/issues</url>
  <!-- <url type="translate">https://hosted.weblate.org/projects/peek/translations/</url> -->
  <translation type="gettext">peek</translation>
  <provides>
    <binary>peek</binary>
  </provides>
  <developer_name>Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_TW">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="zh_CN">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk_UA">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="tr">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sr">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_PT">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt_BR">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nb">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nap">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="lt">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ja">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eu">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="eo">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ar">Philipp Wolfer</developer_name>
  <update_contact>ph.wolfer@gmail.com</update_contact>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="1.5.1" date="2020-02-19" />
    <release date="2020-02-18" version="1.5.0" />
    <release date="2019-09-24" version="1.4.0" />
    <release version="1.3.1" date="2018-03-29" />
    <release date="2018-03-25" version="1.3.0" />
    <release date="2018-01-28" version="1.2.2" />
    <release version="1.2.1" date="2017-12-03" />
    <release version="1.2.0" date="2017-11-25" />
    <release version="1.1.0" date="2017-10-05" />
    <release date="2017-06-13" version="1.0.3" />
    <release version="1.0.2" date="2017-06-13" />
    <release version="1.0.1" date="2017-03-26" />
    <release date="2017-03-11" version="1.0.0" />
    <release version="0.9.1" date="2017-02-21" />
    <release version="0.9.0" date="2017-02-20" />
    <release version="0.8.0" date="2016-10-25" />
    <release version="0.7.2" date="2016-07-07" />
    <release date="2016-02-28" version="0.7.1" />
    <release date="2016-02-26" version="0.7.0" />
    <release version="0.6.0" date="2016-01-28" />
    <release version="0.5.0" date="2016-01-09" />
    <release version="0.4.0" date="2016-01-08" />
    <release date="2016-01-08" version="0.3.0" />
    <release date="2016-01-07" version="0.2.1" />
    <release version="0.2.0" date="2016-01-07" />
    <release version="0.1.0" date="2016-01-05" />
  </releases>
</component>