<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>pentobi</pkgname>
  <icon width="64" type="cached" height="64">pentobi.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">pentobi.png</icon>
  <id>io.sourceforge.pentobi.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Pentobi</name>
  <name lang="ru">Pentobi</name>
  <name lang="es">Pentobi</name>
  <name lang="de">Pentobi</name>
  <summary>Computer opponent for the board game Blokus</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Конкурент компьютерной настольной игры Блокус</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Rival virtual para el juego de mesa Blokus</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Computer-Gegner für das Brettspiel Blokus</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
Pentobi is a computer opponent for the board game Blokus. It has a
strong Blokus engine with different playing levels. The supported game
variants are Classic, Duo, Trigon, Junior, Nexos, Callisto and GembloQ.
</p>
    <p>
Players can determine their strength by playing rated games against the
computer and use a game analysis function. Games can be saved in Smart
Game Format with comments and move variations.
</p>
    <p>
System requirements: 1 GB RAM, 1 GHz CPU (4 GB RAM, 2.5 GHz dual-core or
faster CPU recommended for playing level 9).
</p>
    <p>
Trademark disclaimer: The trademark Blokus and other trademarks referred
to are property of their respective trademark holders. The trademark
holders are not affiliated with the author of the program Pentobi.
</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Pentobi ist ein Computer-Gegner für das Brettspiel Blokus. Es hat eine spielstarke Blokus-Engine mit verschiedenen Spielstufen. Die unterstützten Spielvarianten sind : Klassisch, Duo, Trigon, Junior, Nexos, Callisto und GembloQ.</p>
    <p>Spieler können ihre Spielstärke ermitteln, indem sie gewertete Spiele gegen den Computer spielen, und eine Spielanalysefunktion benutzen. Spiele können im Smart-Game-Format gespeichert werden mit Kommentaren und Zugvarianten.</p>
    <p>Systemminima: 1 GB RAM, 1 GHz CPU (4 GB RAM, 2,5 GHz Dual-Core- oder schnellere CPU empfohlen für Spielstufe 9).</p>
    <p>Hinweis zu Markennamen: Der Markenname Blokus und andere erwähnte Marken sind Eigentum ihrer jeweiligen Markeninhaber. Die Markeninhaber stehen in keiner Verbindung mit dem Autor des Programms Pentobi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Pentobi es un rival virtual para el juego de mesa Blokus. Cuenta con un potente motor para Blokus con diferentes niveles de juego. Las variantes de juego compatibles son Clásico, Dúo, Trigón, Sencillo, Nexos, Calisto y GembloQ.</p>
    <p>Los jugadores pueden conocer su habilidad participando en partidas con selección de nivel contra la máquina y usar una función de análisis de la partida. Las partidas se pueden guardar en formato Smart Game Format con comentarios y variaciones de movimientos.</p>
    <p>Requisitos de sistema: 1 GB RAM, 1 GHz CPU (4 GB RAM, 2,5 GHz dual-core o  CPU más rápida recomendada para jugar en el nivel 9).</p>
    <p>Exención de responsabilidad de la marca comercial: la marca comercial Blokus y otras marcas comerciales mencionadas son propiedad de sus respectivos propietarios. Los propietarios de las marcas comerciales no están afiliados con el autor del programa Pentobi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Pentobi оппонент компьютерной настольной игры Блокус. Он имеет сильный движок Блокус с различными уровнями игры. Поддерживаемые варианты игры-Классический, Двое, Тригон, Юниор, Нексос, Каллисто и ГемблоQ.</p>
    <p>Игроки могут определить свою силу, играя в рейтинговые игры против компьютера и используя функцию анализа игры. Игры могут быть сохранены в формате Smart Game с комментариями и вариациями ходов.</p>
    <p>Системные требования: 1 GB RAM, 1 GHz CPU (4 GB RAM, 2.5 GHz dual-core или больше CPU рекомендуется для игрового уровня 9).</p>
    <p>Отказ от ответственности за товарный знак: товарный знак Blokus и другие упомянутые товарные знаки являются собственностью их соответствующих владельцев товарных знаков. Владельцы товарных знаков не связаны с автором программы Pentobi.</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.sourceforge.pentobi.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="1248" height="702">
https://pentobi.sourceforge.io/pentobi-classic.png</image>
      <caption>Game variant Classic</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Вариант игры Классический</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Variante de juego Clásico</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Spielvariante Klassisch</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image height="702" width="1248">
https://pentobi.sourceforge.io/pentobi-duo.png</image>
      <caption>Game variant Duo</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Вариант игры Двое</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Variante de juego Dúo</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Spielvariante Duo</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image width="1248" height="702">
https://pentobi.sourceforge.io/pentobi-trigon.png</image>
      <caption>Game variant Trigon</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Вариант игры Тригон</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Variante de juego Trigón</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Spielvariante Trigon</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image height="702" width="1248">
https://pentobi.sourceforge.io/pentobi-nexos.png</image>
      <caption>Game variant Nexos</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Вариант игры Нексос</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Variante de juego Nexos</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Spielvariante Nexos</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image height="702" width="1248">
https://pentobi.sourceforge.io/pentobi-gembloq.png</image>
      <caption>Game variant GembloQ</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Вариант игры ГемблоQ</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Variante de juego GembloQ</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Spielvariante GembloQ</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://pentobi.sourceforge.io/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/enz/pentobi/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://sourceforge.net/p/pentobi/donate/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://www.transifex.com/markus-enzenberger/pentobi/</url>
  <developer_name>Markus Enzenberger</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Markus Enzenberger</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Markus Enzenberger</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Markus Enzenberger</developer_name>
  <update_contact>enz@users.sourceforge.net</update_contact>
  <provides>
    <binary>pentobi</binary>
    <mediatype>application/x-blokus-sgf</mediatype>
  </provides>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="20.0" date="2022-01-21" />
  </releases>
</component>