<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>pidgin</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">pidgin.desktop</launchable>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">pidgin.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" type="cached" width="128">pidgin.png</icon>
  <id type="desktop">pidgin.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <summary>Instant Messaging Client</summary>
  <summary lang="br">Arval postelerezh prim</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Instant Messaging Klient</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Klient til straksbeskeder</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Client für Instant Messaging (Sofortnachrichten)</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Πελάτης άμεσων μηνυμάτων </summary>
  <summary lang="en_AU">Instant Messaging Client</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Cliente de mensajería instantánea</summary>
  <summary lang="es_AR">Cliente de mensajería instantánea</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Pikaviestinsovellus</summary>
  <summary lang="ga">Cliant Teachtaireachtaí Meandaracha</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Cliente de mensaxería instantánea</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Azonnaliüzenet-küldő kliens</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Client di messaggistica istantanea</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Pokalbių klientas</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Tūlītējās ziņojumapmaiņas klients</summary>
  <summary lang="ms_MY">Klien Pemesejan Segera</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Lynmeldingsklient</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Instant Messaging Cliënt</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Lynmeldingsklient</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Komunikator</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Cliente de Mensagens Instântaneas</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Cliente de mensagens instantâneas</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Client mesagerie instantă</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Клиент для мгновенного обмена сообщениями</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Odjemalec za klepet</summary>
  <summary lang="sq">Klient Mesazhesh të Atypëratyshme</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Snabbmeddelandeklient</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Anında Mesajlaşma İstemcisi</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Pidgin is a chat program which lets you log in to accounts on multiple chat networks simultaneously.</p>
    <p>This means that you can be chatting with friends on AIM, talking to a friend on Google Talk, and sitting in an IRC chat room all at the same time.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="br">
    <p>Ur meziant kaozeal eo Pidgin, a laosk ac'hanoc'h da gennaskañ d'ho kontoù war meur a rouedad kaozeal er memes mare.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Pidgin je chatovací program umožňující přihlášení k účtům na různých sítích současně. </p>
    <p>To znamená chatování s přáteli na AIM, rozhovory na Google Talk a sezení v chatovacích místnostech IRC současně.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Pidgin er et chatprogram som giver dig mulighed for at logge på konti på flere chatnetværk på samme tid.</p>
    <p>Det betyder at du kan chatte med venner på AIM, snakke med en ven på Google Talk og være i et IRC-chatrum, på samme tid.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Pidgin ist eine Chat-Anwendung, welche es Ihnen erlaubt, sich gleichzeitig bei mehreren Chat-Netzwerken anzumelden.</p>
    <p>Dies bedeutet, dass Sie mit Freunden auf AIM chatten können, sich mit einem Freund auf Google Talk unterhalten können und in einem IRC-Chatraum sitzen können und all dies gleichzeitig.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το Pidgin είναι μια εφαρμογή συνομιλίας που σας επιτρέπει να συνδεθείτε σε λογαριασμούς σε πολλαπλά δίκτυα συνομιλίας ταυτόχρονα.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_AU">
    <p>Pidgin is a chat program which lets you log in to accounts on multiple chat networks simultaneously.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Pidgin es un programa de mensajería instantánea que le permite registrar en cuentas en distintas redes de chat simultáneamente.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es_AR">
    <p>Pidgin es un programa de mensajería instantánea que te permite iniciar sesiones en múltiples redes de chat, simultáneamente.</p>
    <p>Esto significa que podés chatear con amigos en Facebook, Telegram, Google Talk/Hangout y también estar en una sala de chat IRC, todo al mismo tiempo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Pidgin on pikaviestinsovellus, jolla voit kirjautua useisiin eri keskusteluverkkoihin samanaikaisesti.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ga">
    <p>Is feidhmchlár comhrá é Pidgin a ligeann duit go leor líonraí comhrá a úsáid san am céanna.</p>
    <p>Ciallaíonn seo gur féidir leat comhrá a dhéanamh le cairde ar AIM agus Google Talk, agus páirt a ghlacadh i seomra IRC san am céanna. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Pidgin é un programa de conversas que permite conectarse simultaneamente  con contas en múltiples redes de conversa.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Pidgin egy csevegőprogram, ami lehetővé teszi egyszerre több csevegőhálózat fiókjaiba való belépést.</p>
    <p>Ez azt jelenti, hogy egyidejűleg cseveghet ismerőseivel az AIM-en, beszélhet a Google Talkon, és ülhet egy IRC csevegőszobában.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Pidgin è un'applicazione per le chat che ti permette di accedere simultaneamente a diversi account.</p>
    <p>Questo significa che puoi chattare con gli amici su AIM, essere disponibile su Google Talk, e nello stesso momento chattare su IRC utilizzando lo stesso programma.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>„Pidgin“ yra programa kuri suteikia galimybę vienu metu būti prijungus prie kelių pokalbių tinklų.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>Pidgin ir tērzēšanas programma, kura ļauj jums pieteikties kontos uz vairākiem tērzēšanas tīkliem vienlaicīgi.</p>
    <p>Tas nozīmē, ka jūs varat tērzēt ar draugiem AIM, runāt ar draugu Google Talk un sēdēt IRC tērzētavā visur vienlaicīgi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Pidgin er et lynmeldingsprogram som lar deg logge inn på flere kontoer på forskjellige nettverk samtidig.</p>
    <p>Dette betyr at du kan prate med dinne venner på AIM, med enn venn på Google-talk, og sitte i et IRC-samtalerom samtidig.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Pidgin is een chatprogramma waarmee je met meerdere accounts op verschillende chatnetwerken aangemeld kan zijn.</p>
    <p>Dit betekent dat je tegelijkertijd kan chatten met vrienden op AIM, praten met vrienden op Google Talk en zitten en een IRC chatruimte.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>Pidgin er eit prateprogram som let deg logge på konti frå fleire pratenettverk samstundes.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Pidgin jest komunikatorem umożliwiającym logowanie do wielu sieci jednocześnie.</p>
    <p>Oznacza to, że można jednocześnie rozmawiać ze swoimi znajomymi przez AIM, z przyjacielem przez Google Talk i siedzieć w pokoju rozmów IRC.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Pidgin é um programa de chat que lhe permite entrar em várias contas em múltiplas redes de chat simultâneamente.</p>
    <p>Isto significa que, num único lugar, pode conversar com os seus amigos via AIM, falar com um amigo no Google Talk e acompanhar uma sala de conversação do IRC.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Pidgin é um programa de bate-papo que permite entrar em múltiplas redes de bate-papo ao mesmo tempo.</p>
    <p>Isso significa que você pode estar conversando com amigos no AIM, falando com um amigo no Google Talk, e estar numa sala IRC tudo ao mesmo tempo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Пиджин - программа, позволяющая вам вести переписку по нескольким сетям общения одновременно.</p>
    <p>Это означает, что вы можете общаться с друзьями по AIM, говорить по Google Talk и сидеть в комнате IRC в одно и то же время.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Pidgin je program za klepet, ki omogoča prijavo v račune na več omrežjih za klepet hkrati.</p>
    <p>To pomeni, da lahko obenem klepetate s prijatelji na AIM, s prijateljem v Google Talk in v klepetalnici IRC.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sq">
    <p>Pidgin-i është një program fjalosjesh që ju lejon të hyni dhe përdorni shumë llogari njëherazi në disa rrjete fjalosjesh.</p>
    <p>Kjo do të thotë se mund të fjaloseni me miqtë në AIM, të bisedoni me një shok në Google Talk, dhe të merrni pjesë në një dhomë fjalosjeje IRC, njëherazi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Pidgin är ett chattprogram som låter dig logga in på flera chattnätverk samtidigt.</p>
    <p>Det betyder att du kan chatta med vänner på AIM, prata med en vän på Google Talk samt delta i ett IRC-chattrum samtidigt.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Pidgin aynı anda farklı sohbet ağlarında oturum açabileceğiniz bir sohbet programıdır.</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.pidgin.im/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://old.pidgin.im/shared/img/contact_window.png</image>
      <caption>The buddy list showing friends on different networks.</caption>
      <caption lang="br">Roll an darempredoù o tiskouez mignoned war rouedadoù disheñvel.</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Seznam kamarádů zobrazuje kamarády na různých sítích.</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Vennelisten som viser venner på forskellige netværk.</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Die Kontaktliste zeigt die Freunde aus den veschiedenen Netzwerken.</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Η λίστα φίλων εμφανίζει φίλους σε διαφορετικά δίκτυα.</caption>
      <caption lang="en_AU">The buddy list showing friends on different networks.</caption>
      <caption lang="es">La lista de amigos muestra amigos en distintas redes.</caption>
      <caption lang="es_AR">La lista de contacto muestra a usuarios en diferentes redes.</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Kaveriluettelo esittää yhteystiedot eri verkoista.</caption>
      <caption lang="ga">Taispeánann an liosta cairde do chuid teagmhálaithe ar líonraí éagsúla.</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">A lista de contactos amosa  os seus amigos en diferentes redes.</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">A partnerlista különböző hálózatokon elérhető ismerősökkel.</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La lista dei contatti che mostra gli utenti di reti diverse.</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Draugų sąrašas rodo draugus skirtinguose tinkluose.</caption>
      <caption lang="lv">Draugu saraksts, kurš parāda draugus dažādos tīklos.</caption>
      <caption lang="ms_MY">Senarai rakan menunjukkan rakan yang berada dalam pelbagai rangkaian.</caption>
      <caption lang="nb">Kontaktlisten viser flere kontakter på forskjellige nettverk.</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">De vriendenlijst toont vrienden van verschillende netwerken</caption>
      <caption lang="nn">Vennelista viser venner på ulike nettverk.</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Lista znajomych wyświetlająca osoby używające różnych sieci.</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">A lista de amigos mostrando amigos em diferentes redes.</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">A lista de amigos mostrando amigos em diferentes redes.</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Список, отображающий друзей из разных сетей.</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Seznam prijateljev prikazuje prijatelje z različnih omrežij.</caption>
      <caption lang="sq">Listë shokësh që shfaq shokë në rrjete të ndryshme.</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Kompislistan visar vänner på olika nätverk.</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Arkadaş listeniz farklı ağlardaki arkadaşlarınızı gösterir.</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <updatecontact>devel@pidgin.im</updatecontact>
</component>