<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>piper</pkgname>
  <icon width="64" type="cached" height="64">org.freedesktop.Piper.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" type="cached" height="128">org.freedesktop.Piper.png</icon>
  <id>org.freedesktop.Piper</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0" />
  <name translatable="no">Piper</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">Piper</name>
  <name lang="sv">Piper</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Piper</name>
  <name lang="pl">Piper</name>
  <name lang="nl">Piper</name>
  <name lang="it">Piper</name>
  <name lang="hr">Piper</name>
  <name lang="fr">Piper</name>
  <name lang="es">Piper</name>
  <name lang="de">Piper</name>
  <name lang="bg">Piper</name>
  <name lang="be">Piper</name>
  <summary>Configurable mouse configuration utility</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">可設定的滑鼠組態實用工具</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Konfigurationsprogram för programmerbara möss</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Ferramenta de configuração de mouses programáveis</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Konfigurowalne narzędzie do konfiguracji myszy</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Uitgebreid hulpmiddel voor het instellen van muizen</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Utility di configurazione per mouse configurabili</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Pomagalo za podešavanje miša</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Outil de configuration de souris programmable</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Utilidad de configuración de ratón configurable</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Konfigurationsprogramm für konfigurierbare Mäuse</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Инструмент за управление на настройките на мишката</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Прыстасаванне для наладкі мышы</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Piper is a graphical user interface to configure gaming mice.
      Configuration options include changing the resolution (DPI) of the
      mouse, adding and removing profiles, setting LED colors and changing
      button behaviors.
    </p>
    <p>
      Piper requires libratbag’s ratbagd, the daemon to actually communicate with the
      mice. Piper is merely a front end to ratbagd, ratbagd must be
      installed and running when Piper is launched.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Piper - гэта графічны інтэрфэйс карыстальніка для наладкі гульнявых мышэй. Варыянты канфігурацыі ўключаюць змену адрознівальнай здольнасці (DPI) мышы, даданне і выдаленне профіляў, наладкі колеру святлодыёда і змяненне паводзін кнопкі.</p>
    <p>Piper патрабуе бібліятэку libratbagd ад сэрвісу ratbagd, каб камунікаваць з мышшу. Piper - гэта проста графічны інтэрфэйс, ratbagd павінен быць усталяваны і запушчаны перад запускам Piper.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Piper е програма за управление на настройките на мишки, предназначени за ползване в игри. С Piper можете да променяте разделителната способност на мишката (DPI), да добавяте и премахвате профили, да задавате цветовете на светодиодите и да променяте това какво правят бутоните.</p>
    <p>Piper изисква ratbagd – демон, който всъщност осъществява връзката с мишката. Piper е само потребителски интерфейс за ratbagd, и за да функционира, трябва ratbagd да е инсталиран и да работи при стартирането на Piper.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Piper ist eine Grafische Benutzerschnittstelle zur Konfiguration von Gaming Mäuse. Mögliche Konfigurationsoptionen sind die Auflösung der Maus (DPI), das Editieren von Profilen, LED Farbeinstellungen und der Tastenzuweisung.</p>
    <p>Piper benötigt libratbags ratbagd, der Daemon der die eigentliche Kommunikation mit der Maus verwaltet. Piper ist nur eine Graphische Benutzeroberfläche für ratbagd, ratbagd muss installiert sein und laufen wenn Piper gestartet wird.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Piper es una interfaz gráfica de usuario para configurar ratones «gaming». Las opciones de configuración incluyen cambiar la resolución PPP (DPI) del ratón, añadir y eliminar perfiles, configurar los colores de los LED y cambiar el comportamiento de los botones.</p>
    <p>Piper necesita ratbagd de libratbag, el demonio, para poder comunicarse con los ratones. Piper es simplemente un frontal para ratbagd, ratbagd debe estar instalado y funcionando cuando inicie Piper.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Piper est une interface graphique pour configurer votre souris. Les options de configuration comprennent changer la resolution (DPI) de la souris, ajouter et supprimer des profils, définir la couleurs des LEDs et changer le comportement des boutons.</p>
    <p>Piper a besoin de ratbagd, le démon de libratbag qui permet de communiqueravec la souris. Piper est seulement une interface à ratbagd. ratbagd doit donc être installé, et doit être exécuté quand Piper est lancé.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Piper je korisničko grafičko sučelje za podešavanje miševa namijenjenih igranju. Mogućnosti podešavanja uključuju promjenu razlučivosti (DPI) miša, dodavanje i uklanjanje profila, prilagodba LED boja i ponašanja tipka.</p>
    <p>Piper zahtijeva libratbagov ratbag, pozadinski program za komunikaciju s mišem. Piper je prednji program za ratbagd, ratbagd mora biti instaliran i pokrenut kada se Piper pokrene.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Piper è un'interfaccia grafica per configurare mouse da gioco. Le opzioni di configurazione includono il cambiamento della risoluzione (DPI) del mouse, l'aggiunta e la rimozione di profili, l'impostazione dei colori dei LED e il cambiamento del comportamento dei pulsanti.</p>
    <p>Piper necessita di ratbagd (incluso in libratbag), il demone che comunica effettivamente con il mouse. Piper è una semplice interfaccia per ratbagd, ratbagd deve essere installato e in esecuzione quando Piper viene lanciato.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Piper is een grafische toepassing voor het instellen van gamemuizen. Zo kun je onder meer de resolutie (DPI) van je muis instellen, profielen toevoegen en verwijderen, en LED-kleuren en knoptoewijzingen aanpassen.</p>
    <p>Piper is afhankelijk van libratbag's ratbagd, de achtergronddienst die daadwerkelijk met de muis communiceert. Piper is slechts een grafische schil hieromheen. ratbagd moet dus geïnstalleerd en actief zijn voordat je Piper opstart.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Piper to graficzny interfejs użytkownika do konfiguracji myszy do gier komputerowych. Można między innymi zmieniać rozdzielczość (DPI) myszy, dodawać i usuwać profile, ustawiać kolory diod LED i zmieniać zachowanie przycisków.</p>
    <p>Piper wymaga ratbagd biblioteki libratbag, usługi do komunikacji z myszą. Piper to tylko interfejs dla usługi ratbagd, która musi być zainstalowana i uruchomiona przed włączeniem programu Piper.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Piper é uma interface gráfica para configurar mouses para jogos. As opções de configuração incluem alterar a resolução (DPI) do mouse, adicionar e remover perfis, alterar as cores dos LEDs e alterar o comportamento dos botões.</p>
    <p>O Piper requer o programa ratbagd, um daemon que realiza a comunicação  com o mouse. O aplicativo é apenas uma interface para o ratbagd, ou seja, o daemon precisa estar instalado e executando ao iniciar o Piper.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Piper är ett användargränssnitt för att konfigurera möss. Det finns optioner för att ändra musens upplösning (DPI), lägga till och ta bort profiler, ställa in LED färger och ändra knappbindningar.</p>
    <p>Piper behöver libratbags ratbagd, demonen som kommunicerar faktiskt med musen.Piper är bara ett användargränssnitt för ratbagd, ratbagd måste vara installerad och körs.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>Piper 是用來設定遊戲滑鼠的圖形化使用者介面。設定選項包含了變更滑鼠解析度 (DPI)、新增與移除設定檔、設定 LED 色彩並變更按鈕行為等等。</p>
    <p>Piper 依賴於 libratbag 的 ratbagd，這是實際與滑鼠溝通的幕後程式。Piper 只是 ratbagd 的前端，ratbagd 必須在 Piper 啟動前安裝並執行。</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.freedesktop.Piper.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>The button configuraton page</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">按鈕設定頁面</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Öppna konfigurationsdialogen för knappar</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">A página de configuração dos botões</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Strona konfiguracji przycisków</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">De knopinstellingenpagina</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La pagina di configurazione dei pulsanti</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Stranica podešavanja tipki</caption>
      <caption lang="es">La página de configuración de botones</caption>
      <caption lang="bg">Страницата за настройка на бутоните</caption>
      <caption lang="be">Старонка наладкі кнопак</caption>
      <image>https://github.com/libratbag/piper/raw/wiki/screenshots/flathub/piper-buttonpage.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The LED configuraton page</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">LED 設定頁面</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Öppna konfigurationsdialogen för lysdioder</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">A página de configuração do(s) LED(s)</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Strona konfiguracji diod LED</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">De LED-instellingenpagina</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La pagina di configurazione dei LED</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Stranica LED podešavanja</caption>
      <caption lang="es">La página de configuración de LEDs</caption>
      <caption lang="bg">Страницата за настройка на светодиодите</caption>
      <caption lang="be">Старонка наладкі LED</caption>
      <image>https://github.com/libratbag/piper/raw/wiki/screenshots/flathub/piper-ledpage.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The resolution configuraton page</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">解析度設定頁面</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Öppna konfigurationsdialogen för upplösningar</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">A página de configuração das resoluções</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Strona konfiguracji rozdzielczości</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">De resolutie-instellingenpagina</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La pagina di configurazione della risoluzione</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Stranica podešavanja razlučivosti</caption>
      <caption lang="es">La página de configuración de resolución</caption>
      <caption lang="bg">Страницата за настройка на разделителната способност</caption>
      <caption lang="be">Старонка наладкі разрознасці (DPI)</caption>
      <image>https://github.com/libratbag/piper/raw/wiki/screenshots/flathub/piper-resolutionpage.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/libratbag/piper/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/libratbag/piper/issues</url>
  <url type="help">https://github.com/libratbag/piper/wiki</url>
  <translation type="gettext">piper</translation>
  <provides>
    <binary>piper</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.5.1" date="2020-06-22" />
  </releases>
</component>