<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>plank</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">plank.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" height="64" type="cached">plank.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" type="cached" height="128">plank.png</icon>
  <id>plank.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <name>Plank</name>
  <summary>Stupidly simple.</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">極簡。</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">简单得无语。</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Cực kì đơn giản.</summary>
  <summary lang="uz">Ahmoqona darajada sodda.</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Просто легкий.</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Son derece basit.</summary>
  <summary lang="th">ง่ายเหี้ยๆ</summary>
  <summary lang="te">చాలా సరళమైనది.</summary>
  <summary lang="ta">மிகவும் எளிது</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Galet enkelt.</summary>
  <summary lang="sr@latin">Glupavo jenostavan.</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Шашаво једноставно.</summary>
  <summary lang="sma">dle dan aelhkies.</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Bedasto preprost.</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Primitívne jednoduchý.</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">До безумного прост.</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Stupid de simplu.</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Estupidamente simples.</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Estupidamente simples.</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Idiotycznie prosty.</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Idiotsikkert</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Belachelijk eenvoudig.</summary>
  <summary lang="ne">एकदमै सरल</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Uforstandig enkelt.</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Ringkas la sangat.</summary>
  <summary lang="ml">അനായാസം.</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Muļķīgi vienkārši.</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Kvailai paprastas.</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">어처구니없으리 만치 단순한.</summary>
  <summary lang="ka">ძალიან მარტივი აი ძალიან</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">超シンプル</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Stupidamente semplice.</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Begitu sederhana.</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Nagyszerűen egyszerű.</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Neviđeno jednostavan</summary>
  <summary lang="he">טפשי עד כמה שזה פשוט</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Estupidamente simple.</summary>
  <summary lang="gd">Cho furasta 's a ghabhas.</summary>
  <summary lang="ga">Simplíocht shimplí.</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Stupidement simple.</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Todella yksinkertainen.</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Erraza baino errazagoa.</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Hämmastavalt lihtne.</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Estúpidamente simple.</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Stulte simple.</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Stupidly simple.</summary>
  <summary lang="en_CA">Stupidly simple.</summary>
  <summary lang="en_AU">Stupidly simple.</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Βλακωδώς απλό.</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Lächerlich einfach.</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Super simpel.</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Stupidně jednoduchý.</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Estúpidament simple.</summary>
  <summary lang="bs">Glupavo jednostavan.</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Пределно прост.</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">بسيط بغباء.</summary>
  <summary lang="am">በጣም ቀላል</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Plank is meant to be the simplest dock on the planet. The goal is to provide just what a dock needs and
      absolutely nothing more.
    </p>
    <p>
      It is, however, a library which can be extended to create other dock programs with more advanced features.
      Thus, Plank is the underlying technology for Docky (starting in version 3.0.0) and aims to provide all the
      core features while Docky extends it to add fancier things like Docklets, painters, settings dialogs, etc.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>يهدف بلانك لأن يكون أبسط حامل في العالم. الهدف هو تقديم ما يحتاجه حامل أيقونات فقط و لا شيء آخر على الإطلاق</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Plank е замислен като най-семплият док на планетата. Целта на Plank е да предостави само и единствено най-необходимото.</p>
    <p>Това е основната библиотека, която може да се разширява и да се създават и други докове с по-разширени възможности. Plank е технологията скрита в Docky (от версия 3.0.0 насам) и има за да даде всички основни функции, докато Docky прави всички красоти, като доклети, теми, диалози за настройка и т.н.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El Plank pretèn ser el dock més simple del planeta. El seu objectiu és proporcionar allò que un dock necessita, i cap altra cosa més.</p>
    <p>No obstant això, es tracta d'una llibreria que es pot extendre per tal de crear altres programes acoblats amb característiques més avançades. Així doncs, el Plank és la tecnología subjacent per al Docky (a partir de la versió 3.0.0), i té com a objectiu proporcionar totes les característiques bàsiques, mentre que el Docky esten aquestes per incorporar coses més elegants com Docklets, pintors, quadres de diàleg d'ajustos, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Plank má být nejjednodušší dock na planetě. Cílem je poskytnout přesně to, co od docku potřebujete, a absolutně nic víc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Plank er tænkt til at være den simpleste dok på planeten. Målet er at levere lige præcist hvad en dok behøver og intet andet.</p>
    <p>Det er dog et bibliotek som kan udvides for at oprette andre dok-programmer med mere avancerede funktioner. Plank er således den underliggende teknologi for Docky (fra version 3.0.0) og går efter at levere alle kerne-funktionerne, mens Docky udvider Plank med henblik på tilføjelse af smarte ting såsom dokletter, malere, indstillingsdialoger osv.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Plank soll das schlichteste Dock auf dem Planeten sein. Sein Ziel ist, genau die Funktionen bereitzustellen, die ein Dock haben muss, und sonst nichts.</p>
    <p>Es ist jedoch eine Bibliothek, die erweitert werden kann, um andere Dockprogramme mit erweiterten Funktionen zu erstellen. So ist Plank die zugrunde liegende Technik für Docky (ab Version 3.0.0) und zielt darauf ab, die nötigen Kernfunktionen zur Verfügung zu stellen, während Docky diese um schicke Dinge wie Docklets, Painters, Einstellungsdialoge usw. erweitert,</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το Plank προορίζεται να είναι η απλούστερη υποδοχή εικονιδίων στον πλανήτη. Ο στόχος είναι να παρέχει ακριβώς ό, τι χρειάζεται μια υποδοχή εικονιδίων και τίποτα απολύτως περισσότερο.</p>
    <p>Είναι, ωστόσο, μια βιβλιοθήκη η οποία μπορεί να επεκταθεί για να δημιουργήσει άλλα προγράμματα υποδοχής με πιο προηγμένα χαρακτηριστικά. Έτσι, το Plank είναι η υποκείμενη τεχνολογία για το Docky (αρχής γενομένης από την έκδοση 3.0.0) και έχει ως στόχο να παρέχει όλα τα βασικά χαρακτηριστικά, ενώ το Docky επεκτείνεται για να προσθέσετε πιο φανταχτερά πράγματα όπως Υποδοχίδια, χρωματιστές, ρυθμίσεις διαλόγων, κλπ.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Plank is meant to be the simplest dock on the planet. The goal is to provide just what a dock needs and absolutely nothing more.</p>
    <p>It is, however, a library which can be extended to create other dock programs with more advanced features. Thus, Plank is the underlying technology for Docky (starting in version 3.0.0) and aims to provide all the core features while Docky extends it to add fancier things like Docklets, painters, settings dialogues, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Plank está concebido como el «dock» más simple del planeta. El objetivo es proporcionar únicamente las funcionalidades básicas.</p>
    <p>Además es una biblioteca que puede ampliarse para crear otros «docks» con mayores prestaciones. Así, Plank es la tecnología subyacente de Docky (a partir de la versión 3.0.0), proveyendo la funcionalidad básica que Docky extiende con «docklets» y otras funciones.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Plank'i eesmärgiks on olla lihtsaim dokk maailmas ning pakkuda ainult seda, mida üks korralik dokk pakkuma peab.</p>
    <p>See on samuti ka kogumik, mida on võimalik kasutada teiste dokkide loomiseks. Seega, Plank on aluseks Docky'le (alates versioonist 3.0.0) ning üritab pakkuda põhifunktsioone ning Docky omakorda täiendab neid, et lisada rohkem võimalusi, nagu dokletid, värvid, eelistuste dialoogid, jne.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Plank munduko atrakerik errazena izateko sortu zen. Helburua, atrake batek behar duena eskaintzea da, soberako ezer gabe.</p>
    <p>Beraz, zera da, liburutegia zein zabaldu daiteke beste portu programa batzuk sortzeko eginbide aurreratu gehiagorekin. Honela, Plank azpitik dagoen teknologia da Docky-rentzat (3.0.0 bertsiotik aurrera) eta Plank honen asmoa da funtsezko eginbide guztiak eskaintzea. Docky-k, ordea, gauza txundigarriagoak eskaintzen ditu: Dockletak, pintatzaileak, ezarpen menuak, etab.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Plankin on tarkoitus olla maailman yksinkertaisin telakka. Sen tavoite on tarjota vain telakan tarvitsemat asiat, ei mitään muuta.</p>
    <p>Se on kuitenkin samalla kirjasto, jota voi laajentaa samalla luoden muita telakkasovelluksia lisäominaisuuksilla. Plank toimii myös Docky-telakan pohjana versiosta 3.0.0 alkaen. Tavoite on tarjota telakan ydintoiminnot, jolloin Docky voi laajentaa ominaisuuksia omin lisäosin.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Plank a été conçu comme le dock le plus simple de la planète. Son but est de fournir uniquement ce qui est fondamental  pour un dock et rien de plus.</p>
    <p>Par ailleurs, c'est une bibliothèque qui peut être étendue afin de créer d'autres docks comprenant des fonctionnalités plus avancées. Plank est la technologie sous-jacente de Docky (depuis la version 3.0.0) et vise à fournir toutes les fonctionnalités essentielles tandis que Docky la développe pour ajouter des fantaisies telles que les Docklets, les décorateurs, les fenêtres de paramètres, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ga">
    <p>Ceapadh Plank mar an dug is simplí ar an domhan. Is í an sprioc atá againn ná na riachtanais duga a sholáthar agus sin an méid.</p>
    <p>Ach tá sé ina leabharlann freisin gur féidir é a leathnú chun ríomhchláir duga eile a chruthú agus gnéithe níos forbartha acu. Mar sin, is é Plank an bhunteicneolaíocht le haghaidh Docky (ó leagan 3.0.0 amach) agus tá sprioc ann na gnéithe lárnacha Docky a sholáthar cé go bhfuil na gnéithe sin á leathnú ag Docky chun rudaí galánta mar dugaíní, péintéirí, dialóga socruithe, srl. a chur leis.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gd">
    <p>Is fainear Plank gur e an doca as simplidhe air an t-saoghail a bhios ann. Tha sinn ag amas toirt dhut na dh'fheumas tu airson doca gun càil sam bith eile.</p>
    <p>'S e leabharlann a th' ann co-dhiù a ghabhas leudachadh gus prògraman doca eile a chruthachadh air a bheil barrachd roghainnean adhartach. Mar sin, 's e an teicneolas air air a tha Docky stèidhichte (on tionndadh 3.0.0. a-mach) a th' ann am Plank agus tha sinn ag amas na feartan bunasach uile a thoirt dhuibh fhad 's a chuireas Docky ris le rudan spaideil leithid Docklets, peantairean, còmhraidhean airson roghainnean is msaa.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Plank está pensado para ser a doca máis simple no planeta. O obxectivo é ofrecer xusto o que necesita unha doca e absolutamente nada máis.</p>
    <p>Porén, é una biblioteca que pode estenderse para crear outros programas de doca con características máis avanzadas. Polo tanto, Plank é a tecnoloxía subxacente de Docky (a partires da versión 3.0.0) e ten como obxectivo fornecer todas as características básicas, mentres que Docky esténdea  para engadir cousas máis elegantes como trebellos, pintores, diálogos de axuste, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>Plank נועד להיות מעגן היישומים הפשוט בעולם. המטרה היא לספק בדיוק מה שהמעגן צריך ורק את זה.</p>
    <p>עם זאת, זוהי ספרייה הניתנת להרחבה ליצירת תוכנות אחרות לעיגון יישומים עם מאפיינים מתקדמים יותר. כך, למשל, Plank הוא התשתית הטכנולוגית של Docky (החל מגרסה 3.0.0), במטרה לספק את כל מאפייני הליבה, בעוד ש-Docky מרחיב אותו ומאפשר לשנות את העיצוב או את אופן הפעולה, להוסיף לוחיות יישומים נוספות</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Plank szeretne lenni a legegyszerűbb dokk alkalmazás az egész világon. Az a cél, hogy csak annyit nyújtson amennyit egy dokknak feltétlenül kell és semmi többet.</p>
    <p>Ez, ugyanakkor, egy programozói könyvtár ami kibővíthető más dokk programok létrehozására, fejlettebb funkciókkal. Ezért hát a Plank a Docky alatt rejlő technológia (a 3.0.0 verziótól kezdve) és az alapfunkciók biztosítását célozza, míg a Docky ezt kibővítve látványosabb dolgokat ad hozzá, mint például Dockleteket, festőket (painters), beállítóablakot, stb.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Plank ditujukan sebagai dok paling sederhana di muka bumi. Tujuannya menyediakan hanya apa yang diperlukan dok, dan tidak lebih.</p>
    <p>Namun juga, kepustakaannya bisa diperluas guna menciptakan program-program dok lainnya yang memiliki fitur lebih canggih. Oleh karena, Plank adalah teknologi yang mendasari Docky (mulai dari versi 3.0.0) dan bertujuan menyediakan semua  fitur ini sementara Docky meluaskannya dan menambahkan hal-hal menawan seperti Docklets, painter, setelan dialog, dsb.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Plank punta ad essere la dockbar più semplice del pianeta. L'obiettivo è proprio quello di fornire ciò di cui una dockbar ha bisogno e assolutamente niente di più.</p>
    <p>È, tuttavia, una libreria che può essere estesa per creare altri programmi dock con caratteristiche più avanzate. Perciò, Plank è la tecnologia di base per Docky (a partire dalla versione 3.0.0) e mira a fornire tutte le funzionalità di base, mentre Docky le estende per aggiungere cose più elaborate come docklets, pittori, finestre di dialogo con impostazioni, ecc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>"Plank"は地球上で最もシンプルなドックです。他に必要とする物が無いドックを提供することが目標です。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ka">
    <p>Plank არის ყველაზე მარტივი dock-ი მთელს პლანეტაზე.  თუმცა მას გააჩნია ყველაფერი რაც dock-ს სჭირდება და არაფერი სხვა!!</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>플랭크는 세상에서 가장 단순한 독(dock) 프로그램입니다. 이 프로그램의 목적은 독(dock)의 가장 기본적인 기능을 제공하는 것 이상도 이하도 아닙니다.</p>
    <p>다만, 라이브러리를 사용해서 다른 독(dock) 프로그램을 만들고 더 상세한 기능을 개발할 수 있습니다. 플랭크는 도키(Docky 버전 3.0.0 부터)의 기반으로 사용되고 있으며, 저희는 기초적인 기능을 제공하고 도키(Docky)가 더 상세한 기능들을 제공할 것입니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Plank yra skirtas būti pačiu paprasčiausiu skydeliu planetoje. Jo tikslas yra pateikti tai kas reikalinga skydeliui ir visiškai nieko daugiau.</p>
    <p>Kita vertus, jis yra biblioteka, kuri gali būti išplėsta, siekiant sukurti kitas skydelio programas su labiau išplėstinėmis ypatybėmis. Štai kodėl Plank yra esminė Docky (pradedant versijoje 3.0.0) technologija ir siekia pateikti visas pagrindines ypatybes, tuo tarpu kai Docky išplečia jį ir prideda tokius dalykus kaip įskiepiai, nustatymų dialogai ir t.t.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lv">
    <p>Plank ir veidots kā vienkāršākais programmu panelis pasaulē. Mūsu mērķis ir nodrošināt to, kas panelim ir vajadzīgs un ne vairāk.</p>
    <p>Neskatoties uz to, tā ir bibliotēka, kura var tikt papildināta, lai izveidotu citas paneļu programmas ar sarežģītākām funkcijām. Tāpēc, Plank ir pamattehnoloģija programmai Docky ( sākot no 3.0.0 versijas) un tās mērķis ir nodrošināt visas pamatfunkcijas, kamēr Docky paplašina to, lai tam pievienotu jau sarežģītākas lietas, kā Dockleti, painteri, iestatījumu dialogus u.c.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ml">
    <p>പ്ലാങ്ക് ലോകത്തിലെ ഏറ്റവും സുതാര്യമായ ഡോക്ക് ആണ്. ഡോക്കിനു ആവശ്യമായത് എന്തോ അത് നല്കുക,അത് മാത്രം ! ഇതാണ് ലക്ഷ്യം .</p>
    <p>എന്നിരിക്കിലും  ഇത് മികവാർന്ന പുതിയ ഡോക്കുകൾ ഉണ്ടാക്കുവാൻ വേണ്ടി വിപുലീകരിക്കാവുന്ന ആലേഖനങ്ങൾ തന്നെയാണ് .അടിസ്ഥാന പ്രയോഗങ്ങളിൽ മാത്രം ലക്ഷ്യം വെക്കുന്ന പ്ലാങ്ക്, ഡോക്കിയുടെ അടിസ്ഥാന സാങ്കേതികതയാണ് (വെർഷൻ 3.0.0 മുതൽ) എന്നാൽ ഡോക്കി ഭാവനാപരമായ ഡോക്ക്ലെട്സ്,പെയിന്റേർസ്,സെറ്റിംഗ്സ് ലേഖനം തുടങ്ങിയവ ഉള്പെടുതുവാൻ ഇതിനെ വിപുലീകരിച്ചു.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Plank merupakan dok yang paling ringkas. Matlamat Plank adalah untuk menyediakan apa yang dok perlukan dan tiada apa-apa penambahan yang lain.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Plank er ment å være den enkelste dokken på planeten. Målet er å gi akkurat det en dokk trenger og ingenting mer.</p>
    <p>Det er imidlertid et bibliotek som kan utvides for å skape andre dokk programmer med flere avanserte funksjoner. Dermed er Plank den underliggende teknologien for Docky (starter i versjon 3.0.0) og har som mål å gi alle kjernefunksjonene mens Docky utvider det til å legge til mer avanserte ting som docklets, malere, innstillingsdialoger, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ne">
    <p>Plank संसारकै सरल डक हो । यसको उदेश्य केवल डकले जे दिन्छ त्यही हो ।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Plank is bedoeld als het simpelste dock op aarde. Het doel is om slechts een dock te zijn, niet meer en niet minder.</p>
    <p>Het is echter ook een bibliotheek die uitgebreid kan worden met andere dock-toepassingen met meer geavanceerde opties. Plank is dus de onderliggende technologie voor Docky (zal starten in versie 3.0.0) en zal voor al de kernfuncties zorgen terwijl Docky extra dingen toe kan voegen zoals docklets, kleuropties, instellingendialoog, enz.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>Plank er meint å vera den enklaste dokken i verda. Målet er å gje akkurat det ein dokk treng, og ikkje noko meir.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Zamierzeniem Planka jest bycie najprostszym dokiem na świecie. Jego celem jest dostarczenie tego, czego potrzebujesz w doku i nic ponadto.</p>
    <p>Pomimo tego, jest to także biblioteka, która umożliwia tworzenie innych programów dokujących o zaawansowanych możliwościach. I tak, Plank obecny jest w Docky (począwszy od wersji 3.0.0) i obsługuje wszystkie jego podstawowe funkcje, podczas gdy Docky zajmuje się bardziej wymyślnymi sprawami, takimi jak obsługa dokletów, drukarek, okien z ustawieniami itd.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Plank foi criado para ser a barra mais simples do planeta. O objetivo é criar uma barra que apenas faça o essencial.</p>
    <p>É, no entanto, uma biblioteca que pode ser expandida para criar outras barras com muitas mais funcionalidades. O Plank é a infraestrutura da aplicação Docky (a partir da versão 3.0.0) e pretende disponibilizar as funcionalidades básicas, enquanto que o Docky adiciona muitos mais efeitos especiais.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Plank foi criado para ser o dock mais simples do planeta. O objetivo é oferecer apenas o que um dock precisa e absolutamente mais nada.</p>
    <p>Plank é, no entanto, uma biblioteca que pode ser estendida para criar outros docks com recursos mais avançados. Assim, Plank é a tecnologia por trás de Docky (a partir da versão 3.0.0), e pretende fornecer todos os recursos centrais, enquanto Docky o estende, adicionando requintes como Docklets, indicadores, janelas de configuração, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Plank — это самая простая док-панель в мире. Цель — просто панель и ничего лишнего.</p>
    <p>Однако, это библиотека, которая может быть расширена для создания других док-панелей с более продвинутыми функциями. Таким образом, Plank является основной технологией Docky (начиная с версии 3.0.0) и призван обеспечить все основные функции, в то время как Docky расширяет его, чтобы добавить такие фантастические вещи, как доклеты, окраска тем оформления, диалоги настроек и прочее.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Plank má byť najjednoduchším dokom na planéte. Jeho cieľom je poskytnúť iba to, čo jeden dok potrebuje a absolútne nič viac.</p>
    <p>Je to avšak knižnica, ktorá môže byť rozšírená na vytváranie iných dokov s pokročilejšími funkciami. Plank je základom Docky (začínajúc verziou 3.0.0) a jeho cieľom je poskytnúť všetky základné funkcie, kým Docky ho rozšíri a pridá ozdobné veci ako Doklety, paintery, dialógy pre nastavenia a i.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Планк би требао да буде најједноставнији док на планети. Његов циљ је да пружи само оно што док треба да пружи и апсолутно ништа више.</p>
    <p>То је, уствари, библиотека која се може проширити како би се направили други лучки програми са више напредних функција. Стога, Планк је полазна технологија за Доки (почевши од издања 3.0.0) и циљ му је да обезбеди све кључне функције, док их Доки проширује како би додао китњастије ствари као што су справице, сликари, прозорчићи подешавања, итд.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr@latin">
    <p>Plank bi trebao da bude najjednostavniji dok na planeti. Njegov cilj je da pruži samo ono što dok treba da pruži i apsolutno ništa više.</p>
    <p>On je, u stvari, biblioteka koja se može proširiti, kako bi se napravili drugi dok programi sa još naprednijim funkcijama. Stoga, Plank je osnova za Doki (počevši od verzije 3.0.0) i cilj mu je da pruži sve ključne funkcije, dok ih Doki proširuje kako bi dodao naprednije stvari kao što su Dokleti, boje, prozorčići sa podešavanjima, itd.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Plank är menat att vara den enklaste dockan på planeten. Målet är att erbjuda precis vad en docka behöver och absolut ingenting mer.</p>
    <p>Det är, trots allt, ett bibliotek som kan utökas för att skapa andra panelprogram med mera avancerade funktioner.
Plank är den underliggande teknologin för Docky (med start i version 3.0.0) och strävar efter att tillhandahålla alla grundfunktioner medan Docky utökar det med lite elegantare effekter som dockprogram, målare, inställningsdialoger med mera.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="te">
    <p>ప్లాంక్ ప్రపంచంలోనే సరళమైన డాక్. ఇది అవసరమైన ఫీచర్లు మాత్రమే కలిగి ఉంది .</p>
    <p>ఇది ఒక సాఫ్ట్ వేర్ లిబ్రరీ. దీనిని ఉపయోగించి కొత్త ప్రొగ్రామ్ లను మరియు అత్యాధునిక ఫీచర్లను తయారు చేయవచ్చు. డాకీ ప్లాంక్ మీదే ఆధార పది పని చేస్తుంది.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="th">
    <p>แพลงค์ไม่ได้อยากเป็นดอคที่เรียบง่ายที่สุดในโลก แต่จุดมุ่งหมายหลักแค่ให้ในสิ่งที่ควรจะเป็นกับดอค ไม่ได้มีอะไรมากไปกว่านี้</p>
    <p>อย่างไรก็ตามไลบรารี่ยังสามารถไปเพิ่มเติมคุณสมบัติพิเศษได้มากมาย เพราะงั้นแพลงค์จึงถูกใช้เป็นเทคโลยีหลักข้างใน Docky (ตั้งแต่เวอร์ชั่น 3.0.0 เป็นต้นมา) และแพลงค์มุ่งหมายที่จะเพิ่มความสามารถหลักๆ ต่างจาก Docky ที่มุ่งเพิ่มฟีเจอร์หรูหราอย่างเช่น Docklets, วาดภาพ, การตั้งค่าไดอะลอก ฯลฯ</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Plank, gezegendeki en basit dock demektir. Hedefi, bir docktan beklediğiniz tüm ihtiyaçları karşılamaktır, fazlası değil.</p>
    <p>Ancak, daha gelişmiş özelliklerle başka dock programları oluşturabilecek genişletilebilir bir kütüphanedir de. Bu yüzden Plank, Docky'nin (sürüm 3.0.0'dan itibaren) altında yatan teknolojidir ve Docky'nin Docklets, resimler, ayarlar, iletişim kutuları gibi süslü tüm temel özelliklerini karşılamayı amaçlar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Plank має намір бути найпростішим доком в світі. Мета - забезпечити тільки ті функції, для яких потрібні доки та нічого зайвого.</p>
    <p>Це, проте, бібліотека, яка може бути розширена для створення інших доків-програм з більш розширеним функціоналом. Таким чином, Plank - це основа для Docky (починаючи з версії 3.0.0), яка прагне забезпечити всі основні функції в той час, як Docky розширює його, додаючи гарні речі, як то Доклети, промалювання, діалоги налаштувань, тощо.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uz">
    <p>Plank dunyodagi eng sodda dok bo'lishga mo'ljallangan. Maqsad shunchaki dok bo'lish va boshqa hech narsa emas.</p>
    <p>Ammo, bu kutubxona kengaytirlishi mumkin va rivojlangan funksiyalarga ega boshqa dok dasturlarini yaratish mumkin. Dock Docky (3.0.0 versiyadan boshlab) uchun asos texnlogiya va asosiy xususiyatlarni ta'minlashga qaratilgan, Docky esa qo'shimchalarni qamrab olgan.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="vi">
    <p>Plank được mệnh danh là dock đơn giản nhất trên thế giới. Mục tiêu của Plank chỉ cung cấp những gì dock cần và không còn gì khác.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>Plank绝对是地球上最简洁的Dock。宗旨是拒绝华而不实、只提供一个Dock该有的功能。</p>
    <p>与此同时，它也是一个可以扩展创建更多特性的Dock程序库。因此，Plank实际上是Docky(从版本3.0.0开始)的底层技术，为Docky提供了所有核心的功能。Docky在其基础上扩展了更多酷炫特性如Docklet、画笔、设置对话框等。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>Plank 決心要成為地球上最簡易的 Dock。目的是要做出 Dcok 的所有需求，但沒有任何多餘的東西。</p>
    <p>它，雖然也是個可以擴展開來建立其他具備更多進階功能的 Dock 程式函式庫。因此，Plank 是 Docky (3.0.0 版起) 的基底技術，以提供所有基本核心功能為目標；而 Docky 將之擴展，增添更多新穎的功能，例如 Dock 元件、繪製器、設定對話盒…等等。</p>
  </description>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>dock</keyword>
    <keyword>launch</keyword>
    <keyword>panel</keyword>
    <keyword>start</keyword>
  </keywords>
  <url type="homepage">https://launchpad.net/plank</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.launchpad.net/plank</url>
  <url type="faq">https://answers.launchpad.net/plank</url>
  <url type="translate">https://translations.launchpad.net/plank</url>
  <provides>
    <library>libplank.so.1</library>
    <binary>plank</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.11.89" timestamp="1566230400" />
    <release version="0.11.4" timestamp="1490644800" />
    <release timestamp="1481047200" version="0.11.3" />
    <release version="0.11.2" timestamp="1465190929" />
    <release version="0.11.1" timestamp="1459324800" />
    <release timestamp="1457816400" version="0.11.0" />
    <release version="0.10.1" timestamp="1444388400" />
    <release version="0.10.0" timestamp="1441623600" />
    <release timestamp="1430564400" version="0.9.1" />
    <release version="0.9.0" timestamp="1428836400" />
    <release timestamp="1422187200" version="0.8.1" />
    <release timestamp="1420200000" version="0.8.0" />
    <release timestamp="1411470000" version="0.7.1" />
    <release version="0.7.0" timestamp="1410778800" />
    <release version="0.6.1" timestamp="1400583600" />
    <release timestamp="1397473200" version="0.6.0" />
    <release timestamp="1384689600" version="0.5.0" />
    <release version="0.4.0" timestamp="1382094000" />
    <release version="0.3.0" timestamp="1372158000" />
  </releases>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://people.ubuntu.com/~ricotz/appdata/plank_dock.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://people.ubuntu.com/~ricotz/appdata/plank_preferences_appearance.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://people.ubuntu.com/~ricotz/appdata/plank_preferences_behaviour.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <developer_name>The Plank Developers</developer_name>
  <update_contact>ricotz_at_ubuntu.com</update_contact>
</component>