<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>pulseeffects-legacy</pkgname>
  <icon type="cached" height="64" width="64">pulseeffects.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">pulseeffects.png</icon>
  <id>com.github.wwmm.pulseeffects.desktop</id>
  <name>PulseEffects</name>
  <name lang="sv">PulseEffects</name>
  <name lang="sk">PulseEffects</name>
  <name lang="ru">PulseEffects</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">PulseEffects</name>
  <name lang="pl">PulseEffects</name>
  <name lang="it_IT">PulseEffects</name>
  <name lang="id_ID">PulseEffects</name>
  <name lang="hr">PulseEffects</name>
  <name lang="fr_FR">PulseEffects</name>
  <name lang="de">PulseEffects</name>
  <name lang="cs">PulseEffects</name>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <summary>Audio Effects for PulseAudio Applications</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Ljudeffekter för PulseAudio applikationer</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Zvukové efekty pre aplikácie využívajúce PulseAudio</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Аудиоэффекты для приложений PulseAudio</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Efeitos de Áudio para Programas que Utilizam Pulseaudio</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Efekty dźwiękowe dla programu Pulseaudio</summary>
  <summary lang="it_IT">Effetti Audio per Applicazioni PulseAudio</summary>
  <summary lang="id_ID">Penerap Efek Suara untuk Aplikasi Berbasis Pulseaudio</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Zvučni efekti za Pulseaudio aplikacije</summary>
  <summary lang="fr_FR">Effets audio pour applications PulseAudio</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Audio Effekte für Pulseaudio Anwendungen</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Zvukové efekty pro programy využívající PulseAudio</summary>
  <developer_name>Wellington Wallace</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">Wellington Wallace</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sk">Wellington Wallace</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Уоллис Веллингтон</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Wellington Wallace</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it_IT">Wellington Wallace</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id_ID">Wellington Wallace</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="hr">Wellington Wallace</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Wellington Wallace</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Wellington Wallace</developer_name>
  <description>
    <p>
      PulseEffects is an advanced audio manipulation tools. It includes an
      equalizer, limiter, compressor and a reverberation tool, just to mention
      a few. To complement this there is also a built in spectrum analyzer.
    </p>
    <p>
      Because PulseEffects uses the default PulseAudio sound server it will
      work with most, if not all, applications you use. All supported
      applications are presented in the main window, where each can be enabled
      individually.
    </p>
    <p>
      Besides manipulating sound output, PulseEffects is able to apply effects
      to an input device, such as a microphone. This is, for example, useful in
      audio recording, but it also works well during voice conversations.
    </p>
    <p>
      When PulseEffects is launched it will conveniently remember the
      configuration used in the last session. It is also possible to save
      all the current settings as profiles.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>PulseEffects je pokročilým nástrojem pro zacházení se zvukem. Obsahuje mimo jiné nástroj ekvalizéru, omezovače (limiter), kompresoru a dozvuku. Na doplnění je také vestavěn analyzátor spektra.</p>
    <p>Protože PulseEffects používá výchozí zvukový server PulseAudio, bude pracovat s většinou, pokud už ne se všemi vámi používanými programy. Všechny podporované programy jsou ukázány v hlavním okně, v němž je možné kterýkoli z nich ručně povolit.</p>
    <p>Vedle práce se zvukovým výstupem dokáže PulseEffects efekty použít i na vstupní zařízení, jako je mikrofon. To je užitečné mimo jiné při nahrávání zvuku, pracuje to ale dobře během hlasových hovorů.</p>
    <p>Když je PulseEffects spuštěn, zapamatuje si příhodně nastavení používané při posledním sezení. Je možné i uložení všech nynějších nastavení jako profilů.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>PulseEffects ist ein Audio-Manipulations-Tool. Es enthält einen Equalizer, Limiter, Kompressor, Hall und ein Spektrumanalysator.</p>
    <p>Da PulseEffects den Standard PulseAudio Sound Server benutzt, funktioniert es mit so ziemlich allen Anwendungen. Alle unterstützten Anwendungen werden im Hauptfenster angezeigt, wo alle individuell Ein-/Ausgeschaltet werden können.</p>
    <p>Neben der Sound Manipulation des Ausgangs, kann PulseEffects auch Effekte auf Eingabegeräte, z.B. Mikrofone, anwenden. Dies ist sinnvoll für z.B. Audioaufnahmen oder VOIP Anwendungen.</p>
    <p>Wenn PulseEffects startet, stellt es die Konfiguration der letzten Sitzung wieder her. Es ist auch möglich, die aktuellen Einstellungen als Profil / Preset in einer Datei zu speichern.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr_FR">
    <p>PulseEffects est un outil avancé de manipulation audio. Il inclut, entre autres, un égaliseur, limiteur, compresseur et effet de réverbération. Aussi présent est un analyseur de fréquences.</p>
    <p>Parce que PulseEffects utilise le serveur PulseAudio par défaut, cet outil fonctionne avec la grande majorité des applications. Les applications compatibles sont présentées dans la fenêtre principale, où vous pouvez les activer manuellement.</p>
    <p>En plus de la manipulation de la sortie audio, PulseEffects peut aussi manipuler l'entrée audio, depuis par exemple un microphone; ce qui est utile pour l'enregistrement audio ou pour une conversation.</p>
    <p>PuseEffets se rappelle de la configuration utilisée lors du lancement précédent. Il est aussi possible de sauvegarder tous les paramètres dans des profils personnalisés.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>PulseEffects je napredan alat za manipulaciju zvukom. Uključuje ekvalizator, graničnik, kompresor, alat odjeka te mnoge druge druge alate. Još sadrži i ugrađeni analizator spektra.</p>
    <p>Zato što PulseEffects koristi zadani PulseAudio zvučni poslužitelj, radit će s većinom, ako ne i sa svim aplikacijama koje koristite. Sve podržane aplikacije su prikazane u glavnom prozoru, gdje se na svaku pojedinačno može omogućiti utjecaj efekata.</p>
    <p>Osim manipuliranja izlaza zvuka, PulseEffects može primijeniti efekte i na ulazni uređaj, poput mikrofona. To je na primjer korisno pri snimanju zvuka, ali isto tako funkcionira dobro i tijekom glasovnih razgovora.</p>
    <p>Kad je PulseEffects pokrenut, upotrijebit će podešavanja od prošlog puta. Također je moguće spremiti sve trenutne postavke kao predloške.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id_ID">
    <p>PulseEffects merupakan aplikasi pengubah efek suara. Berisi modul-modul seperti ekualiser, pembatas, kompresor, dan modul penggema. Dilengkapi juga dengan Penganalisis Spektrum untuk memantau efek yang diterapkan.</p>
    <p>PulseEffects bekerja dengan aplikasi berbasis PulseAudio. Aplikasi yang mendukung PulseEffects akan ditampilkan pada jendela utama aplikasi.</p>
    <p>Selain mengolah suara yang keluar, PulseEffects dapat mengolah efek suara seperti pada mikrofon dan pengakat masukan lainnya. PulseEffects juga bekerja dengan baik ketika dipakai dalam percakapan suara.</p>
    <p>Ketika PulseEffects dijalankan, preset terakhir yang dipakai akan termuat otomatis. Anda juga dapat menyimpan pengaturan yang telah dibuat ke dalam profil tersendiri.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it_IT">
    <p>PulseEffects è uno strumento avanzato di manipolazione dell'audio. Include diversi plugin tra cui un equalizzatore, un limitatore, un compressore e uno strumento per il riverbero. È dotato inoltre di un analizzatore di spettro.</p>
    <p>Utilizzando il server audio predefinito PulseAudio, PulseEffects funzionerà con quasi tutte le applicazione installate. Le applicazioni supportate sono mostrate nella finestra principale dove si possono abilitare individualmente.</p>
    <p>Oltre a manipolare il suono in uscita, PulseEffects è in grado di applicare effetti ad un dispositivo di input, come un microfono. È utile, per esempio, nelle registrazioni audio e nelle conversazioni vocali.</p>
    <p>All'avvio di PulseEffects verrà caricata la configurazione usata nell'ultima sessione. È anche possibile salvare tutte le impostazioni correnti in file di profili.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>PulseEffects to zaawansowane narzędzie do manipulacji dźwiękiem. Zawiera między innymi korektor, limiter, kompresor i narzędzie do generowania pogłosu. Uzupełnieniem tego jest wbudowany analizator widma.</p>
    <p>Ponieważ PulseEffects używa domyślnego serwera dźwięku PulseAudio, będzie on działał z większością, jeśli nie wszystkimi używanymi programami. Wszystkie obsługiwane programy są prezentowane w oknie głównym, gdzie każdy z nich może być aktywowany indywidualnie.</p>
    <p>Oprócz manipulowania wyjściem dźwiękowym, PulseEffects jest w stanie zastosować efekty do urządzenia wejściowego, takiego jak mikrofon. Jest to przydatne na przykład przy nagrywaniu dźwięku, ale sprawdza się również podczas rozmów głosowych.</p>
    <p>Podczas uruchamiania, PulseEffects wygodnie przypomni sobie konfigurację użytą w ostatniej sesji. Możliwe jest również zapisanie wszystkich bieżących ustawień w postaci profilów.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>PulseEffects é uma ferramenta avançada de edição de áudio. Ele inclui equalizador, limitador, compressor e um plugin de reverberação. Estas ferramentas são complementadas por um analisador de espectro.</p>
    <p>Como o PulseEffects usa o servidor de áudio padrão PulseAudio ele irá funcionar com a maioria das aplicações que você usa, senão todas. Todos os aplicativos suportados estão presentes na janela principal, onde cada uma pode ser habilitada individualmente.</p>
    <p>Além de manipular saída de som o PulseEffects também é capaz de aplicar efeitos em dispositivos de entrada, como um microfone. Isto é útil, por exemplo, em gravação de áudio mas também funciona em conversas.</p>
    <p>Quando inicializado, o PulseEffects irá convenientemente lembrar das configurações utilizadas na última sessão. Também é possível salvar todas as configurações
como perfis.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>PulseEffects — это продвинутая программа манипуляции звуком в режиме реального времени. Она включает в себя эквалайзер, ограничитель (лимитер), компрессор, утилиту для ревербации и многое другое. Более того, имеется встроенный анализатор аудиоспектра.</p>
    <p>Так как PulseEffects использует стандартный сервер PulseAudio, программа будет работать с большинством используемых Вами приложений. Все поддерживаемые представлены в главном окне, где для каждого могут быть произведены настройки эффектов </p>
    <p>Помимо изменения звука на выходе, PulseEffects также может добавлять аудиоэффекты к входным аудиопотокам, таким как микрофон. Это полезно, например, во время аудиозаписи или голосовой конференции.</p>
    <p>Удобно то, что при запуске PulseEffects автоматически подгрузит настройки из предыдущей сессии работы. Также можно сохранить текущие настройки в набор преднастроек.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>PulseEffects je pokročilý nástroj pre úpravu zvuku. Obsahuje taktiež Equalizér, Limiter, Kompresor, nástroj Ozveny, a viacero ďalších.Pre doplnenie napríklad aj zabudovaný analyzátor spektra.</p>
    <p>Pretože PulseEffects používa predvolene zvukový server PulseAudio, funguje s väčšinou ak nie všetkými programami. Všetky podprované programy sú zobrazené v hlavnom okne, kde je ich možné individuálne povoliť.</p>
    <p>Popri práci s úpravou výstupného zvuku, PulseEffects je možné použiť aj na úpravu vstupných zvukov z mikrofónu. To má výhodu napríklad pri nahrávaní, ale je výborný aj pre hlasové hovory.</p>
    <p>Keď je PulseEffect spustený, zapamätá si posledné používané nastavenia, Taktiež je možné uložiť všetky aktuálne nastavenia ako profily</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>PulseEffects är ett avancerat verktyg för manipulation av ljud. Det innehåller en ljudutjämnare (equalizer), ljudbegränsare (limiter), kompressor och ett efterklangsverktyg (eko), för att bara nämna några få. Där finns även en inbyggd frekvensanalysator som kompletterar dessa.</p>
    <p>Eftersom PulseEffects använder sig av standard PulseAudio som ljudserver stödjer den de flesta, om inte alla, program du använder. Alla applikationer som stöds presenteras i huvudfönstret, där var och en kan aktiveras individuellt.</p>
    <p>Förutom att manipulera dina programs ljud kan PulseEffects tillämpa effekter på en ingångsenhet, såsom en mikrofon. Detta är exempelvis användbart vid ljudinspelning, men det fungerar även bra under röstsamtal.</p>
    <p>När PulseEffects startas kommer det ihåg konfigurationen som användes under den senaste sessionen. Det är också möjligt att spara alla aktuella inställningar som profiler.</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.github.wwmm.pulseeffects.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/wwmm/pulseeffects</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/wwmm/pulseeffects/issues</url>
  <url type="help">https://github.com/wwmm/pulseeffects/blob/master/README.md</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/wwmm/pulseeffects/master/images/appdata-screenshot-01.png</image>
      <caption>Set the volume and turn on/off effects</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Nastaviť hlasitosť a zapnúť/vypnúť efekty</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Настройка громкости и вкл/откл эффектов</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Definir o volume e ligar / desligar efeitos</caption>
      <caption lang="it_IT">Imposta il volume e abilita/disabilita effetti</caption>
      <caption lang="id_ID">Atur Volume dan hidupkan/matikan Efek</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Postavi razinu zvuka te uključi/isključi efekte</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Einstellen der Lautstärke und Ein-/Ausschalten von Effekten</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Nastavit hlasitost a zapnout/vypnout efekty</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/wwmm/pulseeffects/master/images/appdata-screenshot-02.png</image>
      <caption>Includes an equalizer with built-in presets</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Zahrňuje ekvalizér s prednastavenými profilmy</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Содержит эквалайзер с предустановками</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Inclui um equalizador com predefinições incorporadas</caption>
      <caption lang="it_IT">Include un equalizzatore con profili preesistenti</caption>
      <caption lang="id_ID">Dilengkapi dengan Ekualiser dengan Preset Bawaan</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Uključuje i ekvalizator s ugrađenim predlošcima</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Enthält einen Equalizer mit integrierten Presets</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Zahrnuje ekvalizér s vestavěnými přednastaveními</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/wwmm/pulseeffects/master/images/appdata-screenshot-03.png</image>
      <caption>Input Limiter</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Ingångs-begränsning</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Vstupný Obmedzovač</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Ограничитель ввода</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Limitador de Entrada</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Limiter wejścia</caption>
      <caption lang="it_IT">Limitatore Ingresso</caption>
      <caption lang="id_ID">Pembatas Masukan</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Graničnik ulaza</caption>
      <caption lang="fr_FR">Limiteur d'entrée</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Eingabe-Limiter</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Omezovač vstupu</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/wwmm/pulseeffects/master/images/appdata-screenshot-04.png</image>
      <caption>Compressor</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Kompressor</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Kompresor</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Компрессор</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Compressor</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Kompresor</caption>
      <caption lang="it_IT">Compressore</caption>
      <caption lang="id_ID">Kompresor</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Kompresor</caption>
      <caption lang="fr_FR">Compresseur</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Kompressor</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Kompresor</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/wwmm/pulseeffects/master/images/appdata-screenshot-05.png</image>
      <caption>Calibration</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Kalibrering</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Kalibrácia</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Калибровка</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Calibração</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Kalibracja</caption>
      <caption lang="it_IT">Calibrazione</caption>
      <caption lang="id_ID">Kalibrasi</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Kalibracija</caption>
      <caption lang="fr_FR">Calibration</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Kalibrierung</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Kalibrace</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release date="2020-12-21" version="4.8.4" />
    <release date="2020-12-03" version="4.8.3" />
    <release version="4.8.2" date="2020-09-21" />
    <release date="2020-09-18" version="4.8.1" />
    <release version="4.8.0" date="2020-08-15" />
    <release version="4.7.3" date="2020-06-16" />
    <release version="4.7.2" date="2020-03-22" />
    <release version="4.7.1" date="2019-01-14" />
    <release date="2019-12-25" version="4.7.0" />
    <release date="2019-11-28" version="4.6.9" />
    <release date="2019-09-16" version="4.6.8" />
    <release date="2019-09-10" version="4.6.7" />
    <release version="4.6.6" date="2019-08-04" />
    <release date="2019-06-23" version="4.6.5" />
    <release version="4.6.4" date="2019-06-19" />
    <release date="2019-06-02" version="4.6.3" />
    <release version="4.6.2" date="2019-05-30" />
    <release version="4.6.1" date="2019-05-22" />
    <release version="4.6.0" date="2019-04-28" />
    <release version="4.5.9" date="2019-04-13" />
    <release version="4.5.8" date="2019-03-21" />
    <release version="4.5.7" date="2019-03-19" />
    <release date="2019-03-13" version="4.5.6" />
    <release version="4.5.5" date="2019-03-06" />
    <release version="4.5.4" date="2019-03-03" />
    <release version="4.5.3" date="2019-02-27" />
    <release version="4.5.2" date="2019-02-24" />
    <release date="2019-02-10" version="4.5.0" />
    <release version="4.4.7" date="2019-01-21" />
    <release date="2019-01-09" version="4.4.6" />
    <release version="4.4.5" date="2019-01-04" />
    <release date="2018-12-31" version="4.4.4" />
    <release version="4.4.3" date="2018-12-30" />
    <release version="4.4.2" date="2018-12-30" />
    <release version="4.4.1" date="2018-12-03" />
    <release date="2018-10-31" version="4.4.0" />
    <release date="2018-10-24" version="4.3.9" />
    <release version="4.3.8" date="2018-10-16" />
    <release version="4.3.7" date="2018-09-25" />
    <release version="4.3.6" date="2018-09-25" />
    <release date="2018-09-16" version="4.3.5" />
    <release date="2018-09-01" version="4.3.4" />
    <release version="4.3.3" date="2018-08-31" />
    <release date="2018-08-30" version="4.3.2" />
    <release version="4.3.1" date="2018-08-28" />
    <release date="2018-08-28" version="4.3.0" />
    <release version="4.2.9" date="2018-08-26" />
    <release version="4.2.8" date="2018-08-14" />
    <release date="2018-08-12" version="4.2.7" />
    <release version="4.2.6" date="2018-08-10" />
    <release date="2018-08-09" version="4.2.5" />
    <release version="4.2.4" date="2018-08-05" />
    <release version="4.2.3" date="2018-07-30" />
    <release version="4.2.2" date="2018-07-29" />
    <release version="4.2.1" date="2018-07-28" />
    <release date="2018-07-24" version="4.2.0" />
    <release date="2018-07-18" version="4.1.9" />
    <release version="4.1.8" date="2018-07-16" />
    <release date="2018-07-14" version="4.1.7" />
    <release version="4.1.6" date="2018-07-14" />
    <release version="4.1.5" date="2018-07-13" />
    <release date="2018-07-13" version="4.1.4" />
    <release version="4.1.3" date="2018-07-06" />
    <release date="2018-07-01" version="4.1.2" />
    <release date="2018-06-27" version="4.1.1" />
    <release date="2018-06-24" version="4.1.0" />
    <release date="2018-06-24" version="4.0.9" />
    <release date="2018-06-19" version="4.0.8" />
    <release version="4.0.7" date="2018-06-17" />
    <release date="2018-06-16" version="4.0.6" />
    <release date="2018-06-15" version="4.0.5" />
    <release version="4.0.4" date="2018-06-12" />
    <release date="2018-06-12" version="4.0.3" />
    <release version="4.0.2" date="2018-06-08" />
    <release version="4.0.1" date="2018-06-04" />
    <release version="4.0.0" date="2018-06-03" />
    <release date="2018-04-21" version="3.2.3" />
    <release date="2018-04-20" version="3.2.2" />
    <release date="2018-03-01" version="3.2.1" />
    <release version="3.2.0" date="2018-02-04" />
    <release version="3.1.9" date="2018-01-30" />
    <release date="2018-01-30" version="3.1.8" />
    <release version="3.1.7" date="2018-01-23" />
    <release version="3.1.6" date="2017-12-31" />
    <release version="3.1.5" date="2017-12-25" />
    <release version="3.1.4" date="2017-12-18" />
    <release date="2017-12-13" version="3.1.3" />
    <release version="3.1.2" date="2017-12-12" />
    <release version="3.1.1" date="2017-12-09" />
    <release date="2017-12-09" version="3.1.0" />
    <release date="2017-11-28" version="3.0.9" />
    <release version="3.0.8" date="2017-11-16" />
    <release date="2017-11-11" version="3.0.7" />
    <release version="3.0.6" date="2017-10-31" />
    <release version="3.0.5" date="2017-10-22" />
    <release date="2017-10-22" version="3.0.4" />
    <release version="3.0.3" date="2017-10-21" />
    <release date="2017-10-21" version="3.0.2" />
    <release version="3.0.1" date="2017-10-14" />
    <release version="3.0.0" date="2017-09-21" />
    <release version="2.3.6" date="2017-09-01" />
    <release version="2.3.5" date="2017-08-25" />
    <release version="2.3.4" date="2017-08-25" />
    <release version="2.3.3" date="2017-08-22" />
    <release date="2017-08-21" version="2.3.2" />
    <release date="2017-08-20" version="2.3.1" />
    <release date="2017-08-20" version="2.3.0" />
    <release version="2.2.1" date="2017-08-15" />
    <release date="2017-08-15" version="2.2.0" />
    <release version="2.1.2" date="2017-07-29" />
    <release version="2.1.1" date="2017-07-23" />
    <release version="2.1.0" date="2017-07-17" />
    <release date="2017-07-16" version="2.0.9" />
    <release date="2017-07-15" version="2.0.8" />
    <release version="2.0.7" date="2017-07-11" />
    <release version="2.0.6" date="2017-07-08" />
    <release version="2.0.5" date="2017-07-07" />
    <release date="2017-07-07" version="2.0.4" />
    <release version="2.0.3" date="2017-07-04" />
    <release version="2.0.2" date="2017-07-02" />
    <release version="2.0.1" date="2017-07-01" />
    <release version="2.0.0" date="2017-06-30" />
    <release version="1.6.7" date="2017-06-26" />
    <release date="2017-06-25" version="1.6.6" />
    <release date="2017-06-24" version="1.6.5" />
    <release version="1.6.4" date="2017-06-22" />
    <release date="2017-06-20" version="1.6.3" />
    <release version="1.6.2" date="2017-06-18" />
    <release version="1.6.1" date="2017-06-17" />
    <release date="2017-06-15" version="1.6.0" />
    <release version="1.5.8" date="2017-06-13" />
    <release version="1.5.7" date="2017-06-11" />
    <release version="1.5.6" date="2017-06-10" />
    <release version="1.5.5" date="2017-06-08" />
    <release version="1.5.4" date="2017-06-08" />
    <release date="2017-06-06" version="1.5.3" />
    <release date="2017-06-06" version="1.5.2" />
    <release version="1.5.1" date="2017-06-04" />
    <release date="2017-06-04" version="1.5.0" />
    <release date="2017-06-03" version="1.4.8" />
    <release version="1.4.7" date="2017-06-01" />
    <release date="2017-05-30" version="1.4.6" />
    <release version="1.4.5" date="2017-05-30" />
    <release version="1.4.4" date="2017-05-28" />
    <release date="2017-05-27" version="1.4.3" />
    <release version="1.4.2" date="2017-05-27" />
    <release date="2017-05-25" version="1.4.1" />
    <release version="1.4.0" date="2017-05-23" />
    <release date="2017-05-20" version="1.3.6" />
    <release version="1.3.5" date="2017-05-20" />
    <release date="2017-05-20" version="1.3.4" />
    <release version="1.3.3" date="2017-05-18" />
    <release date="2017-05-16" version="1.3.2" />
    <release date="2017-05-12" version="1.3.1" />
    <release date="2017-05-10" version="1.3.0" />
    <release date="2017-05-09" version="1.2.9" />
    <release date="2017-05-06" version="1.2.8" />
    <release version="1.2.7" date="2017-05-02" />
    <release date="2017-05-01" version="1.2.6" />
    <release date="2017-04-25" version="1.2.5" />
    <release version="1.2.4" date="2017-04-23" />
    <release date="2017-04-23" version="1.2.3" />
    <release date="2017-04-23" version="1.2.2" />
    <release version="1.2.1" date="2017-04-22" />
    <release version="1.2.0" date="2017-04-21" />
    <release version="1.1.9" date="2017-04-21" />
    <release date="2017-04-20" version="1.1.8" />
    <release version="1.1.7" date="2017-04-20" />
    <release date="2017-04-19" version="1.1.6" />
    <release date="2017-04-18" version="1.1.5" />
    <release date="2017-04-17" version="1.1.4" />
    <release date="2017-04-14" version="1.1.3" />
    <release date="2017-04-14" version="1.1.2" />
    <release version="1.1.1" date="2017-04-13" />
    <release version="1.1.0" date="2017-04-11" />
    <release version="1.0.9" date="2017-04-09" />
    <release version="1.0.8" date="2017-04-07" />
    <release version="1.0.7" date="2017-03-28" />
    <release version="1.0.6" date="2017-03-28" />
    <release version="1.0.5" date="2017-03-28" />
    <release version="1.0.4" date="2017-03-27" />
    <release date="2017-03-27" version="1.0.3" />
    <release version="1.0.2" date="2017-03-25" />
    <release version="1.0.1" date="2017-03-25" />
    <release version="1.0" date="2017-03-25" />
    <release version="0.9" date="2017-03-24" />
    <release date="2017-03-23" version="0.8" />
    <release version="0.7" date="2017-03-23" />
    <release version="0.6" date="2017-03-23" />
    <release version="0.5" date="2017-03-23" />
    <release version="0.4" date="2017-03-23" />
    <release version="0.3" date="2017-03-23" />
    <release version="0.2" date="2017-03-23" />
    <release version="0.1" date="2017-03-21" />
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <update_contact>contact_AT_hembas.se</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">PulseEffects</translation>
</component>