<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>redshift</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">redshift-gtk.desktop</launchable>
  <icon height="64" width="64" type="cached">redshift.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" height="128" width="128">redshift.png</icon>
  <id type="desktop">redshift-gtk.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>Redshift adjusts the color temperature of your screen according to your surroundings. This may help your eyes hurt less if you are working in front of the screen at night.</p>
    <p>The color temperature is set according to the position of the sun. A different color temperature is set during night and daytime. During twilight and early morning, the color temperature transitions smoothly from night to daytime temperature to allow your eyes to slowly adapt.</p>
    <p>This program provides a status icon that allows the user to control Redshift.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Redshift рэгулюе каляровую тэмпературу экрана ў адпаведнасці з асяроддзем. Гэта можа дапамагчы вашым вачам, калі вы працуеце ноччу.</p>
    <p>Каляровая тэмпература прызначаецца ў адпаведнасці са становішчам сонца. Розная каляровая тэмпература прызначаецца ў начны час і днём. Падчас змяркання і на золку, каляровая тэмпература паступова пераходзіць ад тэмпературы ночы да тэмпературы ў дзённы час, каб вашыя вочы паступова прызвычаіліся.</p>
    <p>У праграмы ёсць значок на прасторы апавяшчэнняў, праз які можна кіраваць Redshift.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El Redshift ajusta la temperatura de color de la pantalla d'acord amb l'entorn. Aquest ajust pot ajudar a reduir el dolor d'ulls si treballeu davant una pantalla a la nit.</p>
    <p>La temperatura de color s'estableix segons la posició del sol. S'estableix una temperatura diferent durant el dia i durant la nit. Durant el capvespre i l'alba, la temperatura de color canvia suaument, de temperatura diürna a temperatura nocturna o viceversa, per permetre que els ulls s'adaptin lentament.</p>
    <p>Aquest programa proporciona una icona de notificació que permet a l'usuari controlar el Redshift.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Aplikace Redshift přizpůsobuje barevnou teplotu obrazovky v závislosti na okolních podmínkách. To může pomoci od únavy očí při práci s počítačem v noci.</p>
    <p>Barevná teplota je nastavována dle pozice Slunce na obloze. Jiná barevná teplota je nastavena během noci a jiná během dne. Při stmívání a rozednívání, barevná teplota pozvolna přejde z jednoho režimu do druhého, aby se oči stačily přizpůsobit.</p>
    <p>Tato aplikace poskytuje stavovou ikonu, pomocí níž je možné Redshift ovládat.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Redshift justerer farvetemperaturen på din skærm i overensstemmelse med dine omgivelser. Dette kan mindske anstrengelser i øjnene hvis du arbejder foran skærmen om natten.</p>
    <p>Farvetemperaturen bliver sat i forhold til solens position og temperaturen ændrer sig fra dag til nat. Omkring solnedgang og solopgang sker der en glidende overgang mellem nattemperatur og dagtemperatur som langsomt lader dine øjne vænne sig til den ændrede farvetemperatur.</p>
    <p>Dette program indeholder et statuslinjeikon som lader brugeren styre Redshift.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Redshift passt die Farbtemperator des Bildschirms an die Umgebung an. Somit werden die Augen geschont wenn man nachts am Bildschirm arbeitet.</p>
    <p>Die Farbtemperatur wird entsprechend zum Stand der Sonne eingestellt. In der Nacht und am Tag werden verschiedene Farbtemperaturen verwendet. Während der Dämmerung und am frühen Morgen wird die Farbtemperatur weich von Nacht auf Tag umgestellt, damit sich Ihre Augen langsam anpassen können.</p>
    <p>Dieses Programm bietet ein Statussymbol, das es dem Benutzer ermöglicht, Redshift zu steuern.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Redshift adjusts the colour temperature of your screen according to your surroundings. This may help your eyes hurt less if you are working in front of the screen at night.</p>
    <p>The colour temperature is set according to the position of the Sun. A different colour temperature is set during night and daytime. During twilight and early morning, the colour temperature transitions smoothly from night to daytime temperature to allow your eyes to slowly adapt.</p>
    <p>This program provides a status icon that allows the user to control Redshift.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Redshift ajusta la temperatura de color de la pantalla de acuerdo con el entorno. Este ajuste puede ayudar a reducir el dolor de ojos si trabaja frente una pantalla por la noche.</p>
    <p>La temperatura de color se establece según la posición del sol. Se establece una temperatura distinta para el día y para la noche. Durante el atardecer y el amanecer, la temperatura de color cambia suavemente, de temperatura diurna a temperatura nocturna o viceversa, para permitir que los ojos se adapten lentamente.</p>
    <p>Este programa proporciona un ícono de notificación que permite al usuario controlar Redshift.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Redshift adapte la température de couleur de votre écran en fonction de l'environnement. Cela peut aider à diminuer les douleurs oculaires si vous travaillez sur un écran de nuit.</p>
    <p>La température de couleur est définie en fonction de la position du soleil. Une température de couleur différente est appliquée durant le jour ou la nuit. Lors du lever ou du coucher du soleil, la température de couleur change doucement pour permettre à vos yeux de s'adapter.</p>
    <p>Ce programme fournit une icône de notification permettant à l'utilisateur de contrôler Redshift.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>Redshift מתאימה את טמפרטורת הצבע של המסך בהתאם לסביבה. דבר שיכול לעזור להפחית כאב בעיניים בעבודה מול המסך בלילה.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>Redshift beállítja a kijelzője színhőmérsékletét a környezetétől függően. Ez segít, hogy kevésbé fájjon a szeme, ha képernyő előtt dolgozik az éjszaka folyamán.</p>
    <p>A színhőmérsékletet a nap helyzetéhez igazítja. Különböző színhőmérsékletet állít be nappal és éjszaka. Szürkületben és kora reggel a színhőmérséklet átmenete az éjszakiról a nappali hőmérsékletre lehetővé teszi, hogy a szem lassan alkalmazkodhasson.</p>
    <p>Ez a program elérhetővé tesz egy állapot ikont, melyen keresztül a felhasználó beállíthatja a Redshift alkalmazást.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Reshift regola la temperatura del colore dello schermo in base all'ambiente circostante. Questo può aiutare a non affaticare la vista se si lavora davanti allo schermo di notte.</p>
    <p>La temperatura del colore è impostata in base alla posizione del sole. Vengono impostate temperature di colore differenti per la notte e per il giorno. Al crepuscolo e al mattino presto, la temperatura del colore passa delicatamente da quella notturna a quella diurna per consentire alla vista di abituarsi in modo graduale.</p>
    <p>Questo programma fornisce un'icona di stato che consente all'utente di controllare Redshift.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>Redshift は環境に応じてお使いの画面の色温度を調整します。これは夜間に画面の前で作業している場合に目への悪影響を軽減させる助けになるかもしれません。</p>
    <p>色温度は太陽の位置に応じて設定されます。昼と夜とでは異なる色温度が設定されます。夕暮れ時や早朝の間は、 色温度は滑らかに変化してゆっくり目を慣れさせることができます。</p>
    <p>このプログラムはユーザが Redshift を制御できるようにするためのステータス アイコンを提供します。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Redshift reguliuoja jūsų ekrano spalvos temperatūrą, priklausomai nuo jus supančios aplinkos. Tai gali sumažinti akių skausmą tuo atveju, jei naktį dirbate priešais kompiuterio ekraną.</p>
    <p>Spalvos temperatūra nustatoma pagal Saulės vietą. Dienos metu ir nakties metu yra nustatomos skirtingos spalvos temperatūros. Sutemus ir ankstų rytą, spalvos temperatūra glotniai pereina iš nakties temperatūros į dienos temperatūrą, taip leisdama jūsų akims po truputį prisitaikyti.</p>
    <p>Ši programa pateikia būsenos piktogramą, kuri leidžia valdyti Redshift.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Rødskift justerer fargetemperaturen på skjermen din etter omgivelsene. Dette bedrer øyenes arbeidsforhold hvis du sitter foran skjermen om natta.</p>
    <p>Fargetermperaturen blir satt i henhold til solas posisjon. Fargetermperaturen er forskjellig for natt og dagtid. I skumringen og tidlig på morgenen toner fargetemperaturen mykt over i dagtermperatur for å la øyene dine tilpasse seg.</p>
    <p>Dette programmet har et statusikon som lar brukeren kontrollere Rødskift.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Redshift stelt de kleurtemperatuur bij van uw scherm aan de hand van uw omgeving. Dit kan u helpen om oogpijn te verminderen als u 's avonds of 's nachts achter een computerscherm werkt.</p>
    <p>De kleurtemperatuur wordt ingesteld aan de hand van de positie van de zon. Bij nacht wordt er een andere kleurtemperatuur ingesteld dan bij dag. Als het schemert of vroeg in de ochtend is, wordt de kleurtemperatuur geleidelijk en soepel van nacht naar dag gebracht, zodat uw ogen er langzaam aan kunnen wennen.</p>
    <p>Dit programma bevat een statuspictogram dat de gebruiker in staat stelt om Redshift te bedienen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Redshift dostosowuje temperaturę barwową wyświetlacza do warunków zewnętrznych. Pomaga w ten sposób uniknąć zmęczenia oczu przy pracy w nocy.</p>
    <p>Temperatura barwowa jest ustawiana w zależności od pozycji słońca. Różni się w dzień i w nocy. Podczas zmierzchania (i świtania), temperatura łagodnie zmienia się z dziennej na nocną (i odwrotnie), pozwalając oczom na powolne przyzwyczajanie się.</p>
    <p>Program dostarcza ikonę, która pozwala użytkownikowi kontrolować Redshift.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Redshift ajusta a temperatura da cor de sua tela de acordo com o que o cerca. Isso ajuda a irritar menos os olhos se você está trabalhando em frente a uma tela à noite.</p>
    <p>A temperatura da cor é definida de acordo com a posição do Sol. Diferentes temperaturas de cores são utilizadas durante a noite e o dia. Ao anoitecer e ao amanhecer, ocorre uma transição suave entre a temperatura de cor da noite para o dia para que seus olhos lentamente se adaptem.</p>
    <p>Esse programa exibe um ícone de status para que seja possível controlar o Redshift.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Redshift настраивает цветовую температуру экрана в соответствии с окружающими вас условиями. Это может, например, помочь снизить усталость глаз при работе на компьютере ночью.</p>
    <p>Цветовая температура устанавливается в зависимости от положения солнца. Ночью и днём используется различная цветовая температура. В сумерки и ранним утром цветовая температура плавно переходит от ночных настроек к дневным, позволяя глазам постепенно адаптироваться.</p>
    <p>Эта программа позволяет управлять RedShift через иконку в трее.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Редшифт мења температуру боје вашег екрана у складу са вашим окружењем. Ово вам може помоћи уколико осећате бол у очима када радите за рачунаром ноћу.</p>
    <p>Температура боје се се подешава у складу са положајем сунца. Другачија температура боје се поставља ноћу а другачија дању. У сумрак и рано јутро температура боје лагано прелази из ноћне у дневну температуру да би се вашим очима омогућило лакше привикавање.</p>
    <p>Овај програм пружа иконицу стања која омогућава кориснику да управља Редшифтом.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Redshift justerar färgtemperaturen på skärmen utefter din omgivning. Det kan göra att dina ögon mindre irriterade om du arbetar framför skärmen på natten.</p>
    <p>Färgtemperaturen ställs in beroende på positionen av solen. En annan färgtemperatur sätts under natten och dagen. Under skymning och tidigt på morgonen övergår färgtemperaturen smidigt från natt till dagtidstemperatur för att ge dina ögon tid att långsamt anpassa sig.</p>
    <p>Detta program skapar en statusikon som gör det möjligt för användaren att styra Redshift.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Redshift налаштовує колірну температуру вашого дисплею відповідно до навколишнього природного середовища. Це може зменшити втому ваших очей під час роботи перед екраном в ночі.</p>
    <p>Колірна температура налаштовується відповідно до позиції сонця. Різна колірна температура відображення монітору вмикається у залежності від періоду доби. Під час настання сутінків чи сходу сонця, колірна температура повільно переходить із нічної до денної температури, що дозволяє вашим очам повільно адаптуватися.</p>
    <p>Ця програма супроводжується статусною піктограмою, що дозволяє користувачеві контролювати Redshift.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>红移(Redshift) 根据你的周围环境调节你的屏幕色温。如果夜晚在屏幕前工作，这可以减少你眼睛受到的伤害。</p>
    <p>该软件可以根据日照位置、日夜变化来设置屏幕色温，随着时间推移，色温会逐渐转变，保证让您的眼睛能够舒舒服服地适应。</p>
    <p>该程序提供了状态图标允许用户通过它控制 Redshift 。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>Redshift 根據你周圍環境來調節整螢幕色溫。
如果夜晚在螢幕前工作，這可以減少眼睛受到傷害。</p>
    <p>根據太陽位置日夜變化來設置螢幕色溫。隨著日夜交替時間轉換，色溫設置則會逐漸變化，可讓您的眼睛能夠漸漸地適應。</p>
    <p>軟體提供狀態圖示，讓使用者來控制 Redshift 。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://jonls.dk/assets/screenshot1.png</image>
      <caption>The Redshift information window overlaid with an example of the redness effect</caption>
      <caption lang="be">Інфармацыйнае акно Redshift пакажа прыклад эфекту пачырванення</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">La finestra d'informació del Redshift es superposa amb un exemple de l'efecte d'envermelliment</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Informační okno aplikace Redshift, překryté ukázkou efektu zabarvení do červena</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Informationsvinduet i Redshift med en effekt lagt over som viser et eksempel på den rødlige effekt</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Das Redshift-Informationsfenster mit einem Beispiel des Rötungseffektes überlagert</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">The Redshift information window overlaid with an example of the redness effect</caption>
      <caption lang="es">La ventana de información de Redshift se superpone con un ejemplo del efecto de enrojecimiento</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">La fenêtre d'information de Redshift superpose un exemple de l'effet de rougeur.</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">A Redshift információs ablak egy példa vörös effektus átmenettel borított</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La finestra delle informazioni di Redshift mostra un esempio sovrapposto dell'effetto rosso</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">赤み効果の例で覆われた Redshift 情報ウィンドウ</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Redshift informacinis langas, padengtas pavyzdiniu raudonumo efektu</caption>
      <caption lang="nb">Rødskift sitt informasjonsvindu med et eksempel på rødhetseffekten lagt over det</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Het Redshift-informatievenster getoond met een voorbeeld van het rode effect</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Okno Redshift przedstawia przykład dostosowania przesunięcia ku czerwieni.</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">A janela de informação sobreposta do redshift exibe um exemplo do efeito avermelhado</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Информационное окно Redshift перекрыто примером эффекта тёплого света</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Прозор са подацима Редшифта који је прекриван примером ефекта црвенила.</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Informationsfönstret för Redshift övertäckt med ett exempel på rödhetseffekten</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Інформаційне вікно Redshift  накладене прикладом ефекту почервонніння</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">Redshift 信息窗口覆盖了红移效果的示例。</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">Redshift 資訊視窗鋪上一層紅暈效果的的示範</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">http://jonls.dk/redshift/</url>
  <updatecontact>jonlst@gmail.com</updatecontact>
</component>