<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>rsibreak</pkgname>
  <icon width="64" type="cached" height="64">rsibreak.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" height="128" type="cached">rsibreak.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.rsibreak</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="ca">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="cs">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="de">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="el">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="es">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="et">RSIBreak</name>
  <name lang="fi">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="fr">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="gl">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="id">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="it">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="ko">RSI 휴식</name>
  <name lang="lt">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="nl">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="pl">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="pt">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="sk">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="sl">RSI Break</name>
  <name lang="sv">RSIbreak</name>
  <name lang="uk">RSIBreak</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxRSI Breakxx</name>
  <summary>Utility to help prevent repetitive strain injury</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Utilitat per ajudar a prevenir la síndrome del canal carpià</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Utilitat per ajudar a prevenir la síndrome del canal carpià</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Dienstprogramm zur Vorbeugung gegen das RSI-Syndrom</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Εργαλείο για την αποφυγή κακώσεων λόγω επεναλαμβανόμενης καταπόνησης</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Utility to help prevent repetitive strain injury</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Utilidad para prevenir las lesiones por esfuerzo repetitivo</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Tööriist ülekoormuskahjustuse vältimiseks</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Auttaa ehkäisemään rasitusvammoja</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Utilitaire contribuant à éviter les troubles musculo-squelettiques</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Utilidade para axudar a evitar as lesións por tensión repetitiva</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Utilitas untuk membantu mencegah cedera regangan berulang</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Strumento per la prevenzione del disturbo degli arti superiori da lavoro</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">반복성 긴장 장애를 예방하는 유틸리티</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Paslaugų programa, skirta neleisti pasikartojančios įtampos traumų</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Hulpmiddel om te helpen RSI te voorkomen</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Narzędzie pomagające uniknąć urazów wskutek powtarzającego się wysiłku</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Utilitário para ajudar a evitar lesões por tensão repetitiva</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Utilitário para ajudar a prevenir lesões por esforço repetitivo</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Pomožni program za preprečevanje poškodb zaradi ponavljajočih se gibov</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Verktyg för att hjälpa till att förhindra belastningsskador</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Програма, яка намагається запобігти шкоді вашому здоров'ю від постійного напруження</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxUtility to help prevent repetitive strain injuryxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Prolonged use of a mouse and keyboard can cause a repetitive strain injury
    (RSI), so computer users are advised to take regular breaks.</p>
    <p>RSIBreak helps prevent repetitive strain injuries by keeping track of usage
    patterns and periodically informing users to take breaks.  During break
    periods, RSIBreak can either show an unobtrusive message, lock the screen
    entirely, or present a slideshow.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>L'ús prolongat del ratolí i el teclat pot provocar la síndrome del canal carpià (en anglès «repetitive strain injury» o RSI), de manera que aconsella als usuaris d'ordinador que facin pauses regulars.</p>
    <p>El RSIBreak ajuda a evitar la síndrome del canal carpià fent un seguiment dels patrons d'ús i informant periòdicament als usuaris que facin pauses. Durant els períodes de pausa, el RSIBreak pot mostrar un missatge no intrusiu, bloquejar completament la pantalla, o mostrar un passi de dispositives.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>L'ús prolongat del ratolí i el teclat pot provocar la síndrome del canal carpià (en anglés «repetitive strain injury» o RSI), de manera que aconsella als usuaris d'ordinador que facen pauses regulars.</p>
    <p>El RSIBreak ajuda a evitar la síndrome del canal carpià fent un seguiment dels patrons d'ús i informant periòdicament als usuaris que facen pauses. Durant els períodes de pausa, el RSIBreak pot mostrar un missatge no intrusiu, bloquejar completament la pantalla, o mostrar un passe de dispositives.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Η παρατεταμένη χρήση ποντικιού και πληκτρολογίου ίσως προκαλέσει σύνδρομο κακώσεων λόγω επαναλαμβανόμενης καταπόνησης (RSI), έτσι συνιστάται στους χρήστες υπολογιστών να κάνουν συχνά διαλείμματα.</p>
    <p>Το RSIBreak βοηθάει στην αποφυγή κακώσεων λόγω επαναλαμβανόμενης καταπόνησης ανιχνεύοντας μοτίβα χρήσης και ενημερώνοντας περιοδικά τους χρήστες για να κάνουν διάλειμμα. Κατά τις περιόδους των διαλειμμάτων το RSIBreak μπορεί να εμφανίσει ένα μη παρεμβατικό μήνυμα, να κλειδώσει την οθόνη ή να κάνει παρουσίαση διαφανειών.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>Prolonged use of a mouse and keyboard can cause a repetitive strain injury (RSI), so computer users are advised to take regular breaks.</p>
    <p>RSIBreak helps prevent repetitive strain injuries by keeping track of usage patterns and periodically informing users to take breaks. During break periods, RSIBreak can either show an unobtrusive message, lock the screen entirely, or present a slideshow.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>El uso prolongado del ratón y del teclado puede provocar una lesión por esfuerzo repetitivo (RSI), por lo que se recomienda hacer pausas regulares.</p>
    <p>RSIBreak le ayuda a prevenir lesiones por esfuerzo repetitivo haciendo un seguimiento de patrones de uso e informando periódicamente al usuario de que debe hacer pausas. Durante los periodos de pausa, RSIBreak puede mostrar un mensaje no intrusivo, bloquear completamente la pantalla o mostrar una presentación.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Pikaajaline hiire ja klaviatuuri kasutamine võib tekitada ülekoormuskahjustust (RSI), mistõttu arvutikasutajatel on soovitatav teha regulaarseid pause.</p>
    <p>RSIBreak aitab vältida ülekoormuskahjustusi, hoides silma peal arvuti kasutamise mustril ja teavitades kasutajat perioodiliselt vajaduse kohta teha paus. Pauside ajal võib RSIBreak näidata meeleolu leevendavat sõnumit, lukustada ekraani või panna käima slaidiseansi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Hiiren ja näppäimistön pitkäaikainen käyttö voi aiheuttaa rasitusvamman, joten tietokoneen käytössä olisi hyvä pitää säännöllisesti taukoja.</p>
    <p>RSI Break auttaa ehkäisemään rasitusvammoja tarkkailemalla tietokoneen käyttöä ja opastamalla käyttäjää pitämään säännöllisesti taukoja. Taukojen aikana RSI Break näyttää joko huomaamattoman viestin, lukitsee näytön täydellisesti tai esittää diaesityksen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>L'utilisation prolongée d'une souris et d'un clavier est susceptible d'occasionner des troubles musculo-squelettiques, il est conseillé aux utilisateurs d'ordinateurs de faire des pauses régulières.</p>
    <p>RSIBreak contribue à éviter les troubles musculo-squelettiques en surveillant leur utilisation et en leur recommandant régulièrement de faire une pause. Durant les pauses, RSIBreak peut afficher un message non bloquant, verrouiller entièrement l'écran ou présenter des diapositives.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>O uso prolongado de rato ou teclado pode causar lesións por tensión repetitiva (RSI), así que aos usuarios de computador recoméndaselles facer descansos regulares.</p>
    <p>RSIBreak axuda a evitar as lesións por tensión repetitiva facendo un seguimento dos padróns de uso e informando de maneira periódica aos usuarios de que fagan descansos. Durante os períodos de descanso, RSIBreak pode mostrar unha mensaxe non intrusiva, bloquear completamente a pantalla ou reproducir unha presentación de diapositivas.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Penggunaan mouse dan keyboard yang lama bisa menyebabkan cedera regangan berulang (RSI), sehingga pengguna komputer disarankan untuk beristirahat secara teratur.</p>
    <p>RSIBreak membantu mencegah cedera regangan berulang dengan melacak pola penggunaan dan secara berkala memberi tahu pengguna untuk beristirahat. Selama periode istirahat, RSIBreak bisa menampilkan pesan yang tidak mencolok, mengunci layar seluruhnya, atau menyuguhkan tampilan slide.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>L'uso prolungato di mouse e tastiera può causare il disturbo degli arti superiori da lavoro (repetitive strain injury, RSI), per cui si consiglia agli utenti di computer di effettuare delle pause con regolarità.</p>
    <p>RSIBreak aiuta a prevenire il disturbo degli arti superiori da lavoro tenendo traccia degli schermi di utilizzo ed informando gli utenti di effettuare delle pause. Negli intervalli di pausa, RSIBreak può mostrare un messaggio non appariscente, bloccare totalmente lo schermo, o mostrare una sequenza di immagini.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>마우스와 키보드를 오래 사용하면 반복성 긴장 장애(RSI)가 발생할 수 있습니다. 컴퓨터를 사용하는 중간중간 휴식을 취하는 것을 권장합니다.</p>
    <p>RSIBreak는 사용 패턴을 추적하고 주기적으로 휴식 알림을 표시하여 반복성 긴장 장애를 예방합니다. 휴식 시간 동안에는 RSIBreak에서 메시지를 표시하거나, 화면을 잠그거나 슬라이드 쇼를 표시할 수 있습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Užsitęsęs naudojimasis pele ar klaviatūra gali sukelti pasikartojančios įtampos traumas (RSI), todėl kompiuterio naudotojams yra patariama daryti reguliarias pertraukas.</p>
    <p>Programa RSIBreak padeda išvengti pasikartojančios įtampos traumų, sekdama naudojimosi kompiuteriu šablonus ir periodiškai informuodama naudotojus, kad pasidarytų pertrauką. Pertraukų metu, RSIBreak gali rodyti neįkyrų pranešimą, visiškai užrakinti ekraną arba pateikti skaidrių rodymą.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Langdurig gebruik van een muis en toetsenbord kan repetitive strain injury (RSI) veroorzaken, computergebruikers worden geadviseerd om regelmatig pauzes te nemen.</p>
    <p>RSIBreak helpt om repetitive strain injuries te voorkomen door het gebruikspatroon te volgend en periodiek gebruikers te informeren om pauzes te nemen. Gedurende pauzemomenten kan RSIBreak een niet vervelend bericht tonen, het scherm geheel blokkeren of een diashow tonen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Długie używanie myszy i klawiatury może spowodować uraz wskutek powtarzającego się wysiłku (RSI), więc zachęca się użytkowników komputera do robienia sobie regularnych przerw.</p>
    <p>RSIBreak pomaga uniknąć urazów wskutek powtarzającego się wysiłku śledząc aktywność i okresowo zachęcając użytkownika do zrobienia sobie przerwy. Podczas przerw, RSIBreak może pokazać nieprzeszkadzającą wiadomość, całkowicie zablokować ekran, lub przedstawić pokaz obrazów.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O uso prolongado de um rato ou teclado poderá criar lesões por tensão repetitiva (RSI), como problemas de túnel cárpico, pelo que os utilizadores de computadores são aconselhados a fazer pausas regulares.</p>
    <p>O RSIBreak ajuda a evitar essas lesões, mantendo um registo dos padrões de utilização e avisando periodicamente os utilizadores para fazerem pausas. Durante os períodos de pausa, o RSIBreak poderá mostrar uma mensagem não incómoda, bloquear o ecrã por inteiro ou mostrar uma apresentação.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>O uso prolongado do mouse ou teclado pode causar lesões por esforço repetitivo (LER), sendo recomendado que os usuários de computadores façam pausas regulares.</p>
    <p>O RSIBreak ajuda a prevenir essas lesões, mantendo um registro dos padrões de uso e avisando os usuários para fazerem pausas periódicas. Durante os períodos de pausa, o RSIBreak poderá mostrar uma mensagem discreta, bloquear a tela por completo ou mostrar uma apresentação de slides.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Dolgotrajna uporaba miške in tipkovnice lahko povzroči poškodbe zaradi ponavljajočih se gibov (RSI), zato uporabnikom računalnikov svetuje redne odmore.</p>
    <p>RSIBreak poskuša preprečevati poškodbe zaradi ponavljajočih se gibov s sledenjem vzorcev uporabe in občasno obvešča uporabnike, da si odpočijejo. Med odmori lahko RSIBreak prikaže nevsiljivo sporočilo, v celoti zaklene zaslon ali pa predstavi diaprojekcijo.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Långvarig användning av mus och tangentbord kan orsaka belastningsskador (Repetitive Strain Injury - RSI), och därför råds datoranvändare att ta regelbundna raster.</p>
    <p>RSIbreak hjälper till att förhindra belastningsskador genom att hålla reda på användningsmönster och periodiskt informera användare om att ta raster. Under raster kan RSIbreak antingen visa ett diskret meddelande, låsa skärmen helt och hållet eller visa ett bildspel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Надмірне тривале користування мишею та клавіатурою може призвести до шкоди здоров'ю, заподіяної постійним напруженням (RSI), тому лікарі рекомендують користувачам комп'ютерів робити регулярні перерви у роботі.</p>
    <p>RSIBreak допомагає запобігти шкідливій для здоров'я надмірній втомі, стежачи за користуванням комп'ютером і періодично інформуючи користувача про те, що слід робити перерви у роботі. Під час перерв RSIBreak може показувати ненав'язливе повідомлення, блокувати екран повністю або показувати вказані користувачем слайди.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxProlonged use of a mouse and keyboard can cause a repetitive strain injury (RSI), so computer users are advised to take regular breaks.xx</p>
    <p>xxRSIBreak helps prevent repetitive strain injuries by keeping track of usage patterns and periodically informing users to take breaks. During break periods, RSIBreak can either show an unobtrusive message, lock the screen entirely, or present a slideshow.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://userbase.kde.org/RSIBreak</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=rsibreak</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=rsibreak&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.rsibreak.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>RSIBreak Stats.</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Estadístiques del RSIBreak.</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">Estadístiques del RSIBreak.</caption>
      <caption lang="de">RSIBreak-Statistik</caption>
      <caption lang="el">RSIBreak stats.</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">RSIBreak Stats.</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Estadísticas de RSIBreak.</caption>
      <caption lang="et">RSIBreaki statistika.</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">RSI Breakin tilastot.</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Statistiques RSIBreak.</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Estatísticas de RSIBreak.</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Statistik RSIBreak.</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Statistiche di RSIBreak.</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">RSIBreak 통계.</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">RSIBreak statistika.</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">RSIBreak Statistieken.</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Statystyki RSIBreak.</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Estatísticas do RSIBreak.</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Estatísticas do RSIBreak.</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">RSIBreak štatistiky</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">RSIBreak statistike.</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">RSIbreak statistik.</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Статистика у RSIBreak.</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxRSIBreak Stats.xx</caption>
      <caption lang="zh-TW">RSIBreak 統計</caption>
      <image type="source" height="518" width="801">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/rsibreak/rsibreak.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>rsibreak</binary>
  </provides>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>