<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>skrooge</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.skrooge.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" height="64" type="cached">skrooge.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" type="cached" width="128">skrooge.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.skrooge</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="ar">راصد</name>
  <name lang="ca">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="cs">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="da">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="de">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="el">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="es">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="et">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="fi">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="fr">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="gl">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="ia">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="id">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="it">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="ko">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="nl">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="pl">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="pt">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="ru">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="sk">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="sl">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="sv">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="tr">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="uk">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxSkroogexx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">Skrooge</name>
  <summary>Single-entry bookkeeping for home use</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">مسك الدفاتر للاستخدام المنزلي</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Comptabilitat d'entrada única per a ús particular</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Comptabilitat d'entrada única per a ús particular</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Einfache Buchführung für den privaten Gebrauch</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Λογιστική απλών εγγραφών για οικιακή χρήση</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Single-entry bookkeeping for home use</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Contabilidad de registro único para uso doméstico</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Comptabilité à partie simple pour un usage domestique</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Pembukuan tunggal untuk penggunaan rumahan</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Contabilità a partita semplice per uso domestico</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">가정용 단식 부기 가계부</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Enkelvoudige boekhouding voor thuisgebruik</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Pojedyncze wpisy księgujący do domowego użytku</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Contabilidade de registo único para uso doméstico</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Contabilidade de entrada única para uso doméstico</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Управление личными финансами, основанное на принципе простой записи</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Enostavno knjigovodstvo za domačo rabo</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Enkel bokföring för hemanvändning</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Бухгалтерська система із одинарним записом для домашнього використання</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxSingle-entry bookkeeping for home usexx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Skrooge is a personal finance manager powered by KDE that aims to be simple and intuitive. Skrooge allows you to keep track of your expenses and income, categorize them, and build reports of them.</p>
    <p lang="ar">راصد هو مدير مالي شخصي مدعوم من كدي ويهدف إلى أن يكون بسيطًا وبديهيًا. يسمح لك راصد بتتبع نفقاتك ودخلك، وتصنيفها، وإنشاء تقارير عنها.</p>
    <p lang="ca">L'Skrooge és un gestor de les finances personals desenvolupat pel KDE, que té l'objectiu de ser senzill i intuïtiu. L'Skrooge permet registrar els ingressos i les despeses, categoritzar-les i fer-ne informes.</p>
    <p lang="ca-valencia">L'Skrooge és un gestor de les finances personals desenvolupat pel KDE, que té l'objectiu de ser senzill i intuïtiu. L'Skrooge permet registrar els ingressos i les despeses, categoritzar-les i fer-ne informes.</p>
    <p lang="de">Skrooge ist eine persönliche Finanzverwaltung auf Basis von KDE, der einfach und intuitiv sein soll. Mit Skrooge können Sie Ihre Ausgaben und Einnahmen im Auge behalten, sie zu kategorisieren und Berichte darüber erstellen.</p>
    <p lang="el">Το Skrooge είναι ένας προσωπικός διαχειριστής των οικονομικών από το KDE που στοχεύει να είναι απλός και διαισθητικός. Με το Skrooge πρακολουθείτε τα έξοδα και τα έσοδα, τα κατηγοριοποιείτε και εκδίδετε σχετικές αναφορές.</p>
    <p lang="en-GB">Skrooge is a personal finance manager powered by KDE that aims to be simple and intuitive. Skrooge allows you to keep track of your expenses and income, categorise them, and build reports of them.</p>
    <p lang="es">Skrooge es un gestor de finanzas personales creado por KDE que pretende ser sencillo e intuitivo. Skrooge le permite seguir el rastro de sus gastos e ingresos, asignarles categorías y crear informes sobre ellos.</p>
    <p lang="et">Skrooge on KDE isiklike rahaasjade haldamise tööriist, mille siht on olla lihtne ja mõistetav. Skrooge võimaldab hoida silma peal väljaminekutel ja sissetulekutel, neid liigitada ja nende kohta aruandeid koostada lasta.</p>
    <p lang="fr">Skrooge est un gestionnaire de finances personnelles de KDE, qui vise à être simple et intuitif. Skooge vous permet de suivre vos dépenses et revenus, de les catégoriser, et de fabriquer des rapports.</p>
    <p lang="gl">Skrooge é un xestor de finanzas persoais baseado en KDE, e que ten por obxectivo ser sinxelo e intuitivo. Skrooge permite facer un seguimento dos gastos e ingresos, organizalos por categorías, e construír informes sobre os mesmos.</p>
    <p lang="id">Skrooge adalah sebuah pengelola keuangan personal yang diberdayakan oleh KDE yang bertujuan untuk menjadi sederhana dan intuitif. Skrooge memungkinkan Anda melacak pengeluaran dan pendapatan Anda, mengategorikannya, dan membuat laporannya.</p>
    <p lang="it">Skrooge è un gestore delle finanze personali, semplice e intuitivo, che utilizza KDE, il cui scopo è tenere traccia delle tue entrate e uscite, di categorizzarle e creare rapporti.</p>
    <p lang="ko">Skrooge는 KDE의 간단하고 직관적인 개인 재무 관리자입니다. Skrooge에서는 수입과 지출을 관리하고, 각각 항목에 분류를 할당하고, 보고서를 작성할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p lang="nl">Skrooge is een persoonlijke beheerder van financiën binnen KDE, met als doel eenvoudig en intuïtief te zijn. Skrooge stelt u in staat uw uitgaven en inkomsten bij te houden, ze te categoriseren en er over te rapporteren.</p>
    <p lang="pl">Skrooge jest programem do zarządzania finansami osobistymi napędzanym przez KDE, którego celem jest bycie prostym i intuicyjnym. Skrooge umożliwia śledzenie twoich rozchodów, przychodów, kategoryzowanie ich i tworzenie dla nich sprawozdań.</p>
    <p lang="pt">O Skrooge é um gestor de finanças pessoais que usa a plataforma KDE, pretendendo ser simples e intuitivo. O Skrooge permite-lhe manter um registo das suas despesas e receitas, classificá-las e criar relatórios sobre elas.</p>
    <p lang="pt-BR">Skrooge é um gerenciador de finanças pessoais desenvolvido pelo KDE com o objetivo de ser simples e intuitivo. Ele permite manter um registro das suas despesas e receitas, classificá-las e criar relatórios sobre elas.</p>
    <p lang="ru">Skrooge — приложение для управления личными финансами с интуитивно-понятным интерфейсом, разработанное KDE. Skrooge позволяет отслеживать доходы и расходы, назначать им категории и формировать по ним отчёты.</p>
    <p lang="sl">Skrooge je osebni finančni upravljalnik, ki ga poganja KDE, s ciljem da preprost in intuitiven. Skrooge vam omogoča, da spremljate svoje stroške in dohodke, jih kategorizirate in sestavite poročila o njih.</p>
    <p lang="sv">Skrooge är ett hemekonomiprogram drivet av KDE, med målsättning att vara enkelt och intuitivt. Skrooge låter dig hålla reda på dina utgifter och intäkter, kategorisera dem, och skapa rapporter om dem.</p>
    <p lang="uk">Skrooge — програма для керування особистими фінансами, створена на основі технологій KDE. Вона проста і інтуїтивно зрозуміла. За допомогою Skrooge ви зможете стежити за вашими витратами та прибутками, розподіляти записи за категоріями та створювати на їхній основі звіти.</p>
    <p lang="x-test">xxSkrooge is a personal finance manager powered by KDE that aims to be simple and intuitive. Skrooge allows you to keep track of your expenses and income, categorize them, and build reports of them.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p lang="ar">الميزات:</p>
    <p lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p lang="el">Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <p lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p lang="es">Funciones:</p>
    <p lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p lang="fi">Ominaisuuksia:</p>
    <p lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p lang="ia">Characteristicas:</p>
    <p lang="id">Fitur:</p>
    <p lang="it">Caratteristiche:</p>
    <p lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p lang="tr">Özellikler:</p>
    <p lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p lang="zh-CN">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY import/export</li>
      <li lang="ar">استيراد / تصدير QIF ، CSV ، SKROOGE ، KMYMONEY </li>
      <li lang="ca">Importació/exportació de QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Importació/exportació de QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="de">Import und Export der Formate QIF, CSV, Skrooge, KMymoney</li>
      <li lang="el">Εισαγωγή/εξαγωγή QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY import/export</li>
      <li lang="es">Importar y exportar QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="et">QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY import/eksport</li>
      <li lang="fi">QIF-, CSV-, Skrooge- ja KMyMoney-tuonti ja -vienti</li>
      <li lang="fr">Importation / exportation QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY </li>
      <li lang="gl">Permite importar e exportar ficheiros nos formatos QIF, CSV, SKROOGE e KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="ia">importation/exportation de QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="id">Impor/ekspor QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="it">Importazione ed esportazione QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="ko">QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY 가져오기/내보내기</li>
      <li lang="nl">Importeren/exporteren van QIF, CSV, SKROOGE en KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="pl">Import/eksport QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="pt">Importação/exportação para QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Importação/exportação para QIF, CSV, SKROOGE e KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="ru">Импорт и экспорт файлов QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="sl">uvoz/zvoz QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="sv">Import och export av QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="tr">QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY içe aktarma/dışa aktarma</li>
      <li lang="uk">Імпортування та експортування даних QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxQIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY import/exportxx</li>
      <li lang="zh-CN">QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY 导入/导出</li>
      <li>Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK and MONEY MANAGER EX import</li>
      <li lang="ar">استيراد Microsoft Money و OFX و QFX و MT940 و GNUCASH و GRISBI و HOMEBANK و MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="ca">Importació del Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK i MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Importació del Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK i MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="de">Import der Formate Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK und MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="el">Εισαγωγή Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK και MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK and MONEY MANAGER EX import</li>
      <li lang="es">Importar de Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK y MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="et">Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK ja MONEY MANAGER EX import</li>
      <li lang="fi">Microsoft Money-, OFX-, QFX-, MT940-, GNUCash-, Grisbi-, Homebank- ja Money Manager Ex -tuonti</li>
      <li lang="fr">Importation Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK et MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="gl">Permite importar ficheiros nos formatos Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK e MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="ia">Importation de Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK e MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="id">Impor Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK dan MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="it">Importazione Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK e MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="ko">Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK, MONEY MANAGER EX 가져오기</li>
      <li lang="nl">Importeren van Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK en MONEY MANAGER</li>
      <li lang="pl">Import Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK oraz MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="pt">Importação do Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK e MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Importação do Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK e MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="ru">Импорт файлов Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK и MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="sl">uvoz Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK in MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="sv">Import av Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK och MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="tr">Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK ve MONEY MANAGER EX içe aktarma</li>
      <li lang="uk">Імпортування даних Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK та MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxMicrosoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK and MONEY MANAGER EX importxx</li>
      <li lang="zh-CN">Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK 和 MONEY MANAGER EX 导入</li>
      <li>Advanced Graphical Reports</li>
      <li lang="ar">تقارير رسومية متقدمة</li>
      <li lang="ca">Informes gràfics avançats</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Informes gràfics avançats</li>
      <li lang="de">Erweiterte grafische Berichte</li>
      <li lang="el">Προηγμένες γραφικές αναφορές</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Advanced Graphical Reports</li>
      <li lang="es">Informes gráficos avanzados</li>
      <li lang="et">Täiustatud graafilised aruanded</li>
      <li lang="fi">Edistyneet graafiset raportit</li>
      <li lang="fr">Rapports graphique avancés</li>
      <li lang="gl">Informes gráficos avanzados</li>
      <li lang="id">Laporan Grafikal Tingkat-lanjut</li>
      <li lang="it">Rapporti grafici avanzati</li>
      <li lang="ko">고급 그래픽 보고서</li>
      <li lang="nl">Geavanceerde grafische rapporten</li>
      <li lang="pl">Rozbudowane sprawozdania graficzne</li>
      <li lang="pt">Relatórios Gráficos Avançados</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Relatórios gráficos avançados</li>
      <li lang="ru">Расширенные графические отчёты</li>
      <li lang="sl">Napredna grafična poročila</li>
      <li lang="sv">Avancerade grafiska rapporter</li>
      <li lang="tr">Gelişmiş Grafik Raporları</li>
      <li lang="uk">Розширені графічні звіти</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxAdvanced Graphical Reportsxx</li>
      <li lang="zh-CN">高级图形报表</li>
      <li>Multiple tabs to help you organize your work</li>
      <li lang="ar">علامات تبويب متعددة لمساعدتك على تنظيم عملك</li>
      <li lang="ca">Múltiples pestanyes us ajuden a organitzar el treball</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Múltiples pestanyes vos ajuden a organitzar el treball</li>
      <li lang="de">Mehrere Unterfenster um Ihre Arbeit zu organisieren</li>
      <li lang="el">Πολλές καρτέλες για την οργάνωση της εργασίας σας</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Multiple tabs to help you organise your work</li>
      <li lang="es">Múltiples pestañas para ayudarle a organizar su trabajo</li>
      <li lang="et">Mitme kaardi kasutamine tegevuse paremaks korraldamiseks</li>
      <li lang="fr">Plusieurs onglets pour vous aider à organiser votre travail</li>
      <li lang="gl">Dispón de varios separadores para permitirlle organizar o traballo</li>
      <li lang="id">Tab yang multipel untuk membantu Anda mengatur pekerjaan Anda</li>
      <li lang="it">Più schede ti aiutano a organizzare il tuo lavoro</li>
      <li lang="ko">작업을 정리할 수 있는 다양한 탭</li>
      <li lang="nl">Meerdere tabbladen om uw werk te helpen organiseren</li>
      <li lang="pl">Wiele kart ułatwiających pracę</li>
      <li lang="pt">Diversas páginas que o ajudam a organizar o seu trabalho</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Diversas abas que auxiliam na organização do seu trabalho</li>
      <li lang="ru">Вкладки для удобной организации работы</li>
      <li lang="sl">Več zavihkov, ki vam pomagajo organizirati svoje delo</li>
      <li lang="sv">Flera flikar för att hjälpa till att organisera arbetet</li>
      <li lang="uk">Декілька вкладок для упорядковування вашої роботи</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxMultiple tabs to help you organize your workxx</li>
      <li>Infinite undo/redo (even after the file was closed !)</li>
      <li lang="ar">التراجع / الإعادة اللانهائية (حتى بعد إغلاق الملف!)</li>
      <li lang="ca">Desfer/refer infinits (inclús després de tancar el fitxer!)</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Desfer/refer infinits (inclús després de tancar el fitxer!)</li>
      <li lang="de">Unbegrenztes Zurücknehmen und Wiederherstellen, sogar nach dem Schließen der Datei.</li>
      <li lang="el">Απεριόριστες αναιρέσεις/επαναλήψεις (ακόμη και αφού το αρχείο έχει κλείσει !)</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Infinite undo/redo (even after the file was closed !)</li>
      <li lang="es">Deshacer/rehacer sin límite (incluso tras cerrar archivos)</li>
      <li lang="et">Piiramata hulgal tagasivõtmisi ja uuestitegemisi (isegi pärast faili sulgemist!)</li>
      <li lang="fi">Rajaton kumoaminen ja uudelleen tekeminen (vaikka tiedosto suljettaisiin välillä!)</li>
      <li lang="fr">Annuler / Refaire infini (même après la fermeture du fichier!)</li>
      <li lang="gl">Funcionalidade de desfacer e refacer sen limitacións (incluso tras pechar o ficheiro)</li>
      <li lang="id">Urungkan/lanjurkan yang tak terbatas (bahkan setelah file ditutup !)</li>
      <li lang="it">Infinite operazioni di annullamento/ripristino (anche quando il file è stato chiuso!)</li>
      <li lang="ko">무한 실행 취소/다시 실행 지원(파일이 닫힌 이후에도 사용 가능!)</li>
      <li lang="nl">Oneindig ongedaan maken/opnieuw doen (zelfs nadat het bestand was gesloten!)</li>
      <li lang="pl">Nieskończona historia cofania/przywracania (nawet po zamknięciu pliku !)</li>
      <li lang="pt">Capacidade infinita de desfazer/refazer operações (mesmo depois de fechar o ficheiro!)</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Capacidade infinita de desfazer/refazer operações (mesmo depois de fechar o arquivo!)</li>
      <li lang="ru">Неограниченное количество операций отмены/повтора (даже после закрытия файла!)</li>
      <li lang="sl">Neskončno število razveljavitev/ponovitev (celo po zaprtju datoteke!)</li>
      <li lang="sv">Obegränsat stöd för ångra och gör om (även efter filen har stängs)</li>
      <li lang="tr">Sınırsız geri alma/ileri alma (dosya kapatıldıktan sonra bile!)</li>
      <li lang="uk">Підтримка нескінченного буфера скасування і повторення дій (навіть після закриття файла!)</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxInfinite undo/redo (even after the file was closed !)xx</li>
      <li lang="zh-CN">无限制撤销/重做支持 (文件关闭后也支持！)</li>
      <li>Instant filtering on operations and reports</li>
      <li lang="ar">تصفية فورية للعمليات والتقارير</li>
      <li lang="ca">Filtratge instantani d'operacions i informes</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Filtratge instantani d'operacions i informes</li>
      <li lang="de">Sofortige Filterung von Vorgängen und Berichten</li>
      <li lang="el">Στιγμιαίο φιλτράρισμα σε πράξεις και αναφορές</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Instant filtering on operations and reports</li>
      <li lang="es">Filtrado instantáneo en operaciones e informes</li>
      <li lang="et">Tehingute ja aruannete kiirfiltreerimine</li>
      <li lang="fi">Toimintojen ja raporttien välitön suodatus</li>
      <li lang="fr">Filtre immédiat sur les opérations et rapports</li>
      <li lang="gl">Filtro instantáneo de operacións e informes</li>
      <li lang="id">Pemfilteran sekejap saat operasi dan laporan</li>
      <li lang="it">Filtro istantaneo su operazioni e rapporti</li>
      <li lang="ko">작업과 보고서에서 즉시 필터링</li>
      <li lang="nl">Onmiddellijke filtering op bewerkingen en rapporten</li>
      <li lang="pl">Natychmiastowe filtrowanie operacji i sprawozdań</li>
      <li lang="pt">Filtragem instantânea nas operações e relatórios</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Filtragem instantânea nas operações e relatórios</li>
      <li lang="ru">Мгновенное применение фильтров к операциям и отчётам</li>
      <li lang="sl">Takojšnje filtriranje operacij in poročil</li>
      <li lang="sv">Omedelbar filtrering av transaktioner och rapporter</li>
      <li lang="tr">İşlem ve raporların anında süzülebilmesi</li>
      <li lang="uk">Миттєве фільтрування операцій та звітів</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxInstant filtering on operations and reportsxx</li>
      <li>Infinite category levels</li>
      <li lang="ar">مستويات فئات لا حصر لها</li>
      <li lang="ca">Nivells infinits de categories</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Nivells infinits de categories</li>
      <li lang="de">Unbegrenzte Kategorieebenen</li>
      <li lang="el">Απεριόριστα επίπεδα κατηγοριών</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Infinite category levels</li>
      <li lang="es">Infinitos niveles de categorías</li>
      <li lang="et">Piiramata hulgal kategooriatasemeid</li>
      <li lang="fr">Niveaux de catégories infinis</li>
      <li lang="gl">Niveis de categorías sen limitacións</li>
      <li lang="id">Level kategori tak terbatas</li>
      <li lang="it">Livelli infiniti di categorie</li>
      <li lang="ko">무한 분류 단계 수준</li>
      <li lang="nl">Oneindig aantal categorieniveaus</li>
      <li lang="pl">Nieskończone poziomy kategorii</li>
      <li lang="pt">Níveis infinitos de categorias</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Níveis de categoria infinitos</li>
      <li lang="ru">Неограниченное количество уровней категорий</li>
      <li lang="sl">Neskončno število nivojev kategorij</li>
      <li lang="sv">Obegränsade kategorinivåer</li>
      <li lang="uk">Можливість створення необмеженої за кількістю рівнів ієрархії категорій</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxInfinite category levelsxx</li>
      <li>Mass update of operations</li>
      <li lang="ar">تحديث جماعي للعمليات</li>
      <li lang="ca">Actualització massiva d'operacions</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Actualització massiva d'operacions</li>
      <li lang="de">Massenaktualisierung von Vorgängen</li>
      <li lang="el">Μαζική ενημέρωση πράξεων</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Mass update of operations</li>
      <li lang="es">Actualización de operaciones en masa</li>
      <li lang="et">Tehingute massiline uuendamine</li>
      <li lang="fi">Toimintojen joukkopäivitys</li>
      <li lang="fr">Modification massive de opérations</li>
      <li lang="gl">Actualización masiva de operacións</li>
      <li lang="id">Operasi pembaruan massal</li>
      <li lang="it">Aggiornamento di massa delle operazioni</li>
      <li lang="ko">작업 대량 업데이트</li>
      <li lang="nl">Massaal bijwerken van bewerkingen</li>
      <li lang="pl">Masowe uaktualnianie operacji</li>
      <li lang="pt">Actualização em lote de operações</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Atualização de operações em lote</li>
      <li lang="ru">Массовое обновление операций</li>
      <li lang="sl">Množična posodobitev operacij</li>
      <li lang="sv">Mängduppdatering av transaktioner</li>
      <li lang="tr">İşlemlerin toplu güncellenmesi</li>
      <li lang="uk">Пакетне оновлення операцій</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxMass update of operationsxx</li>
      <li>Scheduled operations</li>
      <li lang="ar">العمليات المجدولة</li>
      <li lang="ca">Operacions planificades</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Operacions planificades</li>
      <li lang="cs">Naplánované operace</li>
      <li lang="de">Geplante Vorgänge</li>
      <li lang="el">Προγραμματισμένες πράξεις</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Scheduled operations</li>
      <li lang="es">Operaciones planificadas</li>
      <li lang="et">Tehingute ajastamine</li>
      <li lang="fi">Ajastetut tapahtumat</li>
      <li lang="fr">Opérations programmées</li>
      <li lang="gl">Operacións planificadas</li>
      <li lang="id">Operasi terjadwal</li>
      <li lang="it">Operazioni pianificate</li>
      <li lang="ko">예약된 작업</li>
      <li lang="nl">Geplande bewerkingen</li>
      <li lang="pl">Zaplanowane operacje</li>
      <li lang="pt">Operações agendadas</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Operações agendadas</li>
      <li lang="ru">Плановые операции</li>
      <li lang="sk">Plánované operácie</li>
      <li lang="sl">Časovno načrtovane operacije</li>
      <li lang="sv">Schemalagda transaktioner</li>
      <li lang="tr">Zamanlanmış işlemler</li>
      <li lang="uk">Заплановані операції</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxScheduled operationsxx</li>
      <li>Track refund of your expenses</li>
      <li lang="ar">تتبع استرداد نفقاتك</li>
      <li lang="ca">Seguiment del reemborsament de les despeses</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Seguiment del reemborsament de les despeses</li>
      <li lang="de">Verfolgen Sie die Erstattung Ihrer Ausgaben</li>
      <li lang="el">Παρακολούθηση επιστροφής χρημάτων στα έξοδά σας</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Track refund of your expenses</li>
      <li lang="es">Seguimiento de reembolsos de sus gastos</li>
      <li lang="et">Kuluhüvituste jälgimine</li>
      <li lang="fi">Kulujesi suoritusten jäljitys</li>
      <li lang="fr">Suivi des remboursements de dépenses</li>
      <li lang="gl">Seguimento da devolución dos gastos</li>
      <li lang="id">Lacak kembalian pengeluaran Anda</li>
      <li lang="it">Traccia i rimborsi delle tue spese</li>
      <li lang="ko">지출 환불 추적</li>
      <li lang="nl">Volgen van aanvullen van uitgaven</li>
      <li lang="pl">Śledzenie zwrotu twoich wydatków</li>
      <li lang="pt">Seguir o reembolso das suas despesas</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Acompanhe o reembolso das suas despesas</li>
      <li lang="ru">Отслеживание возмещения расходов</li>
      <li lang="sl">Sledenje povračil stroškov</li>
      <li lang="sv">Följ återbetalning av utgifter</li>
      <li lang="tr">Harcamalarınızın geri ödemesini takip edin</li>
      <li lang="uk">Стеження за відшкодуваннями ваших витрат</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxTrack refund of your expensesxx</li>
      <li>Automatically process operations based on search conditions</li>
      <li lang="ar">معالجة العمليات تلقائيًا بناءً على شروط البحث</li>
      <li lang="ca">Procés automàtic d'operacions basat en les condicions de cerca</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Procés automàtic d'operacions basat en les condicions de cerca</li>
      <li lang="de">Vorgänge automatisch auf der Grundlage von Suchbedingungen bearbeiten</li>
      <li lang="el">Αυτόματη επεξεργασία πράξεων με βάση συνθήκες αναζήτησης</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Automatically process operations based on search conditions</li>
      <li lang="es">Procesamiento automático de operaciones basado en condiciones de búsqueda</li>
      <li lang="et">Tehingute automaatne töötlemine otsingutingimuste alusel</li>
      <li lang="fi">Toimenpiteiden automaattinen käsittely hakuehtojen perusteella</li>
      <li lang="fr">Traitement automatique des opérations sur la base de condition de recherche</li>
      <li lang="gl">Procesamento automático de operacións baseado en condicións de busca</li>
      <li lang="id">Operasi proses secara otomatis berdasarkan pada kondisi pencarian</li>
      <li lang="it">Elabora automaticamente le operazioni basandosi sulle condizioni di ricerca</li>
      <li lang="ko">검색 조건으로 작업 자동 처리</li>
      <li lang="nl">Automatisch procesbewerkingen gebaseerd op zoekcondities</li>
      <li lang="pl">Samoczynne przetwarzanie operacji na podstawie warunków wyszukiwania</li>
      <li lang="pt">Processar automaticamente as operações com base nas condições de pesquisa</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Processa operações automaticamente com base nas condições de pesquisa</li>
      <li lang="ru">Автоматическая обработка операций на основе условий поиска</li>
      <li lang="sl">Samodejno obdelane operacije na podlagi pogojev iskanja</li>
      <li lang="sv">Behandla automatiskt transaktioner baserat på sökvillkor</li>
      <li lang="tr">Arama koşullarına bağlı olarak otomatik süreçler</li>
      <li lang="uk">Автоматична обробка операцій на основі умов пошуку</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxAutomatically process operations based on search conditionsxx</li>
      <li>Multiple currencies</li>
      <li lang="ar">عملات متعددة</li>
      <li lang="ca">Múltiples divises</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Múltiples divises</li>
      <li lang="cs">Více měn</li>
      <li lang="de">Mehrere Währungen</li>
      <li lang="el">Πολλά νομίσματα</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Multiple currencies</li>
      <li lang="es">Múltiples divisas</li>
      <li lang="et">Paljude vääringute kasutamise võimalus</li>
      <li lang="fr">Multi-devises</li>
      <li lang="gl">Permite combinar divisas distintas</li>
      <li lang="id">Multipel mata uang</li>
      <li lang="it">Valute multiple</li>
      <li lang="ko">다중 통화</li>
      <li lang="nl">Meerdere valuta</li>
      <li lang="pl">Wiele walut</li>
      <li lang="pt">Múltiplas moedas</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Múltiplas moedas</li>
      <li lang="ru">Множество валют</li>
      <li lang="sl">Več valut</li>
      <li lang="sv">Flera valutor</li>
      <li lang="uk">Можливість використання декількох валют</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxMultiple currenciesxx</li>
      <li>Budget</li>
      <li lang="ar">الميزانية</li>
      <li lang="ca">Pressupost</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Pressupost</li>
      <li lang="cs">Rozpočet</li>
      <li lang="de">Budget</li>
      <li lang="el">Προϋπολογισμός</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Budget</li>
      <li lang="es">Presupuestos</li>
      <li lang="et">Eelarve</li>
      <li lang="fi">Budjetti</li>
      <li lang="fr">Budget</li>
      <li lang="gl">Orzamento</li>
      <li lang="ia">Budget</li>
      <li lang="id">Anggaran</li>
      <li lang="it">Budget</li>
      <li lang="ko">예산</li>
      <li lang="nl">Budget</li>
      <li lang="pl">Budżet</li>
      <li lang="pt">Orçamento</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Orçamento</li>
      <li lang="ru">Бюджет</li>
      <li lang="sk">Rozpočet</li>
      <li lang="sl">Proračun</li>
      <li lang="sv">Budget</li>
      <li lang="tr">Bütçe</li>
      <li lang="uk">Бюджет</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxBudgetxx</li>
      <li lang="zh-CN">预算</li>
      <li>Dashboard</li>
      <li lang="ar">لوحة التحكم</li>
      <li lang="ca">Tauler</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Tauler</li>
      <li lang="cs">Přístrojová deska</li>
      <li lang="de">Übersichtsseite</li>
      <li lang="el">Πίνακς ελέγχου</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Dashboard</li>
      <li lang="es">Tablero de mandos</li>
      <li lang="et">Vidinavaade</li>
      <li lang="fi">Kojelauta</li>
      <li lang="fr">Tableau de bord</li>
      <li lang="gl">Cadro de control</li>
      <li lang="ia">Pannello de instrumentos</li>
      <li lang="id">Dashboard</li>
      <li lang="it">Quadro degli strumenti</li>
      <li lang="ko">대시보드</li>
      <li lang="nl">Dashboard</li>
      <li lang="pl">Tablica</li>
      <li lang="pt">Painel</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Painel</li>
      <li lang="ru">Виджеты</li>
      <li lang="sk">Nástenka</li>
      <li lang="sl">Pregledna plošča</li>
      <li lang="sv">Instrumentpanel</li>
      <li lang="tr">Pano</li>
      <li lang="uk">Панель приладів</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxDashboardxx</li>
      <li lang="zh-CN">部件板</li>
      <li>Advice</li>
      <li lang="ar">النصيحة</li>
      <li lang="ca">Consells</li>
      <li lang="ca-valencia">Consells</li>
      <li lang="cs">Doporučení</li>
      <li lang="de">Empfehlungen</li>
      <li lang="el">Συμβουλή</li>
      <li lang="en-GB">Advice</li>
      <li lang="es">Consejos</li>
      <li lang="et">Nõuanded</li>
      <li lang="fr">Conseils</li>
      <li lang="gl">Consellos</li>
      <li lang="ia">Consilio</li>
      <li lang="id">Penasehat</li>
      <li lang="it">Suggerimento</li>
      <li lang="ko">조언</li>
      <li lang="nl">Advies</li>
      <li lang="pl">Porady</li>
      <li lang="pt">Aviso</li>
      <li lang="pt-BR">Aviso</li>
      <li lang="ru">Рекомендации</li>
      <li lang="sl">Svetovanje</li>
      <li lang="sv">Råd</li>
      <li lang="uk">Поради</li>
      <li lang="x-test">xxAdvicexx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://skrooge.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=skrooge</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=skrooge</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>The default screenshot</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">لقطة المبدئيّة</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">La captura de pantalla predeterminada</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">La captura de pantalla predeterminada</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Výchozí snímek obrazovky</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Standard-Bildschirmfoto</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Το προκαθορισμένο στιγμιότυπο</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">The default screenshot</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Captura de pantalla predeterminada</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Vaikimisi ekraanipilt</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Oletusruutukaappaus</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">La copie d'écran par défaut</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">A captura de pantalla predeterminada</caption>
      <caption lang="ia">Le instantanee de schermo predefinite</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Screenshot baku</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La schermata predefinita</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">기본 스크린샷</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">De standaard schermafbeelding</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Domyślny zrzut ekranu</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">A captura do ecrã predefinida</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Captura de tela padrão</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Снимок экрана по умолчанию</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Privzeti posnetek zaslona</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Standardskärmbilden</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Типовий знімок вікна</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxThe default screenshotxx</caption>
      <image>https://skrooge.org/sites/skrooge.org/files//images/skrooge_screenshot_16x9_0.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>skrooge</binary>
  </provides>
  <developer_name>Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ar">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca-valencia">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Stephane Mankowski</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en-GB">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Stephane Mankowski</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="et">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">Stephane Mankowski</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ia">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt-BR">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="x-test">xxStephane MANKOWSKIxx</developer_name>
  <update_contact>support@mankowski.fr</update_contact>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release date="2019-06-20" version="2.20.0" />
    <release date="2019-04-20" version="2.19.0" />
    <release date="2019-02-11" version="2.18.0" />
    <release version="2.17.0" date="2018-12-16" />
  </releases>
  <translation type="gettext">skrooge</translation>
</component>