<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <description>
    <p>Skrooge is a personal finance manager powered by KDE that aims to be simple and intuitive. Skrooge allows you to keep track of your expenses and income, categorize them, and build reports of them.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY import/export</li>
      <li>Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK and MONEY MANAGER EX import</li>
      <li>Advanced Graphical Reports</li>
      <li>Multiple tabs to help you organize your work</li>
      <li>Infinite undo/redo (even after the file was closed !)</li>
      <li>Instant filtering on operations and reports</li>
      <li>Infinite category levels</li>
      <li>Mass update of operations</li>
      <li>Scheduled operations</li>
      <li>Track refund of your expenses</li>
      <li>Automatically process operations based on search conditions</li>
      <li>Multiple currencies</li>
      <li>Budget</li>
      <li>Dashboard</li>
      <li>Advice</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>راصد هو مدير مالي شخصي مدعوم من كدي ويهدف إلى أن يكون بسيطًا وبديهيًا. يسمح لك راصد بتتبع نفقاتك ودخلك، وتصنيفها، وإنشاء تقارير عنها.</p>
    <p>الميزات:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>استيراد / تصدير QIF ، CSV ، SKROOGE ، KMYMONEY </li>
      <li>استيراد Microsoft Money و OFX و QFX و MT940 و GNUCASH و GRISBI و HOMEBANK و MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>تقارير رسومية متقدمة</li>
      <li>علامات تبويب متعددة لمساعدتك على تنظيم عملك</li>
      <li>التراجع / الإعادة اللانهائية (حتى بعد إغلاق الملف!)</li>
      <li>تصفية فورية للعمليات والتقارير</li>
      <li>مستويات فئات لا حصر لها</li>
      <li>تحديث جماعي للعمليات</li>
      <li>العمليات المجدولة</li>
      <li>تتبع استرداد نفقاتك</li>
      <li>معالجة العمليات تلقائيًا بناءً على شروط البحث</li>
      <li>عملات متعددة</li>
      <li>الميزانية</li>
      <li>لوحة التحكم</li>
      <li>النصيحة</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>L'Skrooge és un gestor de les finances personals desenvolupat pel KDE, que té l'objectiu de ser senzill i intuïtiu. L'Skrooge permet registrar els ingressos i les despeses, categoritzar-les i fer-ne informes.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Importació/exportació de QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Importació del Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK i MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Informes gràfics avançats</li>
      <li>Múltiples pestanyes us ajuden a organitzar el treball</li>
      <li>Desfer/refer infinits (inclús després de tancar el fitxer!)</li>
      <li>Filtratge instantani d'operacions i informes</li>
      <li>Nivells infinits de categories</li>
      <li>Actualització massiva d'operacions</li>
      <li>Operacions planificades</li>
      <li>Seguiment del reemborsament de les despeses</li>
      <li>Procés automàtic d'operacions basat en les condicions de cerca</li>
      <li>Múltiples divises</li>
      <li>Pressupost</li>
      <li>Tauler</li>
      <li>Consells</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca-valencia">
    <p>L'Skrooge és un gestor de les finances personals desenvolupat pel KDE, que té l'objectiu de ser senzill i intuïtiu. L'Skrooge permet registrar els ingressos i les despeses, categoritzar-les i fer-ne informes.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Importació/exportació de QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Importació del Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK i MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Informes gràfics avançats</li>
      <li>Múltiples pestanyes vos ajuden a organitzar el treball</li>
      <li>Desfer/refer infinits (inclús després de tancar el fitxer!)</li>
      <li>Filtratge instantani d'operacions i informes</li>
      <li>Nivells infinits de categories</li>
      <li>Actualització massiva d'operacions</li>
      <li>Operacions planificades</li>
      <li>Seguiment del reemborsament de les despeses</li>
      <li>Procés automàtic d'operacions basat en les condicions de cerca</li>
      <li>Múltiples divises</li>
      <li>Pressupost</li>
      <li>Tauler</li>
      <li>Consells</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Vlastnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Naplánované operace</li>
      <li>Více měn</li>
      <li>Rozpočet</li>
      <li>Přístrojová deska</li>
      <li>Doporučení</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Skrooge ist eine persönliche Finanzverwaltung auf Basis von KDE, der einfach und intuitiv sein soll. Mit Skrooge können Sie Ihre Ausgaben und Einnahmen im Auge behalten, sie zu kategorisieren und Berichte darüber erstellen.</p>
    <p>Funktionen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Import und Export der Formate QIF, CSV, Skrooge, KMymoney</li>
      <li>Import der Formate Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK und MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Erweiterte grafische Berichte</li>
      <li>Mehrere Unterfenster um Ihre Arbeit zu organisieren</li>
      <li>Unbegrenztes Zurücknehmen und Wiederherstellen, sogar nach dem Schließen der Datei.</li>
      <li>Sofortige Filterung von Vorgängen und Berichten</li>
      <li>Unbegrenzte Kategorieebenen</li>
      <li>Massenaktualisierung von Vorgängen</li>
      <li>Geplante Vorgänge</li>
      <li>Verfolgen Sie die Erstattung Ihrer Ausgaben</li>
      <li>Vorgänge automatisch auf der Grundlage von Suchbedingungen bearbeiten</li>
      <li>Mehrere Währungen</li>
      <li>Budget</li>
      <li>Übersichtsseite</li>
      <li>Empfehlungen</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το Skrooge είναι ένας προσωπικός διαχειριστής των οικονομικών από το KDE που στοχεύει να είναι απλός και διαισθητικός. Με το Skrooge πρακολουθείτε τα έξοδα και τα έσοδα, τα κατηγοριοποιείτε και εκδίδετε σχετικές αναφορές.</p>
    <p>Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Εισαγωγή/εξαγωγή QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Εισαγωγή Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK και MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Προηγμένες γραφικές αναφορές</li>
      <li>Πολλές καρτέλες για την οργάνωση της εργασίας σας</li>
      <li>Απεριόριστες αναιρέσεις/επαναλήψεις (ακόμη και αφού το αρχείο έχει κλείσει !)</li>
      <li>Στιγμιαίο φιλτράρισμα σε πράξεις και αναφορές</li>
      <li>Απεριόριστα επίπεδα κατηγοριών</li>
      <li>Μαζική ενημέρωση πράξεων</li>
      <li>Προγραμματισμένες πράξεις</li>
      <li>Παρακολούθηση επιστροφής χρημάτων στα έξοδά σας</li>
      <li>Αυτόματη επεξεργασία πράξεων με βάση συνθήκες αναζήτησης</li>
      <li>Πολλά νομίσματα</li>
      <li>Προϋπολογισμός</li>
      <li>Πίνακς ελέγχου</li>
      <li>Συμβουλή</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="en-GB">
    <p>Skrooge is a personal finance manager powered by KDE that aims to be simple and intuitive. Skrooge allows you to keep track of your expenses and income, categorise them, and build reports of them.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY import/export</li>
      <li>Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK and MONEY MANAGER EX import</li>
      <li>Advanced Graphical Reports</li>
      <li>Multiple tabs to help you organise your work</li>
      <li>Infinite undo/redo (even after the file was closed !)</li>
      <li>Instant filtering on operations and reports</li>
      <li>Infinite category levels</li>
      <li>Mass update of operations</li>
      <li>Scheduled operations</li>
      <li>Track refund of your expenses</li>
      <li>Automatically process operations based on search conditions</li>
      <li>Multiple currencies</li>
      <li>Budget</li>
      <li>Dashboard</li>
      <li>Advice</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Skrooge es un gestor de finanzas personales creado por KDE que pretende ser sencillo e intuitivo. Skrooge le permite seguir el rastro de sus gastos e ingresos, asignarles categorías y crear informes sobre ellos.</p>
    <p>Funciones:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Importar y exportar QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Importar de Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK y MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Informes gráficos avanzados</li>
      <li>Múltiples pestañas para ayudarle a organizar su trabajo</li>
      <li>Deshacer/rehacer sin límite (incluso tras cerrar archivos)</li>
      <li>Filtrado instantáneo en operaciones e informes</li>
      <li>Infinitos niveles de categorías</li>
      <li>Actualización de operaciones en masa</li>
      <li>Operaciones planificadas</li>
      <li>Seguimiento de reembolsos de sus gastos</li>
      <li>Procesamiento automático de operaciones basado en condiciones de búsqueda</li>
      <li>Múltiples divisas</li>
      <li>Presupuestos</li>
      <li>Tablero de mandos</li>
      <li>Consejos</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Skrooge on KDE isiklike rahaasjade haldamise tööriist, mille siht on olla lihtne ja mõistetav. Skrooge võimaldab hoida silma peal väljaminekutel ja sissetulekutel, neid liigitada ja nende kohta aruandeid koostada lasta.</p>
    <p>Omadused:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY import/eksport</li>
      <li>Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK ja MONEY MANAGER EX import</li>
      <li>Täiustatud graafilised aruanded</li>
      <li>Mitme kaardi kasutamine tegevuse paremaks korraldamiseks</li>
      <li>Piiramata hulgal tagasivõtmisi ja uuestitegemisi (isegi pärast faili sulgemist!)</li>
      <li>Tehingute ja aruannete kiirfiltreerimine</li>
      <li>Piiramata hulgal kategooriatasemeid</li>
      <li>Tehingute massiline uuendamine</li>
      <li>Tehingute ajastamine</li>
      <li>Kuluhüvituste jälgimine</li>
      <li>Tehingute automaatne töötlemine otsingutingimuste alusel</li>
      <li>Paljude vääringute kasutamise võimalus</li>
      <li>Eelarve</li>
      <li>Vidinavaade</li>
      <li>Nõuanded</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Ominaisuuksia:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>QIF-, CSV-, Skrooge- ja KMyMoney-tuonti ja -vienti</li>
      <li>Microsoft Money-, OFX-, QFX-, MT940-, GNUCash-, Grisbi-, Homebank- ja Money Manager Ex -tuonti</li>
      <li>Edistyneet graafiset raportit</li>
      <li>Rajaton kumoaminen ja uudelleen tekeminen (vaikka tiedosto suljettaisiin välillä!)</li>
      <li>Toimintojen ja raporttien välitön suodatus</li>
      <li>Toimintojen joukkopäivitys</li>
      <li>Ajastetut tapahtumat</li>
      <li>Kulujesi suoritusten jäljitys</li>
      <li>Toimenpiteiden automaattinen käsittely hakuehtojen perusteella</li>
      <li>Budjetti</li>
      <li>Kojelauta</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Skrooge est un gestionnaire de finances personnelles de KDE, qui vise à être simple et intuitif. Skooge vous permet de suivre vos dépenses et revenus, de les catégoriser, et de fabriquer des rapports.</p>
    <p>Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Importation / exportation QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY </li>
      <li>Importation Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK et MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Rapports graphique avancés</li>
      <li>Plusieurs onglets pour vous aider à organiser votre travail</li>
      <li>Annuler / Refaire infini (même après la fermeture du fichier!)</li>
      <li>Filtre immédiat sur les opérations et rapports</li>
      <li>Niveaux de catégories infinis</li>
      <li>Modification massive de opérations</li>
      <li>Opérations programmées</li>
      <li>Suivi des remboursements de dépenses</li>
      <li>Traitement automatique des opérations sur la base de condition de recherche</li>
      <li>Multi-devises</li>
      <li>Budget</li>
      <li>Tableau de bord</li>
      <li>Conseils</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Skrooge é un xestor de finanzas persoais baseado en KDE, e que ten por obxectivo ser sinxelo e intuitivo. Skrooge permite facer un seguimento dos gastos e ingresos, organizalos por categorías, e construír informes sobre os mesmos.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Permite importar e exportar ficheiros nos formatos QIF, CSV, SKROOGE e KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Permite importar ficheiros nos formatos Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK e MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Informes gráficos avanzados</li>
      <li>Dispón de varios separadores para permitirlle organizar o traballo</li>
      <li>Funcionalidade de desfacer e refacer sen limitacións (incluso tras pechar o ficheiro)</li>
      <li>Filtro instantáneo de operacións e informes</li>
      <li>Niveis de categorías sen limitacións</li>
      <li>Actualización masiva de operacións</li>
      <li>Operacións planificadas</li>
      <li>Seguimento da devolución dos gastos</li>
      <li>Procesamento automático de operacións baseado en condicións de busca</li>
      <li>Permite combinar divisas distintas</li>
      <li>Orzamento</li>
      <li>Cadro de control</li>
      <li>Consellos</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ia">
    <p>Characteristicas:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>importation/exportation de QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Importation de Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK e MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Budget</li>
      <li>Pannello de instrumentos</li>
      <li>Consilio</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Skrooge adalah sebuah pengelola keuangan personal yang diberdayakan oleh KDE yang bertujuan untuk menjadi sederhana dan intuitif. Skrooge memungkinkan Anda melacak pengeluaran dan pendapatan Anda, mengategorikannya, dan membuat laporannya.</p>
    <p>Fitur:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Impor/ekspor QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Impor Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK dan MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Laporan Grafikal Tingkat-lanjut</li>
      <li>Tab yang multipel untuk membantu Anda mengatur pekerjaan Anda</li>
      <li>Urungkan/lanjurkan yang tak terbatas (bahkan setelah file ditutup !)</li>
      <li>Pemfilteran sekejap saat operasi dan laporan</li>
      <li>Level kategori tak terbatas</li>
      <li>Operasi pembaruan massal</li>
      <li>Operasi terjadwal</li>
      <li>Lacak kembalian pengeluaran Anda</li>
      <li>Operasi proses secara otomatis berdasarkan pada kondisi pencarian</li>
      <li>Multipel mata uang</li>
      <li>Anggaran</li>
      <li>Dashboard</li>
      <li>Penasehat</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Skrooge è un gestore delle finanze personali, semplice e intuitivo, che utilizza KDE, il cui scopo è tenere traccia delle tue entrate e uscite, di categorizzarle e creare rapporti.</p>
    <p>Caratteristiche:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Importazione ed esportazione QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Importazione Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK e MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Rapporti grafici avanzati</li>
      <li>Più schede ti aiutano a organizzare il tuo lavoro</li>
      <li>Infinite operazioni di annullamento/ripristino (anche quando il file è stato chiuso!)</li>
      <li>Filtro istantaneo su operazioni e rapporti</li>
      <li>Livelli infiniti di categorie</li>
      <li>Aggiornamento di massa delle operazioni</li>
      <li>Operazioni pianificate</li>
      <li>Traccia i rimborsi delle tue spese</li>
      <li>Elabora automaticamente le operazioni basandosi sulle condizioni di ricerca</li>
      <li>Valute multiple</li>
      <li>Budget</li>
      <li>Quadro degli strumenti</li>
      <li>Suggerimento</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>Skrooge는 KDE의 간단하고 직관적인 개인 재무 관리자입니다. Skrooge에서는 수입과 지출을 관리하고, 각각 항목에 분류를 할당하고, 보고서를 작성할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p>기능:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY 가져오기/내보내기</li>
      <li>Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK, MONEY MANAGER EX 가져오기</li>
      <li>고급 그래픽 보고서</li>
      <li>작업을 정리할 수 있는 다양한 탭</li>
      <li>무한 실행 취소/다시 실행 지원(파일이 닫힌 이후에도 사용 가능!)</li>
      <li>작업과 보고서에서 즉시 필터링</li>
      <li>무한 분류 단계 수준</li>
      <li>작업 대량 업데이트</li>
      <li>예약된 작업</li>
      <li>지출 환불 추적</li>
      <li>검색 조건으로 작업 자동 처리</li>
      <li>다중 통화</li>
      <li>예산</li>
      <li>대시보드</li>
      <li>조언</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Skrooge is een persoonlijke beheerder van financiën binnen KDE, met als doel eenvoudig en intuïtief te zijn. Skrooge stelt u in staat uw uitgaven en inkomsten bij te houden, ze te categoriseren en er over te rapporteren.</p>
    <p>Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Importeren/exporteren van QIF, CSV, SKROOGE en KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Importeren van Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK en MONEY MANAGER</li>
      <li>Geavanceerde grafische rapporten</li>
      <li>Meerdere tabbladen om uw werk te helpen organiseren</li>
      <li>Oneindig ongedaan maken/opnieuw doen (zelfs nadat het bestand was gesloten!)</li>
      <li>Onmiddellijke filtering op bewerkingen en rapporten</li>
      <li>Oneindig aantal categorieniveaus</li>
      <li>Massaal bijwerken van bewerkingen</li>
      <li>Geplande bewerkingen</li>
      <li>Volgen van aanvullen van uitgaven</li>
      <li>Automatisch procesbewerkingen gebaseerd op zoekcondities</li>
      <li>Meerdere valuta</li>
      <li>Budget</li>
      <li>Dashboard</li>
      <li>Advies</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Skrooge jest programem do zarządzania finansami osobistymi napędzanym przez KDE, którego celem jest bycie prostym i intuicyjnym. Skrooge umożliwia śledzenie twoich rozchodów, przychodów, kategoryzowanie ich i tworzenie dla nich sprawozdań.</p>
    <p>Możliwości:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Import/eksport QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Import Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK oraz MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Rozbudowane sprawozdania graficzne</li>
      <li>Wiele kart ułatwiających pracę</li>
      <li>Nieskończona historia cofania/przywracania (nawet po zamknięciu pliku !)</li>
      <li>Natychmiastowe filtrowanie operacji i sprawozdań</li>
      <li>Nieskończone poziomy kategorii</li>
      <li>Masowe uaktualnianie operacji</li>
      <li>Zaplanowane operacje</li>
      <li>Śledzenie zwrotu twoich wydatków</li>
      <li>Samoczynne przetwarzanie operacji na podstawie warunków wyszukiwania</li>
      <li>Wiele walut</li>
      <li>Budżet</li>
      <li>Tablica</li>
      <li>Porady</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Skrooge é um gestor de finanças pessoais que usa a plataforma KDE, pretendendo ser simples e intuitivo. O Skrooge permite-lhe manter um registo das suas despesas e receitas, classificá-las e criar relatórios sobre elas.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Importação/exportação para QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Importação do Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK e MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Relatórios Gráficos Avançados</li>
      <li>Diversas páginas que o ajudam a organizar o seu trabalho</li>
      <li>Capacidade infinita de desfazer/refazer operações (mesmo depois de fechar o ficheiro!)</li>
      <li>Filtragem instantânea nas operações e relatórios</li>
      <li>Níveis infinitos de categorias</li>
      <li>Actualização em lote de operações</li>
      <li>Operações agendadas</li>
      <li>Seguir o reembolso das suas despesas</li>
      <li>Processar automaticamente as operações com base nas condições de pesquisa</li>
      <li>Múltiplas moedas</li>
      <li>Orçamento</li>
      <li>Painel</li>
      <li>Aviso</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt-BR">
    <p>Skrooge é um gerenciador de finanças pessoais desenvolvido pelo KDE com o objetivo de ser simples e intuitivo. Ele permite manter um registro das suas despesas e receitas, classificá-las e criar relatórios sobre elas.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Importação/exportação para QIF, CSV, SKROOGE e KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Importação do Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK e MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Relatórios gráficos avançados</li>
      <li>Diversas abas que auxiliam na organização do seu trabalho</li>
      <li>Capacidade infinita de desfazer/refazer operações (mesmo depois de fechar o arquivo!)</li>
      <li>Filtragem instantânea nas operações e relatórios</li>
      <li>Níveis de categoria infinitos</li>
      <li>Atualização de operações em lote</li>
      <li>Operações agendadas</li>
      <li>Acompanhe o reembolso das suas despesas</li>
      <li>Processa operações automaticamente com base nas condições de pesquisa</li>
      <li>Múltiplas moedas</li>
      <li>Orçamento</li>
      <li>Painel</li>
      <li>Aviso</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Skrooge — приложение для управления личными финансами с интуитивно-понятным интерфейсом, разработанное KDE. Skrooge позволяет отслеживать доходы и расходы, назначать им категории и формировать по ним отчёты.</p>
    <p>Возможности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Импорт и экспорт файлов QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Импорт файлов Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK и MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Расширенные графические отчёты</li>
      <li>Вкладки для удобной организации работы</li>
      <li>Неограниченное количество операций отмены/повтора (даже после закрытия файла!)</li>
      <li>Мгновенное применение фильтров к операциям и отчётам</li>
      <li>Неограниченное количество уровней категорий</li>
      <li>Массовое обновление операций</li>
      <li>Плановые операции</li>
      <li>Отслеживание возмещения расходов</li>
      <li>Автоматическая обработка операций на основе условий поиска</li>
      <li>Множество валют</li>
      <li>Бюджет</li>
      <li>Виджеты</li>
      <li>Рекомендации</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Funkcie:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Plánované operácie</li>
      <li>Rozpočet</li>
      <li>Nástenka</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Skrooge je osebni finančni upravljalnik, ki ga poganja KDE, s ciljem da preprost in intuitiven. Skrooge vam omogoča, da spremljate svoje stroške in dohodke, jih kategorizirate in sestavite poročila o njih.</p>
    <p>Zmožnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>uvoz/zvoz QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>uvoz Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK in MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Napredna grafična poročila</li>
      <li>Več zavihkov, ki vam pomagajo organizirati svoje delo</li>
      <li>Neskončno število razveljavitev/ponovitev (celo po zaprtju datoteke!)</li>
      <li>Takojšnje filtriranje operacij in poročil</li>
      <li>Neskončno število nivojev kategorij</li>
      <li>Množična posodobitev operacij</li>
      <li>Časovno načrtovane operacije</li>
      <li>Sledenje povračil stroškov</li>
      <li>Samodejno obdelane operacije na podlagi pogojev iskanja</li>
      <li>Več valut</li>
      <li>Proračun</li>
      <li>Pregledna plošča</li>
      <li>Svetovanje</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Skrooge är ett hemekonomiprogram drivet av KDE, med målsättning att vara enkelt och intuitivt. Skrooge låter dig hålla reda på dina utgifter och intäkter, kategorisera dem, och skapa rapporter om dem.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Import och export av QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Import av Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK och MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Avancerade grafiska rapporter</li>
      <li>Flera flikar för att hjälpa till att organisera arbetet</li>
      <li>Obegränsat stöd för ångra och gör om (även efter filen har stängs)</li>
      <li>Omedelbar filtrering av transaktioner och rapporter</li>
      <li>Obegränsade kategorinivåer</li>
      <li>Mängduppdatering av transaktioner</li>
      <li>Schemalagda transaktioner</li>
      <li>Följ återbetalning av utgifter</li>
      <li>Behandla automatiskt transaktioner baserat på sökvillkor</li>
      <li>Flera valutor</li>
      <li>Budget</li>
      <li>Instrumentpanel</li>
      <li>Råd</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Özellikler:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY içe aktarma/dışa aktarma</li>
      <li>Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK ve MONEY MANAGER EX içe aktarma</li>
      <li>Gelişmiş Grafik Raporları</li>
      <li>Sınırsız geri alma/ileri alma (dosya kapatıldıktan sonra bile!)</li>
      <li>İşlem ve raporların anında süzülebilmesi</li>
      <li>İşlemlerin toplu güncellenmesi</li>
      <li>Zamanlanmış işlemler</li>
      <li>Harcamalarınızın geri ödemesini takip edin</li>
      <li>Arama koşullarına bağlı olarak otomatik süreçler</li>
      <li>Bütçe</li>
      <li>Pano</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Skrooge — програма для керування особистими фінансами, створена на основі технологій KDE. Вона проста і інтуїтивно зрозуміла. За допомогою Skrooge ви зможете стежити за вашими витратами та прибутками, розподіляти записи за категоріями та створювати на їхній основі звіти.</p>
    <p>Можливості:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Імпортування та експортування даних QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY</li>
      <li>Імпортування даних Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK та MONEY MANAGER EX</li>
      <li>Розширені графічні звіти</li>
      <li>Декілька вкладок для упорядковування вашої роботи</li>
      <li>Підтримка нескінченного буфера скасування і повторення дій (навіть після закриття файла!)</li>
      <li>Миттєве фільтрування операцій та звітів</li>
      <li>Можливість створення необмеженої за кількістю рівнів ієрархії категорій</li>
      <li>Пакетне оновлення операцій</li>
      <li>Заплановані операції</li>
      <li>Стеження за відшкодуваннями ваших витрат</li>
      <li>Автоматична обробка операцій на основі умов пошуку</li>
      <li>Можливість використання декількох валют</li>
      <li>Бюджет</li>
      <li>Панель приладів</li>
      <li>Поради</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="x-test">
    <p>xxSkrooge is a personal finance manager powered by KDE that aims to be simple and intuitive. Skrooge allows you to keep track of your expenses and income, categorize them, and build reports of them.xx</p>
    <p>xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>xxQIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY import/exportxx</li>
      <li>xxMicrosoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK and MONEY MANAGER EX importxx</li>
      <li>xxAdvanced Graphical Reportsxx</li>
      <li>xxMultiple tabs to help you organize your workxx</li>
      <li>xxInfinite undo/redo (even after the file was closed !)xx</li>
      <li>xxInstant filtering on operations and reportsxx</li>
      <li>xxInfinite category levelsxx</li>
      <li>xxMass update of operationsxx</li>
      <li>xxScheduled operationsxx</li>
      <li>xxTrack refund of your expensesxx</li>
      <li>xxAutomatically process operations based on search conditionsxx</li>
      <li>xxMultiple currenciesxx</li>
      <li>xxBudgetxx</li>
      <li>xxDashboardxx</li>
      <li>xxAdvicexx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-CN">
    <p>功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>QIF, CSV, SKROOGE, KMYMONEY 导入/导出</li>
      <li>Microsoft Money, OFX, QFX, MT940, GNUCASH, GRISBI, HOMEBANK 和 MONEY MANAGER EX 导入</li>
      <li>高级图形报表</li>
      <li>无限制撤销/重做支持 (文件关闭后也支持！)</li>
      <li>预算</li>
      <li>部件板</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>skrooge</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.skrooge.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" type="cached" height="64">skrooge.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">skrooge.png</icon>
  <id>org.kde.skrooge</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="ar">راصد</name>
  <name lang="ca">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="ca-valencia">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="cs">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="da">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="de">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="el">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="en-GB">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="es">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="et">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="fi">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="fr">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="gl">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="ia">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="id">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="it">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="ko">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="nl">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="pl">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="pt">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="pt-BR">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="ru">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="sk">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="sl">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="sv">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="tr">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="uk">Skrooge</name>
  <name lang="x-test">xxSkroogexx</name>
  <name lang="zh-CN">Skrooge</name>
  <summary>Single-entry bookkeeping for home use</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">مسك الدفاتر للاستخدام المنزلي</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Comptabilitat d'entrada única per a ús particular</summary>
  <summary lang="ca-valencia">Comptabilitat d'entrada única per a ús particular</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Einfache Buchführung für den privaten Gebrauch</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Λογιστική απλών εγγραφών για οικιακή χρήση</summary>
  <summary lang="en-GB">Single-entry bookkeeping for home use</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Contabilidad de registro único para uso doméstico</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Comptabilité à partie simple pour un usage domestique</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Pembukuan tunggal untuk penggunaan rumahan</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Contabilità a partita semplice per uso domestico</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">가정용 단식 부기 가계부</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Enkelvoudige boekhouding voor thuisgebruik</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Pojedyncze wpisy księgujący do domowego użytku</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Contabilidade de registo único para uso doméstico</summary>
  <summary lang="pt-BR">Contabilidade de entrada única para uso doméstico</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Управление личными финансами, основанное на принципе простой записи</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Enostavno knjigovodstvo za domačo rabo</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Enkel bokföring för hemanvändning</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Бухгалтерська система із одинарним записом для домашнього використання</summary>
  <summary lang="x-test">xxSingle-entry bookkeeping for home usexx</summary>
  <url type="homepage">https://skrooge.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=skrooge</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=skrooge</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>The default screenshot</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">لقطة المبدئيّة</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">La captura de pantalla predeterminada</caption>
      <caption lang="ca-valencia">La captura de pantalla predeterminada</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Výchozí snímek obrazovky</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Standard-Bildschirmfoto</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Το προκαθορισμένο στιγμιότυπο</caption>
      <caption lang="en-GB">The default screenshot</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Captura de pantalla predeterminada</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Vaikimisi ekraanipilt</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Oletusruutukaappaus</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">La copie d'écran par défaut</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">A captura de pantalla predeterminada</caption>
      <caption lang="ia">Le instantanee de schermo predefinite</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Screenshot baku</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La schermata predefinita</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">기본 스크린샷</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">De standaard schermafbeelding</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Domyślny zrzut ekranu</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">A captura do ecrã predefinida</caption>
      <caption lang="pt-BR">Captura de tela padrão</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Снимок экрана по умолчанию</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Privzeti posnetek zaslona</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Standardskärmbilden</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Типовий знімок вікна</caption>
      <caption lang="x-test">xxThe default screenshotxx</caption>
      <image>https://skrooge.org/sites/skrooge.org/files//images/skrooge_screenshot_16x9_0.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>skrooge</binary>
  </provides>
  <developer_name>Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ar">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ca-valencia">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="cs">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="de">Stephane Mankowski</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="el">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="en-GB">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="es">Stephane Mankowski</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="et">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fi">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="fr">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="gl">Stephane Mankowski</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ia">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="id">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="it">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ko">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="nl">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pl">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="pt-BR">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="ru">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sl">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="sv">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="uk">Stephane MANKOWSKI</developer_name>
  <developer_name lang="x-test">xxStephane MANKOWSKIxx</developer_name>
  <update_contact>support@mankowski.fr</update_contact>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="2.20.0" date="2019-06-20" />
    <release version="2.19.0" date="2019-04-20" />
    <release version="2.18.0" date="2019-02-11" />
    <release date="2018-12-16" version="2.17.0" />
  </releases>
  <translation type="gettext">skrooge</translation>
</component>