<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <description>
    <p>Synfig Studio is a free and open-source 2D animation software, designed as powerful industrial-strength solution for creating film-quality animation using a vector and bitmap artwork. It eliminates the need to create animation frame-by frame, allowing you to produce 2D animation of a higher quality with fewer people and resources.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Can manipulate vector and bitmap artwork</li>
      <li>Automatic tweening (independent from FPS)</li>
      <li>Multitude of layers of various types (geometry primitives, shapes, gradients, fratals)</li>
      <li>Full-featured bone system</li>
      <li>Filters and effects for compositing (blurs, distortions, color manipulation, masks)</li>
      <li>All color operations use High Dynamic-Range Imaging (HDRI)</li>
      <li>Pentablet-friendly tools</li>
      <li>Sound support</li>
      <li>Linking data on file- or parameter-level</li>
      <li>Automatic animation using mathematical functions</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>أستوديو سنفغ برنامج رسوم متحركة 2 الأبعاد مجاني مفتوح المصدر، مصمم كحل إنتاجي قوي لإنشاء رسوم متحركة بجودة مناسبة للأفلام باستخدام فن  الرسومات المتجهة والصور النقطية. إنه يُغ عنني صنع الرسوم المتحركة إطارا إطارا، مما يسمح لك بإنتاج رسوم متحركة بجودة أعلى بأقل المصادر والعاملين.</p>
    <p>المزايا:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>يمكن التعامل مع الأعمال الشعاعية أو النقطية</li>
      <li>نظام عظام مكتمل المميزات</li>
      <li>ادوات مهيأة لاجهزة الكتابة اللوحية</li>
      <li>دعم الصوت</li>
      <li>تحريك تلقائي باستخدام دوال رياضية.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="bs">
    <p>Svojstva:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca@valencia">
    <p>El Synfig Studio és un programari d'animació 2D, lliure i de codi obert, dissenyat com una solució d'una eficàcia professional per a la creació d'animacions de qualitat cinematogràfica utilitzant il·lustracions vectorials i de mapa de bits. Elimina la necessitat de crear les animacions fotograma per fotograma, i us permet produir animacions 2D d'una qualitat elevada amb menys persones i recursos.</p>
    <p>Característiques:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Eines compatibles amb les tauletes gràfiques</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Synfig Studio je bezplatný a otevřený 2D animační software, který je navržen jako výkonné průmyslové řešení pro vytváření animací s vysokou kvalitou, pomocí vektorového a bitmapového systému. To eliminuje potřebu vytvářet jednotlivé snímky animace ručně, to umožňuje vytvářet 2D animaci vyšší kvality s menším počtem lidí a zdrojů.</p>
    <p>Funkce:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Grafický tablet - Nástroje</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Synfig Studio er gratis open-source software til 2D animation, designet som en stærk professionel løsning til at skabe animationer i filmkvalitet med vektor- og bitmapgrafik. Det overflødiggør behovet for at skabe animationer billed-for-billed og giver dig mulighed for at lave 2D animation i en højere kvalitet med mindre tidsforbrug og færre ressourcer.</p>
    <p>Muligheder:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Velegnet til pen-tablet</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Synfig Studio ist eine freie und quelloffene 2D-Animationssoftware, die als industrietaugliche Lösung für die Erstellung von Animationen mit Vektor- und Rastergrafiken in Filmqualität entwickelt wurde. Mit Synfig müssen Animationen nicht mehr länger Bild für Bild erstellt werden, sodass die Produktion von 2D-Animationen von höherer Qualität mit weniger Mitarbeitern und Ressourcen möglich wird.</p>
    <p>Funktionen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Für Grafiktabletts geeignete Werkzeuge</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="el_GR">
    <p>Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Υποστήριξη ήχου:</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Synfig Studio es un programa libre de animación 2D, diseñado como una solución poderosa de potencia-industrial para la creación de animaciones de calidad cinematográfica utilizando ilustraciones vectoriales y de mapa de bits. Esto elimina la necesidad de crear una animación cuadro por cuadro, permitiendo producir una animación 2D de una calidad superior con pocas personas y recursos. </p>
    <p>Características:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Puede manipular artwork vectorial y de mapa de bits</li>
      <li>Imágenes intermedias (tweening) automáticas independientes de FPS (Frames per second), imágenes por segundo</li>
      <li>Multitud de capas de varios tipos (primitivas geométricas, formas, gradientes, fractales)</li>
      <li>Sistema de huesos completamente funcional</li>
      <li>Filtros y efectos para composición (difumino, distorsiones, manipulaciones de color, máscaras)</li>
      <li>Todas la operaciones de color utilizan HDRI (Imagen de alto rango dinámico)</li>
      <li>Herramientas amigables para dibujo en tabletas</li>
      <li>Soporte de sonido</li>
      <li>Enlace de tados anivel de fichero- o parámetro</li>
      <li>Animacion automática utilizando funciones matemáticas</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Synfig Studio 2D animazioko doako eta kode irekiko softwarea da, bektore eta bitmap artelanen bidez filmaren kalitateko animazioa sortzeko industria-sendotasuneko irtenbide indartsu gisa diseinatua. Animazioa fotogramaz fotograma sortzeko beharra ezabatzen du, kalitate altuko 2D animazioak pertsona eta baliabide gutxiagorekin ekoizteko aukera ematen du.</p>
    <p>Ezaugarriak:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Landu daitezke bektore edota bitmapa artelanak</li>
      <li>Soinua onartzen du</li>
      <li>Animazio automatikoa funtzio matematikoen bidez</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu_ES">
    <p>Ezaugarriak:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Bektore eta bitmap artelanak manipulatu ditzake</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fa_IR">
    <p>ویژگی ها:</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Synfig Studio est un logiciel libre et open-source d'animation 2D, pensé comme une solution d'une efficacité professionnelle pour la création d'animations de qualité cinéma utilisant des illustrations vectorielles ou matricielles. Il élimine la nécessité de créer les animations image par image, et vous permet de produire des animations 2D d'une qualité élevée avec moins de personnes et de ressources. </p>
    <p>Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Permet de manipuler des oeuvres vectorielles et bitmaps</li>
      <li>Génération d'images intermédiaires (indépendamment du nombre d'images par seconde)</li>
      <li>Multitude de calques de types variés (primitives géométriques, formes, dégradés, fractales)</li>
      <li>Système d'ossature complet</li>
      <li>Filtres et effets pour la composition (flous, distortions, manipulation de couleur, masques)</li>
      <li>Toutes les opérations en couleurs utilisent le High Dynamic-Range Imaging (HDRI)</li>
      <li>Outils compatible avec les tablettes graphiques</li>
      <li>Support du Son</li>
      <li>Animation automatique utilisant des fonctions mathématiques</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Synfig Studio è un software di animazione 2D free e open source, sviluppato con i migliori standard del settore per la creazione di animazioni di alta qualità con grafiche vettoriali e bitmap. Elimina la necessità di creare animazioni frame-by-frame semplificando la produzione di animazioni 2D.</p>
    <p>Funzionalità:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Modifica grafiche vettoriali e bitmap</li>
      <li>Interpolazione automatica (indipendente da FPS)</li>
      <li>Livelli di vari tipi (primitive geometriche, forme, gradienti, frattali)</li>
      <li>Sistema scheletro multifunzionale</li>
      <li>Filtri ed effetti per compositing (sfocature, distorsioni, manipolazione colore, maschere)</li>
      <li>Tutte le operazioni sui colori usano High Dynamic-Range Imaging (HDRI)</li>
      <li>Strumenti a misura di tavoletta grafica</li>
      <li>Supporto Audio</li>
      <li>Collegamento dati a livello di file o parametro</li>
      <li>Animazione automatica mediante funzioni matematiche</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja_JP">
    <p>特色:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>ペンタブレットに最適化したツール群</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="kab">
    <p>Tiwuriwin:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Ifecka imṣadan akked tfelwin tudlifin</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko_KR">
    <p>Synfig Studio는 무료 오픈 소스 2D 애니메이션 소프트웨어로, 벡터 및 비트 맵 아트 워크를 사용하여 영화 품질의 애니메이션을 만들기위한 강력한 산업적 솔루션으로 설계되었습니다. 프레임 단위로 애니메이션을 만들 필요가 없으므로 더 적은 인원과 리소스로 더 높은 품질의 2D 애니메이션을 제작할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p>특징:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>벡터 및 비트맵 아트 제작 가능</li>
      <li>자동 트위닝 (FPS와 무관)</li>
      <li>다양한 유형의 다양한 레이어 (기하학적 기본 요소, 모양, 그라데이션, 프랙탈)</li>
      <li>모든 기능을 갖춘 뼈대 시스템</li>
      <li>합성을 위한 필터 및 효과 (흐림, 왜곡, 색상 조작, 마스크)</li>
      <li>모든 색상 작업에서 HDRI (High Dynamic-Range Imaging) 사용</li>
      <li>펜태블릿 친화적인 도구</li>
      <li>사운드 지원</li>
      <li>파일 또는 파라미터 수준의 데이터 연결</li>
      <li>수학적 함수를 사용한 자동 애니메이션</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Kenmerken:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Pentablet-vriendelijke hulpmiddelen</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl_PL">
    <p>Synfig Studio jest darmowym i open-sourcowym oprogramowaniem do animacji 2D, posiadające funkcjonalności porównywalne z najlepszymi produktami w branży, tworzące animacje o jakości profesjonalnych filmów z wykorzystaniem grafiki wektorowe i bitmap. Eliminuje konieczność tworzenia animacji klatka po klatce, co pozwala produkować animacje 2D wyższej jakości, z mniejszą ilością ludzi i zasobów.</p>
    <p>Cechy:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Narzędzia współpracujące z tabletami do rysowania</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Synfig Studio é um programa de animação 2D livre e de código aberto, desenhado como uma poderosa solução de nível industrial para criar animação de qualidade cinematográfica utilizando arte vetorial e de bitmap. Evitando assim a necessidade de criar animações quadro a quadro, permitindo produzir animação 2D de alta qualidade com poucas pessoas e recursos.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Pode manipular arte bitmap ou vetorial</li>
      <li>Ferramentas compatíveis com mesas gráficas</li>
      <li>Suporte de som</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Synfig Studio é um software de animação 2D livre e de código aberto, desenhado como uma poderosa solução de nível industrial para criar animação de qualidade cinematográfica utilizando arte vetorial e de bitmap. Ele elimina a necessidade de criar animação quadro a quadro, permitindo produzir animação 2D de alta qualidade com poucas pessoas e recursos.</p>
    <p>Funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Pode manipular arte vetorial e de bitmap</li>
      <li>Animação automática entre quadros (independente da taxa de quadros)</li>
      <li>Diversas camadas de vários tipos (primitivas geométricas, formas, gradientes, fractais)</li>
      <li>Sistema de ossos completo</li>
      <li>Filtros e efeitos de composição (desfoques, distorções, manipulação de cores, máscaras)</li>
      <li>Todas as operações de cores usam  High Dynamic-Range Imaging (HDRI)</li>
      <li>Ferramentas amigáveis à mesa gráfica</li>
      <li>Suporte a sons</li>
      <li>Vinculação de dados em nível de parâmetros ou arquivos</li>
      <li>Animações automáticas baseadas em funções matemáticas</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Synfig Studio - это свободное и с открытым исходным кодом программное обеспечение 2D анимации, разработанное как мощное индустриальное решение для создания анимации кинематографического качества, используя векторные и растровые изображения. Это устраняет необходимость создания анимации кадр за кадром, что позволяет производить 2D анимации более высокого качества с меньшим количеством людей и ресурсов.</p>
    <p>Возможности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Может манипулировать векторным и растровым изображением</li>
      <li>Автоматические промежуточные кадры (независимо от количества кадров в секунду)</li>
      <li>Множество слоев различных типов (геометрические примитивы, формы, градиенты, фракталы)</li>
      <li>Полнофункциональная костная система</li>
      <li>Фильтры и эффекты для композитинга (размытия, искажения, цветные манипуляции, маски)</li>
      <li>Все операции с цветом используют высокоинтенсивную визуализацию (HDRI)</li>
      <li>Утилиты дружественные с графическим планшетом</li>
      <li>Звуковая поддержка</li>
      <li>Связывание данных по файлам или параметрам уровня</li>
      <li>Автоматическая анимация с использованием математических функций</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk_SK">
    <p>Možnosti programu:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Nástroje prispôsobené pre grafický tablet</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Synfig Studio je brezplačen in odpro-koden 2d program za animacijo, zasnovan na industrijski ravni. Je zmogljiva rešitev za ustvarjanje animacije filmske kakovosti, z uporabo vektorjev in bitne slike. Odpravi potrebo po risanju vsake sličice, kar vam omogoča izdelavo 2d animacij višje kakovosti in pri tem porabiti manj virov in osebja.</p>
    <p>Značilnosti:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Orodja prijazna risarskim tablicam</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr_RS">
    <p>Синфиг Студио је бесплатан софтвер отвореног кода за 2Д анимације, осмишљен као моћно решење на индустријском нивоу за стварање анимација филмског квалитета коришћењем векторских и растерских уметничких дела. С њиме нема више потребе за стварањем анимација кадар-по-кадар, што вам омогућава да створите 2Д анимацију вишег квалитета са мањим бројем људи и са мање средстава.</p>
    <p>Могућности:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Графичкој табли наклоњене алатке</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv_SE">
    <p>Synfig Studio är ett gratisprogram med öppen källkod för 2D-animation, gjort för att vara en kraftfull lösning i världsklass för att skapa vektor- och rasteranimationer med filmkvalitet. Med Synfig slipper du göra animationer bildruta för bildruta, vilket låter dig producera 2D-animationer med bättre kvalitet och färre människor och resurser.</p>
    <p>Funktioner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Verktyg anpassade för ritplattor</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Synfig Studio, ücretsiz ve açık kaynak 2B animasyon yazılımıdır, vektör ve bitmap eserlerini kullanarak film kalitesinde animasyonlar hazırlamak için güçlü endüstriyel bir çözüm olarak tasarlanmıştır.</p>
    <p>Özellikler:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Vektör ve biteşlem çizimlerini hareketlendirebilir.</li>
      <li>Tam özellikli kemik sistemi</li>
      <li>Ses desteği</li>
      <li>Verileri dosya ya da değişken seviyesinde bağlama</li>
      <li>Matematiksel işlevleri kullanarak otomatik canlandırma</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh-Hant">
    <p>特點：</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>Synfig Studio 是自由、开放源代码的 2D 动画软件，它被设计成工业级别的，使用矢量或者位图作品来制作影片级动画的解决方案。它消除了逐帧制作的需求，让您用更少的人力和其他资源就可以生产高质量 2D 动画。</p>
    <p>功能特性：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>各种数位板友好的工具</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>功能:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>完整特性的骨骼系統</li>
      <li>聲音支援</li>
      <li>自動動畫使用數學函式</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>synfigstudio</pkgname>
  <icon type="cached" height="64" width="64">org.synfig.SynfigStudio.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">org.synfig.SynfigStudio.png</icon>
  <id>org.synfig.SynfigStudio</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.synfig.SynfigStudio.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <name>Synfig Studio</name>
  <summary>Create and edit 2D animations and compositions</summary>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot width="1232" height="693" type="default">
      <image>https://www.synfig.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/screenshot-01.png</image>
      <caption>Synfig Studio workspace</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">مساحة عمل استديو Synfig</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Espacio de trabajo de Synfig Studio</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Synfig Studioren lan-esparrua</caption>
      <caption lang="eu_ES">Synfig Studio lan eremua</caption>
      <caption lang="fa_IR">فضای کاری سین فیگ استودیو</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Espace de travail de Synfig Studio</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Area lavoro Synfig Studio</caption>
      <caption lang="ko_KR">Synfig Studio 작업공간</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Espaço de trabalho do Synfig Studio</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Área de Trabalho do Synfig Studio</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Рабочее пространство Synfig Studio</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Synfig Studio Çalışma Alanı</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">Synfig Studio 工作區</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.synfig.org</url>
  <update_contact>contact_at_synfig.org</update_contact>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>2D</keyword>
    <keyword>Vector</keyword>
    <keyword>Animation</keyword>
    <keyword>Cartoon</keyword>
    <keyword>Anime</keyword>
    <keyword>FX</keyword>
    <keyword>Draw</keyword>
    <keyword>Cutout</keyword>
    <keyword>Moho</keyword>
    <keyword>Toomboon</keyword>
    <keyword>Flash</keyword>
    <keyword>ToonBoom</keyword>
  </keywords>
  <developer_name>Synfig</developer_name>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/synfig/synfig/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.synfig.org/donate/</url>
  <url type="help">https://wiki.synfig.org/Category:Manual</url>
  <url type="translate">https://www.transifex.com/morevnaproject/synfig/</url>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="1.5.1" date="2021-10-21" />
  </releases>
</component>