<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>transmission-gtk</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">transmission-gtk.desktop</launchable>
  <icon width="64" height="64" type="cached">transmission.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" type="cached" width="128">transmission.png</icon>
  <id type="desktop">transmission-gtk.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0 OR GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <name>Transmission</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="vi">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="uz">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="uk">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="ug">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="tr">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="th">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="te">ట్రాన్స్‍మిషన్</name>
  <name lang="sv">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="sr">Трансмисија</name>
  <name lang="sq">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="sl">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="sk">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="si">ට්‍රාන්ස්මිෂන්</name>
  <name lang="ru">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="ro">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="pt">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="pl">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="oc">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="nn">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="nl">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="nb">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="ms">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="mk">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="lv">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="lt">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="li">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="ky">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="ku">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="ko">트랜스미션</name>
  <name lang="kk">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="ja">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="it">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="is">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="id">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="hu">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="hr">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="hi">ट्रांसमिशन</name>
  <name lang="he">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="gl">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="fr_CA">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="fr">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="fo">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="fil">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="fi">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="fa">ترنسمیشن</name>
  <name lang="eu">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="et">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="es">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="eo">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="en_CA">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="en_AU">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="el">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="de">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="da">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="cs">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="ckb">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="ca@valencia">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="ca">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="bn">ট্রান্সমিশন</name>
  <name lang="bg">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="be">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="ast">Transmission</name>
  <name lang="ar">ترانزميشن</name>
  <name lang="an">Transmission</name>
  <summary>Download and share files over BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">透過 BitTorrent 協定來下載和分享檔案</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_HK">透過 BitTorrent 來下載和分享檔案</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">通过 BitTorrent 下载和共享文件</summary>
  <summary lang="vi">Tải và chia sẻ tập tin qua BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="uz">BitTorrent orqail fayllarni yuklab olish va bo‘lishish</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Завантажуйте та розповсюджуйте файли через BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="ug">بىتتوررېنت ئارقىلىق ھۆججەت چۈشۈرۈش ۋە ھەمبەھىرلەش</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Dosyaları BitTorrent üzerinden indir ve paylaş</summary>
  <summary lang="th">ดาวน์โหลดและแลกเปลี่ยนแฟ้มผ่าน BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="te">దిగుమతిచేయి మరియు దస్త్రాలను బిట్ టోరెంట్ మీదుగా పంచుకొను</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Hämta och dela ut filer över BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Преузимајте и размењујте датотеке преко БитТорент протокола</summary>
  <summary lang="sq">Shkarko dhe shpërnda skedarët me BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Prejemajte in dajte datoteke v souporabo preko BitTorrenta</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Sťahujte a zdieľajte súbory cez BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Загружайте и обменивайтесь файлами в сети BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="ro">Descarcă și partajează fișiere prin BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Baixar e compartilhar arquivos pelo BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Receber e partilhar ficheiros via bittorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Pobieranie i udostępnianie plików przez sieć BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="oc">Recep e parteja de fichièrs via BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Last ned og del filer over BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Bestanden downloaden en delen via BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Last ned og del filer med BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Muat turun dan kongsi fail melalui BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="mk">Преземете и споделувајте датотеки преку BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="lv">Lejupielādēt un dalīties ar datnēm caur BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Atsiųskite ir dalinkitės failais per „BitTorrent“</summary>
  <summary lang="li">Bestanje binnehoalen en deilen via BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="ky">BitTorrent'тен файлдарды жүктөңүз жана бөлүшүңүз</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">비트토렌트를 이용하여 파일을 다운로드 및 공유합니다</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">BitTorrent желісінде файлдарды жүктеңіз және бөлісіңіз</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">BitTorrent を通じてファイルのダウンロードと共有</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Scarica e condivide file via BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Sækja og deila skrám með BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Unduh dan berbagi berkas melalui BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Fájlok letöltése és megosztása BitTorrenten keresztül</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Preuzimajte i dijelite datoteke preko BitTorrenta</summary>
  <summary lang="hi">बिट-टोरेंट पर संचिका को डाउनलोड तथा साझा करें</summary>
  <summary lang="he">הורדה ושיתוף קבצים ברשת ביטורנט</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Descargue e comparta ficheiros a través da rede BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="fr_CA">Télécharger et partager des fichiers avec BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Télécharger et partager des fichiers avec BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="fo">Tak niður og deil fílur yvir BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Lataa ja jaa tiedostoja BitTorrentin avulla</summary>
  <summary lang="fa">بارگیری و هم‌رسانی پرونده‌ها با بیت‌تورنت</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Deskargatu eta partekatu fitxategiak BitTorrent bidez</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Laadi alla ja levita faile BitTorrenti kaudu</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Descargue y comparta archivos mediante BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Elŝuti kaj kunhavigi dosierojn per BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Download and share files over BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="en_CA">Download and share files over BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="en_AU">Download and share files over BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Λήψη και διαμοιρασμός των αρχείων μέσω του BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Dateien über BitTorrent herunterladen und verteilen</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Download og del filer via BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Stahovat a sdílet soubory přes BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="ca@valencia">Baixeu i compartiu fitxers mitjançant el BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Baixeu i compartiu fitxers mitjançant BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="bn">সমস্ত BitTorrent এ ফাইল ডাউনলোড এবং অংশগ্রহন করুন</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Изтегляне и споделяне на файлове чрез BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Спампоўванне і раздача файлаў праз BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="ast">Baxar y compartir ficheros per aciu de BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">نزّل وشارك ملفات عبر «بت تورنت»</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      BitTorrent is a peer-to-peer file-sharing protocol that is commonly used to
      distribute large amounts of data between multiple users.
    </p>
    <p>
      Transmission is a BitTorrent client with an easy-to-use frontend on top a
      cross-platform backend.
      Native frontends are available for OS X and Windows, as well as command line and
      web frontends.
    </p>
    <p>
      Notable features of Transmission include support for Local Peer Discovery, encryption,
      DHT, µTP, PEX and Magnet Link.
    </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>BitTorrent - пратакол абмену файламі peer-to-peer, які звычайна выкарыстоўваецца для распаўсюджавання вялікага аб’ему даных паміж некалькімі карыстальнікамі.</p>
    <p>Transmission - кліент для пратаколу BitTorrent з простым і зручным інтэрфейсам паверх кросплатформагава рухавіка. Ёсць інтэрфейс для OS X і Windows, сеціўны інтэрфейс, інтэрфейс для загаднага радка.</p>
    <p>Адметнымі магчымасцямі Transmission з’яўляюцца: лакальнае выяўленне вузлоў, шыфраванне, падтрымка DHT, µTP, PEX магнэт-спасылак.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>BitTorrent е протокол за споделяне на файлове от тип "участник до участник", който обикновено се използва за разпространение на големи количества данни между множество потребители.</p>
    <p>Transmission е BitTorrent клиент с лесен за ползване, мултиплатформен графичен интерфейс. Достъпни са графични интерфейси за OS X и Windows, а, също конзолни и уеб интерфейси.</p>
    <p>Забележителните характеристики на Transmission, включват поддръжка на локално откриване на участник, криптиране, DHT, μTP, PEX и магнитни връзки.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>BitTorrent és un protocol de compartició de fitxers d'igual a igual que s'utilitza habitualment per distribuir grans quantitats de dades entre diversos usuaris.</p>
    <p>Transmission és un client de BitTorrent amb un frontal fàcil d'utilitzar, a la part superior d'un frontal multiplataforma. Hi ha disponibles interfícies d'usuari natives per a OS X i Windows, així com a frontals de línies d'ordres i interfícies web.</p>
    <p>Les característiques destacades de Transmission inclouen la compatibilitat amb el descobriment de clients locals, xifratge, DHT, µTP, PEX i enllaços magnet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>BitTorrent er en modpart-til-modpart-fildelingsprotokol som almindeligvis bruges til at distribuere store mængder data mellem flere brugere.</p>
    <p>Transmission er en BitTorrent-klient med en brugervenlig brugerflade oven på en multiplatform backend. Native brugerflader er tilgængelige til OS X og Windows, såvel som en kommandolinje og web-brugerflader.</p>
    <p>Bemærkelsesværdige facilitet af Transmission inkluderer understøttelse af lokal modpartsopdagelse, kryptering, DHT, µTP, PEX og magnet-link.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>BitTorrent ist ein peer-to-peer Datenaustausch Protokoll welches oft für das verteilen großer Daten zwischen mehrere Nutzer gebraucht wird.</p>
    <p>Transmission ist ein BitTorrent Klient mit einfaches Frontend und Plattformübergreifendes Backend. Native Frontends sind für MacOS und Windows verfügbar, sovie Kommandozeile und Web Frontend.</p>
    <p>Bemerkenswerte Merkmale der Transmission App sind unter anderem Untestützung für Local Peer Discovery, Verschlüsselung, DHT, µTP, PEX und Magnet Link.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το BitTorrent είναι ένα πρωτόκολλο μεταφοράς αρχείων χρήστη-προς-χρήστη που συχνά χρησιμοποιείται για τη διανομή μεγάλων ποσοτήτων δεδομένων μεταξύ πολλών χρηστών.</p>
    <p>Στα αξιοσημείωτα χαρακτηριστικά του Transmission εντάσσεται η υποστήριξη για Local Peer Discovery, κρυπτογράφηση, DHT, μTP, PEX και Σύνδεσμο Magnet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>BitTorrent es un protocolo diseñado para el intercambio de archivos punto a punto (peer-to-peer) en Internet. Es uno de los protocolos más comunes para la transferencia de archivos grandes entre múltiples usuarios.</p>
    <p>Transmission es un cliente BitTorrent multiplataforma, con una interfaz facil de usar. Hay disponibles Interfaces nativas para OSX y Windows, también una web y de linea de comandos.</p>
    <p>Las características mas notorias de transmission incluyen soporte para descubrimiento de pares locales, DHT, µTP, PEX y Magnet Links.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>BitTorrent on vertaisverkkopohjainen tiedostonjakoprotokolla, jota käytetään yleisesti suurien tietomäärien välittämiseen useiden käyttäjien välillä.</p>
    <p>Transmission on BitTorrent-asiakassovellus toteutetuna helppokäyttöisellä käyttöliittymällä ja järjestelmäriippumattomalla taustaosalla. Sovellus on natiivisti saatavilla macOS:lle, Windowsille ja Linuxille. Lisäksi saatavilla on komentorivi- ja selainkäyttöliittymä.</p>
    <p>Transmissionin huomionarvoisia ominaisuuksia ovat muun muassa Local Peer Discovery, salaus, DHT, µTP, PEX ja Magnet-linkit.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>BitTorrent est un protocole de partage de fichiers pair à pair qui est couramment utilisé pour distribuer de grandes quantités de données entre plusieurs utilisateurs.</p>
    <p>Transmission est un client BitTorrent muni d’une interface frontale conviviale sur une dorsale multiplate-forme. Des interfaces frontales natives sont proposées pour macOS et Windows, ainsi que des interfaces frontales en ligne de commande et Web.</p>
    <p>Les caractéristiques notables de Transmission comprennent la prise en charge de la découverte de pairs locaux, le chiffrement, DHT, µTP, PEX et les liens Magnet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>ביטטורנט הוא פרוטוקול שיתוף קבצים ישירות בין עמיתים והוא משמש בדרך כלל להפיץ כמות גדולה של נתונים בין מגוון משתמשים.</p>
    <p>Transmission (בעברית: תמסורת) הוא לקוח ביטטורנט עם מנשק משתמש פשוט על גבי מנגנון חוצה פלטפורמות. יש מנשקי משתמש זמינים ל־OS X ול־Windows לרבות שורת פקודה ומנשקי דפדפן מקוונים.</p>
    <p>תכונות בולטות של Transmission כוללות תמיכה בגילוי מקומי של עמיתים, הצפנה, DHT,‏ µTP,‏ PEX וקישורי מגנט.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>BitTorrent je točka-u-točka protokol dijeljenja datoteka koji se uobičajeno koristi za prijenos velike količine podataka između više korisnika.</p>
    <p>Transmission je BitTorrent klijent s jednostavnim korisničkim sučeljem povrh višeplatformske pozadine. Izvorna korisnička sučelja su dostupna za OS X i Windowse, kao i naredbeni redak i web sučelja.</p>
    <p>Bitne značajke Transmissiona uključuju podršku za lokalno otkrivanje točaka, šifriranje, DHT, µTP, PEX i Magnetne poveznice.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A BitTorrent egy peer-to-peer fájlmegosztó protokoll, amelyet jellemzően arra használnak, hogy nagy mennyiségű adatot osszanak szét több felhasználó közt.</p>
    <p>A Transmission egy könnyen használható kezelőfelülettel, és keresztplatformos háttérrendszerrel rendelkező BitTorrent kliens. A natív előtétprogramok elérhetőek macOS-ra és Windowsra, valamint parancssoros és webes előtétprogramok is léteznek.</p>
    <p>A Transmission fontos funkciói közé tartozik a Helyi peer felderítés, titkosítás, DHT, µTP, PEX és a mágnes linkek kezelése.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>BitTorrent adalah protokol berbagi berkas peer-to-peer yang biasanya digunakan untuk mendistribusikan sejumlah besar data antara banyak pengguna.</p>
    <p>Transmission adalah klien BitTorrent dengan frontend yang mudah digunakan di atas backend lintas platform. Frontend asli tersedia untuk OS X dan Windows, maupun frontend baris perintah dan web.</p>
    <p>Fitur-fitur penting Transmission termasuk dukungan untuk Local Peer Discovery, enkripsi, DHT, TP, PEX, dan Magnet Link.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>BitTorrent è un protocollo di condivisione nodo-a-nodo comunemente utilizzato per distribuire grandi quantità di dati tra molteplici utenti.</p>
    <p>Transmission è un programma BitTorrent con un'interfaccia utente di facile uso e un motore compatibile con più sistemi operativi. Sono disponibili interfacce native per OS X e Windows, strumenti a riga di comando e un'interfaccia web.</p>
    <p>Tra le varie funzionalità di Transmission, le più note sono: Local Peer Discovery, cifratura, DHT, µTP, PEX e collegamenti magnetici.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>BitTorrent は多数のユーザー間で大量のデータを配信するために一般的に使用されるピアツーピアのファイル共有プロトコルです。</p>
    <p>Transmission は、クロスプラットフォームのバックエンド層上にお手軽なフロントエンドを備えた BitTorrent クライアントです。用意されたフロントエンドは、OS X と Windows のほか、コマンドラインやウェブでも利用できます。</p>
    <p>Transmission の特徴的な機能には、ローカルピア探索、暗号化、DHT、μTP、PEX、およびマグネットリンクへの対応が含まれます。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>트랜스미션은 크로스 플랫폼 백엔드 위에서 동작하는 쉽게 사용가능한 프론트엔드인 비트토렌트 클라이언트입니다. 네이티브 프론트엔드는 OS X와 Windows, 커멘드라인 및 웹 프론트엔드가 존재합니다.</p>
    <p>트랜스미션의 주목할만한 기능에는 로컬 피어 검색, 암호화, DHT, μTP, PEX 및 마그넷 링크에 대한 지원이 포함되어 있습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>BitTorrent er en likemann-til-likemannsdelingsprotokoll som er i vanlig bruk til å distribuere store mengder data mellom forskjellige brukere.</p>
    <p>Transmission er en BitTorrent-klient med en grenseflate som er lett å bruke, på toppen av en bakende, som fungerer på flere plattformer. Innebygde grenseflater er tilgjengelige på macOS og Windows, sågar også kommandolinje og nettbaserte grenseflater.</p>
    <p>Merkverdige funksjoner i Transmission inkluderer støtte for lokal likemannsoppdaging, kryptering, µTP, PEX og magnetlenker.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>BitTorrent is een peer-to-peer protocol om bestanden te delen, welke doorgaans gebruikt wordt om grote hoeveelheden data aan verschillende gebruikers te verzenden.</p>
    <p>Transmission is een BitTorrent programma met een eenvoudig te gebruiken frontend en een cross-platform backend. Standaard frontends zijn beschikbaar voor OS X en Windows, net als command line en web frontends.</p>
    <p>Opvallende eigenschappen van Transmission voegen ondersteuning toe voor Local Peer Discovery, encryptie, DHT, µTP, PEX en Magnet Link.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>BitTorrent to protokół udostępniania plików P2P często używany do rozprowadzania dużych ilości danych między wieloma użytkownikami.</p>
    <p>Transmission to klient sieci BitTorrent z łatwym w użyciu interfejsem na podstawie wieloplatformowego mechanizmu. Natywne interfejsy są dostępne dla systemów macOS i Windows, a także dla wiersza poleceń i przez przeglądarki WWW.</p>
    <p>Transmission obsługuje między innymi wykrywanie partnerów lokalnych, szyfrowanie, DHT, µTP, PEX i odnośniki magnet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>BitTorrent é um protocolo de compartilhamento de arquivos peer-to-peer muito usado para distribuir grandes quantidades de dados entre diferentes usuários.</p>
    <p>Transmission é um cliente BitTorrent com um front-end fácil de usar em um back-end de plataforma cruzada. Frontends nativos estão disponíveis para OS X e Windows, bem como frontends de linha de comando e web.</p>
    <p> As notáveis características de Transmission incluem suporte para Descoberta de Peer Local, criptografia, DHT, µTP, PEX e Magnet Link.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>BitTorrent - протокол обмена файлами пиринговой сети, который обычно используется для распространения больших объемов данных между несколькими пользователями.</p>
    <p>Transmission - BitTorrent клиент с простым в использовании интерфейсом поверх кросс-платформенного бэкэнда. Родные интерфейсы доступны для OS X и Windows так же как командная строка и веб-интерфейс.</p>
    <p>Заслуживающие внимания функции Transmission включают в себя поддержку локального обнаружения пиров, шифрования, DHT, μTP, PEX и Магнитных ссылок.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>БитТорен је парњачки протокол за дељење датотека који се обично користи за дистрибуцију великих количина података између више корисника.</p>
    <p>Трансмисија је БитТорент протокол са лако употребљивим предњим делом који радњи са позадинцима на више платформи. Домаћи предњи делови су доступни за Мек-ОС, Виндоус као и предњи делови за веб и командну линију.</p>
    <p>У издвојене могућности Трансмисије спада подршка за откривање локалних парњака, шифровање, DHT,  µTP, PEX и магнетне везе.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>BitTorrent är ett peer-to-peer-protokoll för fildelning som ofta används för att distribuera stora mängder data mellan flera användare.</p>
    <p>Transmission är en BitTorrent-klient med ett lättanvänt gränssnitt ovanpå en grund gjord för flera plattformar. Gränssnitt finns för OS X och Windows, samt som kommandorad och webbgränssnitt.</p>
    <p>Viktiga funktioner i Transmission är bland annat stöd för att upptäcka lokala noder, kryptering, DHT, µTP, PEX och magnet-länkar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>BitTorrent çok sayıda kullanıcı arasında büyük miktarda veri dağıtmak için yaygın olarak kullanılan bir uçtan uca dosya paylaşım protokolüdür.</p>
    <p>Transmission BitTorrent istemcisi, hızlı ve kullanışlı bütün plotformarda ve web arayüzünde çalışabilir. Windows, OS X, Linux başta olmak üzere bir çok alanda çalışabilir.</p>
    <p>Yerel Eş Keşfi için dahili destek, şifreleme, DHT, µTP, PEX ve Magnet Bağlantısı Transmission'ın dikkate değer özellikleridir.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>BitTorrent 是一个对等网络文件共享协议，多用于在多个用户间分发大量的数据。</p>
    <p>Transmission 是个 BitTorrent 客户端，具有易用的前端和跨平台的后端。有适用于 OS X 和 Windows 的本地客户端，也包括命令行和 Web 前端。</p>
    <p>Transmission 值得注意的功能包括支持本地节点发现（LPD）、加密、DHT、µTP、PEX 和磁力链接。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://transmissionbt.com/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/transmission/transmission/master/gtk/screenshots/a.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <update_contact>info_AT_transmissionbt.com</update_contact>
</component>