<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>virt-manager</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">virt-manager.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">virt-manager.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" type="cached" width="128">virt-manager.png</icon>
  <id>virt-manager.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Virtual Machine Manager</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">虛擬系統管理器</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">虚拟系统管理器</name>
  <name lang="uk">Інструмент керування віртуальними машинами</name>
  <name lang="tr">Virtual Machine Manager</name>
  <name lang="te">వర్చ్యువల్ కంప్యూటరు నిర్వహణాధికారి</name>
  <name lang="ta">மெய்நிகர் கணினி மேலாளர்</name>
  <name lang="sv">Administrerare av virtuella maskiner</name>
  <name lang="sr">Управник виртуелне машине</name>
  <name lang="sr@latin">Upravnik virtuelne mašine</name>
  <name lang="sk">Správca virtuálnych počítačov</name>
  <name lang="ru">Менеджер виртуальных машин</name>
  <name lang="ro">Manager maşină virtuală</name>
  <name lang="pt">Gestor de Máquinas Virtuais</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Gerenciador de máquinas virtuais</name>
  <name lang="pl">Menedżer maszyn wirtualnych</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਵਰਚੁਅਲ ਮਸ਼ੀਨ ਮੈਨੇਜਰ</name>
  <name lang="or">ଆଭାସୀ ମେସିନ ପରିଚାଳକ</name>
  <name lang="nl">Virtuele machine beheerder</name>
  <name lang="ms">Pengurus Mesin Maya</name>
  <name lang="mr">वर्च्युअल मशीन व्यवस्थापक</name>
  <name lang="ml">വിര്‍ച്ച്വല്‍ മഷീന്‍ മാനേജര്‍</name>
  <name lang="ko">가상 머신 관리자</name>
  <name lang="kn">ವರ್ಚುವಲ್‌ ಗಣಕ ವ್ಯವಸ್ಥಾಪಕ</name>
  <name lang="ja">仮想マシンマネージャー</name>
  <name lang="it">Virtual Machine Manager</name>
  <name lang="id">Manajer Mesin Virtual</name>
  <name lang="hu">Virtuális gép vezérlőpult</name>
  <name lang="hr">Upravljač virtualnog računala</name>
  <name lang="hi">वर्चुअल मशीन प्रबंधक</name>
  <name lang="gu">વર્ચ્યુઅલ મશીન વ્યવસ્થાપક</name>
  <name lang="fur">Gjestôr di Machinis Virtuâls</name>
  <name lang="fr">Gestionnaire de machines virtuelles</name>
  <name lang="fi">Virtuaalikoneiden hallitsin</name>
  <name lang="es">Gestor de máquinas virtuales</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Virtual Machine Manager</name>
  <name lang="de">Virtuelle Maschinenverwaltung</name>
  <name lang="da">Administration for virtuel maskine</name>
  <name lang="cs">Správce virtuálních strojů</name>
  <name lang="ca">Eina de gestió de màquines virtuals</name>
  <name lang="bs">Upravljač virtualnog računala</name>
  <name lang="bn_IN">ভার্চুয়াল মেশিন ম্যানেজার</name>
  <name lang="bg">Мениджър на виртуални машини</name>
  <name lang="as">ভাৰ্চুৱেল ডিভাইচ ব্যৱস্থাপক</name>
  <summary>Graphically manage KVM, Xen, or LXC via libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">通過 libvirt 圖形化管理 KVM、Xen 或 LXC 虛擬系統</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">通过 libvirt 图形化管理 KVM、Xen 或 LXC 虚拟系统</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Графічний засіб керування KVM, Xen або LXC за допомогою libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">KVM, Xen veya LXC'yi libvirt aracılığıyla grafiksel olarak yönetin</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Hantera grafiskt KVM, Xen eller LXC via libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Графический интерфейс для управления KVM, Xen или LXC с помощью libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Gerir KVM, Xen, ou LXC graficamente via libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Gerencia graficamente KVM, Xen ou LXC via libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Graficzne zarządzanie maszynami KVM, Xen lub LXC przez bibliotekę libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Grafisch beheren van KVM, Xen of LXC via libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">KVM, Xen, 또는 libvirt를 통한 LXC를 그래픽으로 관리</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">libvirt 経由の KVM、Xen、LXC に対するグラフィカルな管理</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Gestire graficamente KVM, Xen, o LXC via libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Mengelola KVM, Xen, atau LXC secara grafis melalui libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Grafikusan kezelheti a KVM-et, a Xen-t vagy az LXC-t a libvirt segítségével</summary>
  <summary lang="fur">Gjestìs in mût grafic KVM, Xen o LXC vie libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Gérer KVM, Xen, ou LXC de manière graphique via libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Hallitse graafisesti KVM:ää, Xeniä tai LXC:tä libvirtin välityksellä</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Administrar graficamente KVM, Xen, o LXC via libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Graphically manage KVM, Xen, or LXC via libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Grafische Verwaltung von KVM, Xen oder LXC mittels libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Grafická správa KVM, Xen nebo LXC prostřednictvím libvirt</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Gestiona de forma gràfica KVM, Xen, o LXC a través de libvirt</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
   Virtual Machine Manager provides a graphical tool for administering virtual
   machines for KVM, Xen, and LXC. Start, stop, add or remove virtual devices,
   connect to a graphical or serial console, and see resource usage statistics
   for existing VMs on local or remote machines. Uses libvirt as the backend
   management API.
  </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Virtual Machine Manager proporciona una eina gràfica per administrar màquines virtuals per KVM, Xen i LXC. Comenceu, atureu, afegiu o suprimiu dispositius virtuals, connecteu-vos a una consola gràfica o sèrie i consulteu les estadístiques d'ús dels recursos per a les MV existents en màquines locals o remotes. Utilitza libvirt com a API d'administració del dorsal.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Virtual Machine Manager poskytuje grafický nástroj pro správu virtuálních strojů pro KVM, Xen a LXC. Pro spouštění, zastavování, přidávání nebo odebírání virtuálních zařízení, připojení ke grafické nebo sériové konzoli a statistiky využívání prostředků pro existující virt. stroje na místním nebo vzdálených strojích. Na pozadí používá jako API pro správu libvirt.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Virtual Machine Manager bietet ein grafisches Tool zur Verwaltung virtueller Maschinen für KVM, Xen und LXC. Starten, Stoppen, Hinzufügen oder Entfernen virtueller Geräte, Herstellen einer Verbindung zu einer grafischen oder seriellen Konsole und Anzeigen von Ressourcennutzungsstatistiken für vorhandene VMs auf lokalen oder Remote-Rechnern. Verwendet libvirt als Backend-Verwaltungs-API.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Virtual Machine Manager provides a graphical tool for administering virtual machines for KVM, Xen, and LXC. Start, stop, add or remove virtual devices, connect to a graphical or serial console, and see resource usage statistics for existing VMs on local or remote machines. Uses libvirt as the backend management API.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>El Administrador de Maquinas Virtuales Virtual Machine provee una interfaz gráfica para administrar maquinas virtuales para KVM, Xen, y LXC. Inicie, detenga, agregue o remueva dispositivos virtuales, acceda a una consola grafía o serial,  visualice estadisticas de uso de recursos de las Maquinas Virtuales existentes en maquinas locales o remotas. Utiliza libvirt como API de la herramienta de administración.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Virtuaalikoneiden hallitsin tarjoaa graafisen käyttöliittymän KVM-, Xen- ja LXC-virtuaalikoneiden hallintaan. Käynnistä, pysäytä, lisää tai poista virtuaalikoneita, yhdistä graafiseen tai sarjakonsoliin ja tarkastele olemassa olevien virtuaalikoneiden resurssinkäyttötilastoja. Taustalla hallintaan tarkoitetun rajapinnan tarjoaa libvirt.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Virtual Machine Manager est un outil graphique pour administrer des machines virtuelles utilisant KVM, Xen ou LXC. Il permet de démarrer, arrêter, ajouter ou supprimer des périphériques virtuels, de se connecter à une console graphique ou série, et d’obtenir des statistiques d’utilisation des ressources pour des machines virtuelles existant sur des machines physiques locales ou distantes. Il utilise libvirt comme API de gestion des machines virtuelles.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fur">
    <p>Gjestôr di Machinis Virtuâls al furnìs un strument grafic par aministrâ machinis virtuâls par KVM, Xen e LXC. Fâ partî, fermâ, zontâ e gjavâ dispositîfs virtuâi, conetisi a une console grafiche o seriâl, visualizâ statistichis sul ûs des risorsis pes MV esistentis su machinis locâls o rimotis. Al dopre libvirt come API di gjestion dal backend.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Virtuális gép vezérlőpult egy grafikus eszközt biztosít a virtuális gépek kezeléséhez KVM, Xen és LXC esetén. Indítsa el, állítsa le, adjon hozzá vagy távolítson el virtuális gépeket, kapcsolódjon grafikusan vagy soros konzolon, és tekintse meg a létező helyi vagy távoli virtuális gépek erőforrás-használatát.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Manajer Mesin Virtual menyediakan alat grafis untuk mengelola mesin virtual untuk KVM, Xen, dan LXC. Memulai, menghentikan, menambah, atau ,menghapus perangkat virtual, menyambungkan ke konsol grafis atau serial, dan melihat statistik penggunaan sumber daya untuk VM yang ada di mesin lokal atau jarak jauh. Menggunakan libvirt sebagai API manajemen backend.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Virtual Machine Manager fornisce uno strumento grafico per amministrare macchine virtuali KVM, Xen e LXC. Avviare, fermare, aggiungere e rimuovere dispositivi virtuali, connettersi con una console grafica o testuale, visualizzare statistiche sull'utilizzo delle risorse di VM esistenti su macchine locali o remote. Utilizza libvirt come interfaccia di gestione.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>仮想マシンマネージャーは、KVM、Xen、LXC の仮想マシンを管理するためのグラフィカルツールです。ローカルもしくはリモートホスト上の仮想マシンの起動、停止、仮想デバイスの追加/削除、グラフィカルコンソール/シリアルコンソールへの接続、既存の仮想マシンのリソース使用量の統計的な可視化を行うことができます。管理 API のバックエンドとして libvirt を使用します。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>가상 장비(machine) 관리자는 KVM, Xen과 LXC와 함께 가상장비 관리를 위해 그래픽 도구를 제공합니다. 시작하고, 멈추고, 추가하거나 제거하기, 그래픽 또는 시리얼 콘솔에 연결하기, 그리고 가상 장치는 로컬 또는 원격 장비에 가상장비가 존재하기 위해 자원 사용 통계를 참조하세요. 백엔드 관리 API로 libvirt를 사용하세요.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Virtual machine manager biedt een grafische gereedschap voor het beheer van virtuele machines voor KVM, Xen en LXC. Starten, stoppen, toevoegen of verwijderen van virtuele apparaten, verbinding maken met een grafische of seriële console en bekijken van de statistieken van het brongebruik voor bestaande VM's op lokale of machines op afstand. Gebruikt libvirt als de backend management API.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Menedżer maszyn wirtualnych dostarcza graficzne narzędzie do administrowania maszynami wirtualnymi dla KVM, Xen i LXC. Umożliwia uruchamianie, zatrzymywanie, dodawanie i usuwanie urządzeń wirtualnych, łączenie z konsolą graficzną lub szeregową oraz wyświetlanie statystyk użycia zasobów istniejących maszyn wirtualnych na lokalnych lub zdalnych maszynach. Używa biblioteki libvirt jako API zarządzania.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Gestor de Máquinas Virtuais fornece uma ferramenta gráfica para administrar máquinas virtuais, para KVM, Xen e LXC. Inicia, para, adiciona ou remove dispositivos virtuais, conecta a uma consola gráfica ou em série, e vê estatísticas de utilização de recursos para VMs existentes em máquinas locais ou remotas. Usa a libvirt como API de gestão de infraestrutura.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>O gerenciador de máquinas virtuais oferece uma ferramenta gráfica para administrar máquinas virtuais KVM, Xen e LXC. Inicia, para, adiciona ou remove dispositivos virtuais, conecta a um console gráfico ou serial, visualiza estatísticas de uso de recursos de VMs existentes em máquinas locais ou remotas. Usa o libvirt como API de gerenciamento.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Менеджер виртуальных машин предоставляет графический интерфейс для управления виртуальными машинами KVM, Xen и LXC. Предусмотрена возможность запускать, останавливать, добавлять и удалять виртуальные устройства, устанавливать соединения с графической или последовательной консолью и просматривать статистику по использованию ресурсов для имеющихся виртуальных машин на локальных или удалённых компьютерах. В качестве API для управления виртуализацией используется libvirt.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Hanteraren för virtuella maskiner tillhandahåller ett grafiskt verktyg för att administrera virtuella maskiner för KVM, Xen och LXC. Starta, stoppa, lägg till eller ta bort virtuella enheter, anslit till en grafisk eller seriell konsol och se statistik över resursanvändningen för befintliga VM:er på lokala eller fjärrmaskiner. Använder libvirt som API i bakänden.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Virtual Machine Manager, KVM, Xen ve LXC için sanal makineleri yönetmek için grafiksel bir araç sağlar. Sanal aygıtları başlatın, durdurun, ekleyin veya kaldırın, bir grafiksel veya seri konsola bağlanın ve yerel veya uzak makinelerdeki mevcut sanal makineler için kaynak kullanım istatistiklerini görün. Arka uç yönetim API'si olarak libvirt kullanır.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Засіб керування віртуальними машинами є графічним інструментом адміністрування віртуальних машин, зокрема машин KVM, Xen та LXC. Передбачено можливість запускати, зупиняти, додавати і вилучати віртуальні пристрої, встановлювати з'єднання із графічною або послідовною консоллю і переглядати статистику щодо використання ресурсів для наявних віртуальних машин на локальному або віддаленому комп'ютері. Для роботи використовує програмний інтерфейс модулів libvirt.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>虚拟系统管理器为管理 KVM、Xen 和 LXC 虚拟机提供了一个图形化工具。可以启动、停止、添加或移除虚拟设备，连接到图形或串行控制台，并能查看本地或远程计算机上现有虚拟机的资源使用情况统计。其使用了 libvirt 作为后端管理 API。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>虛擬系統管理器為管理 KVM、Xen 和 LXC 虛擬機提供了一個圖形化工具。可以啟動、停止、添加或移除虛擬裝置，連接到圖形或串列控制台，並能查看本機或遠端電腦上現有虛擬機的資源使用情況統計。其使用了 libvirt 作為後端管理 API。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://virt-manager.org/appdata/en_US/manager.png</image>
      <caption>Main manager window</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">主管理器視窗</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">主管理器窗口</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Головне вікно засобу керування</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Ana yönetici penceresi</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Huvudhanteringsfönster</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Главное окно менеджера</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Janela principal do gestor</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Janela principal do gerenciador</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Główne okno menedżera</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Hoofd beheersvenster</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">주요 관리자 창</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">メインのマネージャーのウィンドウ</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Finestra principale di amministrazione</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Jendela manajer utama</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Vezérlőpult</caption>
      <caption lang="fur">Barcon principâl dal gjestôr</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Fenêtre principale du gestionnaire</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Pääikkuna</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Ventana principal del administrador</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">Main manager window</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Hauptfenster</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Hlavní okno správy</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Finestra principal del gestor</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://virt-manager.org/appdata/en_US/details.png</image>
      <caption>Virtual machine configuration screen</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">虛擬系統配置介面</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">虚拟系统配置界面</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Вікно налаштовування віртуальної машини</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Sanal makine yapılandırma ekranı</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Konfigurationsskärm för en virtuell maskin</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Окно настройки виртуальной машины</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Ecrã de configuração da máquina virtual</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Tela de configuração da máquina virtual</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Ekran konfiguracji maszyny wirtualnej</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Virtuele machine configuratiescherm</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">가상 장비 설정 화면</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">仮想マシンの設定画面</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Schermata di configurazione della macchina virtuale</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Layar konfigurasi mesin virtual</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">Virtuális gép konfiguráció</caption>
      <caption lang="fur">Videade di configurazion de machine virtuâl</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Écran de configuration des machines virtuelles</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Virtuaalikoneen asetusnäkymä</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Configuración de pantalla de la maquina virtual</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">Virtual machine configuration screen</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Einstellungsfenster der virtuellen Maschine</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Obrazovka nastavení virtuálního stroje</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Pantalla de configuració de la màquina virtual</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://virt-manager.org/appdata/en_US/console.png</image>
      <caption>Graphical console connection for a virtual machine</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">虛擬系統圖形化控制台連接</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">虚拟系统图形化控制台连接</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Графічний засіб з'єднання з консоллю віртуальної машини</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Bir sanal makine için grafiksel konsol bağlantısı</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Grafisk konsolanslutning för en virtuell maskin</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Подключение графической консоли для виртуальной машины</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">Ligação de consola gráfica para uma máquina virtual</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Conexão de console gráfico para uma máquina virtual</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Połączenie konsoli graficznej dla maszyny wirtualnej</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Grafische consoleverbinding voor een virtuele machine</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">가상 장비를 위한 그래픽 콘솔 연결</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">この仮想マシンに対するグラフィカルコンソールの接続</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Connessione alla console grafica di una macchina virtuale</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Koneksi konsol grafis untuk mesin virtual</caption>
      <caption lang="fur">Conession de console grafiche par une machine virtuâl</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Connexion par console graphique d’une machine virtuelle</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Graafinen konsoliyhteys virtuaalikoneeseen</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Conexión gráfica de consola para una máquina virtual</caption>
      <caption lang="en_GB">Graphical console connection for a virtual machine</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Grafische Konsole der virtuellen Maschine</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Připojení grafickou konzolí ke vzdálenému stroji</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Connexió a la consola gràfica per a una màquina virtual</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.virt-manager.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/virt-manager/virt-manager/issues/new/choose</url>
  <url type="translate">https://translate.fedoraproject.org/projects/virt-manager/virt-manager/</url>
  <update_contact>virt-tools-list@redhat.com</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">virt-manager</translation>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>virtualization</keyword>
    <keyword>libvirt</keyword>
    <keyword>qemu</keyword>
    <keyword>kvm</keyword>
  </keywords>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-03-02" version="4.0.0" />
    <release version="3.2.0" date="2020-11-14" />
    <release date="2020-09-30" version="3.1.0" />
    <release date="2020-09-15" version="3.0.0" />
    <release version="2.2.1" date="2019-07-03" />
    <release date="2019-06-17" version="2.2.0" />
  </releases>
</component>