<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>xfce.xfdashboard</pkgname>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">org.xfce.xfdashboard.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">org.xfce.xfdashboard.png</icon>
  <id>org.xfce.xfdashboard.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-3.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>xfdashboard</name>
  <summary>Maybe a Gnome shell like dashboard for Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Інтэрфейс Gnome shell для абалонкі Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Табло за управление за Xfce подобно на „Gnome Shell“</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Potser un tauler de control similar a Gnome Shell per a Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Måske et instrumentbræt til Xfce i stil med det der findes i GNOME Shell</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Ein Gnome Shell ähnliches Dashboard für Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Ενδεχομένως ένα ταμπλό δραστηριοτήτων όμοιο με αυτό του κελύφους Gnome</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Un tablero para Xfce similar al de GNOME Shell</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Agian Gnome shell antzeko aginte-taula bat Xfcerako</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Peut-être un tableau de bord façon Gnome pour Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Un panel de control parecido ao intérprete de ordes Gnome para Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="he">אולי לוח מחוונים דומה Gnome עבור Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Sebuah dasbor mirip Gnome shell untuk Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="ie">Un panel de control por Xfce in li stil de Gnome shell</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Una dashboard per Xfce simile a Gnome shell</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">Gnome シェル のような Xfce 向けダッシュボード</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">xfce용 그놈 셸 유사 대시보드</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Galbūt, į Gnome apvalkalą panašus skydelis, skirtas Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Et oversiktsprogram for Xfce som kanskje ligner på Gnome-skallet</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Een bedieningspaneel voor Xfce dat lijkt op dat van Gnome Shell.</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Pulpit nawigacyjny dla Xfce podobny do powłoki Gnome</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Talvez um painel de controlo como o Gnome shell para o Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Talvez um painel semelhante ao shell do Gnome para o Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Интерфейс GNOME shell, для среды Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Morda nadzorna plošča podobna Gnome lupini za Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="sq">Një pult për Xfce-në, i ngjashëm ndoshta me shellin Gnome</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Полетник Иксфце-а који подсећа на Гномову шкољку</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Kanske en Gnome shell liknande dashboard för Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Xfce için belki Gnome shell'e benzeyen kumanda paneli</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">也许是一个适用于 Xfce，像仪表板的 Gnome shell</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Xfdashboard provides a GNOME shell dashboard like interface for use with Xfce desktop.</p>
    <p>It can be configured to run to any keyboard shortcut and when executed provides an overview of applications currently open enabling the user to switch between different applications. The search feature works like Xfce's app finder which makes it convenient to search for and start applications.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Xfdashboard падае панэль інструментаў GNOME як інтэрфейс для XFCE.</p>
    <p>Яе можна наладзіць для запуску любым спалучэннем клавіш. Пасля запуску забяспечваецца магчымасць прагляду запушчаных праграм і пераключэння паміж рознымі праграмамі. Функцыя пошуку працуе як Хfce App finder.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Xfdashboard предлага GNOME shell подобно табло за управление, предназначено за Xfce.</p>
    <p>Той може да бъде конфигуриран да стартира всеки на пряк път и когато се изпълни предоставя преглед на приложенията, които в момента са отворени, което позволява на потребителя да превключва между различни приложения. Функцията за търсене работи като търсачката на програми на Xfce, което го прави удобен за търсене и стартиране на приложения.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Xfdashboard proporciona una interfície de tauler de control similar a Gnome Shell per utilitzar amb l'escriptori Xfce.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Xfdashboard giver en grænseflade med et instrumentbræt til Xfce-skrivebordet i stil med det der findes i GNOME Shell.</p>
    <p>Det kan konfigureres til at køre med en hvilken som helst tastaturgenvej og når den udføres vises en oversigt med programmer som er åbne så brugeren kan skifte mellem dem. Søgefunktionaliteten virker ligesom i Xfce's programfinder hvilket gør det nemt at søge efter og starte programmer.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Xfdashboard bietet ein GNOME Shell ähnliches Dashboard Interface für die Benützung mit dem Xfce Desktop an.</p>
    <p>Es kann so konfiguriert werden, dass es auf jedem beliebigen Tastenkürzel läuft und bei der Ausführung einen Überblick über die derzeit geöffneten Anwendungen bietet, so dass der Benutzer zwischen verschiedenen Anwendungen wechseln kann. Die Suchfunktion funktioniert wie der App-Finder von Xfce, was das Suchen und Starten von Anwendungen bequem macht.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>To Xfdashboard παρέχει μια διεπαφή όμοια με την επισκόπηση δραστηριοτήτων του κελύφους GNOME προς χρήση με το περιβάλλον εργασίας Xfce.</p>
    <p>Μπορεί να ρυθμιστεί ώστε να εκτελείται με οποιαδήποτε εντολή και όταν εκτελείται παρέχει μια επισκόπηση των ανοιχτών εφαρμογών δίνοντας στο χρήστη τη δυνατότητα εναλλαγής μεταξύ διαφορετικών εφαρμογών. Η λειτουργία αναζήτησης λειτουργεί όπως η εύρεση εφαρμογών του Xfce πράγμα που καθιστά βολική την αναζήτηση και εκκίνηση εφαρμογών.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Xfdashboard provee una interfaz similar al tablero de GNOME Shell para el escritorio Xfce.</p>
    <p>Se puede configurar para que se ejecute con cualquier atajo de teclado. Al ejecutarse proporciona una vista general de las aplicaciones abiertas y permite al usuario cambiar entre diferentes aplicaciones. La función de búsqueda funciona como el buscador de aplicaciones de Xfce, lo que facilita la búsqueda y el inicio de aplicaciones.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Xfdashboard GNOME shell interfazearen antzeko aginte-mahai bat hornitzen du Xfce mahaigainean erabiltzeko.</p>
    <p>Edozein teklatu lasterbide exekutatzeko konfiguratu daiteke eta exekutatzerakoan unean irekitako aplikazioen ikuspegia ematen du, erabiltzaileari aplikazioen aldatzeko aukera emanez. Bilaketa ezaugarriak Xfceren aplikazio bilatzailea bezala funtzionatzen du, aplikazioak bilatzea eta abiaraztea erraztuz.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Xfdashboard fournit une interface de tableau de bord façon GNOME Shell pour une utilisation avec le bureau Xfce.</p>
    <p>Il peut être configuré pour fonctionner avec n'importe quel raccourci clavier et lorsqu'il est exécuté donne un aperçu des applications actuellement ouvertes permettant à l'utilisateur de basculer entre différentes applications. La fonction de recherche fonctionne comme l'application Finder de Xfce qui le rend pratique pour rechercher et démarrer des applications.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>O Xfdashboard fornece un interprete de ordes de panel de control Gnome para usar no escritorio Xfce</p>
    <p>Pode configurarse para se executar con calquera atallo de teclado e cando se executa fornece unha visión xeral das aplicacións que están abertas permitindo ao usuario cambiar entre diferentes aplicacións. A función de busca funciona como buscador de aplicacións do Xfce o que fai que sexa útil para buscar e iniciar aplicacións.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>Xfdashboard מספק ממשק דומה ללוח מחוונים של מעטפת GNOME לשימוש עם שולחן עבודה Xfce.</p>
    <p>הוא ניתן להגדרה כך שירוץ מכל קיצור דרך במקלדת וכאשר מופעל הוא מספק סקירה של ישומים שכרגע פתוחים ומאפשר למשתמש לעבור בין ישומים שונים. תכונת החיפוש עובדת כמו מוצא הישומים של Xfce והופכת לנח חיפוש והתחלה של ישומים.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Xfdashboard menyediakan sebuah antarmuka mirip dasbor GNOME shell untuk digunakan dengan desktop Xfce.</p>
    <p>Xfdashboard dapat dikonfigurasi untuk dijalankan melalui suatu pintasan papan tik, dan ketika dijalankan, akan menyediakan sebuah ikhtisar aplikasi-aplikasi yang sedang terbuka, memungkinkan pengguna untuk berpindah antar aplikasi yang berbeda. Fitur pencarian bekerja seperti pencari aplikasi Xfce yang memudahkan untuk mencari dan menjalankan aplikasi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Xfdashboard fornisce una dashboard simile a GNOME shell che può essere utilizzata nell'ambiente Xfce.</p>
    <p>Può essere configurato per essere avviato con qualunque scorciatoia da tastiera per provvedere una panoramica delle applicazioni aperte e l'abilità di passare da un'applicazione all'altra. La funzione di ricerca agisce come l'app finder di Xfce rendendola comoda per la ricerca e l'avvio delle applicazioni.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>Xfdashboard は GNOME shell ダッシュボードのような Xfce デスクトップで使用するためのインターフェースを提供します。</p>
    <p>任意のショートカットキーで実行するように構成でき、実行すると現在アプリケーションの概要が表示され、ユーザーはさまざまなアプリケーションを切り替えることができます。検索機能は Xfce のアプリファインダーのように機能し、アプリケーションの検索と起動が便利になります。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>xf대시보드는 Xfce 데스크톱용 그놈 셸 대시보드 유사 인터페이스를 제공합니다.</p>
    <p>실행할 바로가기 키를 설정할 수 있고 제각기 다른 프로그램을 전환할 수 있게 현재 열린 프로그램의 미리보기 화면을 보여줍니다. 검색 기능은 Xfce 앱 검색기처럼 동작하며, 검색을 간편하게 수행하고 프로그램을 쉽게 시작할 수 있게 해줍니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Xfdashboard pateikia į Gnome apvalkalo skydelį panašią sąsają, skirtą naudoti Xfce darbalaukyje.</p>
    <p>Skydelis gali būti susietas su bet kuriuo sparčiuoju klavišu, o jį paleidus, skydelis pateikia esamu metu atvertų programų apžvalgą, taip leisdamas naudotojui perjungti tarp įvairių programų. Paieškos ypatybė veikia taip pat, kaip ir Xfce programų paieška, dėl to, ją patogu naudoti programų paieškai bei paleidimui.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Xfdashboard er et oversiktsprogram som ligner på GNOME-skallet, og kan brukes sammen med skrivebordsmiljøet Xfce.</p>
    <p>Det kan settes opp til å kjøre programmer med hurtigtaster. Når oversiktsprogrammet starter viser det en liste over åpne programmer slik at man kan bytte mellom dem. Søkefunksjonen tilsvarer programfinneren i Xfce, og gjør det enkelt å søke etter og starte programmer.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Xfdashboard is vergelijkbaar met het GNOME Shell-dashboard.</p>
    <p>Het kan worden ingesteld om elke gewenste sneltoets uit te voeren en biedt een overzicht van thans geopende toepassingen, zodat de gebruiker tussen verschillende toepassingen kan schakelen. De zoekfunctie werkt als de toepassingenzoeker van Xfce, wat het makkelijk maakt om toepassingen te zoeken en te starten.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Xfdashboard dostarcza interfejs wzorowany na panelu powłoki GNOME do użycia w Xfce.</p>
    <p>Może zostać skonfigurowany do uruchomienia pod dowolnym skrótem klawiszowym. Kiedy uruchomiony, wyświetla podgląd uruchomionych aplikacji i pozwala na przełączanie pomiędzy nimi. Funkcja wyszukiwania działa podobnie do Wyszukiwarki aplikacji Xfce, pozwalając szybciej uruchomić aplikacje.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Xfdashboard fornece uma interface semelhante ao painel de controlo do GNOME para utilização com o ambiente de trabalho Xfce.</p>
    <p>Pode ser configurado para executar qualquer tecla de atalho e quando executado, fornece uma visão geral das aplicações abertas no momento, permitindo ao utilizador trocar entre as diferentes aplicações. O recurso de pesquisa funciona como o localizador de aplicações do Xfce, o que torna mais conveniente pesquisar e iniciar aplicações.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>O Xfdashboard fornece um painel do shell do GNOME como interface para uso com a área de trabalho do Xfce.</p>
    <p>Ele pode ser configurado para ser executado em qualquer atalho do teclado e, quando executado, fornece uma visão geral dos aplicativos atualmente abertos, permitindo que o usuário alterne entre diferentes aplicativos. O recurso de pesquisa funciona como o localizador de aplicativos do Xfce, o que facilita a pesquisa e o início de aplicativos.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Xfdashboard представляет собой аналог обзорного режима GNOME shell для использования в окружении Xfce.</p>
    <p>Он может быть сконфигурирован для работы с любым сочетанием клавиш и при выполнении обеспечивает обзор приложений открытых в настоящее время, позволяет пользователю переключаться между различными приложениями. Функция поиска работает как xfce App finder, что делает его удобным для поиска и запуска приложений.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Xfdashboard za namizje Xfce ponuja vmesnik v obliki nadzorne plošče, ki je podobna GNOME lupini</p>
    <p>Mogoče ga je nastaviti  za zaganjanje poljubnih bližnjiv na tipkovnici in ko je zagnan ponuja pregled nad trenutno odprtimi aplikacijami, kar omogoča uporabniku preklapljanje med njimi. Iskalnik deluje kakor Xfce iskalnik programov, zaradi česar je primeren za iskanje in zagon apliakcij.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sq">
    <p>Xfdashboard furnizon një pult të ngjashëm me shellin GNOME për përdorim me desktopin Xfce.</p>
    <p>Mund të formësohet për t’u vënë në punë me çfarëdo shkurtoreje tastiere dhe, kur ekzekutohet, furnizon një përmbledhje të aplikacioneve aktualisht të hapura, duke i bërë të mundur përdoruesit të kalojë nga një aplikacion në tjetrin. Veçoria e kërkimit funksionon në mënyrë të ngjashme me gjetësin e aplikacioneve të Xfce-së, çka e bën të lehtë kërkimin dhe nisjen e aplikacioneve.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Полетник Иксфце-а је сучеље попут Гномове шкољке за употребу на радној површи Иксфце-а.</p>
    <p>Може се подесити да се покреће на било коју пречицу дугмади, и када се изврши даје преглед тренутно отворених програма, омогућујући кориснику да прелази са једног програма на други. Претрага ради попут претраживача програма за Иксфце што чини полетника згодним за претрагу и покретање програма.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Xfdashboard tillhandahåller ett GNOME shell liknande gränssnitt för användning med Xfce-skrivbordet.</p>
    <p>Det kan konfigureras till att köra godtyckliga tangentbordsgenvägar, och ger vid körning en översikt av öppna program, vilket låter användaren växla mellan olika program. Sökfunktionen fungerar precis som Xfces programsökning, vilket gör det smidigt att söka efter och starta program.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Xfdashboard, Xfce masaüstüyle kullanmak için GNOME kabuğu kumanda paneli benzeri arayüz sağlar.</p>
    <p>Başlatıldığında, açık uygulamaları göstererek kullanıcının farklı uygulamalar arasında geçiş yapmasını sağlar ve herhangi bir klavye kısayolunu çalıştırmak üzere yapılandırılabilir. Arama özelliği, Xfce'nin uygulama bulucusu gibi çalışır, böylece uygulamaları başlatmak ve aramak kolaylaşır.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>Xfdashboard 提供了一个 GNOME shell 仪表盘的接口，用于与Xfce桌面使用。</p>
    <p>可以将其配置为运行到任何键盘快捷键，并且在执行时可以概述当前打开的应用程序，从而使用户可以在不同的应用程序之间进行切换。 搜索功能的作用类似于 Xfce 的 app finder，它使搜索和启动应用程序变得非常方便。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://docs.xfce.org/_media/apps/xfdashboard/starting-up.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Browsing applications</caption>
      <caption lang="be">Прагляд праграм</caption>
      <caption lang="bg">Преглед на програмите</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Navegació per les aplicacions</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Gennemser programmer</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Anwendungen durchsuchen</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Περιήγηση στις εφαρμογές</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Navegar por las aplicaciones</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Sirvin rakendusi</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Aplikazioak arakatzen</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Applications de navigation</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Navegación por aplicacións</caption>
      <caption lang="he">סיור באפליקציות</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Meramban aplikasi</caption>
      <caption lang="ie">Navigation inter applicationes</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Navigazione delle applicazioni</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">アプリケーションの閲覧</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">프로그램 탐색</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Programų naršymas</caption>
      <caption lang="nb">Blar gjennom programmer</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Toepassingen verkennen</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Przeglądanie aplikacji</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">A explorar aplicações</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Navegando em aplicativos</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Просмотр приложений</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Brskanje po aplikacijah</caption>
      <caption lang="sq">Aplikacione shfletimi</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Преглед програма</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Bläddra bland program</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Uygulamalara göz atma</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">浏览应用</caption>
      <image>https://docs.xfce.org/_media/apps/xfdashboard/applications-view.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Searching applications</caption>
      <caption lang="be">Пошук праграм</caption>
      <caption lang="bg">Търсене на програми</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">Cerca d'aplicacions</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Søger efter programmer</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Suche Anwendungen</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Αναζήτηση εφαρμογών</caption>
      <caption lang="es">Buscar aplicaciones</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Otsin rakendusi</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Aplikazioak bilatzen</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">Applications de recherche</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">Busca de aplicacións</caption>
      <caption lang="he">חיפוש אפליקציות</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Mencari aplikasi</caption>
      <caption lang="ie">Sercha por applicationes</caption>
      <caption lang="it">Ricerca delle applicazioni</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">アプリケーションを検索</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">프로그램 검색</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Programų paieška</caption>
      <caption lang="nb">Søker etter programmer</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Toepassingen zoeken</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Wyszukiwanie aplikacji</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">A procurar aplicações</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">Procurando aplicativos</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Поиск приложений</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Iskanje aplikacij</caption>
      <caption lang="sq">Aplikacione kërkimi</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Претрага програма</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Sök efter program</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Uygulamaları arama</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">搜索应用</caption>
      <image>https://docs.xfce.org/_media/apps/xfdashboard/search-view.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://docs.xfce.org/apps/xfdashboard/start/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.xfce.org/apps/xfdashboard/-/issues</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/gmc-holle/xfdashboard/issues</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.xfce.org/apps/xfdashboard/manual</url>
  <project_group>XFCE</project_group>
  <updatecontact>nomad@froevel.de</updatecontact>
  <provides>
    <binary>xfdashboard</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.xfce.xfdashboard.desktop</launchable>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>window management</keyword>
    <keyword>application management</keyword>
    <keyword>organize</keyword>
    <keyword>search tool</keyword>
    <keyword>search</keyword>
  </keywords>
  <releases>
    <release timestamp="1633152304" version="0.9.5">
      <description>
        <p>This unstable development version fixes the mode to run in background.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1632293693" version="0.9.4">
      <description>
        <p>This unstable development version introduces a new plugin to pin windows on secondary monitors automatically.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази нестабилна версия в процес на разработка, въвежда нова приставка за автоматично закрепване на прозорци на вторични монитори.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne ustabile udviklingsversion indfører et nyt plugin til automatisk at fastgøre vinduer til sekundære skærme.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese instabile Entwicklungsversion führt ein neues Plugin ein, um Fenster automatisch an sekundäre Monitore anzuheften.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión inestable en desarrollo introduce un nuevo complemento para fijar automáticamente ventanas en los monitores secundarios.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version de développement instable introduit un nouveau greffon pour épingler automatiquement les fenêtres secondaires sur des moniteurs secondaires.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסת פיתוח לא יציבה זו מציגה תוסף חדש להצמדת חלונות אוטומטית במסכי משנה.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione instabile di sviluppo introduce una nuova estensione per agganciare automaticamente le finestre su schermi secondari. </p>
        <p lang="ja">この不安定な開発版では、セカンダリモニターにウィンドウを自動的にピン留めするための新しいプラグインが導入されています。</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši nestabili plėtojimo versija pristato naują įskiepį, skirtą automatiškai prisegti langus antriniuose monitoriuose.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne ustabile utviklerversjonen innfører et nytt programtillegg for å feste vinduer på sekundærskjermer automatisk.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze onstabiele ontwikkelversie introduceert een nieuw invoegsel om vensters automatisch vast te zetten op secundaire beeldschermen.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta niestabilna wersja deweloperska wprowadza nową wtyczkę do automatycznego przypinania okien na monitorach dodatkowych.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão de desenvolvimento instável apresenta um novo plug-in para afixar janelas em monitores secundários automaticamente.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Ky version mjedisi të paqëndrueshëm sjell për herë të parë një shtojcë të re, për fiksim vetvetiu dritaresh në ekrane dytësorë.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово нестабилно издање представља нови прикључак за самостално лепљење прозора на помоћном приказу.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个不稳定的开发版本引入了一个新插件来自动将窗口固定在辅助显示器上。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1619428997" version="0.9.3">
      <description>
        <p>This unstable development version improves window placement and a new search plugin looking for matches against the recently used documents.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтай нестабільнай версіі палепшана размяшчэнне акон і дададзена новая ўбудова пошуку, якая шукае супадзенні з нядаўна выкарыстанымі дакуметамі.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази нестабилна версия в процес на разработка подобрява разположението на прозореца и е с нов плъгин за търсене, който търси съвпадения в наскоро използваните документи.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne ustabile udviklingsversioner forbedrer vinduesplacering og et nyt søgeplugin leder efter match i de seneste brugte dokumenter.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese instabile Entwicklungsversion verbessert die Fensterplatzierung und ein neues Such-Plugin, das nach Übereinstimmungen mit den zuletzt verwendeten Dokumenten sucht.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión inestable en desarrollo mejora la colocación de las ventanas y cuenta con un nuevo complemento de búsqueda para encontrar coincidencias en los documentos usados recientemente.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Garapeneko bertsio ezegonkor honek leihoen kokapena hobetzen du eta azkenaldian erabilitako dokumentuak bilatzen dituen bilaketa plugin berri bat dakar.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version de développement instable améliore le placement des fenêtres et un nouveau greffon de recherche recherchant des correspondances avec les documents récemment utilisés.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión de desenvolvemento inestábel mellora a colocación de xanelas xunto cun novo engadido de busca o cal procura coincidencias cos documentos usados recentemente.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסת פיתוח לא יציבה זו משפרת מיקום חלון ותוסף חיפוש חדש לאיתור התאמות כנגד מסמכים בשימוש לאחרונה.</p>
        <p lang="id">Versi pengembangan tak stabil ini meningkatkan peletakan jendela dan sebuah plugin pencarian yang baru untuk mencari kecocokan dengan dokumen yang baru-baru ini digunakan.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione instabile di sviluppo migliora il piazzamento delle finestre ed una nuova estensione di ricerca per documenti usati di recente.</p>
        <p lang="ja">この不安定な開発版は、ウィンドウの配置と、最近使用したドキュメントを探す新しい検索プラグインを改善します。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 불안정 개발 버전에서는 창 배치 기능을 개선했고, 최근 사용한 문서 내용과 일치하는 부분을 검색하는 새 검색 플러그인을 도입했습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši nestabili plėtojimo versija patobulina langų išdėstymą ir naują paieškos įskiepį, kuris atlieka atitikmenų paiešką paskiausiai naudotuose dokumentuose.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne ustabile utviklerversjonen forbedrer vindusplassering og har et nytt søketillegg som kan lete etter treff i nylig brukte dokumenter.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze onstabiele ontwikkelingsversie verbetert vensterplaatsing en bevat een nieuw invoegsel voor het zoeken naar overeenkomsten met onlangs gebruikte documenten.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta niestabilna wersja deweloperska poprawia rozmieszczanie okien oraz nową wtyczkę wyszukującą dopasowania względem ostatnio używanych dokumentów.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão de desenvolvimento instável melhora a colocação de janelas e um novo plugin de pesquisa à procura de correspondência com os documentos recentemente utilizados.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão de desenvolvimento instável melhora a colocação de janelas e um novo plugin de pesquisa à procura de correspondência com os documentos recentemente utilizados.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta nestabilna razvojna različica izboljša pozicioniranje oken in ima nov vtičnik za iskanje, ki primerja nedavno rabljene dokumente.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Ky mjedis i paqëndrueshëm, zhvillimesh, përmirëson vendosje dritaresh dhe sjell një shtojcë të re kërkimi që sheh për përputhje kundrejt dokumenteve të përdorur së fundi.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово нестабилно развојно издање побољшава смештај прозора и нови погон претраге за поклапањима међу скорашње коришћеним документима.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här ostabila utvecklingsversionen förbättrar fönsterplacering och ett nytt sökinsticksprogram som letar efter träffar mot nyligen använda dokument.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu kararsız geliştirme sürümü pencere yerleşimini iyileştirir, son kullanılan belgelere karşı eşleşmelere bakmak için yeni arama eklentisi sunar.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个不稳定的开发版本改善了窗口位置，并提供一个新的搜索插件，用于根据最近使用的文档查找匹配项。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.2" timestamp="1617869265">
      <description>
        <p>This unstable development version completes gradients with linear gradients for outline and background filling.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтай нестабільнай версіі градыенты дапаўняюцца лінейнымі градыентамі для заліўкі контуру і фону.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази нестабилна версия в процес на разработка допълва градиентите с линейни градиенти за контур и запълване на фона.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne ustabile udviklingsversioner indfører gradienter med lineære gradienter til udfyldning af omrids og baggrunde.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese instabile Entwicklungsversion vervollständigt die Farbverläufe mit linearen Verläufen für die Kontur- und Hintergrundfüllung.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión inestable en desarrollo completa los gradientes con gradientes lineales para el contorno y el relleno del fondo.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Garapeneko bertsio ezegonkor honek ingeradetarako bide gradienteak eta atzealdearen betetzea osatzen ditu.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version de développement instable complète les dégradés avec des dégradés linéaires pour le remplissage des contours et de l'arrière-plan.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión de desenvolvemento inestábel completa os gradientes con gradientes lineais para o contorno e o recheo do fondo.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסת פיתוח לא יציבה זו משלימה גרדיינטים עם גרדיינטים ליניארים לקו חיצון ומילוי רקע.</p>
        <p lang="id">Versi pengembangan tak stabil ini melengkapi gradien dengan gradien linier untuk pengisian garis besar dan latar belakang.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione instabile di sviluppo completa i gradienti con gradienti lineari per il contorno ed il riempimento dello sfondo.</p>
        <p lang="ja">この不安定な開発版では、アウトラインと背景塗りつぶしの線形グラデーションでグラデーションを完了します。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 불안정 개발 버전에서는 외곽선과 배경 채우기에 선형 그레디언트로 완전한 그레디언트 채우기 기능을 완성했습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši nestabili plėtojimo versija užbaigia gradientus su tiesiniais gradientais, skirtais kontūrams ir fono užpildui.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne ustabile utviklerversjonen ferdigstiller fargeoverganger. Det er lineære overganger for utheving og bakgrunnsfyll.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze onstabiele ontwikkelingsversie vult gradiënten aan met lineaire gradiënten voor het vullen van omtrek en achtergrond.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta niestabilna wersja deweloperska uzupełnia gradienty liniowymi gradientami do wypełnienia konturów i tła.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão de desenvolvimento instável completa os gradientes com gradientes lineares para preenchimento de contornos e fundo.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão de desenvolvimento instável completa os gradientes com gradientes lineares para preenchimento de contornos e fundo.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta nestabilna razvojna različica dopolnjuje prelive z linearnimi prelivi za polnilo roba ali ozadja.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Ky version zhvillimi, jo i qëndrueshëm, plotëson shndërrimin e gradientëve me gradiente lineare për përvija dhe mbushje sfondi.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово нестабилно развојно издање употпуњује градијент линијским градијентом за спољњи оквир као пуњач позадине.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här ostabila utvecklingsversionen fyller i färgtoningar med linjära färgtoningar för kontur- och bakgrundsfyllning.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu kararsız geliştirme sürümü, dış çizgi ve arka plan dolumu için gradyanları çizgisel gradyanlarla tamamlar.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个不稳定的开发版本可以通过轮廓和背景填充的线性渐变来完成渐变。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1616140047" version="0.9.1">
      <description>
        <p>This unstable development version introduces completes turning libxfdashboard into a real library and introduces path gradients for outlines.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтай нестабільнай версіі завершана пераўтварэнне libxfdashboard ў сапраўдную бібліятэку і ўведзеныя шляхі градыентаў для контураў.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази нестабилна версия в процес на разработка въвежда пълното превръщане на libxfdashboard в истинска библиотека и въвежда градиенти на пътя за контурите.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne ustabile udviklingsversion indfører fuldførelse libxfdashboard som et ægte bibliotek og introducerer stigradienter til omrids.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese instabile Entwicklungsversion führt Ergänzungen ein, die libxfdashboard zu einer echten Bibliothek machen und führt Pfadverläufe für Umrisse ein.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión inestable en desarrollo introduce complementos que convierten a libxfdashboard en una biblioteca real e introduce gradientes de trayectoria para los contornos.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Garapeneko bertsio ezegonkor honek libxfdashboard benetako liburutegi batean bihurtzen amaitzen du eta bide gradienteak sartzen ditu ingeradetarako.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version de développement instable introduit  la transformation complète de libxfdashboard en une véritable bibliothèque et introduit des dégradés de chemin pour les contours.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión de desenvolvemento inestábel engade a transformación de libxfdashboard nunha biblioteca real e introduce gradientes de camiño para contornos.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסת פיתוח לא יציבה זו משלימה הפיכת libxfdashboard לספרייה אמיתית ומכניסה לשימוש גרדיינטים של נתיב עבור קוים חיצוניים.</p>
        <p lang="id">Versi pengembangan tak stabil ini mengenalkan perubahan libxfdashboard menjadi sebuah pustaka nyata dan mengenalkan gradien path untuk garis besar.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione di sviluppo instabile introduce il completamento della trasformazione di libxfdashboard in una vera libreria ed introduce i gradienti di percorso per i contorni.</p>
        <p lang="ja">この不安定な開発版では、libxfdashboard が実際のライブラリに導入され、アウトラインのパスグラデーションが導入されています。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 불안정 개발 버전에서는 libxfdashboard를 실 라이브러리로 도입 완료했고, 외곽선의 경로 그레디언트를 도입했습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Šioje nestabilioje plėtojimo versijoje pristatomas užbaigtas libxfdashboard pavertimas tikrąja biblioteka ir pristatomi kontūrų kelio gradientai.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne ustabile utviklerversjonen ferdigstiller flytting av libxfdashboard til et ordentlig bibliotek, og innfører fargeoverganger for uthevinger.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze instabiele ontwikkelingsversie voltooit de omzetting van libxfdashboard in een echt bibliotheekbestand en introduceert padgradiënten voor omtrekken.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta niestabilna wersja deweloperska wprowadza kompletne przekształcenie libxfdashboard w prawdziwą bibliotekę oraz ścieżeki gradientu dla konturów.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão de desenvolvimento instável introduz a completa transformação do libxfdashboard numa verdadeira biblioteca e introduz gradientes de percurso para contornos.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão instável de desenvolvimento apresenta uma transformação completa do libxfdashboard em uma biblioteca real e introduz padrão de gradientes para contornos.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta nestabilna razvojna različica uvaja dokončano pretvorbo libxfdashboard v pravo knjižnico in uvaja prilegajoče se prelive za obrise.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Ky version zhvillimi, jo i qëndrueshëm, plotëson shndërrimin e libxfdashboard-it në një bibliotekë të njëmendtë dhe sjell për herë të parë gradientë shtigjesh për përvijat.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово је нестабилно развојно издање које представља потпуни прелазак либиксдашбода у стварну датотеку и представља градирање путање за спољње оквире.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här instabila utvecklingsversionen introducerar ingenting synligt förutom att börja flytta libxfdashboard till ett riktigt bibliotek och introducerar stigningar för konturer.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu kararsız geliştirme sürümü, libxfdashboard'un gerçek kitaplığa dönüşümünü tamamlar ve dış çizgiler için yol geçişlerini tanıtır.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个不稳定的开发版本引入了将 libxfdashboard 变成真实库的完整功能，并引入了轮廓的路径渐变。 </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.0" timestamp="1614942988">
      <description>
        <p>This unstable development version introduces nothing user visible but begin moving libxfdashboard into a real library.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтай нестабільнай версіі распачаты перавод libxfdashboard у сапраўдную бібліятэку.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази нестабилна версия за разработка не въвежда нищо видимо за потребителя, но започваме да преместваме libxfdashboard в реална библиотека.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne ustabile udviklingsversion indfører ikke noget som er synligt for brugeren men flytter libxfdashboard ind i et ægte bibliotek.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese instabile Entwicklungsversion führt nichts für den Benutzer Sichtbares ein, sondern beginnt damit, libxfdashboard in eine echte Bibliothek zu verwandeln.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión inestable en desarrollo no introduce nada visible para el usuario, sino que empieza a convertir libxfdashboard en una biblioteca real.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Garapeneko bertsio ezegonkor honek ez dakar ikus daitekeen ezer baina libxfdashboard benetako liburutegi bihurtzen hasten da.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version de développement instable ne présente rien de visible pour l'utilisateur mais commence à déplacer libexfdashboard dans une vraie bibliothèque.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión de desenvolvemento inestábel non engade nada visíbel polo usuario, pero comeza a mover libxfdashboard a unha biblioteca real.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסת הפיתוח הלא יציבה הזו אינה מציגה שינויים הנראים למשתמש אבל מתחילה מעבר של libxfdashboard לספריה אמיתית.</p>
        <p lang="id">Versi pengembangan tak stabil ini tidak membawa perubahan yang dapat terlihat oleh pengguna, namun mulai memindahkan libxfdashboard menjadi sebuah pustaka nyata.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione instabile di sviluppo non ha introdotto nulla di visibile all'utente ma indica il punto dal quale libxfdashboard verrà trasferita in una vera libreria.</p>
        <p lang="ja">この不安定な開発バージョンではユーザーに何も表示されませんが、libxfdashboard を実際のライブラリに移動し始めます。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 불안정 개발 버전에서는 사용자 눈에 띄는 부분은 없지만, libxfdashboard를 실 라이브러리로 옮기기 시작했습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Šioje nestabilioje plėtojimo versijoje nepristatoma nieko, kas būtų matoma naudotojui, bet pradėtas libxfdashboard perkėlimas į tikrą biblioteką.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne ustabile utviklerversjonen har ingen endringer som er synlige for brukere. Man har begynt å flytte libxfdashboard til et ordentlig bibliotek.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze onstabiele ontwikkelingsversie introduceert niets nieuws voor de gebruiker maar er wordt een begin gemaakt om libxfdashboard te verplaatsen naar een echt bibliotheekbestand.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta niestabilna wersja deweloperska nie wprowadza niczego widocznego dla użytkownika, ale rozpoczęła przenoszenie libxfdashboard do prawdziwej biblioteki.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão de desenvolvimento instável não introduz nada visível ao utilizador, mas começa a mover a libxfdashboard para uma verdadeira biblioteca.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão de desenvolvimento instável introduz nada visível para o usuário, mas começa a transformar libxfdashboard em uma biblioteca real.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta nestabilna razvojna različica ne uvaja nićesar vidnega, a začenja s pretvorbo libxfdashboard v pravo knjižnico</p>
        <p lang="sq">Ky version zhvillim, jo i qëndrueshëm, nuk sjell gjë të dukshme për përdoruesin, por shënon fillimin e kalimit të libxfdashboard-it në një bibliotekë të njëmendtë.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово нестабилно развојно издање не представља кориснику ништа видно, већ преноси libxfdashboard у праву књижницу.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här instabila utvecklingsversionen introducerar ingenting synligt förutom att börja flytta libxfdashboard till ett riktigt bibliotek.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu kararsız geliştirme sürümü kullanıcının görebileceği bir şey sunmaz ancak libxfdashboard'u gerçek kitaplığa dönüştürmeye başlar.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个不稳定的开发版本没有引入任何用户可见的内容，而是开始将 libxfmdashboard 移至真实库中。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1614859879" version="0.8.1">
      <description>
        <p>This stable version fixes a bug and replaces AppInfo with AppStream metainfo.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтай стабільнай версіі выпраўленыя памылкі, а AppInfo замяняецца AppStream.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази стабилна версия коригира грешка и замества AppInfo с AppStream metainfo.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne stabile version retter en fejl og erstatter AppInfo- med AppStream-metainfo.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese stabile Version behebt einen Fehler und ersetzt AppInfo durch AppStream metainfo.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión estable corrige un error y reemplaza la metainformación de AppInfo por la de AppStream.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio egonkor honek arazo bat konpontzen du eta AppInfo AppStream metainforekin ordezkatzen du.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version stable corrige un bogue et remplace AppInfo par Appstream Metainfo.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión estábel amaña un erro e substitúe a meta información AppInfo por AppStream.</p>
        <p lang="he">הגרסה היציבה הזו מתקנת באג ומחליפה את AppInfo ב-AppStream metainfo.</p>
        <p lang="id">Versi stabil ini memperbaiki sebuah kutu dan mengganti AppInfo dengan metainfo AppStream.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione stabile risolve un bug e sostituisce AppInfo con metainfo di Appstream.</p>
        <p lang="ja">この安定バージョンはバグを修正し、 AppInfo を AppStream metainfo に置き換えます。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 안정 버전에서는 버그를 수정했으며 AppInfo를 AppStream metainfo로 대체했습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši stabili versija ištaiso klaidą ir pakeičia AppInfo į AppStream metainformaciją.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne stabile utgivelsen fikser en feil, og erstatter AppInfo med AppStream metainfo.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze stabiele versie herstelt een fout en vervangt AppInfo door AppStream metainfo.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta stabilna wersja naprawia błąd i wymienia AppInfo na metainfo AppStream.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão estável corrige um erro e substitui AppInfo por AppStream metainfo.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão estável corrige um bug e substitui o AppInfo com o AppStream Metainfo.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta stabilna različica odpravlja hrošča in zamenja Appinfo z AppStream metapodatki.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Ky version i qëndrueshëm ndreq një të metë dhe zëvendëson Appinfo me metainfo AppStream.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово стабилно издање исправља грешку и замењује Апинфо са Апстрим метаинфо.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här stabila versionen fixar ett fel och ersätter AppInfo med AppStream metainfo.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu kararlı sürüm bir hatayı giderir ve AppInfo'yu AppStream üst veri bilgisiyle değiştirir.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此稳定版本修复了一个错误，并用 AppStream metainfo 替换 AppInfo。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1608711235" version="0.8.0">
      <description>
        <p>This stable version introduces lots of new features like animations, pop-up menus, multiple backend and support for jumplists etc. It also includes lots of new and updated translations.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтай стабільнай версіі дадаецца мноства новых функцый: анімацыі, выплыўныя меню, некалькі рухавікоў і іншыя. Дададзены новыя і абноўленыя існыя пераклады.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази стабилна версия въвежда много нови функции като анимации, изскачащи менюта, множество бекенди, поддръжка на прескачане в списъка и т.н. Също така включва много нови и актуализирани преводи.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne stabile version indfører massere af nye funktionaliteter såsom animationer pop op-menuer, adskillige motorer og understøttelse af hoplister osv. Den indeholder også massere af nye og opdaterede oversættelser.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese stabile Version enthält viele neue Funktionen wie Animationen, Pop-up-Menüs, mehrere Backends und Unterstützung für Jumplists usw. Sie enthält auch viele neue und aktualisierte Übersetzungen.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión estable introduce muchas características nuevas, como animaciones, menús emergentes, múltiples motores y compatibilidad con listas de acciones, etc. También incluye muchas traducciones nuevas y actualizadas.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio egonkor honek ezaugarri berri asko dakar, animazioak bezala, goranzko menuak, hainbat backend eta jauzi zerrendak etab. Itzulpen berri eta eguneratu asko dakar ere.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version stable introduit de nombreuses nouvelles fonctionnalités telles que les animations, les menues pop-up, de multiples retours et le support des listes de saut, etc. Il contient également des traductions nouvelles et mise à jour.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión estábel introduce moitas novas funcións como animacións, menús emerxentes, infraestrutura múltiple e soporte para listas de xogos, etc. Tamén inclúe moitas traducións novas e actualizadas.</p>
        <p lang="he">הגרסה היציבה הזו מציגה הרבה תכונות חדשות כמו אנימציות, תפריטים קופצים, מגשר עורפי מרובה ותמיכה ברשימות קופצות ועוד. היא גם כוללת הרבה תרגומים חדשים ומעודכנים.</p>
        <p lang="id">Versi stabil ini mengenalkan banyak fitur-fitur baru seperti animasi, menu pop-up, beberapa backend dan dukungan untuk jumplist, dsb. Juga menyertakan banyak penerjemahan yang baru dan diperbarui.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione stabile introduce molte nuove caratteristiche come animazioni, menu a comparsa, backend multipli, supporto per jumplist, ecc. Contiene inoltre molte traduzioni nuove ed aggiornate.</p>
        <p lang="ja">この安定バージョンではアニメーション、ポップアップメニュー、複数のバックエンド、ジャンプリストのサポートなど、多くの新機能が導入されています。また多くの新規および更新された翻訳も含まれています。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 안정 버전에는 애니메이션, 단축 메뉴, 다중 백엔드, 점프 목록 등의 다양한 새 기능을 도입했습니다. 또한 상당한 분량의 새로운 최신 번역 결과물을 반영했습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši stabili versija pristato daug naujų ypatybių, tokių kaip animacijos, iškylantieji meniu, kelios vidinės pusės, peršokimo sąrašų palaikymas ir t.t. Joje taip pat yra daugybė naujų ir atnaujintų vertimų.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne stabile utgivelsen innfører en del ny funksjonalitet slik som animasjoner, sprettoppmenyer, flere bakstykker og hurtiglister. Den har dessuten flere nye og oppdaterte oversettelser.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze stabiele versie introduceert veel nieuwe functies zoals animaties, opduikmenu's, meervoudige achtergronddiensten, ondersteuning voor springlijsten enz. Zij bevat ook veel nieuwe en bijgewerkte vertalingen.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta stabilna wersja wprowadza wiele nowych funkcji, takich jak animacje, wyskakujące menu, wiele backendów oraz wsparcie dla list szybkiego dostępu itp. Zawiera również wiele nowych i zaktualizowanych tłumaczeń.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão estável apresenta muitas funcionalidades novas como animações, menus pop-up, backend múltiplo e suporte para jumplists etc. Também inclui muitas traduções novas e atualizadas.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão estável apresenta muitos recursos novos como animações, menus pop-up, múltiplo e suporte para jumplists, etc. Também inclui muitas traduções novas e atualizadas.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Эта стабильная версия вводит множество новых функций, таких как анимация, всплывающие меню, несколько способов отрисовки, поддержка списков переходов и т. д. Она также включает в себя множество новых и обновленных переводов.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta stabilna različica uvaja mnogo novosti, kot so animacije, pojavni meniji, številna ozadja in popodra za prekočne sezname itd. Vsebuje tudi nove in posodobljene prevode.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Ky version i qëndrueshëm sjell plotë veçori të reja, të tilla si, animacione, menu flluskë, pjesë të pasme të shumëfishtë dhe mbulim për “jumplists”, etj. Përmban gjithashtu plot përkthime të reja dhe të përditësuara.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово стабилно издање представља мноштво нових могућности попут оживљавања, искачућих изборника, вишеструких позадинских програма и подржава искачуће спискове, итд. Такође, укључује много нових и освежених превода.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna stabila version introducerar många nya funktioner som animationer, popup-menyer, flera backends och stöd för jumplists etc. Den innehåller också massor av nya och uppdaterade översättningar. </p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu kararlı sürüm; animasyonlar, açılır pencere menüler, çoklu arkayüzler ve atlama listeleri için destek gibi yeni özellikleri içerir. Yeni ve güncellenmiş birçok çeviriyi de içerir.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">这个稳定的版本引入了许多新功能，比如动画，弹出菜单，多个后端和支持跳转列表等。它还包括许多新增和更新的翻译。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1482422594" version="0.6.1">
      <description>
        <p>This stable version fixes a bug setting the correct default applications at first use.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтай стабільнай версіі выпраўлена памылка вызначэння прадвызначаных праграм пры першым выкарыстанні.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази стабилна версия коригира грешка при задаване на правилните приложения по подразбиране при ползване за първи път.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne stabile version retter en fejl ved indstilling af de korrekte standardprogrammer første gang det bruges.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese stabile Version behebt einen Fehler bei der Einstellung der korrekten Standardanwendungen bei der ersten Benutzung.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión estable corrige un error en la configuración de las aplicaciones por defecto en el primer uso.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio egonkor honek akats bat zuzentzen du aplikazio lehenetsi egokia ezartzerakoan lehen erabileran.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version stable corrige un bogue définissant les applications par défaut correctes lors de la première utilisation.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión estábel amaña un erro na configuración das aplicacións predeterminadas no primeiro uso.</p>
        <p lang="he">הגרסה היציבה הזו מתקנת באג הקובע את ישומי ברירת המחדל הנכונים בשימוש ראשון.</p>
        <p lang="id">Versi stabil ini memperbaiki sebuah kutu yang mengatur aplikasi bawaan yang tepat pada saat pertama kali digunakan.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione stabile risolve un bug impostando applicazioni predefinite corrette al primo utilizzo.</p>
        <p lang="ja">この安定バージョンは、初回使用時に正しいデフォルトアプリケーションを設定するバグを修正します。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 안정 버전에서는 첫 사용시 기본 프로그램을 올바르게 설정하는 부분의 문제를 해결했습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši stabili versija ištaiso klaidą ir pirmojo paleidimo metu nustato teisingas numatytąsias programas.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne stabile utgivelsen fikser en feil ved valg av forvalgte programmer ved første bruk.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze stabiele versie repareert een fout inzake het instellen van de juiste standaardtoepassingen bij eerste gebruik.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta stabilna wersja naprawia błąd ustawienia prawidłowych programów domyślnych przy pierwszym użyciu.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão estável corrige um erro que define as aplicações padrão corretas na primeira utilização.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão estável corrige um problema ao definir os aplicativos padrões corretos no primeiro uso.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Эта версия исправляет ошибку определения правильных приложений по умолчанию при первом использовании.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta stabilna različica popravi hrošč ob nastavljanju privzete aplikacije ob prvi rabi.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Ky version i qëndrueshëm ndreq një të metë në ujdisjen e aplikacioneve të sakta parazgjedhje gjatë përdorimit të parë fare.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Oво стабилно издање исправља поставке грешака и поправља подразумеване програме при првој употреби.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här stabila versionen åtgärdar ett fel med att ställa in korrekta förvalda program vid första uppstart.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu kararlı sürüm, ilk kullanımda doğru öntanımlı uygulamaları ayarlayan hatayı düzeltir.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此稳定版本修复了在首次使用时设置正确的默认应用程序的错误。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1463772864" version="0.6.0">
      <description>
        <p>This stable version introduces lots of new features like plugins and application tracker. It also contains a huge collection of other larger and smaller improvements.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтай стабільнай версіі дадаецца мноства новых функцый кшталту ўбудоў і трэкера праграм. Таксама ў яе ўключаная вялікая колькасць разнастайных паляпшэнняў.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази стабилна версия въвежда много нови функции като добавки и приложение за проследяване. Той също така съдържа огромна колекция от други по-големи и по-малки подобрения.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne stabile version introducerer massere af nye funktionaliteter såsom plugins og programsporer. Den indeholder også en stor samling af andre større og mindre forbedringer.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese stabile Version führt viele neue Funktionen wie Plugins und Application Tracker ein. Sie enthält auch eine riesige Sammlung anderer größerer und kleinerer Verbesserungen.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión estable introduce muchas características nuevas como los complementos y el buscador de aplicaciones. También contiene una enorme colección de otras mejoras mayores y menores.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio egonkor honek ezaugarri berri asko dakar, adibidez pluginak eta aplikazioen jarraitzailea. Beste hobekuntza handi eta txikien bilduma erraldoia dauka ere.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version stable introduit de nombreuses nouvelles fonctionnalités telles que les greffons et le suivi des applications. Il contient également une énorme collection d'autres améliorations plus ou moins grandes.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión estábel insire moitas funcións novas, como engadidos e seguimento de aplicacións. Tamén contén unha inxente cantidade de grandes e pequenas melloras.</p>
        <p lang="he">הגרסה היציבה הזו מציגה הרבה מאפיינים חדשים כמו תוספים ועוקב ישומים. היא גם מכילה אוסף עצום של שיפורים גדולים וקטנים.</p>
        <p lang="id">Versi stabil ini memperkenalkan banyak fitur-fitur baru seperti plugin dan pelacak aplikasi. Juga berisi sejumlah besar peningkatan, baik peningkatan besar maupun kecil.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa versione stabile introduce molte nuove caratteristiche come le estensioni e il localizzatore di applicazioni. Contiene anche un'enorme collezione di altri miglioramenti maggiori e minori.</p>
        <p lang="ja">この安定バージョンでは、プラグインやアプリケーショントラッカーなどの多くの新機能が導入されています。 また大小様々な多くの改善点コレクションも含まれています。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 안정 버전에서는 플러그인과 같은 여러 새 기능과 프로그램 트래커를 도입했습니다. 이 부분에 있어 크고 작은 방대한 개선 사항이 있습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši stabili versija pristato daug naujų ypatybių, tokių kaip įskiepiai ir programų sekikliai. Joje taip pat yra didžiulė smulkesnių ir didesnių patobulinimų kolekcija.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne stabile utgivelsen innfører en del ny funksjonalitet slik som tillegg og programsporing. Den har dessuten mange andre små og store forbedringer.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze stabiele versie introduceert vele nieuwe functies zoals invoegsels en een toepassingentraceerder. Hij bevat ook een enorme hoeveelheid grotere en kleinere andere verbeteringen. </p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta stabilna wersja wprowadza wiele nowych funkcji, takich jak wtyczki i narzędzie do śledzenia programów. Zawiera również ogromną kolekcję innych większych i mniejszych ulepszeń.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão estável introduz muitas funcionalidades novas como plugins e rastreio de aplicações. Contém também uma enorme coleção de outras melhorias maiores e menores.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão estável introduz várias novos recursos como plug-ins e o rastreador de aplicativos. Ela também contém uma enorme coleção de outras melhorias grandes e pequenas.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Эта версия представляет множество новых функций, таких как плагины и трекер приложений. Он также содержит огромную коллекцию других больших и маленьких улучшений.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta stabilna različica uvaja mnogo novih funkciji, kot so vtičniki in sledilniki aplikacijam. Vsebuje tudi velik nabor manjših in večjih izboljšav.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Ky version i qëndrueshëm sjell plotë veçori të reja, të tilla si ndjekës shtojcash dhe aplikacionesh. Përmban gjithashtu një koleksion të stërmadh përmirësimesh të tjera më të mëdha dhe më të vogla.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово стабилно издање представља мноштво нових могућности, попут прикључака и пратиоца програма. Оно такође садржи и огромну збирку осталих већих и мањих исправки грешака.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här stabila versionen introducerar många nya funktioner, som insticksprogram och programspårare. Den innehåller också en omfattande lista av andra större och mindre förbättringar.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu kararlı sürüm, eklentiler ve uygulama izleyici gibi birçok yeni özellik sunar. Aynı zamanda diğer büyük ve küçük geliştirmelerden oluşan devasa bir koleksiyon da içerir.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此稳定版本引入了许多新的特性(比如插件和应用追踪器).它还包含大量较大或较小的改进。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>