<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>xfce.orage</pkgname>
  <icon type="cached" height="64" width="64">org.xfce.orage.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" type="cached" height="128">org.xfce.orage.png</icon>
  <id>org.xfce.orage</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Orage</name>
  <name lang="am">ዖራጌ</name>
  <name lang="ar">أوراج</name>
  <name lang="ast">Orage</name>
  <name lang="be">Orage</name>
  <name lang="bg">Orage</name>
  <name lang="ca">Orage</name>
  <name lang="cs">Orage - kalendář</name>
  <name lang="da">Orage</name>
  <name lang="de">Orage</name>
  <name lang="el">Orage</name>
  <name lang="en_AU">Orage</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Orage</name>
  <name lang="eo">Oraĝo</name>
  <name lang="es">Orage</name>
  <name lang="et">Orage</name>
  <name lang="eu">Orage</name>
  <name lang="fi">Orage</name>
  <name lang="fr">Orage</name>
  <name lang="gl">Orage</name>
  <name lang="he">Orage</name>
  <name lang="hr">Orage</name>
  <name lang="hu">Orage</name>
  <name lang="hy_AM">Orage</name>
  <name lang="id">Orage</name>
  <name lang="is">Orage</name>
  <name lang="it">Orage</name>
  <name lang="ja">Orage</name>
  <name lang="ko">Orage</name>
  <name lang="lt">Orage</name>
  <name lang="lv">Orage</name>
  <name lang="ms">Orage</name>
  <name lang="nb">Orage</name>
  <name lang="nl">Orage</name>
  <name lang="nn">Orage</name>
  <name lang="oc">Orage</name>
  <name lang="pl">Orage</name>
  <name lang="pt">Orage</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Orage</name>
  <name lang="ro">Orage</name>
  <name lang="ru">Календарь Orage</name>
  <name lang="si">ඔරේජ්</name>
  <name lang="sk">Orage</name>
  <name lang="sq">Orage</name>
  <name lang="sr">Ораж</name>
  <name lang="sv">Orage</name>
  <name lang="th">Orage</name>
  <name lang="tr">Orage</name>
  <name lang="ug">Orage</name>
  <name lang="uk">Менеджер Orage</name>
  <name lang="ur">کیلینڈر</name>
  <name lang="ur_PK">کیلینڈر</name>
  <name lang="vi">Orage</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">Orage</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">Orage</name>
  <summary>Orage is a time-managing application for the Xfce desktop environment</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Orage е програма за управление на времето за графичната среда  Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Orage er et tidsstyringsprogram til Xfce-skrivebordsmiljøet</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Orage ist eine Zeitverwaltungsanwendung für die Xfce-Desktopumgebung</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Orage es una aplicación de gestión del tiempo para el entorno de escritorio Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Orage on ajahalduse rakendus Xfce töölauakeskkonna jaoks</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Orage est une application de gestion du temps pour l'environnement de bureau Xfce.</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Orage je aplikacija za upravljanje vremenom za Xfce radno okruženje</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Orage adalah sebuah aplikasi pengelola waktu untuk lingkungan desktop Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">Orage は、Xfce デスクトップ環境向けの時間管理アプリケーションです。</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Orage yra laiko valdymo programa, skirta Xfce darbalaukio aplinkai</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Orage er et kalenderprogram for skrivebordsmiljøet Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Orage is een toepassing voor tijdbeheer voor de werkomgeving Xfce.</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Orage to aplikacja do zarządzania czasem dla środowiska graficznego Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">O Orage é uma aplicação de gestão de tempo para o ambiente de trabalho Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Orage é um aplicativo de gerenciamento de tempo para o ambiente de desktop Xfce </summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Orage je aplikácia na správu času pre desktopové prostredie Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="sq">Orage është një aplikacion administrimi kohe për mjedisin desktop Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Ораж је програм за управљање временом радног окружења ИксФЦЕ-а</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Orage är ett tidsplanerings program för Xfce-skrivbordsmiljön</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Orage, Xfce masaüstü ortamı için zaman yönetimi sağlayan bir uygulamadır.</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Orage це "машина часу" для програм оточення Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">Orage 是 Xfce 桌面环境下的一款时间管理应用</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">Orage 是 Xfce 桌面環境的時間管理應用程式</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Orage aims to be a fast and easy to use graphical calendar. It uses portable ical format and includes common calendar features like repeating appointments and multiple alarming possibilities.</p>
    <p>Orage does not have group calendar features, but can only be used for single user. It takes a list of files for ical files that should be imported. Contents of those files are read and converted into Orage, but those files are left untouched.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Orage има за цел да бъде бърз и лесен за използване графичен календар. Той използва преносим формат и включва общи функции на календара като повтарящи се срещи и много възможности за уведомяване.</p>
    <p>Orage няма функции за групов календар, но може да се използва само за един потребител. Той взема списъка с файлове за ical файлове, които трябва да бъдат импортирани. Съдържанието на тези файлове се чете и преобразува в Orage, но тези файлове остават недокоснати.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Orage hat zum Ziel, ein schneller und einfach zu bedienender grafischer Kalender zu sein. Er verwendet das iCal-Format und enthält gängige Kalenderfunktionen wie Terminwiederholungen und mehrere Alarmmöglichkeiten.</p>
    <p>Orage verfügt nicht über Gruppenkalenderfunktionen, sondern kann nur für einzelne Benutzer verwendet werden. Orage ermöglicht den Import einer Liste von iCal-Dateien. Der Inhalt dieser Dateien wird gelesen und in Orage konvertiert, wobei diese Dateien unangetastet bleiben.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Orage es un calendario gráfico rápido y fácil de usar. Usa el formato ical portátil e incluye funciones de calendario usuales, como diversas opciones de alarma y repetición de citas.</p>
    <p>Orage no posee funciones de calendario de grupo, sino que solo se puede usar para un solo usuario. Acepta una lista de archivos para los archivos ical que se deben importar. El contenido de esos archivos se lee y se convierte al formato de Orage, pero los archivos no se modifican.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Orage se veut être un calendrier graphique rapide et facile à utiliser. Il utilise le format ical portable et inclut les fonctionnalités courantes des calendriers, comme la répétition des rendez-vous et les possibilités d'alarmes multiples.</p>
    <p>Orage n'a pas de fonctionnalités pour gérer le calendrier d'un groupe et peut être utilisé que par un seul utilisateur. Il prend une liste de fichiers pour les fichiers ical qui doivent être importés. Le contenu de ces fichiers est lu et converti dans Orage mais ces derniers ne sont pas modifiés.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Orage bertujuan untuk menjadi kalender grafis yang cepat dan mudah digunakan. Ini menggunakan format ical portabel dan mencakup fitur kalender umum seperti janji berulang dan banyak kemungkinan penanda alarm.</p>
    <p>Orage tidak memiliki fitur kalender grup, tetapi hanya dapat digunakan untuk pengguna tunggal. Dibutuhkan daftar berkas untuk berkas ical yang harus diimpor. Isi berkas tersebut dibaca dan diubah menjadi Orage, tetapi berkas tersebut dibiarkan tidak tersentuh.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>Orage は、高速で使いやすいグラフィカルカレンダーを目指しています。ポータブルな ical 形式を使用し、予定の繰り返しや複数のアラームなどの一般的なカレンダー機能を含んでいます。</p>
    <p>Orage にはグループカレンダーの機能がなく、シングルユーザーのみで使用できます。インポートには ical ファイルのファイルリストを使用します。これらのファイルは Orage に読み込まれて変換されますが、ファイル自体は変更されません。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Orage siekia būti greitu ir lengvu naudoti grafiniu kalendoriumi. Programa Orage naudoja perkeliamą ical formatą ir joje yra dažniausiai kalendoriuose naudojamos ypatybės, tokios kaip paskyrimai ir daugelis galimybių naudoti signalus.</p>
    <p>Orage neturi grupės kalendoriaus ypatybių, bet gali būti naudojama tik vienam naudotojui. Jai tereikia pageidaujamų importuoti ical failų sąrašo. Šių failų turinys yra perskaitomas ir konvertuojamas į Orage formatą, o patys failai lieka nepakeisti.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Orage har som mål å være en grafisk kalender som er rask og enkel i bruk. Den bruker det portable filformatet «ical» og har vanlige kalenderfunksjoner slik som gjentakende møter og tilpassede alarmer.</p>
    <p>Orage er ikke laget for flere samtidige brukere. Programmet kan importere ical-filer: Innholdet kan leses og konverteres til Orage, men selve filene endres ikke.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Orage is bedoeld om een snel en makkelijk te gebruiken kalender te zijn. Hij gebruikt de overzetbare ical-opmaak en bevat gebruikelijke kalenderfuncties zoals herhalende afspraken en meervoudige meldingsmogelijkheden.</p>
    <p>Orage heeft geen groepskalenderfuncties, maar kan alleen worden gebruikt voor individuele gebruikers. Wat nodig is, is een lijst van ical-bestanden die geïmporteerd kan worden. De inhoud van die bestanden wordt ingelezen en omgezet naar Orage, maar de bestanden zelf blijven onaangeroerd.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Orage ma być szybkim i łatwym w użyciu kalendarzem. Wykorzystuje przenośny format ical i zawiera typowe funkcje kalendarza, takie jak powtarzanie spotkań i wiele możliwości alarmowania.</p>
    <p>Orage nie zawiera funkcji kalendarza grupowego, może być używany tylko dla jednego użytkownika. Pobiera listę plików dla plików ical, które należy zaimportować. Zawartość tych plików jest odczytywana i konwertowana do Orage, ale te pliki pozostają nietknięte.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Orage pretende ser um calendário gráfico rápido e fácil de usar. Utiliza o formato ical portátil e inclui funcionalidades comuns de calendário como a repetição de compromissos e várias possibilidades de alarme.</p>
    <p>O Orage não tem funcionalidades de calendário de grupo, mas só pode ser utilizado para um único utilizador. É necessária uma lista de ficheiros para ficheiros ical que devem ser importados. O conteúdo desses ficheiros é lido e convertido para o Orage, mas esses ficheiros são deixados intocados.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Orage pretende ser um calendário gráfico rápido e fácil de usar. Ele usa o formato ical portátil e inclui recursos comuns de calendário, como compromissos repetidos e várias possibilidades de alarme. </p>
    <p>O Orage não possui recursos de calendário de grupo, mas só pode ser usado para um único usuário. Leva uma lista de arquivos para arquivos ical que devem ser importados. O conteúdo desses arquivos é lido e convertido em Orage, mas esses arquivos permanecem intocados. </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Orage má za cieľ byť rýchlym a ľahko použiteľným grafickým kalendárom. Používa prenosný formát ical a obsahuje bežné funkcie kalendára, ako sú opakované schôdzky a viaceré možnosti upozorňovania.</p>
    <p>Orage nemá funkcie skupinového kalendára, a môže byť použitý iba pre jedného používateľa. Vyžaduje zoznam súborov ical, ktoré by sa mali importovať. Obsah týchto súborov sa prečíta a skonvertuje do Orage, ale tieto súbory zostanú nedotknuté.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sq">
    <p>Orage synon të jetë një kalendar grafik i shpejtë dhe i lehtë për t’u përdorur. Përdor formatin e bartshëm ical dhe përfshin veçori të zakonshme kalendarësh, bie fjala, përsëritje takimesh dhe mundësi të shumta alarmi.</p>
    <p>Orage nuk ka veçori kalendari grupesh, mund të përdoret vetëm për një përdorues. Pranon një listë kartelash për kartelat ical që duhen importuar. Lënda e këtyre kartelave lexohet dhe shndërrohet në formatin Orage, por këto kartela lihen të paprekura.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Ораж стреми да буде календар брз и лак за употребу. Он користи преносни облик ицал и садржи уобичајене могућности календара као што су понављање састанака и вишеструке могућности аларма.</p>
    <p>Ораж нема могућности групног календара, него може бити једнокориснички. Потребан му је списак датотека ицал-а за увоз. Садржај тих датотека се учитава и претвара у Ораж, а датотеке се остављају неизмењене.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Orage, hızlı ve kullanımı kolay bir grafik takvim olmayı hedeflemektedir. Taşınabilir ical biçimini kullanır ve yinelenen randevular ve birden çok endişe verici olasılık gibi ortak takvim özelliklerini içerir.</p>
    <p>Orage, grup takvimi özelliğine sahip değildir, sadece tek kullanıcı için kullanılabilir. İçe aktarılması gereken ical dosyaları için bir dosya listesi alır. Bu dosyaların içeriği okunur ve Orage'a dönüştürülür, ancak bu dosyalara dokunulmaz.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Orage має на меті бути швидким і простим у використанні графічним календарем. Він використовує портативний формат ical і включає загальні функції календаря, як-от повторювані зустрічі та численні можливості нагадування.</p>
    <p>Orage не має функцій групового календаря, але може використовуватися для одного користувача. Він використовує список для ical файлів, які слід імпортувати. Вміст цих файлів читається та перетворюється в Orage, але оригінальні файли залишаються незмінними.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>Orage 旨在成為一個快速且易於使用的圖形化日曆。它使用可攜式的 ical 格式，並包含常見的行事曆功能，例如重複約會與多種提醒的可能性。</p>
    <p>Orage 沒有群組日曆功能，僅能被單一使用者使用。它需要一個應該匯入的 ical 檔案的檔案清單。這些檔案的內容被讀取並轉換進 Orage，但這些檔案維持不變。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://docs.xfce.org/_media/apps/orage/orage-main.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://xfce.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.xfce.org/apps/orage/</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.xfce.org/apps/orage/start</url>
  <url type="donation">https://opencollective.com/xfce/donate</url>
  <url type="translate">https://docs.xfce.org/contribute/translate/start</url>
  <project_group>Xfce</project_group>
  <update_contact>xfce4-dev@xfce.org</update_contact>
  <developer_name>Orage Team</developer_name>
  <translation type="gettext">orage</translation>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.xfce.orage.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <provides>
    <binary>orage</binary>
  </provides>
</component>