<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>xfce.catfish</pkgname>
  <icon height="64" width="64" type="cached">org.xfce.catfish.png</icon>
  <icon height="128" type="cached" width="128">org.xfce.catfish.png</icon>
  <id>org.xfce.Catfish</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Catfish</name>
  <summary>Versatile file searching tool</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">أداة البحث عن مختلف أنواع الملفات</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Універсальны інструмент для пошуку</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Гъвкав инструмент за търсене на файлове</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Eina versàtil de cerca de fitxers</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Všestranný nástroj pro vyhledávání</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Alsidigt filsøgningsværktøj</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Vielseitiges Dateisuchwerkzeug</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Ευέλικτο εργαλείο αναζήτησης αρχείων</summary>
  <summary lang="en_AU">Versatile file searching tool</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Herramienta versátil de búsqueda de archivos</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Mitmekülgne töövahend failide otsimiseks</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Fitxategiak bilatzeko tresna moldakorra</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Monipuolinen tiedostonhakutyökalu</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Outil de recherche de fichiers polyvalent.</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Ferramenta de busca de ficheiros versátil</summary>
  <summary lang="he">כלי חיפוש קבצים רב שימושי</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Svestrani alat za pronalazak datoteka</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Rugalmas fájlkereső eszköz</summary>
  <summary lang="hy_AM">Նիշերի բազմակողմանի որոնման գործիք</summary>
  <summary lang="hye">Նիշերի բազմակողմանի որոնման գործիք</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Alat pencari yang serba guna</summary>
  <summary lang="ie">Un utensile versatil por serchar files</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Fjölhæft tól til leitar að skrám</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Strumento versatile per la ricerca dei file</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">多機能なファイル検索ツール</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">다양한 검색 도구</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Universalus failų paieškos įrankis</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Alat menggelintar fail yang serba boleh</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Allsidig verktøy for filsøk</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Flexibel gereedschap voor het zoeken van bestanden</summary>
  <summary lang="nn">Allsidig filsøkeverktøy</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Wszechstronne narzędzie wyszukiwania plików</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Instrumento de pesquisa de ficheiros versátil</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Ferramenta de busca de arquivos versátil</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Гибкий инструмент поиска файлов</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Všestranný nástroj na vyhľadávanie súborov</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Vsestransko orodje za iskanje datotek</summary>
  <summary lang="sq">Mjet i zhdërvjellët kërkimesh</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Свестрани прибор за претрагу датотека</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Mångsidigt sökverktyg</summary>
  <summary lang="th">เครื่องมือค้นหาแฟ้มที่เก่งรอบด้าน</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Çok yönlü dosya arama aracı</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Гнучкий інструмент пошуку файлів</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">多功能文件搜索工具</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">多功能的檔案搜尋工具</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Catfish is a small, fast, and powerful file search utility. Featuring a minimal interface with an emphasis on results, it helps users find the files they need without a file manager. With powerful filters such as modification date, file type, and file contents, users will no longer be dependent on the file manager or organization skills.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>كاتفيش هو أداة بحث عن الملفات, صغيرة وسريعة وقوية. تتميز واجهة البرنامج بالبساطة و الحد الأدنى مع التركيز على النتائج ، فإنه يساعد المستخدمين على العثور على الملفات التي يحتاجونها دون مدير الملفات. مع مرشحات قوية مثل تاريخ التعديل ونوع الملف ومحتويات الملف ، لن يعتمد المستخدمون بعد الآن على مدير الملفات.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Catfish - невялічкая, хуткая і магутная праграма для пошуку файлаў. Дзякуючы мінімальнаму інтэрфейсу з акцэнтам на выніках, дапамагае карыстальнікам зручна знаходзіць неабходныя файлы. З магутнымі фільтрамі (дата мадыфікацыі, тып файла, змесціва файла) карыстальнікі больш не будуць залежаць ад кіраўніка файлаў.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Catfish е малък, бърз и мощен инструмент за търсене на файлове.  Отличаващ се с минимален интерфейс и с акцент върху резултатите, той помага на потребителите да намират файловете, от които се нуждаят, без файлов мениджър. С мощни филтри, като например, търсене по  дата на промяна, тип файл и съдържание на файла, потребителите вече няма да бъдат зависими от файловия мениджър или организационни умения.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Catfish és una utilitat de cerca de fitxers petita, ràpida i potent. Amb una interfície mínima que destaca els resultats, ajuda els usuaris a trobar els fitxers que necessiten sense recórrer al gestor de fitxers. Amb filtres potents, com ara el de data de modificació, el de tipus de fitxer i el de contingut dels fitxers, els usuaris ja no depenen del gestor de fitxers ni de les seves habilitats d'organització.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Catfish je malý, rychlý a výkonný vyhledávač souborů. Díky minimalistickému rozhraní s důrazem na výsledky, pomáhá uživatelům najít soubory, které potřebují, aniž by otevřeli správce souborů. S výkonnými filtry jako je datum změny, typ souboru a obsah souboru už uživatelé nebudou závislí na správci souborů nebo svých organizačních schopnostech.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Catfish er et lille, hurtigt og kraftfuldt filsøgningsredskab. Med en minimal grænseflade med vægt på resultater hjælper den brugere med at finde de filer de har brug for uden en filhåndtering. Med kraftfulde filtre såsom ændringsdato, filtype og filindhold, behøver brugere ikke længere at være afhængig af filhåndteringen eller organiseringsværdigheder.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Catfish ist ein kleines, schnelles und leistungsfähiges Suchprogramm. Die kleine Benutzeroberfläche stellt die Suchergebnisse in den Vordergrund und hilft dem Benutzer, die Dateien die er sucht, zu finden, ohne eine Dateiverwaltung zu verwenden. Durch nützliche Filter wie etwa Änderungsdatum, Dateityp oder die Volltextsuche werden Benutzer unabhängiger von der Dateiverwaltung und ihrem Organisationstalent.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το Catfish είναι ένα μικρό, γρήγορο και ισχυρό πρόγραμμα αναζήτησης αρχείων. Έχοντας ελάχιστη διεπαφή και με έμφαση στα αποτελέσματα, βοηθά τους χρήστες να βρουν τα αρχεία που χρειάζονται χωρίς έναν διαχειριστή αρχείων. Με ισχυρά φίλτρα όπως, η ημερομηνία τροποποίησης, ο τύπος αρχείου και τα περιεχόμενα του αρχείου, οι χρήστες δεν θα εξαρτώνται  πλέον από τον διαχειριστή αρχείων ή από τις οργανωτικές τους ικανότητες.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_AU">
    <p>Catfish is a small, fast, and powerful file search utility. Featuring a minimal interface with an emphasis on results, it helps users find the files they need without a file manager. With powerful filters such as modification date, file type, and file contents, users will no longer be dependent on the file manager or organization skills.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Catfish es una utilidad de búsqueda de archivos pequeña, rápida y potente. Con una interfaz mínima que destaca los resultados, ayuda al usuario a encontrar los archivos que necesita sin recurrir al gestor de archivos. Con unos filtros potentes, como el de fecha de modificación, el de tipo de archivo y el de contenido del archivo, el usuario ya no dependerá del gestor de archivos ni de sus habilidades de organización.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Catfish on väike, kiire ja võimas otsingutarvik. Kasutades lakoonilist liidest on rõhk eelkõige otsingutulemustel ja see võimaldab kasutajatel leida faile ilma failihaldurit kasutamata. Kasutades detailseid filtreid nagu muutmise kuupäev, faili tüüp ja faili sisu, ei ole kasutajad enam sõltuvad failihaldurist oma sisu haldamisel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Catfish fitxategiak bilaketzeko tresna txikia, bizkorra eta ahaltsua da. Interfaze minimoarekin eta emaitzetan enfasia jarriz, erabiltzaileak behar dituen fitxategiak aurkitzen laguntzen du fitxategi kudeatzaile bat erabili gabe. Aldatze data, fitxategi mota eta fitxategien edukiak bezalako iragazki ahaltsuekin, erabiltzaileak ez dira gehiago fitxategi kudeatzaileen edo antolaketa trebetasunaren menpekoak izango.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Catfish on pieni, nopea ja tehokas tiedostonhakutyökalu. Sen minimaalinen käyttöliittymä painottuu hakutuloksiin ja auttaa käyttäjiä löytämään tarvitsemansa tiedostot ilman tiedostonhallintasovellusta. Tehokkaiden suodattimien (kuten muokkauspäivämäärä, tiedostotyyppi ja tiedoston sisältö) ansiosta käyttäjät eivät tule olemaan enää riippuvaisia tiedostonhallintasovelluksesta tai omista organisointitaidoistaan.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Catfish est un petit utilitaire de recherche de fichiers, rapide et puissant. Doté d’une interface minimaliste orientée résultats, il aide l’utilisateur à trouver les fichiers dont il a besoin sans gestionnaire de fichiers. Avec des filtres puissants tels que la date de modification, le type de fichier ou son contenu, l’utilisateur n’est plus dépendant d’un gestionnaire de fichiers ou de ses capacités d’organisation.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>O Catfish é unha utilidade de busca de ficheiros pequena, rápida e potente. Cunha interface mínima que realza os resultados, axuda a atopar os ficheiros sen precisar dun xestor de ficheiros. Con filtros potentes, como data de modificación, tipo de ficheiro e contido dos ficheiros, non hai que depender máis do xestor de ficheiros ou das habilidades organizativas.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>שפמנון היא תוכנה קטנה, מהירה ועוצמתית לחיפוש קבצים. עם ממשק מינימלי בדגש על תוצאות, היא עוזרת למשתמשים למצוא את הקבצים שהם צריכים ללא מנהל קבצים. עם מסננים עוצמתיים כמו תאריך עדכון, סוג קובץ ותכולת קובץ, משתמשים כבר לא יהיו תלויים במנהל הקבצים או ביכולות ארגון.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Catfish je mali, brzi i moćni alat za pretraživanje datoteka. Minimalističkim prikazom s naglaskom na rezultate pretrage, pomaže korisnicima pronaći datoteke bez upravitelja datoteka. S moćnim filterima datuma modifikacije, vrste i sadržaja datoteke, korisnici više neće biti ovisni o upravitelju datotekama ili organizacijskim sposobnostima.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Catfish egy kis, gyors és hatékony fájlkereső segédprogram. Minimális felületet ad, amely az eredményre koncentrál, segít a felhasználóknak megtalálni a fájlokat fájlkezelő nélkül. A hatékony szűrőkkel, mint a módosítás dátuma, fájltípus és a fájl tartalma, a felhasználók többé nem függenek a fájlkezelőtől vagy a rendszerezési képességeiktől.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hy_AM">
    <p>Catfish֊ը փոքր, արագ եւ հզոր որոնման գործիք է։ Նուազագոյն միջերեսի եւ արդիւնքների ստացման շեշտադրութեամբ, այն թոյլ է տալիս գտնել նիշեր առանց նիշքի միջամտութեան։ Հզոր զտիչների, (փոփոխման ամսաթիւը, նիշի տիպը, բովանդակութիւնը) շնորհիւ աւգտատէրերն այլեւս չեն ունենայ կախուածութիւն նիշային համակարգից։</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hye">
    <p>Catfish֊ը փոքր, արագ եւ հզոր որոնման գործիք է։ Նուազագոյն միջերեսի եւ արդիւնքների ստացման շեշտադրութեամբ, այն թոյլ է տալիս գտնել նիշեր առանց նիշքի միջամտութեան։ Հզոր զտիչների, (փոփոխման ամսաթիւը, նիշի տիպը, բովանդակութիւնը) շնորհիւ աւգտատէրերն այլեւս չեն ունենայ կախուածութիւն նիշային համակարգից։</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Catfish adalah peralatan pencari berkas yang kecil, cepat, dan mantap. Menggunakan antarmuka yang minimal dengan penekanan pada hasil, ia membantu pengguna menemukan berkas yang mereka inginkan tanpa memerlukan sebuah manajer berkas. Dengan filter yang mantap seperti tanggal modifikasi, tipe berkas, dan isi berkas, pengguna tidak lagi bergantung pada manajer berkas atau keterampilan dalam mengatur berkas.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ie">
    <p>Catfish es un litt, rapid e potent utensile de trovar files. Con su interfacie minimalistic que emfasa sur resultate, it assiste usatores trovar li files que ili besona, sin un gerente de files. Con potent filtres quam un date de modification, un tip de file e contenete de file, usatores es ne plu dependent del gerente de files o su habilitás organisational.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>Catfish er lítið, hraðvirkt og öflugt leitarverkfæri. Með lágmarksviðmóti sem leggur áherslu á leitarniðurstöðurnar, getur það hjálpað notendum að finna skrár án þess að nota skráastjóra. Með öflugum síum á borð við breytingadagsetningu, skráategund og innihald skráa, þurfa notendur ekki að reiða sig eins mikið á skráastjóra eða skipulagshæfileika sína.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Catfish è un piccolo, veloce e potente strumento per la ricerca dei file. Con la sua interfaccia minimale e l'enfasi sui risultati, aiuta gli utenti a trovare i file di cui hanno bisogno senza un gestore di file. Grazie agli utilissimi filtri come la data di modifica, il tipo di file e il contenuto del file, gli utenti non saranno più dipendenti dal gestore dei file o da capacità organizzative.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>Catfishは軽量で速いにもかかわらず強力なファイル検索ユーティリティーです。インターフェースは検索結果に重点を起いた最小限な構成となっており、ユーザーがファイルマネージャーを使わずにフィルを見つけることを助けます。ファイルの変更日、ファイルタイプ、ファイルの内容といった強力なフィルターがあることによって、ユーザーはファイルマネージャーやファイルの整理スキルに頼る必要がなくなります。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>메기는 작고 빠르며 강력한 기능을 보유한 파일 검색 유틸리티입니다. 간단한 인터페이스를 사용하여 결과에 중점을 두었으며, 파일 관리자 없이 필요한 파일들을 찾는데 도움을 줍니다. 수정 일시, 파일 형식, 파일 내용, 사용자와 같은 필터는 더 이상 파일관리자 또는 조직 기술에 의존할 필요가 없습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Catfish yra maža, greita ir galinga failų paieškos paslaugų programa. Minimalios sąsajos, kurioje visas dėmesys sutelkiamas į rezultatus, dėka, programa padeda naudotojams, be failų tvarkytuvės pagalbos, rasti ieškomus failus. Galingų filtrų, tokių kaip keitimo data, failo tipas ir failo turinys, dėka, naudotojai daugiau nebus priklausomi nuo failų tvarkytuvės ar organizuotumo įgūdžių.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Catfish merupakan sebuah utiliti gelintar fail yang kecil, pantas tetapi hebat. Difiturkan dengan antaramuka minimal dengan penumpuan pada keputusan. Ia dapat membantu pengguna mencari fail yang diperlukan tanpa bantuan pengurus fail. Dengan penapis yang hebat seperti tarikh diubahsuai, jenis fail, dan kandungan fail, pengguna tidak lagi bergantung kepada pengurus fail atau kemahiran pengurusan fail.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Catfish er et lite, raskt og kraftig filsøkeverktøy. Det har minimalt grensesnitt med fokus på resultater, det hjelper brukere til å finne de filene de trenger uten en filbehandler. Med kraftige filtere som endringsdato, filtype og filinnhold slipper brukeren å ha spesielt gode ferdigheter i filhåndtering og organisering.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Catfish is een klein, snel, en krachtig hulpmiddel voor het (door)zoeken van bestanden. Met een minimale gebruikersschil die de nadruk legt op resultaten, helpt het gebruikers om de bestanden te vinden die  ze nodig hebben, zonder een bestandbeheerder. Met krachtige filters zoals wijzigingsdatum, bestandtype en bestandinhoud, zijn gebruikers niet langer afhankelijk van de bestandbeheerder of van organisatorische vaardigheden.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nn">
    <p>Catfish er eit lite, raskt og kraftig filsøkeverktøy. Med eit minimalt grensesnitt som legg vekt på resultat, hjelper det brukaren å finna filene dei treng utan ein filutforskar. Med nyttige filter som endringsdato, filtype og filinnhald, så er brukaren ikkje lenger avhengig av filutforskarar eller orden i systemet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Catfish to małe, szybkie i potężne narzędzie do wyszukiwania plików. Dzięki minimalistycznemu interfejsowi z naciskiem na wyniki pomaga użytkownikom znaleźć potrzebne pliki bez menedżera plików. Dzięki potężnym filtrom, takim jak data modyfikacji, typ pliku oraz jego zawartość, użytkownicy nie będą już zależni od menedżera plików lub umiejętności organizacyjnych.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Catfish é um pequeno, rápido, e poderoso utilitário de pesquisa de ficheiros. Com uma interface minimalista e com ênfase nos resultados, o que ajuda os utilizadores a encontrar os ficheiros que necessitam sem um gestor de ficheiros. Com poderosos filtros tal como data de modificação, tipo de ficheiro e conteúdo dos ficheiros, os utilizadoress não serão mais dependentes do gestor de ficheiros ou de habilidades de organização.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Catfish é um pequeno, rápido e poderoso utilitário de busca de arquivos. Com uma interface minimalista, com ênfase em resultados, que ajuda os usuários a encontrar os arquivos que necessitam sem um gerenciador de arquivos. Com poderosos filtros, tais como data de modificação, tipo de arquivo e conteúdo dos arquivos, os usuários não serão mais dependentes do gerenciador de arquivos ou habilidades de organização.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Catfish — это небольшая, быстрая и мощная программа поиска файлов. Минималистичный интерфейс, заточенный на результат, помогает пользователям находить нужные файлы. С такими мощными фильтрами, как: дата изменения, тип и содержимое файла пользователь более не зависит от файлового менеджера и организационных навыков.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Catfish je malý, rýchly a výkonný nástroj na vyhľadávanie súborov. Obsahuje minimalistické rozhranie s dôrazom na výsledok. Pomáha používateľom nájsť súbory, ktoré potrebujú, bez použitia správcu súborov. S výkonnými filtrami ako je dátum zmeny, typ súboru a obsah súboru už používatelia nie sú závislí na správcovi súborov alebo organizačných skúsenostiach.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Catfish je majhno, hitro in zmogljivo iskalno orodje. Ponaša se z minimalnim vmesnikom, s poudarkom na rezultatih. Uporabnikom pomaga najti kar rabijo brez upravljalnika datotek. S pomočjo zmogljivih filtorv, kot so datum spremembe, vrsta in  vsebina datotek, uporabniki niso več odvisni od upravljalnika datotek ali organizacijskih veščin.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sq">
    <p>Catfish është një mjet i vockël kërkimi kartelash, i shpejtë dhe i fuqishëm. Me një ndërfaqe minimale dhe me theksin te përfundimet, ai i ndihmon përdoruesit të gjejnë kartelat që u duhen, pa përgjegjës kartelash. Me filtra të fuqishëm, të tillë si ai për datën e modifikimit, për llojin e kartelave, dhe lëndën e kartelave, përdoruesit s’do të jenë më të varur nga përgjegjësi i kartelave apo aftësi organizative.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Сом је мали, брз и моћан прибор за претрагу датотека. Будући да има мало сучеље са нагласком на налазе претраге, помаже корисницима да пронађу датотеке без помоћи управника датотека. Са његовим моћним условима као што су време измене, врста датотека и садржај датотека, корисници неће више зависити од уређивачких вештина управника датотека.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Catfish är ett litet, snabbt och kraftfullt filsökverktyg. Med ett minimalt gränssnitt med betoning på resultat, hjälper det användare att hitta de filer som de behöver utan en filhanterare. Med kraftfulla filter som ändringsdatum, filtyp och filinnehåll, är användare inte längre beroende av filhanteraren eller organisationsförmåga.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="th">
    <p>Catfish เป็นเครื่องมือค้นหาแฟ้มที่เล็ก เร็ว และทรงพลัง ด้วยส่วนติดต่อที่กะทัดรัดและเน้นที่ผลการค้นหา ช่วยให้ผู้ใช้หาแฟ้มที่ต้องการได้โดยไม่ต้องใช้โปรแกรมจัดการแฟ้มเลย และด้วยตัวกรองที่มีประสิทธิภาพอย่างเช่นเวลาที่แก้ไข ชนิดแฟ้ม และเนื้อหาแฟ้ม ผู้ใช้จะไม่ต้องพึ่งพาโปรแกรมจัดการแฟ้มหรือทักษะการจัดการแฟ้มอีกเลย</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Catfish küçük, hızlı ve güçlü dosya arama programıdır. Sonuç odaklı ve minimal arayüz ile kullanıcıların gereksindikleri dosyaları dosya yöneticisi olmadan bulmalarına yardımcı olur. Değiştirme tarihi, dosya türü ve dosya içeriği gibi güçlü süzgeçlerle kullanıcılar artık dosya yöneticisi veya düzenleme becerilerine bağımlı kalmayacaklardır.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Catfish це невелика, швидка і потужна програма пошуку файлів. Мінімалістичний інтерфейс, заточений на результат, допомагає користувачам знаходити потрібні файли. З такими потужними фільтрами, як: дата зміни, тип і вміст файлу користувач більш не залежить від файлового менеджера і організаційних навичок.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>Catfish是一款小巧、快速、强大的文件搜索工具。特别设置一个突出显示搜索结果的小界面，可以帮助用户不必使用文件管理器就可以找到想要的文件。诸如修改日期、文件类型和文件内容等强大的过滤功能，用户则不必依赖文件管理器或者其它文件管理技能。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>Catfish 是一個輕巧、快速且強大的檔案搜尋工具程式。有著簡潔的介面，並在結果處會加以強調，其協助使用者不用檔案管理員就可以找到他們需要的檔案。因為有強大的過濾器，如修改日期、檔案類型與檔案內容，使用者將不需要依賴檔案管理員或收納技巧。</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.xfce.Catfish.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://screenshots.bluesabre.org/catfish/catfish.png</image>
      <caption>The main Catfish window displaying image search results</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">نافذة كاتفيش الرئيسية التي تعرض نتائج البحث عن الصور</caption>
      <caption lang="be">Галоўнае акно Catfish адлюстроўвае вынікі пошуку выяў</caption>
      <caption lang="bg">Основният прозорец на Catfish, показващ резултатите от търсенето на изображения</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">La finestra principal de catfish que mostra els resultats de cerca d'imatges</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Hlavní okno Catfish zobrazující výsledky vyhledávání obrázků</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Det primære Catfish-vindue som viser resultater for billedsøgning</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Das Hauptfenster von Catfish, das die Ergebnisse der Bildsuche anzeigt.</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Το κυρίως παράθυρο του Catfish εμφανίζει τα αποτελέσματα αναζήτησης από εικόνες</caption>
      <caption lang="en_AU">The main Catfish window displaying image search results</caption>
      <caption lang="es">La ventana principal de Catfish mostrando los resultados de la búsqueda de imágenes</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Catfishi põhivaade, kus on kuvatud pildiotsingu tulemused</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Catfishen leiho nagusia irudi bilaketa emaitzak erakusten</caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Catfishin pääikkuna kuvahakutulosten kera</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">La fenêtre principale de Catfish affichant les résultats de la recherche des images</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">A xanela principal do Catfish que amosa os resultados da busca de imaxes</caption>
      <caption lang="he">החלון הראשי של שפמנון המציג תוצאות חיפוש תמונה</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Glavni Catfish prozor prikazuje rezultate pretrage slika</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">A Catfish főablaka a képkeresés eredményét jeleníti meg</caption>
      <caption lang="hy_AM">Հիմնական Catfish պատուհանը ցուցադրում է որոնուած արդիւնքների նկարները</caption>
      <caption lang="hye">Հիմնական Catfish պատուհանը ցուցադրում է որոնուած արդիւնքների նկարները</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Jendela utama Catfish menampilkan hasil pencarian gambar</caption>
      <caption lang="ie">Li fenestre de Catfish monstra resultates de sercha por images</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La finestra principale di Catfish mostra i risultati della ricerca immagini</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">メインの Catfish ウィンドウに画像の検索結果を表示</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">그림 검색 결과를 나타내는 메인 메기 창</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Pagrindinis Catfish langas, rodantis paveikslų paieškos rezultatus</caption>
      <caption lang="ms">Tetingkap Catfish utama yang memaparkan keputusan gelintar imej</caption>
      <caption lang="nb">Catfish' hovedvindu viser bildesøkeresultater</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Het hoofdvenster van Catfish dat de resultaten toont van afbeeldingzoekopdracht</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Główne okno Catfish wyświetlające wyniki wyszukiwania obrazów</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">A janela principal do Catfish para mostrar resultados de busca de imagem</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">A janela principal do Catfish exibindo resultados de pesquisa de imagens</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Основное окно Catfish, показывающее результаты поиска изображений</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Hlavné okno aplikácie Catfish zobrazujúce výsledky vyhľadávania obrázkov</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Glavno Catfish okno, ki prikazuje rezultate iskanj</caption>
      <caption lang="sq">Dritarja kryesore e Catfish-it duke shfaqur përfundime kërkimi figurash</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Главни прозор Сома са приказима налаза претраге</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Catfish huvudfönster som visar bildsökningsträffar</caption>
      <caption lang="th">หน้าต่างหลัก Catfish แสดงผลลัพธ์การค้นหารูปภาพ</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Görsel arama sonuçlarını gösteren ana Catfish penceresi</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Основне вікно Catfish, яке показує результати пошуку</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">Catfish 的主窗口显示了图片搜索的结果</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">顯示圖片搜尋結果的主要 Catfish 視窗</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://screenshots.bluesabre.org/catfish/catfish-filters.png</image>
      <caption>The main Catfish window displaying available filters and filtered search results</caption>
      <caption lang="ar">نافذة كاتفيش الرئيسية التي تعرض المرشحات المتاحة ونتائج البحث التي تمت تصفيتها</caption>
      <caption lang="be">Галоўнае акно Catfish адлюстроўвае даступныя фільтры і адфільтраваныя вынікі пошуку</caption>
      <caption lang="bg">Основният прозорец на Catfish, показващ наличните филтри и филтрираните резултати от търсенето</caption>
      <caption lang="ca">La finestra principal de catfish que mostra els filtres disponibles i els resultats de cerca filtrats</caption>
      <caption lang="cs">Hlavní okno Catfish zobrazující dostupné filtry a vyfiltrované výsledky vyhledávání</caption>
      <caption lang="da">Det primære Catfish-vindue som viser tilgængelige filtre og filtrerede søgeresultater</caption>
      <caption lang="de">Das Hauptfenster von Catfish zeigt verfügbare Filter und gefilterte Suchergebnisse an.</caption>
      <caption lang="el">Το κυρίως παράθυρο του Catfish εμφανίζει τα διαθέσιμα φίλτρα και τα φιλτραρισμένα αποτελέσματα της αναζήτησης</caption>
      <caption lang="en_AU">The main Catfish window displaying available filters and filtered search results</caption>
      <caption lang="es">La ventana principal de Catfish mostrando los filtros disponibles y los resultados de búsqueda filtrados</caption>
      <caption lang="et">Catfishi põhivaade, kus on näha otsingufiltrid ja filtrite kasutamise tulemused</caption>
      <caption lang="eu">Catfishen leiho nagusia iragazki erabilgarriak eta iragazitako bilaketa emaitzak erakusten </caption>
      <caption lang="fi">Catfishin pääikkuna suodattimien ja suodatettujen hakutulosten kera</caption>
      <caption lang="fr">La fenêtre principale de Catfish affichant les filtres disponibles et les résultats de recherche filtrés</caption>
      <caption lang="gl">A xanela principal do Catfish que amosa os filtros dispoñíbeis e resultados da busca filtrados</caption>
      <caption lang="he">החלון הראשי של שפמנון המציג מסננים זמינים ותוצאות חיפוש מסוננות</caption>
      <caption lang="hr">Glavni Catfish prozor prikazuje dostupne filtere i filtrirane rezultate pretrage</caption>
      <caption lang="hu">A Catfish főablaka az elérhető szűrőket és a szűrt keresés eredményét jeleníti meg</caption>
      <caption lang="hy_AM">Հիմնական Catfish պատուհանը ցուցադրում է առկա զտիչները եւ զտուած որոնման արդիւնքները</caption>
      <caption lang="hye">Հիմնական Catfish պատուհանը ցուցադրում է առկա զտիչները եւ զտուած որոնման արդիւնքները</caption>
      <caption lang="id">Jendela utama Catfish menampilkan filter yang tersedia dan hasil pencarian yang telah difilter</caption>
      <caption lang="ie">Li fenestre de Catfish monstra disponibil filtres e filtrat resultates de sercha</caption>
      <caption lang="it">La finestra principale di Catfish mostra i filtri disponibili e i risultati della ricerca filtrati</caption>
      <caption lang="ja">メインの Catfish ウィンドウに利用可能なフィルタとフィルタされた検索結果を表示</caption>
      <caption lang="ko">가용 조건과 조건으로 걸러낸 검색 결과를 나타내는 메인 메기 창</caption>
      <caption lang="lt">Pagrindinis Catfish langas, rodantis prieinamus filtrus ir filtruotus paieškos rezultatus</caption>
      <caption lang="ms">Tetingkap Catfish utama yang memaparkan penapis yang tersedia dan keputusan gelintar bertapis</caption>
      <caption lang="nb">Catfish' hovedvindu viser tilgjengelige filtre og filtrerte søkeresultater</caption>
      <caption lang="nl">Het hoofdvenster van Catfish dat de beschikbare filters toont en de gefilterde zoekresultaten</caption>
      <caption lang="pl">Główne okno Catfish wyświetlające dostępne filtry oraz przefiltrowane wyniki wyszukiwania</caption>
      <caption lang="pt">A janela principal do Catfish para mostrar filtros disponíveis e resultados filtrados</caption>
      <caption lang="pt_BR">A janela principal do Catfish exibindo filtros disponíveis e resultados de pesquisa filtrados</caption>
      <caption lang="ru">Основное окно Catfish, показывающее доступные фильтры и отфильтрованные результаты поиска</caption>
      <caption lang="sk">Hlavné okno aplikácie Catfish zobrazujúce dostupné filtre a filtrované výsledky vyhľadávania</caption>
      <caption lang="sl">Glavno Catfish okno, ki prikazuje dostopne filtre in filtrirane rezultate.</caption>
      <caption lang="sq">Dritarja kryesore e Catfish-it duke shfaqur filtrat e mundshëm dhe duke filtruar përfundime kërkimi</caption>
      <caption lang="sr">Главни прозор Сома са приказима доступних услова и условљених налаза претраге</caption>
      <caption lang="sv">Catfish huvudfönster som visar tillgängliga filter och filtrerade sökträffar</caption>
      <caption lang="th">หน้าต่างหลัก Catfish แสดงตัวกรองที่มี และผลลัพธ์การค้นหาที่ผ่านตัวกรอง</caption>
      <caption lang="tr">Geçerli süzgeçleri ve süzülmüş arama sonuçlarını gösteren ana Catfish penceresi</caption>
      <caption lang="uk">Основне вікно Catfish, яке показує доступні фільтри і відфільтровані результати пошуку</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_CN">Catfish 的主窗口显示了可用的过滤器以及过滤后的搜索结果</caption>
      <caption lang="zh_TW">顯示可用的過濾器與已過濾的搜尋結果的主要 Catfish 視窗</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <translation type="gettext">catfish</translation>
  <url type="homepage">https://docs.xfce.org/apps/catfish/start</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugzilla.xfce.org</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.xfce.org/apps/catfish/start</url>
  <update_contact>bluesabre@xfce.org</update_contact>
  <provides>
    <binary>catfish</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="4.16.4" date="2022-07-17">
      <description>
        <p>This release improves keyboard shortcuts, desktop environment integration, file manager support, and general look and feel. It also features several bug fixes for non-Xfce users.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.16.3" date="2021-09-26">
      <description>
        <p>This release improves file manager support, zip file support, and handling selected files. It also improves keyboard shortcuts for starting a search or selecting a new search path.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази версия подобрява поддръжката на файловия мениджър, поддръжката на zip файлове и обработката на избрани файлове. Той също така подобрява клавишните комбинации за стартиране на търсене или избор на нов път за търсене.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse forbedrer understøttelse af filhåndtering, understøttelse af zip-filer og håndtering af valgte filer. Den forbedrer også tastaturgenveje til at starte en søgning eller vælge en ny søgesti.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version verbessert die Unterstützung der Dateiverwaltung, die Unterstützung von Zip-Dateien und die Handhabung ausgewählter Dateien. Sie verbessert auch die Tastenkombinationen für den Start einer Suche oder die Auswahl eines neuen Suchpfads.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση βελτιώνει την υποστήριξη του διαχειριστή αρχείων, την υποστήριξη αρχείων zip και τον χειρισμό επιλεγμένων αρχείων. Βελτιώνει επίσης τις συντομεύσεις πληκτρολογίου για εκκίνηση αναζήτησης ή επιλογή νέας διαδρομής αναζήτησης.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión mejora la compatibilidad con el gestor de archivos, la compatibilidad con los archivos zip y el manejo de los archivos seleccionados. También añade atajos de teclado para iniciar una búsqueda o seleccionar una ruta de búsqueda nueva.</p>
        <p lang="et">Selle versiooniga on paranenud failihalduri tugi, zip-failide töötlemine ning valitud failide käitlemine. Parandasime ka otsingu alustamise ja uue otsitee valimise kiirklahvide tööd.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Argitaratze honek fitxategien kudeaketa, zip fitxategien euskarria, eta hautatutako fitxategien erabilera hobetzen ditu. Bilaketa bat hasteko edo bilaketa bide berri baterako teklatuaren lasterbideak hobetzen ditu ere.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version améliore la prise en charge du gestionnaire de fichiers, la prise en charge des fichiers zip et la gestion des fichiers sélectionnés. Elle améliore également les raccourcis clavier pour lancer une recherche ou sélectionner un nouveau chemin de recherche.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión mellora a compatibilidade co xestor de ficheiros, a compatibilidade con ficheiros zip e o manexo de ficheiros seleccionados. Tamén mellora os atallos de teclado para iniciar unha busca ou seleccionar unha nova ruta de busca.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו משפרת תמיכה במנהל קבצים, תמיכה בקבצי זיפ, וטיפול בקבצים נבחרים. היא גם משפרת קיצורי מקלדת להתחלת חיפוש או לבחירת נתיב חיפוש חדש.</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini meningkatkan dukungan peramban berkas, dukungan berkas zip, dan penanganan berkas-berkas terpilih. Serta meningkatkan pintasan papan tik untuk memulai sebuah pencarian atau memilih sebuah path pencarian baru.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio migliora il supporti del gestore dei file, il supporto ai file zip e la gestione dei file selezionati. Migliora anche le scorciatoie da tastiera per avviare una ricerca o per selezionare un nuovo percorso di ricerca.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは、ファイルマネージャーのサポートと、zip ファイルのサポートと、複数ファイル選択時の処理が改善されています。また、検索を開始したり、新しい検索パスを選択したりするキーボードショートカットも改善されています。</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši laida patobulina failų tvarkytuvės palaikymą, zip failų palaikymą ir pasirinktų failų apdorojimą. Joje taip pat patobulinti spartieji klavišai, skirti pradėti paiešką ar pasirinkti naują paieškos kelią.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini menambah baik sokongan pengurus fail, sokongan fail zip, dan pengendalian fail-fail terpilih. Ia juga menambah baik pintasan papan kekunci ketika mula menggelintar atau memilih satu laluan gelintar baharu.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen forbedrer støtte for filbehandleren, zip-filer og håndtering av valgte filer. Den forbedrer også hurtigtaster for å starte søk eller velge ny søkesti.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze versie verbetert de ondersteuning voor de bestandsbeheerder, voor ingepakte bestanden en voor omgaan met gekozen bestanden. Hij verbetert ook de sneltoetsen voor het beginnen van een doorzoeking en voor het kiezen van een nieuw zoekpad.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta wydanie poprawia obsługę menedżera plików, plików zip oraz posługiwanie się wybranymi plikami. Poprawia również skróty klawiaturowe do rozpoczęcia wyszukiwania lub wyboru nowej ścieżki wyszukiwania.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão melhora o suporte do gestor de ficheiros, o suporte de ficheiros zip e o tratamento de ficheiros selecionados. Também melhora as teclas de atalho para iniciar uma pesquisa ou selecionar um novo caminho de pesquisa.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão melhora o suporte do gerenciador de arquivos, o suporte a arquivos zip e o manuseio de arquivos selecionados. Também melhora os atalhos de teclado para iniciar uma pesquisa ou selecionar um novo caminho de pesquisa.</p>
        <p lang="ru">В этом выпуске улучшена поддержка файлового менеджера, поддержка zip-файлов и обработка выбранных файлов. Он также улучшает сочетания клавиш для запуска поиска или выбора нового пути поиска.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie zlepšuje podporu správcu súborov, súborov zip a prácu s označenými súbormi. Vylepšuje tiež klávesové skratky na spustenie vyhľadávania alebo výber novej cesty vyhľadávania.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja izboljšuje podporo za urejevalnik datotek, popdoro zip datotekam in ravnanje z izbranimi datotekami. Izboljšane so bljižnice na tipkovnici za iskanje ali izbiranje nove poti za iskanje.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim përmirëson mbulim përgjegjësish kartelash, mbulim kartelash zip, dhe trajtim të kartelave të përzgjedhura. Përmirëson gjithashtu shkurtore tastiere për nisjen e një kërkimi ose përzgjedhjen e një shtegu të ri kërkimi.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање побољшава подршку управника датотека, подршку зипу и управљање означеним датотекама. Такође, побољшава пречице дугмади за покретање претраге и одабир нове путање претраге.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här versionen förbättrar stödet för filhanteraren, stödet för zip-filer och hanteringen av valda filer. Den förbättrar också tangentbordsgenvägar för att starta en sökning eller välja en ny sökväg.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm, dosya yöneticisi desteğini, zip dosyası desteğini ve seçilen dosyaların işlenmesini iyileştirir. Ayrıca, arama başlatmak veya yeni arama yolu seçmek için klavye kısayollarını iyileştirir.</p>
        <p lang="uk">У цьому випуску покращено підтримку файлового керівника, підтримку файлів zip і обробку виділених файлів. Також покращено комбінації клавіш для початку пошуку або виділення нового шляху пошуку.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此版本改进了文件管理器支持、zip 文件支持和选定文件的处理。 其还改进了用于启动搜索或选取新搜索路径的键盘快捷键。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此版本改善了檔案管理員支援、zip 檔案支援與選定檔案的處理。其也改善了啟動搜尋或選取新搜尋路徑的鍵盤快捷鍵。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-07-31" version="4.16.2">
      <description>
        <p>This release improves file manager support, zip file support, and handling selected files. It also improves keyboard shortcuts for starting a search or selecting a new search path.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази версия подобрява поддръжката на файловия мениджър, поддръжката на zip файлове и обработката на избрани файлове. Той също така подобрява клавишните комбинации за стартиране на търсене или избор на нов път за търсене.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse forbedrer understøttelse af filhåndtering, understøttelse af zip-filer og håndtering af valgte filer. Den forbedrer også tastaturgenveje til at starte en søgning eller vælge en ny søgesti.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version verbessert die Unterstützung der Dateiverwaltung, die Unterstützung von Zip-Dateien und die Handhabung ausgewählter Dateien. Sie verbessert auch die Tastenkombinationen für den Start einer Suche oder die Auswahl eines neuen Suchpfads.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση βελτιώνει την υποστήριξη του διαχειριστή αρχείων, την υποστήριξη αρχείων zip και τον χειρισμό επιλεγμένων αρχείων. Βελτιώνει επίσης τις συντομεύσεις πληκτρολογίου για εκκίνηση αναζήτησης ή επιλογή νέας διαδρομής αναζήτησης.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión mejora la compatibilidad con el gestor de archivos, la compatibilidad con los archivos zip y el manejo de los archivos seleccionados. También añade atajos de teclado para iniciar una búsqueda o seleccionar una ruta de búsqueda nueva.</p>
        <p lang="et">Selle versiooniga on paranenud failihalduri tugi, zip-failide töötlemine ning valitud failide käitlemine. Parandasime ka otsingu alustamise ja uue otsitee valimise kiirklahvide tööd.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Argitaratze honek fitxategien kudeaketa, zip fitxategien euskarria, eta hautatutako fitxategien erabilera hobetzen ditu. Bilaketa bat hasteko edo bilaketa bide berri baterako teklatuaren lasterbideak hobetzen ditu ere.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version améliore la prise en charge du gestionnaire de fichiers, la prise en charge des fichiers zip et la gestion des fichiers sélectionnés. Elle améliore également les raccourcis clavier pour lancer une recherche ou sélectionner un nouveau chemin de recherche.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión mellora a compatibilidade co xestor de ficheiros, a compatibilidade con ficheiros zip e o manexo de ficheiros seleccionados. Tamén mellora os atallos de teclado para iniciar unha busca ou seleccionar unha nova ruta de busca.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו משפרת תמיכה במנהל קבצים, תמיכה בקבצי זיפ, וטיפול בקבצים נבחרים. היא גם משפרת קיצורי מקלדת להתחלת חיפוש או לבחירת נתיב חיפוש חדש.</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini meningkatkan dukungan peramban berkas, dukungan berkas zip, dan penanganan berkas-berkas terpilih. Serta meningkatkan pintasan papan tik untuk memulai sebuah pencarian atau memilih sebuah path pencarian baru.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio migliora il supporti del gestore dei file, il supporto ai file zip e la gestione dei file selezionati. Migliora anche le scorciatoie da tastiera per avviare una ricerca o per selezionare un nuovo percorso di ricerca.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは、ファイルマネージャーのサポートと、zip ファイルのサポートと、複数ファイル選択時の処理が改善されています。また、検索を開始したり、新しい検索パスを選択したりするキーボードショートカットも改善されています。</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši laida patobulina failų tvarkytuvės palaikymą, zip failų palaikymą ir pasirinktų failų apdorojimą. Joje taip pat patobulinti spartieji klavišai, skirti pradėti paiešką ar pasirinkti naują paieškos kelią.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini menambah baik sokongan pengurus fail, sokongan fail zip, dan pengendalian fail-fail terpilih. Ia juga menambah baik pintasan papan kekunci ketika mula menggelintar atau memilih satu laluan gelintar baharu.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen forbedrer støtte for filbehandleren, zip-filer og håndtering av valgte filer. Den forbedrer også hurtigtaster for å starte søk eller velge ny søkesti.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze versie verbetert de ondersteuning voor de bestandsbeheerder, voor ingepakte bestanden en voor omgaan met gekozen bestanden. Hij verbetert ook de sneltoetsen voor het beginnen van een doorzoeking en voor het kiezen van een nieuw zoekpad.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Ta wydanie poprawia obsługę menedżera plików, plików zip oraz posługiwanie się wybranymi plikami. Poprawia również skróty klawiaturowe do rozpoczęcia wyszukiwania lub wyboru nowej ścieżki wyszukiwania.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão melhora o suporte do gestor de ficheiros, o suporte de ficheiros zip e o tratamento de ficheiros selecionados. Também melhora as teclas de atalho para iniciar uma pesquisa ou selecionar um novo caminho de pesquisa.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão melhora o suporte do gerenciador de arquivos, o suporte a arquivos zip e o manuseio de arquivos selecionados. Também melhora os atalhos de teclado para iniciar uma pesquisa ou selecionar um novo caminho de pesquisa.</p>
        <p lang="ru">В этом выпуске улучшена поддержка файлового менеджера, поддержка zip-файлов и обработка выбранных файлов. Он также улучшает сочетания клавиш для запуска поиска или выбора нового пути поиска.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie zlepšuje podporu správcu súborov, súborov zip a prácu s označenými súbormi. Vylepšuje tiež klávesové skratky na spustenie vyhľadávania alebo výber novej cesty vyhľadávania.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja izboljšuje podporo za urejevalnik datotek, popdoro zip datotekam in ravnanje z izbranimi datotekami. Izboljšane so bljižnice na tipkovnici za iskanje ali izbiranje nove poti za iskanje.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim përmirëson mbulim përgjegjësish kartelash, mbulim kartelash zip, dhe trajtim të kartelave të përzgjedhura. Përmirëson gjithashtu shkurtore tastiere për nisjen e një kërkimi ose përzgjedhjen e një shtegu të ri kërkimi.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање побољшава подршку управника датотека, подршку зипу и управљање означеним датотекама. Такође, побољшава пречице дугмади за покретање претраге и одабир нове путање претраге.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här versionen förbättrar stödet för filhanteraren, stödet för zip-filer och hanteringen av valda filer. Den förbättrar också tangentbordsgenvägar för att starta en sökning eller välja en ny sökväg.</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm, dosya yöneticisi desteğini, zip dosyası desteğini ve seçilen dosyaların işlenmesini iyileştirir. Ayrıca, arama başlatmak veya yeni arama yolu seçmek için klavye kısayollarını iyileştirir.</p>
        <p lang="uk">У цьому випуску покращено підтримку файлового керівника, підтримку файлів zip і обробку виділених файлів. Також покращено комбінації клавіш для початку пошуку або виділення нового шляху пошуку.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此版本改进了文件管理器支持、zip 文件支持和选定文件的处理。 其还改进了用于启动搜索或选取新搜索路径的键盘快捷键。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此版本改善了檔案管理員支援、zip 檔案支援與選定檔案的處理。其也改善了啟動搜尋或選取新搜尋路徑的鍵盤快捷鍵。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-07-20" version="4.16.1">
      <description>
        <p>This release expands fulltext search to support more file types and adds support for searching within compressed files. Searching file contents and the preferred view is now preserved across sessions.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание разширява търсенето в пълен текст, за да поддържа повече типове файлове и добавя поддръжка за търсене в компресирани файлове. Търсенето в съдържанието на файла и предпочитаният изглед сега се запазват за всички сесии.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse udvider fuldtekstsøgning til at understøtte flere filtyper og tilføjer understøttelse af søgning i komprimerede filer. Søgning i filindhold og den foretrukne visning bevares nu mellem sessioner.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version erweitert die Volltextsuche um die Unterstützung weiterer Dateitypen und die Suche in komprimierten Dateien. Das Durchsuchen von Dateiinhalten und die bevorzugte Ansicht bleiben nun über Sitzungen hinweg erhalten.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση επεκτείνει την αναζήτηση κειμένου ώστε να υποστηρίζει περισσότερους τύπους αρχείων, και προστίθεται η δυνατότητα για αναζήτηση εντός συμπιεσμένων αρχείων. Η αναζήτηση στα περιεχόμενα των αρχείων και ο προτιμώμενος τύπος θέασης διατηρούνται πλέον μεταξύ των συνεδριών.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión amplía la búsqueda de texto completo para admitir más tipos de archivos y añade la posibilidad de buscar en archivos comprimidos. La búsqueda del contenido de los archivos y la vista preferida se conservan ahora entre sesiones.</p>
        <p lang="et">Selle versiooniga oleme  laiendanud täistekstiotsingut enamatele failitüüpidele ning lisanud pakitud failide sisust otsimise suutlikuse. Failide sisust otsimise ja eelistatud vaate seadistused säilivad ka järgmises sessioonis.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Argitalpen honek testu bilaketa hedatzen du fitxategi mota gehiago onartuz eta konprimatutako fitxategien barruan bilatzea onartzen du ere. Fitxategien edukian bilatzea eta lehenetsitako ikuspegia saioen artean mantentzen da.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version étend la recherche en texte intégral pour prendre en charge davantage de types de fichiers et ajoute la prise en charge de la recherche dans les fichiers compressés. La recherche du contenu du fichier et la vue préférée sont désormais conservées d'une session à l'autre.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión amplía a busca de texto completo para admitir máis tipos de ficheiros e engade a posibilidade de busca dentro de ficheiros comprimidos. A busca de contido do ficheiro e a vista preferida agora consérvase entre sesións.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו מרחיבה חיפוש טקסט מלא לתמיכה בסוגי קבצים נוספים ומוסיפה תמיכה לחיפוש בתוך קבצים מכווצים. חיפוש תכולת קובץ ותצוגה מועדפת נשמרים כעת בין סשנים.</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini memperluas pencarian teks lengkap untuk mendukung lebih banyak jenis berkas dan menambahkan dukungan untuk pencarian dalam berkas terkompresi. Pencarian konten berkas dan tampilan yang disukai sekarang disimpan di seluruh sesi.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio espande la ricerca testuale per supportare più tipologie file e aggiunge il supporto per la ricerca nei file compressi. La ricerca all'interno dei file e la vista preferita è ora salvata tra le sessioni.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは全文検索が拡張され、より多くのファイルタイプがサポートされ、圧縮ファイル内の検索サポートが追加されています。ファイル内容と優先ビューの検索が、セッション間で保持されるようになりました。</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši laida išplėčia absoliučiąją paiešką, kad būtų palaikoma daugiau failų tipų ir pridėtas paieškos suglaudintuose failuose palaikymas. Failų turinio paieška ir pageidaujamas rodinys, dabar, yra išsaugomi tarp seansų.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini mengembangkan gelintar teks penuh untuk lebih sokongan terhadap jenis fail dan menambah sokongan untuk penggelintaran di dalam fail termampat. Penggelintaran kandungan fail dan pandangan digemari masih dikekalkan merentasi sesi.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen forbedrer fulltekst-søk med flere filtyper og støtte for søk i komprimerte arkiv. Søk i filinnhold og foretrukket visning bevares nå mellom øktene.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze versie breidt de doorzoeking van volledige tekst uit met ondersteuning voor meer bestandssoorten en voegt ook ondersteuning toe voor doorzoeken van samengeperste bestanden. Het doorzoeken van de bestandsinhoud en de voorkeursweergave worden nu ook bewaard na afmelden van de gebruiker.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie rozszerza wyszukiwanie pełnotekstowe o obsługę większej liczby typów plików oraz dodaje obsługę wyszukiwania w plikach skompresowanych. Wyszukiwanie zawartości plików i preferowany widok są teraz zachowywane w sesjach.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão expande a pesquisa de texto completo para suportar mais tipos de ficheiros e adiciona suporte para pesquisa dentro de ficheiros comprimidos. A pesquisa do conteúdo dos ficheiros e a visualização preferida é agora preservada ao longo das sessões.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão expande a pesquisa de texto completo para suportar mais tipos de arquivos e adiciona suporte para pesquisa dentro de arquivos compactados. A pesquisa do conteúdo dos arquivos e a visualização preferida é agora preservada ao longo das sessões.</p>
        <p lang="ru">В этом выпуске расширен полнотекстовый поиск для поддержки большего количества типов файлов и добавлена поддержка поиска в сжатых файлах. Поиск содержимого файла и предпочтительный вид теперь сохраняются и между сеансами.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie rozširuje fulltextové vyhľadávanie o podporu ďalších typov súborov a pridáva podporu pre vyhľadávanie v komprimovaných súboroch. Vyhľadávanie obsahu súborov a preferované zobrazenie je teraz zachované vo všetkých reláciách.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja razširja iskanje po celotnem besedilu s podporo več vrstam datotek in dodaja podporo za iskanje v stisnjenih datotekah. Iskanje vsebin datotek in najljubši prikaz se sedaj ohranita skozi seje.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim zgjeron kërkimin në krejt tekstin, për të mbuluar më tepër lloje kartelash dhe shton mbulim për kërkim brenda kartelash të ngjeshura. Kërkimi në lëndë kartelash dhe pamja e parapëlqyer tanimë ruhen nga sesioni në sesion.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање проширује потпуну претрагу писма ради претраге кроз сажмане датотеке. Претрага садржаја датотека и омиљени приказ се сада чувају кроз седнице.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna version utökar fulltextsökning för att stödja fler filtyper och lägger till stöd för sökning i komprimerade filer. Sökning i filinnehåll och den föredragna vyn bevaras nu för alla sessioner.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้ขยายขอบเขตของการค้นเนื้อความให้รองรับแฟ้มหลายชนิดเพิ่มขึ้น และเพิ่มการรองรับการค้นหาในแฟ้มบีบอัด การค้นเนื้อหาแฟ้มและการเลือกรูปแบบการแสดงผลจะมีการรักษาให้มีผลข้ามวาระการใช้งาน</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm, daha çok dosya türünü desteklemek için tam metin aramasını genişletir ve sıkıştırılmış dosyalar içinde arama desteği ekler. Dosya içeriğinin aranması ve yeğlenen görünüm artık oturumlar arasında korunmaktadır.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск розширює повнотекстовий пошук, щоб підтримувати більше типів файлів, і додає підтримку пошуку в стиснутих файлах. Пошук вмісту файлу та бажаного перегляду тепер зберігаються в усіх сеансах.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此版本扩展了全文搜索以支持更多的文件类型，并添加在压缩文件中搜索的支持。搜索文件内容和首选视图现在可以跨会话保留。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此版本擴展了全文搜尋以支援更多檔案類型，並新增了在壓縮檔中的搜尋支援。現在可以跨工作階段保留搜尋檔案內容與偏好的檢視方式。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2021-01-08" version="4.16.0">
      <description>
        <p>This release expands fulltext search to support more encodings and match all keywords instead of matching any.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску палепшаны паўнатэкставы пошук: падтрымка большай колькасці кадаванняў і змена алгарытму для пошуку ўсіх ключавых слоў замест якога-небудзь.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази версия разширява търсенето в пълен текст, за да поддържа повече кодоровки и да регистрира съвпадения с всички ключови думи, вместо всяка поотделно.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání rozšiřuje fulltextové vyhledávání o podporu více kódování a o shodu všech klíčových slov místo částečné shody.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse udvider fuldtekstsøgning til at understøtte flere kodninger og matche alle nøgleord frem for nogle.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version erweitert die Volltextsuche, um mehr Kodierungen zu unterstützen und alle Schlüsselwörter abzugleichen, anstatt nur eines abzugleichen.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση επεκτείνει την αναζήτηση κειμένου ώστε να υποστηρίζει περισσότερες κωδικοποιήσεις και να ταιριάζει όλες τις λέξεις-κλειδιά αντί με οτιδήποτε.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión amplía la búsqueda de todo el texto para que admita más codificaciones y coincida con todas las palabras clave en vez de solo con alguna.</p>
        <p lang="et">Selle versiooniga laiendasime täistekstiotsingut paljudesse märgistikesse ning mitme otsisõna puhul otsime neist kõiki, mitte aga mõnda üksikut.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Argitalpen honek testu-osoko bilaketa zabaltzen du kodeketa gehiago onartuz eta hitz-gako guztiak bilatuz edozein bilatu beharrean.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version élargit la recherche plein texte pour prendre en charge plus de codages et correspondre à tous les mots-clés au lieu de correspondre à tout.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión amplía a busca de texto completo para admitir máis codificacións e facer coincidir todas as palabras clave no canto de coincidir con algunha.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו מרחיבה חיפוש טקסט מלא לתמיכה בקידודים נוספים והתאמה לכל מילות המפתח במקום התאמה לחלק.</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini memperluas pencarian teks penuh untuk mendukung lebih banyak pengkodean dan mencocokkan keseluruhan kata kunci, bukannya mencocokkan tiap kata kunci.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio aggiunge diverse codifiche e cerca tutte le parole chiave quando si cerca tutto il testo nella ricerca del testo.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは全文検索が拡張され、より多くのエンコーディングサポートと、任意のキーワードではなくすべてのキーワードにマッチするようになりました。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이번 출시 버전에서는 더 많은 인코딩과 일부만 일치하는 조건이 아닌 모든 키워드가 일치하는 조건을 지원하도록 전체 문장 검색 기능을 확장했습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši laida išplėčia absoliučiąją paiešką, kad būtų palaikoma daugiau koduočių ir, kad vietoj bet kurio atitinkamo raktažodžio, būtų atitinkami visi raktažodžiai. </p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini mengembangkan gelintar teks penuh untuk menyokong lebih banyak pengekodan dan padanan semua kata kunci berbanding padanan apa sahaja.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen utvider fulltekstsøk med flere tegnkodinger, og søk kan nå samsvare med alle nøkkelord istedenfor noen.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze editie verbetert doorzoeking van volledige tekst door meer coderingen te ondersteunen en door de optie om overeenkomst met alle zoekwoorden te vinden in plaats van overeenkomst met één van de zoekwoorden.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie rozszerza wyszukiwanie pełnotekstowe o obsługę większej liczby kodowań i dopasowywanie wszystkich słów kluczowych zamiast dopasowywania jakichkolwiek.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão expande a busca de texto, aceitando mais codificações e procurando todas as palavras em vez de procurar qualquer uma.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão expande a pesquisa de texto completo para suportar mais codificações e corresponder a todas as palavras-chave em vez de corresponder a qualquer uma.</p>
        <p lang="ru">В этом выпуске расширен полнотекстовый поиск для поддержки большего количества кодировок и поиска по всем, а не только по конкретным, ключевым словам.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie rozširuje fulltextové vyhľadávanie tak, aby podporovalo viac kódovaní, a aby vyhľadalo zhody všetkých kľúčových slov namiesto vyhľadania jedného z nich.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta različica širi iskanje celotnega besedila s podporo več kodam in iskanjem vseh ključnih besed namesto katerekoli od njih.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim zgjeron aftësinë për kërkim teksti të plotë, për të mbuluar më tepër kodime dhe për gjetje përputhjesh për krejt fjalëkyçat, në vend se për cilindo prej tyre.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање проширује потпуну претрагу писма ради подршке додатним кодирањима и поклапања свих кључних речи уместо делимичних поклапања.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna version utökar fulltext-sökning för att stödja fler teckenkodningar och matcha alla nyckelord istället för att matcha några.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้ขยายขอบเขตของการค้นเนื้อความให้รองรับรหัสอักขระเพิ่มขึ้น และจะค้นหาคำหลักทุกคำแทนที่จะค้นเป็นคำๆ</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm, tüm metin aramaya daha çok kodlama ve herhangi biri yerine tüm anahtar sözcükleri eşleme desteği ekler.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск розширює повнотекстовий пошук для підтримки більшої кількості кодувань і відповідати всім ключовим словам замість відповідання будь-чому.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此版本扩展了全文本搜索，以支持更多的编码，并匹配所有关键字，而不是任一关键字。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此版本拓展了全文搜尋，用以支援更多編碼，並符合所有關鍵字而不是任一個。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.15.0" date="2020-10-25">
      <description>
        <p>This release better integrates with the Xfce desktop, better supports the Zeitgeist datahub, and includes many bugfixes and usability improvements.</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذا اﻹصدار أكثر توافقا مع بيئة سطح المكتب Xfce، مع دعم أفضل ل Zeitgeist datahub، كما يتضمن إصلاح العديد من العلل وتحسينات في قابلية الاستخدام.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску палепшана інтэграцыя з Xfce, палепшана падтрымка Zeitgeist, а таксама выпраўлена шмат памылак.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази версия е интегрирана по-добре с Xfce десктоп, поддържа по-добре Zeitgeist datahub и включва много корекции на грешки и подобрения.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió s’integra millor amb l’escriptori Xfce, és més compatible amb Zeitgeist datahub i inclou moltes correccions d’errors i millores d’usabilitat.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání se lépe integruje s prostředím Xfce, lépe podporuje datové centrum Zeitgeist a obsahuje opravy mnoha chyb a vylepšení použitelnosti.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse integrerer bedre med Xfce-skrivebordet, understøtter bedre Zeitgeist-datahubben og inkluderer mange fejlrettelser og forbedringer af anvendeligheden.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version lässt sich besser in den Xfce-Desktop integrieren, unterstützt den Zeitgeist Datahub besser und enthält viele Bugfixes und Verbesserungen der Benutzerfreundlichkeit.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση ενσωματώνεται καλύτερα με το Xfce desktop, υποστηρίζει καλύτερα το Zeitgeist datahub και περιλαμβάνει πολλές διορθώσεις σφαλμάτων και βελτιώσεις χρηστικότητας.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión se integra mejor con el escritorio Xfce, es más compatible con el centro de datos Zeitgeist e incluye muchas correcciones de errores y mejoras de usabilidad.</p>
        <p lang="et">See versioon lõimub paremini Xfce töölauaga ning toetab paremini Zeitgeist'i andmekogu võimalusi. Lisaks tegime korda paljud vead ning parandasime kasutatavust.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Argitalpen honek hobeto moldatzen da Xfce mahaigaianarekin, hobeto funtzionatzen du Zeitgeist datahub-arekin, eta konponketa eta erabilgarritasun hobekuntza asko dakar.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version s’intègre mieux au bureau Xfce, prend mieux en charge le hub de données Zeitgeist, inclut de nombreuses corrections de bogues et améliore la convivialité.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión intégrase mellor co escritorio Xfce, ten mellor compatibilidade co datahub Zeitgeist e inclúe moitas correccións de erros e melloras de usabilidade.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו משתלבת טוב יותר עם שולחן עבודה Xfce, תומכת טוב יותר במרכז מידע Zeitgeist, וכוללת הרבה תיקוני באגים ושיפורים בשימושיות.</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini terintegrasi secara lebih baik dengan desktop Xfce, memiliki dukungan yang lebih baik dengan datahub Zeitgeist, dan menyertakan banyak perbaikan kutu serta peningkatan usabilitas.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio migliora l'integrazione con i componenti di Xfce, migliora il supporto a Zeitgeist e include molte correzioni di bug e miglioramenti dell'usabilità.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースではXfceデスクトップとの統合が改善され、Zeitgeistデータハブのサポートが強化されています。多くのバグが修正され、使いやすさが向上しています。</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši laida geriau integruojasi su Xfce darbalaukiu, geriau palaiko Zeitgeist duomenų mazgą ir joje yra daug klaidų pataisymų bei naudojimosi patogumo patobulinimų.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini disepadukan dengan atas meja Xfce dengan lebih baik, sokongan lebih baik terhadap hab-data Zeitgeist, dan melibatkan banyak pembaikan pepijat dan penambahbaikan kebolehgunaan.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen har bedre integrasjon med Xfce-skrivebordet, støtter bedre datahubben Zeitgeist og har mange feilrettinger og forbedret brukskvalitet.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze versie integreert beter met de Xfce-werkomgeving, ondersteunt Zeitgeist beter, en bevat vele foutreparaties en bruikbaarheidsverbeteringen.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie lepiej integruje się z pulpitem Xfce, lepiej obsługuje koncentrator danych Zeitgeist i zawiera wiele poprawek błędów i ulepszeń użyteczności.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Este lançamento integra-se melhor com o ambiente de trabalho Xfce, suporta melhor o datahub Zeitgeist, e inclui muitas correcções de erros e melhorias de usabilidade.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Este lançamento se integra melhor ao desktop Xfce, suporta melhor o datahub Zeitgeist e inclui muitas correções de bugs e melhorias de usabilidade.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск лучше интегрируется с рабочим столом Xfce, лучше поддерживает хаб данных Zeitgeist, а также включает множество исправлений и улучшений в удобстве использования.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie zlepšuje integráciu s desktopom Xfce, lepšie podporuje datahub Zeitgeist, a obsahuje veľa opráv chýb a vylepšení použiteľnosti.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja ima boljšo integracijo z namizjem xfce, boljšo podporo za Zeitgeist podatkovni hub in vsebuje številne popravke in izboljšave.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim integrohet më mirë me desktopin Xfce, mbulon më mirë qendër të dhënash Zeitgeist, dhe përfshin mjaft ndreqje të metash dhe përmirësime përdorimi.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање се боље уклапа у радно окружење Иксфце-а, боље подржава Цетгејст датахуб, и укључује многе исправе буба и побољшања употребе.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här utgåvan integrerar bättre med Xfce-skrivbordet, har bättre stöd för datanavet Zeitgeist, åtgärdar många fel och har förbättrad användarvänlighet.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้เชื่อมรวมกับเดสก์ท็อป Xfce ได้ดีขึ้น รองรับ Zeitgeist datahub ได้ดีขึ้น รวมถึงแก้บั๊กหลายรายการ และปรับปรุงความสะดวกใช้</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm Xfce masaüstüyle daha iyi tümleşir, Zeitgeist datahub desteğini iyileştirir ve birçok hatayı giderimini ve kullanım iyileştirmesini barındırır.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск краще інтегрується з робочим столом Xfce, краще підтримує центр даних Zeitgeist і містить багато виправлень помилок і покращення зручності використання.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此版本更好地与 Xfce 桌面集成，更好地支持 Zeitgeist datahub，并包含许多错误修正和可用性改进。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此版本與 Xfce 桌面有更好的整合，對 Zeitgeist 資訊站的支援更好，並包含了許多錯誤修復及可用性改進。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.13" date="2020-01-14">
      <description>
        <p>This release resolves packaging errors for Debian and includes optimized assets.</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذا الإصدار يحل أخطاء التحزيم الخاصة بديبيان ويتضمن الأصول المحسنة.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску вырашаныя праблемы з пакункам для Debian і аптымізаваныя рэсурсы.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание решава грешки в пакетирането за Debian и включва оптимизирани активи.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió reso els problemes d'empaquetatge per a Debian i errors nous i inclou actius optimitzats.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání řeší chyby balíčků pro distribuci Debian a obsahuje optimalizované objekty.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse løser fejl ved pakning for Debian og medtager optimerede "assets".</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Veröffentlichung behebt Paketierungsfehler für Debian und enthält optimierte Assets.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση επιλύει σφάλματα πακέτων στο Debian και περιέχει βελτιώσεις.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión resuelve errores de empaquetado para Debian e incluye valores optimizados.</p>
        <p lang="et">Selle versiooniga parandasime Debiani jaoks pakendamise vigu ning  optimeerisime mõned teegid.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek paketatze arazoak konpontzen ditu Debianerako eta aktibo optimizatuak ditu.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version résout des erreurs d’empaquetage pour Debian et inclut des ressources optimisées.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión resolve erros de embalaxe de Debian e inclúe optimizacións.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו פותרת שגיאות חבילה לדביאן וכוללת נכסים מיטביים.</p>
        <p lang="hye">Այս թողարկումը լուծում է Debian- ի փաթեթաւորման սխալները եւ ներառում է բարելաւուած միջոցներ:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini mengatasi kesalahan pemaketan untuk Debian dan menyertakan aset-aset yang dioptimalkan.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio corregge errori di impacchettamento per Debian e include risorse ottimizzate.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは、Debian のパッケージングエラーが修正され、最適化された資源が含まれています。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리즈에서는 데비안의 패키징 문제를 해결하고 최적화한 어셋을 넣었습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši laida išsprendžia Debian pakavimo klaidas, o taip pat joje yra optimizuoti komponentai.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini telah meleraikan ralat-ralat pakej untuk Debian termasuklah aset-aset teroptimum.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen fikser pakkefeil for Debian og har optimerte ressurser.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze editie lost pakketbeheerproblemen op voor Debian en bevat geoptimaliseerde bestanden.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie rozwiązuje błędy pakowania dla Debiana i zawiera zoptymalizowane zasoby.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão resolve erros de empacotamento para Debian e inclui recursos optimizados.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Este versão resolve erros de empacotamento para o Debian e inclui recursos otimizados.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск исправляет ошибки создания пакета для Debian и включает в себя оптимизированные ресурсы.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie rieši chyby balíkov pre Debian a obsahuje optimalizované programové aktíva.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja odpravlja napake pri pakiranju za Debian in vsebuje optimatizirane vire.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim zgjidh gabime paketimi për Debian dhe përfshin burime të përditësuara.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање разрешава грешке пакета у Дебијану и укључује прилагођена својства.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här utgåvan löser paketeringsfel för Debian, och inkluderar optimerade resurser.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้แก้ปัญหาการทำแพกเกจสำหรับเดเบียน และลดขนาดทรัพยากรบางอย่าง</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm Debian için paketleme hatalarını çözer ve düzeltilmiş varlıkları içerir.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск вирішує помилки пакування для Debian і включає оптимізовані набори тестування.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">该版本解决了 Debian 的打包错误，并包括优化的 assets。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本解決了 Debian 打包錯誤並包含了最佳化的資產。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.12" date="2020-01-01">
      <description>
        <p>This release adds support for running under Wayland and features refreshed dialogs with simplified controls.</p>
        <p lang="ar">يضيف هذا الإصدار دعمًا لتشغيل تحت Wayland وميزات حوار منتعشة مع عناصر تحكم مبسطة.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску дададзена падтрымка Wayland і абнавіліся дыялогі са спрошчанымі элементамі кіравання.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание добавя поддръжка за работа под Wayland и предлага обновени диалози с опростени контроли.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió afegeix suport per a l'execució per sota de Wayland i ofereix diàlegs actualitzats amb controls simplificats.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání přidává podporu fungování pod prostředím Wayland a přináší dialogová okna se zjednodušeným ovládáním.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse tilføjer understøttelse af kørsel under Wayland og har fornyede dialoger med forenklet styringer.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version unterstützt nun die Ausführung unter Wayland und bietet aktualisierte Dialoge mit vereinfachten Bedienelementen.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση προσθέτει υποστήριξη για Wayland και ανανεωμένα παράθυρα διαλόγου με απλουστευμένα στοιχεία ελέγχου.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión añade compatibilidad para ejecutarse en Wayland y presenta diálogos renovados con controles simplificados.</p>
        <p lang="et">Selle versiooniga lisame Wayland'i toe ning lihtsustasime rakenduse põhivaateid.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek Wayland-en exekutatzeko aukera gehitzen du eta leiho berriak ditu elementu sinplifikatuekin.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version ajoute la prise en charge de l’exécution sous Wayland et propose des boîtes de dialogue actualisées avec des contrôles simplifiés.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión engade compatibilidade para a execución en Wayland e inclúe diálogos actualizados con controis simplificados.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו מוסיפה תמיכה להפעלה תחת Wayland ומציגה דו שיח רענן עם בקרות פשוטות.</p>
        <p lang="hye">Այս թողարկումը աւելացնում է աջակցութիւն՝ Wayland-ի ներքոյ աշխատելու համար եւ պարունակում է թարմացուած երկխաւսութիւններ՝ պարզեցուած հսկիչներով:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini menambahkan dukungan untuk berjalan di bawah Wayland dan mengedepankan penyegaran dialog dengan kontrol yang disederhanakan.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio aggiunge il supporto a Wayland e aggiorna diverse finestre semplificando i controlli.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは、Wayland で実行するためのサポートが追加され、簡易化された操作に刷新したダイアログが特徴となっています。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리즈에서는 웨일랜드 기반 실행 기능을 추가하였고 대화 상자의 컨트롤을 단순화하였습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši laida prideda palaikymą veikiant Wayland aplinkoje ir joje yra pateikiami atnaujinti dialogai su supaprastintais valdikliais.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini menambah sokongan untuk yang dijalankan bawah Wayland dan memfiturkan dialog-dialog disegar semula dengan kawasan lebih ringkas.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen støtter Wayland og har forenklet dialogvinduene.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze editie voegt ondersteuning toe voor draaien onder Wayland en bevat opgefriste dialoogschermen met vereenvoudigde bediening.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie dodaje obsługę uruchamiania pod Waylandem oraz zawiera odświeżone okna dialogowe z uproszczonymi kontrolkami.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão adiciona suporte para execução com o Wayland e apresenta caixas de diálogo renovadas com controlos simplificados.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão adiciona suporte para execução sob o Wayland e apresenta diálogos atualizados com controles simplificados.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск добавляет поддержку работы под Wayland и обновлённые диалоги с упрощённым управлением.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie pridáva podporu pre beh pod Wayland a obsahuje upravené dialógy so zjednodušenými ovládacími prvkami.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja dodaja podporo za izvajanje pod Wayland-om in ponuja prenovljene dialoge s poenostavljenimi kontrolami.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim shton mbulim për xhirim nën Wayland dhe përmban dialogë të rifreskuar me kontrolle të thjeshtuar.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање додаје подршку за рад под Вејландом и освежене поручне прозоре са упрошћеним управљањем.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här utgåvan lägger till stöd för att köras under Wayland, och har uppdaterat dialogrutor med förenklade kontroller.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้เพิ่มการรองรับการทำงานบน Wayland และมีการปรับปรุงกล่องโต้ตอบให้ควบคุมได้เรียบง่ายขึ้น</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm Wayland altında çalışma desteği ekler ve basitleştirilmiş denetimlerle yenilenmiş iletişim pencereleri sunar.</p>
        <p lang="uk">У цьому випуску додано підтримку роботи під Wayland і містить оновлені діалогові вікна зі спрощеними елементами керування.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此版本增加了在 Wayland 下运行的支持，并带有简化控件的刷新对话框。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本加入了在 Wayland 下執行的支援，以及帶有簡化過的控制元件的對話框。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-12-21" version="1.4.11">
      <description>
        <p>This release addresses some startup errors as well as various issues with traversing symbolic links.</p>
        <p lang="ar">يعالج هذا الإصدار بعض أخطاء بدء التشغيل بالإضافة إلى العديد من المشكلات المتعلقة بعبور الروابط الرمزية.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску выпраўлены некаторыя праблемы з запускам і сімвалічнымі памылкамі.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание адресира някои грешки при стартиране, както и различни проблеми с проследяването на символни връзки.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió tracta alguns errors d’inici, així com diversos problemes amb el creuament d’enllaços simbòlics.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání se zaměřuje na chyby při spuštění a také na chyby s překříženými symbolickými odkazy.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse adresserer opstartsproblemer samt diverse problemer i forbindelse med besøg af symbolske links.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version behebt einige Startfehler sowie verschiedene Probleme beim Durchlaufen symbolischer Links.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση αντιμετωπίζει κάποια σφάλματα εκκίνησης καθώς και διάφορα άλλα θέματα με τους συμβολικούς δεσμούς.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión soluciona algunos errores de inicio, así como varios problemas con el manejo de los enlaces simbólicos.</p>
        <p lang="et">Selle versiooniga parandasime mõned vead rakenduse käivitamisel ning sümbolnimede järgi liikumisel.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek abiarazte orduko errore batzuk konpontzen ditu eta baita lotura sinbolikoen zeharkatzearekin ere.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version corrige quelques erreurs de démarrage ainsi que divers problèmes liés à la traversée de liens symboliques.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión trata algúns erros de inicio, así como varias incidencias de cruzamento de ligazóns simbólicas.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו מטפלת בשגיאות הזנקה וגם בשגיאות שונות עם קישורים סימבוליים בהכחשה.</p>
        <p lang="hye">Այս թողարկումն հասցէյաւորում է մեկնարկման որոշ սխալներ, ինչպէս նաեւ տարբեր խնդիրներ՝ շրջանցող խորհրդանշական յղումներով:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini memperbaiki beberapa kesalahan saat mulai, serta beberapa permasalahan saat melintasi taut simbolis.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio sistema alcuni errori di avvio e vari problemi con i link simbolici.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは、いくつかの起動エラーと、シンボリックリンクトラバーサルに関するさまざまな問題に対処しています。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리즈에서는 심볼릭 링크를 따라갈 때와 같은 다양한 시작 문제 일부를 해결했습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Šioje laidoje buvo pataisytos kai kurios paleisties klaidos, o taip pat įvairios problemos su simbolinių nuorodų perėjimu skersai.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini mempersembahkan beberapa ralat permulaan dan juga pelbagai isu dengan pautan-pautan simbolik yang menyusur.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen fikser noen feil ved oppstart og følging av symbolske lenker.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze editie lost enkele opstartproblemen op alsook verschillende problemen met symbolische koppelingen.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie rozwiązuje pewne błędy uruchamiania, a także różne problemy z przemierzaniem przez dowiązania symboliczne.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão trata alguns erros de iniciação, assim como vários problemas de atravessamento de ligações simbólicas.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão resolve alguns erros de inicialização, assim como vários problemas com links simbólicos que são apresentados.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск исправляет некоторые ошибки при запуске, а также разнообразные проблемы с прохождением по символическим ссылкам.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie rieši niektoré chyby pri spustení, ako aj rôzne problémy s prechádzaním symbolických odkazov.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja naslavlja nekatere napake ob zagonu, kot tudi težave s simboličnimi povezavami.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim merret me disa gabime në nisje, si dhe me probleme të ndryshme me ndjekje lidhjesh simbolike.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање разрешава неке грешке при покретању и разне појаве при путањи кроз симболичне везе.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här utgåvan åtgärdar en del fel vid uppstart, och diverse problem med att följa symboliska länkar.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้มีการแก้ข้อผิดพลาดขณะเริ่มทำงาน รวมถึงปัญหาหลายข้อเกี่ยวกับการท่องตามลิงก์สัญลักษณ์</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm bazı başlatma hatalarının yanı sıra sembolik bağlantılarda geçişle ilgili türlü sorunları ele almaktadır.</p>
        <p lang="uk">У цьому випуску вирішено деякі помилки при запуску, а також різні проблеми з переміщенням символічних посилань.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此版本解决了一些启动错误以及遍历符号链接的各种问题。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本解決了一些啟動錯誤以及多個周遊符號連結的問題。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2019-09-13" version="1.4.10">
      <description>
        <p>This release includes many appearance improvements, introduces a new preferences dialog, and improves search results and performance.</p>
        <p lang="ar">يتضمن هذا الإصدار العديد من تحسينات المظهر ، ويقدم مربع حوار تفضيلات جديد ، ويحسن نتائج البحث والأداء.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэты выпуск уключана шмат паляпшэнняў выгляду, новы дыялог налад, палепшаны працэс пошуку і яго вынікі.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази версия включва много подобрения на външния вид, въвежда нов диалогов прозорец за предпочитания, подобрени са резултатите от търсенето и производителността.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió inclou moltes millores en l’aparença, afegeix un nou diàleg de preferències i millora els resultats i el rendiment de la cerca.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání obsahuje mnoho vylepšení vzhledu, představuje nové dialogové okno s předvolbami a vylepšuje výsledky a výkon vyhledávání.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse inkluderer mange forbedringer til udseendet, introducerer en ny præferencer-dialog og forbedrer søgeresultater og ydelse.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version enthält viele optische Verbesserungen, führt einen neuen Einstellungsdialog ein und verbessert Suchergebnisse und Leistung.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση περιλαμβάνει πολλές βελτιώσεις στην εμφάνιση, εισάγει νέο διάλογο στις προτιμήσεις και βελτιώνει τα αποτελέσματα αναζήτησης και την απόδοση.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión incluye muchas mejoras en la apariencia, incorpora un nuevo diálogo de preferencias y mejora los resultados de los resultados de la búsqueda y el rendimiento.</p>
        <p lang="et">Selle versiooniga oleme parandanud rakenduse välimust, lisanud uue eelistuste vaate ning parandanud otsingute jõudlust ning tulemuste kuvamist.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek hainbat itxura hobekuntza ditu, hobespen leiho berri bat dakar, eta bilaketa emaitzak eta errendimendua hobetzen ditu.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version inclut de nombreuses améliorations de l’apparence, introduit une nouvelle fenêtre des préférences et améliore les résultats de recherche ainsi que les performances.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión inclúe moitas melloras de aparencia, introduce un novo diálogo de preferencias e mellora os resultados da busca e o rendemento.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו כוללת שיפורי הופעה רבים, מציגה דו שיח העדפות חדש, ומשפרת תוצאות חיפוש וביצועים.</p>
        <p lang="hye">Այս թողարկումը ներառում է շատ հայտնի բարելաւումներ, ներկայացնում է նոր նախընտրութիւնների երկխաւսութիւն եւ բարելաւում է որոնման արդիւնքները եւ կատարողականը:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini menyertakan beberapa peningkatan penampilan, memperkenalkan sebuah dialog preferensi baru, dan meningkatkan hasil pencarian dan performa.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio include molti miglioramenti dell'aspetto, introduce un nuovo dialogo di preferenze e migliora i risultati della ricerca e le prestazioni.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースには多くの外観の改善が含まれ、新しい設定ダイアログが導入され、検索結果とパフォーマンスが向上しています。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리스에서는 다양한 모양새 개선을 이루었습니다. 새 대화상자 속성을 도입하였고, 검색 결과 표시와 성능을 개선했습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Į šią laidą įeina daug išvaizdos patobulinimų, pristatomas naujas nuostatų dialogas ir patobulinami paieškos rezultatai bei našumas.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini melibatkan banyak penambahbaikan penampilan, memperkenalkan dialog keutamaan baharu, dan menambahbaik keputusan gelintar dan prestasi.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen har flere forbedringer i utseendet, et nytt innstillingsvindu, og forbedrer søkeresultater og ytelse.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze versie bevat veel verbeteringen van het uiterlijk, introduceert een nieuw dialoogscherm voor de voorkeuren en bevat verbeteringen voor zoekresultaten en prestaties.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera wiele ulepszeń wyglądu, wprowadza nowe okno dialogowe ustawień oraz poprawia wyniki wyszukiwań oraz wydajność.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão inclui muitas melhorias na aparência, apresenta uma nova caixa de diálogo de preferências e melhora os resultados e o desempenho da pesquisa.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Este versão inclui muitas melhorias na aparência, apresenta um novo diálogo de preferências e melhora os resultados e o desempenho da pesquisa.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск содержит много улучшений внешнего вида и новый диалог настроек, а также улучшает результаты и производительность поиска.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje vylepšenia vzhľadu, zavádza nové dialógové okno predvolieb, a zlepšuje výkon a výsledky vyhľadávania.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta različica ima številne vidne izboljšave, uvaja nov dialog za lastnosti in izboljšuje rezultate iskanj ter učinkovitost.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim përfshin mjaft përmirësime të dukjes, sjell për herë të parë një dialog të ri mbi parapëlqimet, dhe përmirëson përfundime kërkimesh dhe funksionimin në përgjithësi.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање садржи многа побољшања изгледа, представља нови прозор поставки, и побољшане налазе претраге и учинка.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här utgåvan inkluderar flera förbättringar av utseendet, introducerar en ny inställningsdialogruta, och förbättrar sökresultat och prestanda.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้มีการปรับปรุงรูปลักษณ์หลายรายการ เพิ่มกล่องโต้ตอบปรับแต่ง และปรับปรุงผลลัพธ์และประสิทธิภาพของการค้นหา</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm birçok görünüm iyileştirmesi içeriyor, yeni bir tercihler iletişim kutusu getiriyor ve arama sonuçlarını ve performansını geliştiriyor.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск містить багато покращень зовнішнього вигляду, нове діалогове вікно налаштувань та покращує результати пошуку та продуктивність.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此版本包括许多外观改进，引入了新的首选项对话框，并改进了搜索结果和性能。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">本次發行包含大量外觀改進、引入了新的偏好設定對話匣、以及改善搜尋結果及效能。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.9" date="2019-08-11">
      <description>
        <p>This release features performance improvements by excluding uncommon search directories.</p>
        <p lang="ar">يتميز هذا الإصدار بتحسينات في الأداء من خلال استبعاد أدلة البحث غير الشائعة.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску палепшана прадукцыйнасць за кошт выключэння з пошуку рэдка выкарыстоўваемых каталогаў.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание включва подобрения на производителността, като изключва необичайни директории за търсене.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió inclou diverses millores de rendiment en excloure directoris poc comuns de cerca.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání přináší zlepšení výkonu vypuštěním neobvyklých vyhledávacích adresářů.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse byder på forbedringer til ydelsen ved at undlade søgemapper som normalt ikke bruges.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version enthält Leistungsverbesserungen durch den Ausschluss ungewöhnlicher Suchverzeichnisse.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση παρουσιάζει βελτιώσεις επιδόσεων εξαιρώντας τους μη συνηθισμένους καταλόγους στην αναζήτηση.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión ofrece mejoras de rendimiento al excluir de la búsqueda carpetas poco comunes.</p>
        <p lang="et">Eemaldades mõned mittevajalikud otsingukaustad oleme selle versiooniga oleme parandanud otsingute jõudlust.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek errendimendua hobetzen du ezohiko karpetak bilaketetik baztertuz.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version apporte des améliorations de performances en excluant des répertoires de recherche inhabituels.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión inclúe melloras no rendemento ao excluír directorios de busca pouco comúns.</p>
        <p lang="he">הגרסה הזו מציגה שיפורים בביצועים על ידי אי הכללת ספריות חיפוש לא נפוצות.</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás teljesítménybeli fejlesztést tartalmaz a kereséshez általában nem használt könyvtárak kizárásával.</p>
        <p lang="hye">Այս թողարկումը պարունակում է կատարողական բարելաւումներ` բացառելով հազուադէպ որոնման նշարաններ:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini mengedepankan peningkatan performa dengan mengecualikan direktori pencarian yang tak umum.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio migliora le prestazioni escludendo le cartelle di ricerca non comuni.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは一般的ではない検索ディレクトリを除外することで、パフォーマンスが向上しています。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이번 릴리스에서는 흔하지 않은 검색 디렉터리를 제외하여 검색 성능을 개선하는 기능을 갖추었습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Šioje laidoje yra našumo patobulinimai, išbraukiant nedažnai naudojamus paieškos katalogus.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini memfiturkan penambahbaikan prestasi dengan mengasingkan direktori-direktori gelintar yang kurang digunakan.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen øker ytelsen ved å utelate mapper man sjelden søker i.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze versie bevat prestatieverbeteringen door het uitsluiten van ongewone zoekmappen.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera ulepszenia wydajności poprzez wykluczenie rzadkich katalogów wyszukiwania.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão apresenta melhorias de desempenho ao excluir diretórios de pesquisa incomuns.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão apresenta melhorias de desempenho ao excluir diretórios de pesquisa incomuns.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск улучшает производительность, исключая из поиска нечастые директории.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje vylepšenia výkonu vylúčením nezvyčajných vyhľadávacích adresárov.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta različica prinaša večjo učinkovitost z izključevanjem map, ki niso pogosto rabljene.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim sjell përmirësimi punimi përmes përjashtimit të drejtorive jo të zakonshme kërkimi.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово је издање са побољшањима учинка одбацивањем фасцикли неуобичајених претрази.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här utgåvan har förbättrat prestandan genom att utesluta ovanliga mappar vid sökning.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้มีการปรับปรุงประสิทธิภาพโดยตัดการค้นในไดเรกทอรีที่มักไม่ค้น</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm, nadir bulunan arama dizinlerini hariç tutarak performans iyileştirmeleri sunar.</p>
        <p lang="uk">У цьому випуску покращено продуктивність за рахунок виключення непотрібних каталогів при пошуку.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此版本通过排除不常用的搜索目录来提高性能。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此版本透過排除不常用的搜尋目錄來得到更好的效能。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.8" date="2019-07-27">
      <description>
        <p>This release features better desktop integration, support for OpenBSD and Wayland, and improved translation support.</p>
        <p lang="ar">يتميز هذا الإصدار بتكامل سطح المكتب بشكل أفضل ، ودعم OpenBSD و Wayland ، ودعم الترجمة المحسن.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску палепшана інтэграцыя з працоўным сталом, дададзена падтрымка OpenBSD і Wayland, палепшаныя пераклады.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание включва по- добра десктоп интеграция, поддръжка за OpenBSD и Wayland, както и подобрена езикова поддръжка.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió destaca una millor integració d’escriptori, un millor suport per a OpenBSD i Wayland i suport millorat per a les traduccions.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání přináší lepší integraci do pracovního prostředí, podporu systémů OpenBDS a Wayland a vylepšenou podporu překladů.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse byder på bedre skrivebordsintegration, understøttelse af OpenBSD og Wayland, og forbedret understøttelse af oversættelse.</p>
        <p lang="de">Dieses Release bietet eine bessere Desktop-Integration, Unterstützung für OpenBSD und Wayland und eine verbesserte Übersetzungsunterstützung.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση παρουσιάζει καλύτερη ενσωμάτωση στα περιβάλλοντα εργασίας, υποστηρίζει OpenBSD και Wayland καθώς και βελτιωμένη υποστήριξη μετάφρασης.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión ofrece una mejor integración con el escritorio, una mayor compatibilidad con OpenBSD y Wayland, y un mejor apoyo para las traducciones.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek mahaigain integrazio hobea, OpenBSDrako eta Waylanderako bateragarritasuna, eta itzulpen laguntza hobetua dakar.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version apporte une meilleure intégration au bureau, la prise en charge d’OpenBSD et de Wayland, ainsi qu’une prise en charge améliorée de la traduction.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión ten unha mellor integración no escritorio, compatibilidade para OpenBSD e Wayland e permite unha mellor tradución.</p>
        <p lang="he">הגרסה הזו מציגה שילוב שולחן עבודה טוב יותר, תמיכה ב-OpenBSD ו-Wayland, ותמיכת תרגום משופרת.</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás jobb asztali integrációt, OpenBSD és Wayland támogatást, valamint továbbfejlesztett nyelvi támogatást tartalmaz.</p>
        <p lang="hye">Այս թողարկումը պարունակում է նախընտրելի աշխատասեղանի ամբողջացումը, աջակցութիւն OpenBSD- ի եւ Wayland- ի համար, եւ թարգմանութեան կատարելագործուած աջակցութեան:</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini mengedepankan integrasi desktop yang lebih baik, dukungan untuk OpenBSD dan Wayland dan peningkatan dukungan penerjemahan.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio presenta una maggiore integrazione nell'ambiente grafico, un migliore supporto per OpenBSD e Wayland e un maggiore supporto per la localizzazione.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースの特徴はデスクトップ統合の改善、OpenBSDおよびWaylandのサポート、翻訳サポートの改善です。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이번 릴리스에서는 OpenBSD, 웨일랜드를 지원하여 더 나은 데스크톱 통합 기능을 갖추었으며, 번역을 개선했습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Šioje laidoje yra geresnė darbalaukių integracija, OpenBSD ir Wayland palaikymas ir patobulintas vertimų palaikymas.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini memfiturkan penyepaduan desktop yang lebih baik, sokongan untuk OpenBSD dan Wayland, dan sokongan terjemahan yang ditambah baik.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen har bedre skrivebordsintegrasjon, støtte for OpenBSD og Wayland og forbedrede oversettelser.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze versie bevat betere integratie met de werkomgeving, ondersteuning voor OpenBSD en Wayland, en verbeterde ondersteuning voor vertalingen.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera lepszą integrację z pulpitem, obsługę OpenBSD i Wayland oraz udoskonaloną obsługę tłumaczeń.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão apresenta uma melhor integração no ambiente de trabalho, suporte para o OpenBSD e Wayland, e melhor suporte à tradução.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão apresenta uma melhor integração de desktop, suporte ao OpenBSD e Wayland, e melhor suporte a traduções.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск предоставляет лучшую интеграцию с рабочим столом, поддержку OpenBSD и Wayland и улучшенную поддержку переводов.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje lepšiu integráciu do desktopu, podporu pre OpenBSD a Wayland, a vylepšenú podporu prekladov.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta različica ponuja boljšo integracijo z namizjem, podporo za OpenBDS in Wayland ter izoboljšano podporo prevodom.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim sjell integrim më të mirë me desktopin, mbulim për OpenBSD-në dhe Wayland-in, dhe mbulim të përmirësuar përkthimesh.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање има бољу усклађеност са радном површи, подршку за ОпенБСД и Вејланд, и побољшану подршку превода.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här utgåvan har bättre skrivbordsintegrering, stöd för OpenBSD och Wayland, och bättre stöd för översättningar.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้มีการเชื่อมรวมกับเดสก์ท็อปที่ดีขึ้น รองรับ OpenBSD และ Wayland และมีการปรับปรุงการรองรับงานแปลข้อความ</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm daha iyi masaüstü tümleşimi, OpenBSD ve Wayland desteği, geliştirilmiş çeviri desteği sunuyor.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск має кращу інтеграцію з робочим столом, підтримку для OpenBSD і Wayland, а також покращену підтримку перекладу.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此版本具有更好的桌面集成、对 OpenBSD 和 Wayland 的支持以及改进的翻译支持。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此版本提供了更好的桌面整合，支援 OpenBSD 與 Wayland，以及改善翻譯支援。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.7" date="2019-01-27">
      <description>
        <p>This release features improved performance, better desktop integration, and a number of long-standing bugs. Quoted search strings are now correctly processed. Files can be dragged into other applications. Thumbnails are only generated when requested by the user.</p>
        <p lang="ar">يتميز هذا الإصدار بتحسين الأداء ، وتكامل سطح المكتب بشكل أفضل ، وعدد من الأخطاء طويلة الأمد. يتم الآن معالجة سلاسل البحث المقتبسة بشكل صحيح. يمكن سحب الملفات إلى تطبيقات أخرى. يتم إنشاء الصور المصغرة فقط عند طلب المستخدم.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску былі палепшаныя прадукцыйнасць, інтэграцыя з працоўным сталом, а таксама выпраўлены шэраг застарэлых памылак. Ад гэтай пары цытаваныя радкі пошуку апрацоўваюцца карэктна. Файлы можна перацягваць у іншыя праграмы. Мініяцюры генеруюцца толькі па запыце карыстальніка.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази версия включва подобрена производителност, по-добра интеграция на десктоп и поправени редица дългосрочни грешки. Посочените низове за търсене вече са правилно обработени се обработват правилно. Файловете могат да се изтеглят в други приложения. Миниатюрите се генерират само при поискване от потребителя.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquest llançament ofereix un rendiment millorat, una millor integració d'escriptori i una sèrie d'errors de llarga durada. Les cadenes de cerca entre cometes ara es processen correctament. Els fitxers es poden arrossegar a altres aplicacions. Les miniatures només es generen quan l'usuari ho sol·licita.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání nabízí vylepšený výkon, lepší integraci s pracovní plochou a mnoho vyřešených dlouhodobých chyb. Hledané výrazy v uvozovkách jsou nyní zpracovávány správně. Soubory lze přetáhnout do jiných aplikací. Náhledy se generují pouze při vyžádání uživatelem.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse byder på forbedret ydelse, bedre skrivebordsintegration og et antal længerevarende fejl. Søgestrenge i citationstegn behandles nu korrekt. Filer kan trækkes ind i andre programmer. Miniaturer genereres kun når det anmodes af brugeren.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version bietet eine verbesserte Leistung, eine bessere Desktop-Integration und die Behebung einer Reihe langjähriger Fehler. Zitierte Suchbegriffe werden nun korrekt verarbeitet. Dateien können in andere Anwendungen gezogen werden. Miniaturansichten werden nur auf Wunsch des Benutzers erzeugt.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση παρουσιάζει βελτιωμένη απόδοση, καλύτερη ενσωμάτωση στα περιβάλλοντα εργασίας και επίλυση μακροχρόνιων σφαλμάτων. Η αναζήτηση επεξεργάζεται σωστά. Αρχεία μπορούν να μετακινηθούν σε άλλες εφαρμογές. Οι μικρογραφίες δημιουργούνται όταν ζητείται από το χρήστη.</p>
        <p lang="en_AU">This release features improved performance, better desktop integration, and a number of long-standing bugs. Quoted search strings are now correctly processed. Files can be dragged into other applications. Thumbnails are only generated when requested by the user.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión presenta un rendimiento mejorado, una mejor integración con el escritorio y una serie de errores corregidos. Las cadenas de búsqueda entre comillas ahora se procesan correctamente. Los archivos pueden ser arrastrados a otras aplicaciones. Las miniaturas solo se generan cuando lo solicita el usuario.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek errendimendua hobetzen du, mahaigaineko integrazio hobea dakar eta arazo zahar ugari konpontzen ditu. Aipatutako bilaketa terminoak ondo prozesatzen dira orain. Fitxategiak beste aplikazioetara arrastatu daitezke. Iruditxoak soilik erabiltzaileak zehaztutakoan sortzen dira.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version apporte une amélioration des performances, une meilleure intégration au bureau et corrige un certain nombre de bogues de longue date. Les chaînes de recherche citées sont maintenant correctement traitées. Les fichiers peuvent être glissés-déposés vers d'autres applications. Les miniatures sont générées uniquement à la demande de l'utilisateur.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión presenta un mellor rendemento, mellor integración co escritorio e a corrección de fallos de hai bastante tempo. As cadeas de busca entre vírgulas agora procésanse correctamente. Os ficheiros pódense arrastrar a outras aplicacións. As miniaturas só se xeran cando o usuario solicita.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו כוללת ביצועים משופרים, אינטגרציה טובה יותר בשולחן עבודה, ומספר באגים ישנים. מחרוזות חיפוש במירכאות מטופלות נכון כעת. קבצים ניתנים לגרירה ליישומים אחרים. תמונות מוקטנות מיוצרות רק לבקשת המשתמש.</p>
        <p lang="hu">E kiadásban a hatékonyság növelése, a jobb asztali integráció és számos régebbi hiba javítása lett megoldva. Az idézőjeles szövegek keresése megfelelően működik. A fájlok áthúzhatók más alkalmazások ablakaiba. Az előnézeti képek csak a felhasználó kérésére kerülnek megjelenítésre.</p>
        <p lang="hy_AM">Տարբեակում հզորացուած է միջերեսը, աշխատասեղանի ամբողջացումը, լուծուած են որոշ խնդիրներ։ Չակերտաւորուած տողերի որոնման պատրաստումը ներկայումս ընթացքի մէջ է։ Նիշերի կարելի է տեղադրել այլ յաւելուածներում։ Փոքրապատկերները ստեղծուուում են միայն ըստ պահանջի։</p>
        <p lang="hye">Տարբեակում հզորացուած է միջերեսը, աշխատասեղանի ամբողջացումը, լուծուած են որոշ խնդիրներ։ Չակերտաւորուած տողերի որոնման պատրաստումը ներկայումս ընթացքի մէջ է։ Նիշերի կարելի է տեղադրել այլ յաւելուածներում։ Փոքրապատկերները ստեղծուուում են միայն ըստ պահանջի։</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini mengedepankan peningkatan performa, integrasi desktop yang lebih baik, dan sejumlah perbaikan untuk kutu yang sudah berlangsung lama. String pencarian dalam tanda petik kini diproses dengan benar. Berkas dapat diseret ke aplikasi lain. Gambar miniatur hanya dibuat jika diminta oleh pengguna.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio migliora le prestazioni, aumenta l'integrazione con il desktop e aggiusta molti bug. Ora le stringhe quotate sono correttamente processare. I file possono essere trascinati in altre applicazioni. Le anteprime sono generate solamente se richieste dall'utente.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは、パフォーマンスの改善、より良いデスクトップ統合、そして長年にわたるバグの修正が行われています。 引用符で囲まれた検索文字列は正しく処理されるようになりました。 ファイルは他のアプリケーションにドラッグできるようになりました。 サムネイルはユーザーが要求した際に生成されます。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리스에서는 성능을 개선했고 데스크톱에 좀 더 어우러지도록 했으며, 오랫동안 남아있던 많은 버그를 수정했습니다. 따옴표로 감싼 검색 문자열을 이제 제대로 처리합니다. 파일을 다른 프로그램으로 끌어다 넣을 수 있습니다. 미리 보기 그림은 사용자가 요청할 때만 만듭니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Šioje laidoje yra patobulintas našumas, geresnė darbalaukio integracija ir daugelio klaidų pataisymai. Dabar paieškos eilutės kabutėse yra apdorojamos teisingai. Failai gali būti velkami į kitas programas. Miniatiūros yra generuojamos tik kai to užklausia naudotojas.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini memfiturkan prestasi ditambah baik, penyepaduan desktop lebih baik, dan sejumlah pepijat lama yang telah dibaiki. Rentetan gelintar berpetikan kini boleh memproses dengan betul. Fail-fail boleh diseret ke dalam aplikasi lain. Lakaran kenit hanya dijana bila dipinta oleh pengguna.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen øker ytelsen, forbedrer skrivebordsintegrasjonen og fikser flere programvarefeil. Siterte søkestrenger håndteres nå riktig. Filer kan dras til andre programmer. Miniatyrbilder dannes kun på brukers forespørsel.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze versie levert verbeterde prestaties, bevat betere integratie met de werkomgeving en bevat reparaties voor een aantal oude fouten. Zoektermen tussen aanhalingstekens worden nu correct verwerkt. Bestanden kunnen worden gesleept naar andere toepassingen. Miniaturen worden alleen aangemaakt wanneer de gebruiker dat wil.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie oferuje ulepszoną wydajność, lepszą integrację pulpitu i poprawki wielu starych błędów. Cytowane ciągi wyszukiwania są teraz poprawnie przetwarzane. Pliki można przeciągać do innych aplikacji. Miniatury są generowane tylko na żądanie użytkownika.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Este lançamento traz desempenho melhorado, melhor integração no ambiente e correção de muitas falhas. Procura de citações são agora processadas corretamente. Ficheiros podem ser arrastados para outras aplicações. Miniaturas são geradas apenas a pedido do utilizador.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão apresenta melhor desempenho, melhor integração com o desktop e várias correções de bugs antigos. As strings de pesquisa com aspas agora são processadas corretamente. Arquivos podem ser arrastados para outros aplicativos. Miniaturas são geradas somente quando solicitadas pelo usuário.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск обеспечивает улучшенную производительность и лучшую интеграцию с рабочим столом, а также несколько долгоживущих багов. Поиск строк в кавычках теперь работает корректно. Файлы можно перетаскивать в другие приложения. Значки генерируются только по запросу пользователя.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie vylepšuje výkon, obsahuje lepšiu integráciu do desktopu a opravuje množstvo dlhodobých chýb. Hľadané reťazce v úvodzovkách sa teraz spracovávajú správne. Súbory je možné presúvať do iných aplikácií. Miniatúry sa generujú iba na žiadosť používateľa.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta različica ponuja večjo zmogljivost, boljšo namizno integracijo in odpravo številnih hroščev. Niz v narekovajih so posleh pravilno obdelani, datoteke je mogoče vleči v druge aplikacije, sličice se generirajo le po potrebi.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim sjell përmirësime në funksionim, integrim më të mirë me desktopin, dhe ndreq një numër të metash shumë të vjetra. Tanimë, vargje kërkimesh përmbledhur në thonjëza përpunohen saktë. Kartelat mund të tërhiqen në aplikacione të tjera. Miniaturat prodhohen vetëm kur kërkohet nga përdoruesi.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање представља побољшани учинак, бољи склад са радним простором, и бројне исправе грешака. Ниске претраге под наводницима су сада исправно обрађене. Датотеке могу бити превлачене у друге програме. Умањене сличице се само образују на захтев корисника.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här utgåvan har förbättrad prestanda, bättre skrivbordsintegrering, och åtgärdar ett antal gamla fel. Söksträngar inom citationstecken behandlas nu korrekt. Filer kan dras till andra program. Miniatyrer genereras bara när användaren ber om det.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้มีการปรับปรุงสมรรถนะ, เชื่อมรวมกับเดสก์ท็อปได้ดีขึ้น, และมีการแก้บั๊กที่คั่งค้างหลายรายการ คำค้นที่คร่อมด้วยเครื่องหมายคำพูดมีการประมวลผลอย่างถูกต้อง, สามารถลากแฟ้มไปยังแอปพลิเคชันอื่นได้, และจะสร้างรูปย่อเฉพาะเมื่อผู้ใช้ร้องขอเท่านั้น</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm, geliştirilmiş performans, daha iyi masaüstü tümleşimi ve kronikleşmiş hataların ayıklanmasını içeriyor. Alıntılanan arama dizeleri artık daha doğru biçimde işlemden geçiyor. Arama sonucunda elde edilen dosyalar başka dizine sürüklenip taşınabilir. Küçük resimler, yalnızca kullanıcı istediğinde oluşturulur.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск містить покращену продуктивність, кращу інтеграцію з робочим столом та виправлення ряду давніх помилок. Тепер рядки пошуку в лапках обробляються правильно. Файли можна перетягувати в інші програми. Ескізи генеруються лише за запитом користувача.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">该发行版本提升了性能、更好的桌面整合能力，以及一些由来已久的漏掉修复。引用搜索语句现已可以正确解析。文件也能够直接拖进其他应用程序中。缩略图只在用户请求的情况之下才会生成。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">此版本改善了效能、更好的桌面整合、並修復了部份長期存在的臭蟲。帶引號的搜尋字串現在可以正確地處理。檔案可以被拖放到其他應用程式中。縮圖只會在使用者要求時生成。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.6" date="2018-07-15">
      <description>
        <p>This release features several improvements to thumbnail processing and numerous bug fixes. Icon previews have been improved and will now match other applications. Items displayed at the bottom of the results window are now accessible with all desktop themes.</p>
        <p lang="ar">يتميز هذا الإصدار بالعديد من التحسينات على معالجة الصور المصغرة والعديد من إصلاحات الأخطاء. تم تحسين معاينات الرمز وستطابق الآن التطبيقات الأخرى. العناصر المعروضة في الجزء السفلي من نافذة النتائج متاحة الآن مع جميع سمات سطح المكتب.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску ўдасканалена апрацоўка мініяцюр і выпраўлена шмат памылак. Значок папярэдняга прагляду быў ўдасканалены і цяпер адпавядае іншым праграмам. Элементы, якія адлюстроўваюцца ў ніжняй частцы акна вынікаў, цяпер даступныя для усіх тэм працоўнага стала.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание включва няколко подобрения в обработката на миниатюри и многобройни корекции на програмни грешки. Визуализация на иконите са подобрени и сега ще съответстват на останалите приложения. Елементите, показани в долната част на прозореца за резултатите, вече са приложими за всички теми на работния плот.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquest llançament ofereix diverses millores al processament de miniatures i nombroses correccions d'errors. S'han millora les vistes prèvies de les icones i ara coincideixen amb altres aplicacions. Els elements que es mostren a la part inferior de la finestra de resultats ara són accessibles amb tots els temes d'escriptori.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání přináší mnohá zlepšení ve zpracování náhledů a četné opravy chyb. Náhledy ikon byly zlepšeny a nyní budou shodné s jinými aplikacemi. Položky zobrazené na konci seznamu výsledků jsou nyní dostupné se všemi motivy pracovního prostředí.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse byder på adskillige forbedringer til behandling af miniature og mange fejlrettelser. Forhåndsvisning af ikoner er blevet forbedret og matcher nu andre programmer. Punkter som vises nederst i resultatsvinduet og kan nu tilgås med alle skrivebordstemaer.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version enthält einige Verbesserungen bei der Verarbeitung von Vorschaubildern und zahlreiche Fehlerbehebungen. Die Symbolvorschau wurde verbessert und passt jetzt zu anderen Anwendungen. Die unten im Ergebnisfenster angezeigten Elemente sind jetzt mit allen Schreibtischthemen zugänglich.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση περιλαμβάνει πολλές βελτιώσεις στην επεξεργασία μικρογραφιών και πολλές διορθώσεις σφαλμάτων. Οι προεπισκοπήσεις εικονιδίων έχουν βελτιωθεί και θα ταιριάζουν τώρα με άλλες εφαρμογές. Τα στοιχεία που εμφανίζονται στο κάτω μέρος του παραθύρου των αποτελεσμάτων είναι πλέον προσβάσιμα από όλα τα θέματα επιφάνειας εργασίας.</p>
        <p lang="en_AU">This release features several improvements to thumbnail processing and numerous bug fixes. Icon previews have been improved and will now match other applications. Items displayed at the bottom of the results window are now accessible with all desktop themes.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión presenta varias mejoras en el procesamiento de miniaturas y numerosas correcciones de errores. Se han mejorado las vistas previas de los iconos y ahora coincidirán con las de otras aplicaciones. Los elementos que se muestran en la parte inferior de la ventana de resultados ahora son accesibles con todos los temas del escritorio.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek argazkitxoen prozesatzean hobekuntzak ditu eta errore asko kopontzen ditu. Ikonoen aurrebista hobetu da eta beste aplikazioekin bat dator. Emaitzen leihoaren beheko aldean zerrendatutako elementuak mahaigain estilo guztiekin eskuragarri daude.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version propose plusieurs améliorations du traitement des miniatures et de nombreuses corrections de bogues. Les aperçus d’icônes ont été améliorés et correspondent désormais aux autres applications. Les éléments affichés en bas de la fenêtre des résultats sont maintenant accessibles avec tous les thèmes de bureau.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión inclúe varias melloras no procesamento das miniaturas e numerosos arranxos de fallos. As vistas previas das iconas son agora melloras e cadran coas doutras aplicacións. Os elementos que se amosan no fondo da xanela de resultados son agora accesíbeis con todos os temas de escritorio.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו מאופיינת בכמה שיפורים לעיבוד תמונות ממוזערות ומספר תיקוני באגים. תצוגות מקדימות של אייקונים שופרו וכעת יתאימו לישומים אחרים. פריטים שמוצגים בתחתית חלון התוצאות נגישים כעת עם כל ערכות נושא שולחן עבודה.</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás számos javítást hoz a bélyegképek feldolgozásában, és hibákat is javít. Az ikon előnézetek jobbak lettek, és most már megegyeznek más alkalmazásokéval. A találati ablak alján lévő elemek most már minden asztaltéma esetén elérhetőek.</p>
        <p lang="hy_AM">Տարբերակում մշակուած է փոքրապատկերների հետ աշխատանքը եւ լուծուած են որոշ խնդիրներ։ Պատկերակների ցուցադրումը հզորացուած է եւ չի համապատասխանի այլ յաւելուածների հետ։ Արդիւնքի պատուհանում ցուցադրուող տարրերն արդէն հասանելի են աշխատասեղանից։</p>
        <p lang="hye">Տարբերակում մշակուած է փոքրապատկերների հետ աշխատանքը եւ լուծուած են որոշ խնդիրներ։ Պատկերակների ցուցադրումը հզորացուած է եւ չի համապատասխանի այլ յաւելուածների հետ։ Արդիւնքի պատուհանում ցուցադրուող տարրերն արդէն հասանելի են աշխատասեղանից։</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini mengedepankan beberapa peningkatan pada pemrosesan gambar miniatur dan sejumlah perbaikan kutu. Pratinjau ikon telah ditingkatkan dan kini pas dengan aplikasi lain. Item yang ditampilkan pada bagian bawah jendela hasil pencarian kini dapat diakses dengan semua tema desktop.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio migliora la generazione delle miniature e corregge numerosi bug. Le icone di anteprima sono state migliorate e da ora si integrano con le altre applicazioni. Gli elementi visualizzati in basso nella finestra dei risultati sono ora accessibili da tutti i temi.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは、サムネイル処理と多数のバグ修正によっていくつか問題が改善されています。アイコンのプレビューが改善され、他のアプリケーションと一致するようになりました。結果ウィンドウの下部に表示される項目は、すべてのデスクトップテーマでアクセスできるようになりました。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리스에서는 몇가지 미리 보기 그림 처리 기능을 개선하고 다양한 문제를 수정했습니다. 미리 보기 아이콘을 개선했으며 다른 프로그램과 어우러집니다. 결과 화면 하단에 나타나는 항목은 모든 데스크톱 테마에서 접근할 수 있습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Šioje laidoje yra keli patobulinimai, skirti miniatiūrų apdorojimui ir daugybė klaidų ištaisymų. Piktogramų peržiūros buvo patobulintos ir dabar jos atitiks kitas programas. Rezultatų apačioje rodomi elementai dabar yra pasiekiami su visomis darbalaukio temomis.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini memfiturkan beberapa penambahbaikan pada pemprosesan lakaran kenit dan banyak pembaikan pepijat. Pratonton ikon telah ditambah baik dan kini akan dipadankan dengan lain-lain aplikasi. Item dipaparkan di bahagian bawah tetingkap keputusan dan kini boleh dicapai dengan semua tema desktop.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen forbedrer håndtering av miniatyrbilder og fikser mange programvarefeil. Forhåndsvisningen av ikoner er forbedret og vil nå passe med andre programmer.  Elementer som vises i bunnen av resultatvinduet er nå tilgjengelige med alle skrivebordsdrakter. </p>
        <p lang="nl">This release features several improvements to thumbnail processing and numerous bug fixes. Icon previews have been improved and will now match other applications. Items displayed at the bottom of the results window are now accessible with all desktop themes.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera kilka ulepszeń w przetwarzaniu miniatur oraz liczne poprawki. Podglądy ikon zostały poprawione i będą teraz pasować do innych aplikacji. Elementy wyświetlane w dolnej części okna wyników są teraz dostępne ze wszystkimi kompozycjami pulpitu.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão apresenta diversas melhorias no processamento de miniaturas e numerosos erros corrigidos. As pré-visualizações de ícones foram melhoradas e agora estão ao nível de outras aplicações. Os itens exibidos no fundo da janela de resultados são agora acessíveis com todos os temas de ambiente de trabalho.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão apresenta várias melhorias para o processamento de miniaturas e várias correções de bugs. As visualizações de ícones foram aprimoradas e agora corresponderão a outros aplicativos. Os itens exibidos na parte inferior da janela de resultados agora podem ser acessados com todos os temas da área de trabalho.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск включает в себя несколько улучшений обработки эскизов и бесчисленные исправления ошибок. Предпросмотр значков был улучшен и теперь совпадает с другими приложениями. Элементы, находящиеся внизу окна результатов, теперь доступны при использовании любых тем рабочего стола.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje niekoľko vylepšení spracovania miniatúr a množstvo opráv chýb. Ukážky ikon boli vylepšené a budú sa zhodovať s inými aplikáciami. Položky zobrazené v spodnej časti okna s výsledkami sú teraz dostupné so všetkými motívmi pracovnej plochy.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta različica vsebuje številne izboljšave pri procesiranju sličic in številne popravke hroščev. predogled ikon so bili izboljšani in sedaj ustrezajo drugim apliakcijam. Predmeti, ki so prikazani na dnu okna z rezultati, so sedaj dosegljivi z vsemi temami namizji.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim përmban disa përmirësime të përpunimit të miniaturave dhe shumë ndreqje të metash. Paraparja e ikonave është përmirësuar dhe tani do të përputhet me atë të aplikacioneve të tjera. Objektet e shfaqura në fund të dritares së përfundimeve tani mund të përdoren me krejt temat grafike të desktopit.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање доноси неколико побољшања у обради умањених сличица и бројне исправке грешака. Преглед сличица је побољшан и сада одговара осталим програмима. Приказане ставке на дну прозора  налаза су сада доступне са свим темама радне површи.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna utgåva innehåller flera förbättringar av förhandsvisningshantering och otaliga felrättningar. Ikonförhandsvisning har förbättrats och matchar nu andra program. Objekt som visas längst ner i resultatfönstret är nu åtkomliga med alla skrivbordsteman.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้มาพร้อมกับการปรับปรุงการจัดการภาพย่อหลายประการ และแก้บั๊กอีกจำนวนมาก การแสดงภาพตัวอย่างด้วยไอคอนได้รับการปรับปรุงจนทัดเทียมกับโปรแกรมอื่นๆ รายการต่างๆ ที่แสดงในหน้าต่างแสดงผลลัพธ์ในรุ่นนี้สามารถเข้าถึงได้จากชุดตกแต่งเดสก์ท็อปทั้งหมด</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm, küçük resim işleme ve türlü hata düzeltmeleri için birkaç iyileştirme sunuyor. Simge ön izlemeleri geliştirildi ve şimdi diğer uygulamalarla eşleşecek. Sonuç penceresinin altında görüntülenen ögeler artık tüm masaüstü temalarıyla erişilebilir durumdadır.</p>
        <p lang="uk">У цьому випуску зроблено покращення обробки мініатюр та виправлено чисельні помилки. Покращено перегляд значків, також для інших програм. Елементи, що показуються внизу вікна, тепер доступні всім темам робочого столу.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">本次更新包括了对缩略图处理进行的一些改进和诸多错误的修复。 图标预览已得到改进，现在将与其他应用程序匹配。 搜索结果窗口底部显示的所有项目现在都可以被所有桌面主题访问。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本有許多的改進，如縮圖處理與許多的臭蟲修復。圖示預覽已經改善，現在可以尋找其他應用程式了。在結果視窗底部顯示的項目現在也在所有的桌面佈景主題都可以看得到了。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-04-11" version="1.4.5">
      <description>
        <p>This is a minor translations-only release.</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذا فقط. إصدار ترجمات طفيفة </p>
        <p lang="be">Гэта нязначны выпуск з абнаўленнем перакладаў.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това е издания с незначително обновяване - само на преводите.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta és una versió menor només per a traduccions.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto je malé vydání obsahující pouze aktualizaci překladů.</p>
        <p lang="da">Dette er en mindre udgivelse som kun har med oversættelser at gøre.</p>
        <p lang="de">Das ist eine kleine Version, die nur Übersetzungen enthält.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή είναι μία μικρή αναβάθμιση μετάφρασης</p>
        <p lang="en_AU">This is a minor translations-only release.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta es una versión menor solo para traducciones.</p>
        <p lang="et">See versiooniga lisandus vaid tõlgete täiendusi.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Hau itzulpenak soilik eguneratzen dituen argitalpen txiki bat da.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä on pieni, vain käännöksiä päivittävä julkaisu.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Il s’agit d’une version de révision mineure des traductions.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta é unha versión menor só de traducións.</p>
        <p lang="he">זוהי גרסה מינורית לתרגומים בלבד.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovo je manje izdanje sa ažuriranim prijevodima.</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez egy kisebb, csak fordításokat tartalmazó kiadás.</p>
        <p lang="hy_AM">Սա սոսկ թարգմանական տարբերակ է։</p>
        <p lang="hye">Սա սոսկ թարգմանական տարբերակ է։</p>
        <p lang="id">Ini adalah rilis minor dengan pemutakhiran terjemahan saja.</p>
        <p lang="ie">Ti es un minori version solmen por actualisation de traductiones.</p>
        <p lang="is">Þessi útgáfa er minniháttar uppfærsla, eingöngu fyrir þýðingar.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questa è un rilascio minore che contiene solamente aggiornamenti di traduzione.</p>
        <p lang="ja">これは翻訳のみのマイナーリリースです。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 출시판은 사소한 번역을 추가했습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Tai yra smulki tik vertimų atnaujinimo laida.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Ini adalah keluaran terjemahan kecil-sahaja.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen har kun nye oversettelser.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Dit is een versie die alleen nieuwe vertalingen bevat.</p>
        <p lang="nn">Dette er ei mindre utgåve med berre omsetjingar.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Jest to małe, skupione tylko na tłumaczeniach, wydanie.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta é uma versão com alterações menores apenas de tradução.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta é uma versão apenas para atualizar traduções.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Это небольшой выпуск, обновляющий только переводы.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje len pre menšie zmeny týkajúce sa prekladov.</p>
        <p lang="sl">To je manjši popravek prevodov.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo është një hedhje e vockël në qarkullim, vetëm për ca përkthime.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово је издање са дорадама превода.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Detta är en mindre endast översättningsutgåva.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้เป็นรุนย่อยที่ปรับคำแปลเพิ่มเติมเท่านั้น</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm yalnızca birkaç çeviriden ibarettir.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Це є невеликий випуск лише для перекладу.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">该版本仅更新了翻译。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這是一個僅有翻譯更新的版本。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.4" date="2018-01-27">
      <description>
        <p>This release features several performance improvements and numerous translation updates.</p>
        <p lang="ar">يتميز هذا الإصدار بالعديد من تحسينات الأداء والعديد من تحديثات الترجمة.</p>
        <p lang="be">Гэты выпуск ўключае ў сябе некалькі паляпшэнняў прадукцыйнасці і шматлікія абнаўленні перакладу.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание включва няколко подобрения на производителността и множество обновления на преводите.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió inclou diverses millores de rendiment i moltes actualitzacions en les traduccions.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání přináší mnohá zlepšení ve výkonu a četné aktualizace překladů.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse byder på adskillige forbedringer til ydelsen og opdateringer af oversættelser.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version enthält mehrere Leistungsverbesserungen und zahlreiche Übersetzungsaktualisierungen.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση περιλαμβάνει πολλές βελτιώσεις απόδοσης και πολλές ενημερώσεις μεταφράσεων.</p>
        <p lang="en_AU">This release features several performance improvements and numerous translation updates.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión presenta varias mejoras de rendimiento y numerosas actualizaciones de las traducciones.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek errendimendu hobekuntza eta itzulpen eguneraketa ugari dakartza.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version offre plusieurs améliorations de performances et de nombreuses mises à jour de traductions.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión inclúe varias melloras no desempeño e numerosas actualizacións da tradución.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו מאופיינת בכמה שיפורי ביצועים ומספר עדכוני תרגום.</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás néhány teljesítménybeli fejlesztést és számos fordítási frissítést hoz.</p>
        <p lang="hy_AM">Տարբերակում թարմացուած է միջերեսը եւ թարմացուած են որոշ թարգմանութիւններ։</p>
        <p lang="hye">Տարբերակում թարմացուած է միջերեսը եւ թարմացուած են որոշ թարգմանութիւններ։</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini mengedepankan beberapa peningkatan performa dan sejumlah pemutakhiran terjemahan.</p>
        <p lang="ie">Ti-ci publication provide quelc ameliorationes de performantie e numerosi actualisamentes de traduction.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio presenta parecchie migliorie di prestazioni e numerosi aggiornamenti di traduzione.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは、いくつかのパフォーマンスの改善と多くの翻訳更新が行われています。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리스에서는 다양한 부분에서 성능 개선을 진행했으며, 수많은 언어로의 번역 업데이트를 실었습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Šioje laidoje yra keli našumo patobulinimai ir daugybės vertimų atnaujinimai.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluar ini memfiturkan beberapa penambahbaikan prestasi dan banyak kemaskini terjemahan.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen øker ytelsen og oppdaterer mange oversettelser.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze versie bevat verschillende prestatieverbeteringen en diverse bijgewerkte vertalingen.</p>
        <p lang="nn">Denne utgåva har fleire betringar i yting og mange oppdateringar av omsetjingane.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera kilka ulepszeń wydajności i liczne aktualizacje tłumaczeń.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão apresenta várias melhorias de desempenho e numerosas actualizações de tradução.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão apresenta várias melhorias de desempenho e inúmeras atualizações de tradução.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск содержит несколько улучшений производительности и бесчисленные обновления переводов.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje niekoľko vylepšení výkonu a množstvo aktualizácií prekladov.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja ima izboljšano zmogljivost in številne popravke prevodov.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim përfshin disa përmirësime të funksionimit dhe përditësime të shumta përkthimesh.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово је издање са побољшањима учинка и бројним побољшањима превода.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den här utgåvan tillhandahåller prestandaförbättringar och flera översättningsuppdateringar.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้มีการปรับปรุงสมรรถนะหลายรายการ และมีการปรับคำแปลจำนวนมาก</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm birçok performans iyileştirmesi ve çok sayıda çeviri güncelleştirmesine sahiptir.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей випуск містить кілька покращень функціонування і чисельні оновлення перекладу.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">该版本包括一些性能上的提升以及大量翻译工作的完善</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本有許多的效能改進，以及許多的翻譯更新。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-03-31" version="1.4.2">
      <description>
        <p>This release now displays all file timestamps according to timezone instead of Universal Coordinated Time (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="ar">يعرض هذا الإصدار الآن جميع الطوابع الزمنية للملفات وفقا للمنطقة الزمنية بدلا من التوقيت العالمي المنسق (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску адлюстроўваюцца ўсе пазнакі часу файлаў у адпаведнасці з часавым поясам замест універсальнага скаардынаванага часу (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази версия вече показва всички файлови времеви отпечатъци според часовата зона вместо универсално координирано време (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió mostra ara totes les marques de temps dels fitxers d'acord amb la zona horària en lloc de amb el temps universal coordinat (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="cs">V tomto vydání se zobrazují časové značky souborů podle časových zón namísto koordinovaného světového času (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse viser nu alle fil-tidsstempler i henhold til tidszone i stedet for Universal Coordinated Time (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version zeigt jetzt alle Dateizeitstempel nach Zeitzone statt nach koordinierter Weltzeit (UTC) an.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση εμφανίζει τώρα όλες τις χρονικές σημάνσεις των αρχείων με βάση τη ζώνη ώρας και όχι με βάση το παγκόσμιο συγχρονισμό του χρόνου (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="en_AU">This release now displays all file timestamps according to timezone instead of Universal Coordinated Time (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión muestra ahora todas las marcas de tiempo de los archivos según la zona horaria en vez de según el tiempo universal coordinado (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek fitxategi denborak ordu eremuaren arabera erakusten ditu eta ez Universal Coordinated Time (UTC)ren arabera.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version affiche maintenant tous les horodatages de fichiers en fonction du fuseau horaire au lieu du temps universel coordonné (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión amosa agora todas as marcas temporais dos ficheiros segundo o fuso horario no canto da Hora Universal Coordinada (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו מציגה כעת את כל חותמות השעה של הקבצים לפי אזור זמן במקום שעה אוניברסלית מתואמת (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás most már az időzóna alapján jeleníti meg az időbélyegeket, egyezményes koordinált világidő (UTC) helyett.</p>
        <p lang="hy_AM">Տարբերակում ցուցադրուում է բոլոր ժամակնիքները, ըստ ժամագաւտու այլ ոչ (UTC)֊ի։</p>
        <p lang="hye">Տարբերակում ցուցադրուում է բոլոր ժամակնիքները, ըստ ժամագաւտու այլ ոչ (UTC)֊ի։</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini menampilkan semua cap waktu berkas berdasarkan zona waktu alih-alih Universal Coordinated Time (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio da ora visualizza tutti i timestamp dei file in base al fuso orario invece che dal Tempo Coordinato Universale (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="ja">今回のリリースでは、世界協定時刻 (UTC) の代わりにタイムゾーンに従って、全てのファイルタイムスタンプが表示されるようになりました。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리즈는 UTC(세계협정표준시)에 따른 모든 타임 스탬프를 표시합니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Dabar, šioje laidoje visos failų laiko žymės yra rodomos atitinkamai pagal laiko juostą, o ne suderintąjį pasaulinį laiką (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini kini memaparkan semua setem masa fail berdasarkan zon waktu selain dari Waktu Universal Selaras (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen viser nå all tidsstempling på filer etter tidssone istedet for universell tid (UTC)</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze versie toont nu alle tijdstempels van bestanden overeenkomstig de tijdzone, in plaats van de Universal Coordinated Time (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie wyświetla teraz wszystkie sygnatury czasowe plików zgodnie ze strefą czasową zamiast uniwersalnego czasu skoordynowanego (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão exibe agora todas as datas de ficheiros de acordo com o fuso horário, em vez de Tempo Universal Coordenado (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão agora exibe todos os registros de data e hora de arquivo de acordo com o fuso horário em vez do Tempo Universal Coordenado (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="ru">Начиная с этого выпуска, программа отображает метки времени всех файлов в соответствии с часовым поясом, а не всемирным координированным временем (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie teraz zobrazuje všetky časové značky súborov podľa časovej zóny namiesto univerzálneho koordinovaného času (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja prikazuje vse časovne oznake v skladu s časovnim pasom in ne UTC časom.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim sjell shfaqjen e krejt vulave kohore në përputhje me zonën kohore, në vend se me Kohën e Bashkërenduar Universale (Universal Coordinated Time - UTC).</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање приказује све временске ознаке датотека по временској области уместо општег времена (УТЦ).</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna version visar nu alla filtidsstämplar efter tidszon istället för Universal Coordinated Time (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้แสดงเวลาต่างๆ ของแฟ้มตามเขตเวลาแทนที่จะเป็นเวลาสากล (UTC)</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm şimdi Evrensel Eşgüdümlı Zaman (UTC) yerine saat dilimine göre tüm dosya zaman damgalarını görüntüler.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей реліз тепер відображає всі файлові мітки часу відповідно до часового поясу замість "універсального координованого часу" (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">该版本会根据用户所处时区来显示文件的时间戳而不是以前使用的UTC时间</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本現在會根據時間而非世界協調時 (UTC) 來顯示時間戳。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-02-24" version="1.4.1">
      <description>
        <p>This release fixes several bugs related to the results window. Files are once again removed from the results list when deleted. Middle- and right-click functionality has been restored. Date range filters are now applied according to timezone instead of Universal Coordinated Time (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="ar">يعمل هذا الإصدار على إصلاح العديد من الأخطاء المتعلقة بـ إطار النتائج. تتم إزالة الملفات مرة أخرى من قائمة النتائج عند حذفها. تم استعادة وظيفة النقرات الوسطى و اليمنى. يتم الآن تطبيق عوامل تصفية نطاق التاريخ وفقاً للمنطقة الزمنية بدلاً من التوقيت العالمي المنسق (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску выпраўлены шэраг хібаў, звязаных з акном вынікаў. Пасля выдалення файлы зноў выдаляюцца са спіса вынікаў. Была адноўлена функцыянальнасць правай і сярэдняй кнопкі мышы. Фільтры дыяпазону дат цяпер ужываюцца ў адпаведнасці з часавым поясам замест універсальнага скаардынаванага часу (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази версия определя няколко грешки, свързани с прозореца за резултатите. Файловете отново се премахват от списъка с резултати, когато са изтрити. Функциите за кликване със среден и десен бутон на мишката са възстановени. Филтрите за диапазон от време сега се прилагат според часова зона вместо Универсално координирано време (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió corregeix diversos errors relacionats amb la finestra de resultats. Els fitxers s'eliminen de la llista de resultats quan se suprimeixen. S'ha restaurat la funcionalitat del botó central i del botó dret del ratolí. El filtre de data de modificació s'aplica ara d'acord amb la zona horària en lloc de amb el temps universal coordinat (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání opravuje několik chyb týkajících se okna s výsledky. Soubory jsou opět po smazání odstraněny z výsledků. Funkce kliknutí prostředním a pravým tlačítkem myši byla obnovena. Filtr časového rozmezí je nyní aplikován podle časové zóny namísto koordinovaného světového času (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse retter adskillige fejl i forbindelse med resultater-vinduet. Filer fjernes nu igen fra resultatslisten når de slettes. Midter- og højreklik er tilbage. Datoområdefiltre anvendes nu i henhold til tidszone i stedet for Universal Coordinated Time (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version behebt mehrere Fehler im Zusammenhang mit dem Ergebnisfenster. Dateien werden beim Löschen wieder aus der Ergebnisliste entfernt. Mittel- und Rechtsklick-Funktionalität wurde wiederhergestellt. Datumsbereichsfilter werden jetzt nach Zeitzone statt nach koordinierter Weltzeit (UTC) angewendet.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση διορθώνει αρκετά σφάλματα σχετικά με το παράθυρο των αποτελεσμάτων. Τα αρχεία αφαιρούνται και πάλι από τα αποτελέσματα όταν διαγράφονται. Έχει επανέλθει η λειτουργικότητα του μεσαίου και του δεξιού κλικ. Τα φίλτρα εύρους της ημερομηνίας εφαρμόζονται πλέον με βάση τη ζώνη ώρας και όχι με βάση το παγκόσμιο συγχρονισμό του χρόνου (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="en_AU">This release fixes several bugs related to the results window. Files are once again removed from the results list when deleted. Middle and right-click functionality has been restored. Date range filters are now applied according to timezone instead of Universal Coordinated Time (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión corrige varios errores relacionados con la ventana de resultados. Los archivos se retiran de la lista de resultados cuando se eliminan. Se ha restaurado la funcionalidad del botón central y del botón derecho del ratón. El filtro de fecha de modificación se aplica ahora de acuerdo con la zona horaria en lugar de con el tiempo universal coordinado (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek emaitzen leihoarekin lotutako hainbat arazo konpontzen ditu. Fitxategiak berriro emaitzen zerrendatik kentzen dira ezabatuak direnean. Erdiko eta eskuineko klik funtzionalitatea berrezarri da. Data iragazkiak ordu-zonaren arabera aplikatzen dira eta ez Universal Coordinated Timeren arabera (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version corrige plusieurs bogues relatifs à la fenêtre des résultats. Les fichiers sont une nouvelle fois enlevés de la liste des résultats quand ils sont supprimés. Les fonctionnalités « clic du milieu / clic droit » ont été restaurées. Les filtres d’intervalle de date sont maintenant appliqués selon le fuseau horaire (timezone), à la place du temps universel coordonné (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión arranxa varios fallos relacionados coa xanela de resultados. É posíbel outra vez retirar os ficheiros desde a lista de resultados ao eliminalos. Restaurouse a funcionalidade dos clics medio e dereito. Os filtros de rango de datas aplícanse agora segundo o fuso horario no canto do tempo coordinado universal (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו מתקנת מספר באגים הקשורים לחלון התוצאות. קבצים שוב אינם מופיעים ברשימת התוצאות כאשר הם נמחקים. פונקציונליות לחצן אמצעי ולחצן ימני שוחזרה. מסנני טווח התאריכים מיושמים כעת לפי איזור זמן במקום שעה אוניברסלית מתואמת (UTC). </p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás számos az eredmények ablakkal kapcsolatos hibát javít. A fájlok újra eltávolításra kerülnek a listából törléskor. A középső és jobb gombos funkciók is helyreállításra kerültek. A dátum intervallum szűrők most már figyelembe veszik az időzónát, és nem egyezményes koordinált világidőt (UTC) használnak.</p>
        <p lang="hy_AM">Տարբերակում ուղղուած են արդիւնքի պատուհանի որոշ սխալներ։ Նիշերը հեռացուում են եւս մեկ անգամ արդիւնքի ցուցակից ջնջուելուց յետոյ։ Վերականգնուել է աջ եւ կենտրոնասեղմումի գործառութիւնը։ Տուեալների ընդգրկոյթային զտիչները կարգաւորուում են ըստ ժամագաւտու այլ ոչ (UTC)֊ի։</p>
        <p lang="hye">Տարբերակում ուղղուած են արդիւնքի պատուհանի որոշ սխալներ։ Նիշերը հեռացուում են եւս մեկ անգամ արդիւնքի ցուցակից ջնջուելուց յետոյ։ Վերականգնուել է աջ եւ կենտրոնասեղմումի գործառութիւնը։ Տուեալների ընդգրկոյթային զտիչները կարգաւորուում են ըստ ժամագաւտու այլ ոչ (UTC)֊ի։</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini memperbaiki beberapa kutu yang terkait dengan jendela hasil. Berkas sekali lagi dibuang dari daftar hasil ketika dihapus. Fungsionalitas klik tengah dan klik kanan telah dikembalikan. Filter rentang tanggal kini diterapkan berdasar pada zona waktu alih-alih Universal Coordinated Time (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio corregge diversi bug relativi alla finestra dei risultati. I file sono ancora una volta rimossi dall'elenco dei risultati quando eliminati. Le funzioni dei tasti centrale e destro del mouse sono stati ripristinate. I filtri sull'intervallo delle date sono ora applicati in base al fuso orario invece che dal Tempo Coordinato Universale (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは、結果ウィンドウに関するいくつかのバグが修正されています。 ファイルは削除されたとき、結果リストから再び削除されます。 中間および右クリック機能が復活しました。 日付範囲フィルタは、世界協定時刻 (UTC) ではなく、タイムゾーンに従って適用されるようになりました。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리즈는 결과 창에 관련된 몇몇 버그가 수정되었습니다. 파일을 삭제하면 목록에서 다시 한 번 제거됩니다. 중간과 오른쪽 클릭 기능은 복구되었습니다. 날짜 범위 필터는 이제 UTC(세계협정표준시)에 따라 적용됩니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši laida ištaiso kelias klaidas, susijusias su rezultatų langu. Failai ir vėl, juos ištrinus, yra pašalinami iš rezultatų sąrašo. Buvo atkurtas vidurinio ir dešiniojo pelės mygtuko funkcionalumas. Datos rėžio filtrai dabar yra pritaikomi pagal laiko juostą, o ne pagal suderintąjį pasaulinį laiką (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini membaiki beberapa pepijat yang dikaitkan dengan tetingkap keputusan. Fail sekali lagi dibuang dari senarai keputusan jika dipadamkan. Kefungsian klik-tengah dan kanan telah dipulihkan. Penapis julat tarikh kini boleh digunakan berdasarkan zon waktu berbanding Waktu Universal Terselaras (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen har rettet flere feil forbundet med søkevinduet. Filer er igjen fjernet fra resultatlisten når de blir slettet. Midt- og høyre-klikk funksjonalitet er tilbake. Datoavgrensningsfilteret gjelder nå tidssone og ikke universel tid (UTC)</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze versie herstelt verschillende fouten die te maken hebben met het resultatenvenster. Bestanden worden wederom verwijderd uit de resultatenlijst na wissen. Middel- en rechtsklikfunctionaliteit is hersteld. Datumbereikfilters worden nu toegepast overeenkomstig de tijdzone in plaats van Universal Coordinated Time (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie naprawia kilka błędów związanych z oknem wyników. Po usunięciu pliki są ponownie usuwane z listy wyników. Przywrócono funkcje kliknięcia środkowym i prawym przyciskiem myszy. Filtry zakresu dat są teraz stosowane zgodnie ze strefą czasową zamiast uniwersalnego czasu skoordynowanego (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão corrige vários bugs relacionados com a janela de resultados. Os ficheiros são outra vez removidos da lista de resultados quando excluídos. As funcionalidades de clique com o botão direito e o botão central do rato foram restauradas. Os filtros de intervalos de data são agora aplicados de acordo com o fuso horário em vez de Tempo Universal Coordenado (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão corrige vários bugs relacionados à janela de resultados. Os arquivos são novamente removidos da lista de resultados quando excluídos. A funcionalidade do clique do botão do meio e direito foi restaurada. Agora os filtros de período são aplicados de acordo com o fuso horário em vez do Tempo Coordenado Universal (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск исправляет несколько проблем с окном результатов. Файлы снова убираются из списка результатов при удалении. Восстановлен функционал щелчков средней и правой кнопок мыши. Фильтры дат теперь применяются в соответствии с часовым поясом, а не всемирным координированным временем (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie opravuje niekoľko chýb spojených s oknom výsledkov. Súbory sú ešte raz odstránené zo zoznamu výsledkov po ich odstránení. Bola obnovená funkčnosť kliknutia stredným a pravým tlačidlom myši. Filtre rozsahu dátumu sú teraz použité podľa časovej zóny namiesto univerzálneho koordinovaného času (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja odpravlja številne hrošče, ki so povezani z rezultati iskanja. Datoteke so izbrisane iz rezulatata, če so izbrisane. Obnovnljena je funkcionalnost srednje in desne tipke miške. Datumski razponi sedaj ustrezajo časovnemu pasu in in več UTC.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim ndreq disa të meta të lidhura me dritaren e përfundimeve. Kartelat janë hequr sërish nga lista e përfundimeve, kur fshihen. Është rikthyer aftësia për klikim me butonin e mesit dhe atë të djathtë të miut. Filtrat mbi intervale datash tani zbatohen sipas zonën kohore, në vend se sipas Kohës së Bashkërenduar Universale (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање решава неколико буба у вези прозора налаза. Датотеке се поново уклањају из списка налаза по брисању. Радње средњег и десног клика су повраћене. Опсези временских услова се сада примењују према временској области уместо општег времена (УТЦ).</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna version rättar till flera fel relaterade till resultatfönstret. Filer undantas återigen från resultatlistan när de är borttagna. Mitten- och högerklicksfunktionalitet har blivit återställd. Datumintervallsfilter tillämpas nu enligt tidszon istället för Universal Coordinated Time (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้มีการแก้บั๊กหลายรายการเกี่ยวกับหน้าต่างแสดงผลลัพธ์ โดยกลับมาลบแฟ้มออกจากการแสดงผลลัพธ์เมื่อมีการลบแฟ้ม การรองรับการคลิกเมาส์ปุ่มกลางและปุ่มขวาได้กลับมาทำงานอีกครั้ง ตัวกรองช่วงวันที่ในรุ่นนี้ทำงานตามเขตเวลาแทนที่จะเป็นเวลาสากล (UTC) แล้ว</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm, sonuç penceresiyle ilgili türlü hataları giderir. Silinirken dosyalar sonuç listesinden bir kez daha çıkarılır. Orta ve sağ tıklama işlevselliği geri yüklendi. Tarih aralığı süzgeçleri artık Evrensel Eşgüdümlı Saat (UTC) yerine saat dilimine göre uygulanır.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей реліз виправляє ряд помилок, пов'язаних з вікном результатів. Файли знову вилучаються зі списку результатів при видаленні. Відновлено функціонал середньої та правої клавіші миші . Діапазон дат фільтри в даний час застосовується в залежності від часового поясу замість "універсального координованого часу" (UTC).</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">本次更新修正了一些关于搜索结果窗口的错误. 文件现在又可以从搜索结果列表中被删除. 鼠标中键和右键的功能被得以恢复. 过滤时间段现在可以根据时区而不是协调时间时 (UTC) 来执行.</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本修復了多個關於結果視窗的臭蟲。檔案只要從結果清單中移除就會被刪除。中鍵與右鍵點選功能已經恢復。資料範圍過濾器現在是使用目前時間而非世界協調時 (UTC)。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.0" date="2016-02-19">
      <description>
        <p>This release includes a significant interface refresh, improves search speed, and fixes several bugs. The workflow has been improved, utilizing some of the latest features of the GTK+ toolkit, including optional headerbars and popover widgets. Password handling has been improved with the integration of PolicyKit when available.</p>
        <p lang="ar">يتضمن هذا الإصدار تحديثات هامة على مستوى الواجهة، ويحسن سرعة البحث، وإصلاح العديد من الأخطاء. وقد تم تحسين سير العمل ، وذلك باستخدام بعض من أحدث الميزات من مجموعة أدوات GTK + ، بما في ذلك رؤوس اختياري والحاجيات popover. تم تحسين معالجة كلمة المرور مع دمج PolicyKit عندما تكون متوفرة.</p>
        <p lang="be">Гэты выпуск ўключае ў сябе значнае абнаўленне інтэрфейсу, павышае хуткасць пошуку і выпраўляе шэраг хібаў. Працоўны працэс быў удасканалены з дапамогаю некаторых з апошніх магчымасцяў GTK + , уключаючы дадатковыя панэлі і віджэты. Апрацоўка пароляў была палепшаная з дапамогаю PolicyKit.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това издание включва значително опресняване на интерфейса, подобрява скоростта на търсене и поправя няколко грешки. Работният процес бе подобрен, като се използват някои от най-новите функции на GTK + инструментариума, включително опционални headerbares и popup widgets. Работата с паролата бе подобрена с интегрирането на PolicyKit, когато е налице.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió inclou una actualització significativa de la interfície, millora la velocitat de cerca i corregeix diversos errors. El flux de treball s'ha millorat mitjançant l'ús d'algunes de les últimes característiques del conjunt d'eines GTK+, incloent les barres de capçalera opcionals i els elements gràfics emergents. La gestió de contrasenyes s'ha millorat amb la integració de PolicyKit quan estigui disponible.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání obsahuje značné změny rozhraní, rychlejší vyhledávání a opravuje několik chyb. Byl vylepšen postup práce pomocí některých nových vlastností GTK+, včetně volitelných záhlaví a rozklikávatelných grafických komponent. Práce s hesly byla vylepšena zahrnutím PolicyKit tam, kde to bylo možné.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse inkluderer en betydelig genopfriskning af grænsefladen, forbedre søgehastighed og rettelse af adskillige fejl. Arbejdsgangen er blevet forbedret, som gør brug af nogen af de seneste faciliteter i GTK+-toolkittet, inklusiv valgfrie headerlinjer og popover-widgets. Adgangskodehåndtering er blevet forbedret med integreringen af PolicyKit når det er tilgængeligt.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version enthält eine beträchtliche Aktualisierung der Benutzeroberfläche, verbessert die Suchgeschwindigkeit und behebt mehrere Fehler. Der Arbeitsablauf wurde verbessert und nutzt einige der neuesten Funktionen des GTK+-Werkzeugkastens, einschließlich optionaler Kopfleisten und Popover-Widgets. Die Handhabung von Passwörtern wurde durch die Integration von PolicyKit verbessert, sofern verfügbar.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση περιλαμβάνει σημαντική ανανέωση της διεπαφής, βελτιώνει την ταχύτητα αναζήτησης και διορθώνει αρκετά σφάλματα. Η ροή εργασίας έχει βελτιωθεί, χρησιμοποιώντας μερικά από τα τελευταία χαρακτηριστικά του GTK+ όπως, τις προαιρετικές επικεφαλίδες παραθύρων και τα αναδυόμενα γραφικά. Η διαχείριση των κωδικών έχει βελτιωθεί, με την ενσωμάτωση του PolicyKit όπου είναι διαθέσιμο.</p>
        <p lang="en_AU">This release includes a significant interface refresh, improves search speed, and fixes several bugs. The workflow has been improved, utilizing some of the latest features of the GTK+ toolkit, including optional headerbars and popover widgets. Password handling has been improved with the integration of PolicyKit when available.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión incluye una actualización significativa de la interfaz, mejora la velocidad de búsqueda y corrige varios errores. El flujo de trabajo se ha mejorado mediante el uso de algunas de las últimas características del conjunto de herramientas GTK+, incluyendo las barras de encabezado opcionales y los elementos gráficos emergentes. El manejo de contraseñas se ha mejorado con la integración de PolicyKit cuando esté disponible.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek interfaze freskatua dakar, bilaketa abiadura hobetzen du, eta hainbat akats konpontzen ditu. Lan-fluxua hobetu da, GTK+ toolkit-aren azken ezaugarri batzuk erabiliz, adibidez hautazko goiburu barrak edo sagua gainetik pasatzerakoan ikusten diren widgetak. Pasahitzen kudeaketa hobetu da PolicyKitekin, erabilgarri dagoenean.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version comporte un rafraîchissement important de l’interface, une amélioration de la vitesse de recherche et corrige plusieurs bogues. Le flux de travail a été amélioré en utilisant quelques-unes des dernières fonctionnalités de la boîte à outils GTK+, incluant des barres d’en-tête optionnelles et des widgets. La gestion du mot de passe a été améliorée avec l’intégration de PolicyKit lorsque disponible.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión inclúe feitura nova da interface, mellora a velocidade da busca e arranxa varios fallos. O fuxo de traballo foi mellorado utilizando algunha das funcionalidades máis recentes da caixa de ferramentas GTK+, incluíndo as barras de cabeceira opcionais e os trebellos sobrepostos. A xestión dos contrasinais foi mellorada coa integración de PolicyKit onde está dispoñíbel.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו כוללת ריענון ממשק משמעותי, משפרת את מהירות החיפוש, ומתקנת מספר באגים. זרימת העבודה שופרה, תוך שימוש בחלק מהמאפיינים החדשים ביותר של ערכת הכלים GTK+, כולל כותרות אופציונליות ויישומונים קופצים. טיפול בסיסמאות שופר עם השילוב של ערכת מדיניות כאשר ישימה.</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás jelentés felületi frissítést tartalmaz, javítja a keresés sebességét, és számos hibát javít. A munkafolyamat fejlesztésre került, kihasználva a GTK+ eszközkészlet legfrissebb funkcióit, köztük a nem kötelező címsávot, és a popover felületi elemeket. A jelszókezelés is fejlesztve lett a PolicyKit integrálásával, ha az elérhető.</p>
        <p lang="hy_AM">Տարբերակում թարմացուած է միջերեսը, որոնման արագութիւնը, ուղղուած են որոշ խնդիրներ։ Մշակուել է աշխատահոսքը, որն իր մեջ ներառում GTK+ գործիքակազմի ամենաթարմ յատկութիւնները։ Թարմացուել է գաղտնաբառերի հետ աշխատանքը, որն արդէն ներառում է PolicyKit֊ը։</p>
        <p lang="hye">Տարբերակում թարմացուած է միջերեսը, որոնման արագութիւնը, ուղղուած են որոշ խնդիրներ։ Մշակուել է աշխատահոսքը, որն իր մեջ ներառում GTK+ գործիքակազմի ամենաթարմ յատկութիւնները։ Թարմացուել է գաղտնաբառերի հետ աշխատանքը, որն արդէն ներառում է PolicyKit֊ը։</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini menyertakan penyegaran antarmuka yang signifikan, peningkatan kecepatan pencarian, dan perbaikan beberapa kutu. Alur kerja telah ditingkatkan, memanfaatkan beberapa fitur terbaru dari toolkit GTK+, termasuk bilah kepala opsional dan widget popover. Penanganan kata sandi telah ditingkatkan dengan integrasi PolicyKit jika tersedia.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio include un aggiornamento significativo dell'interfaccia, migliora la velocità della ricerca e corregge diversi bug. Il flusso di lavoro è stato migliorato, utilizzando le ultime funzionalità di GTK+, come le barre header opzionali e widget a comparsa. La gestione delle password è stata migliorata con l'integrazione di PolicyKit se disponibile.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは、重要なインタフェースの更新、検索速度の向上、いくつかのバグの修正が行われています。オプションのヘッダーバーやポップオーバーウィジェットを含む、GTK+ ツールキットの最新機能のいくつかを利用することによってワークフローが向上しました。 PolicyKit の統合により、パスワード処理が改善されました。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리즈는 중요한 최신 인터페이스가 들어있으며, 검색 속도를 개선했고, 몇몇 버그를 수정했습니다. 처리 흐름을 개선했으며, GTK+ toolkit의 최신 기능을 사용하며, 추가적으로 더 나은 위젯과 헤더바를 추가 하고 있습니다. 암호 처리 기능은 PolicyKit 통합으로 개선했습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Šioje laidoje yra pastebimai atnaujinta sąsaja, pagerintas paieškos greitis bei ištaisytos kelios klaidos. Buvo patobulinta darbo eiga, panaudojant kai kurias naujausias GTK+ įrankinės ypatybes, įskaitant neprivalomas antraščių juostas bei iššokančius valdiklius. Buvo patobulintas slaptažodžių apdorojimas su PolicyKit integravimu, kai tai yra prieinama.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini menyertakan antaramuka yang serba baharu, menambahbaik kelajuan gelintar, dan membaiki beberapa pepijat. Aliran kerja juga telah ditambah baik, dengan menggunakan beberapa fitur terkini dari kit alat GTK+, termasuklah palang pengepala dan widget timbul pilihan. Pengendalian kata laluan telah ditambah baik dengan penyepaduan PolicyKit jika tersedia.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen inkluderer en stor mengde grensesnitt oppdateringer, økt søkehastighet og retter flere feil. Arbeidsflyten har blitt forbedret, bruker nå funksjoner i nyeste GTK+ verktøykskassen, inkludert valgbare faner og popover elementer. Passordbehandling har blitt forbedret med integrasjon av PolicyKit når det er tilgjengelig.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze versie bevat een belangrijke vernieuwing van de gebruikersschil, verbetert de zoeksnelheid, en herstelt verschillende fouten. Het werkingsproces is verbeterd, met gebruikmaking van enkele van de nieuwste functies van de GTK+ gereedschapskist, inclusief optionele kopbalken en opduikvensters. Wachtwoordafhandeling is verbeterd met de integratie van PolicyKit (indien die beschikbaar is).</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera znaczne odświeżenie interfejsu, poprawia szybkość wyszukiwania i naprawia kilka błędów. Udoskonalono przepływ pracy, wykorzystując niektóre z najnowszych funkcji zestawu narzędzi GTK+, w tym opcjonalne nagłówki i widżety popover. Obsługa haseł została ulepszona dzięki integracji z PolicyKit, gdy jest dostępny.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão inclui uma atualização significativa da interface, melhora a velocidade de pesquisa e corrige vários bugs. O fluxo de trabalho foi melhorado, utilizando alguns dos mais recentes recursos do kit de ferramentas GTK+, incluindo barras opcionais de cabeçalho e widgets popover. O tratamento da palavra-passe foi melhorado com a integração do PolicyKit, quando disponível.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão inclui uma atualização de interface significativa, melhora a velocidade de pesquisa e corrige vários bugs. O fluxo de trabalho foi aprimorado, utilizando alguns dos recursos mais recentes da biblioteca GTK+, incluindo barras de cabeçalho opcionais e widgets popover. O tratamento de senhas foi melhorado com a integração do PolicyKit, quando disponível.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск содержит значительное обновление интерфейса, улучшает скорость поиска и исправляет несколько проблем. Поток работ улучшен с помощью использования самых свежих возможностей тулкита GTK+, включая опциональные заголовки и всплывающие виджеты. Работа с паролями улучшена интеграцией с PolicyKit при возможности.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie obsahuje významnú aktualizáciu rozhrania, zlepšuje rýchlosť vyhľadávania a opravuje niekoľko chýb. Pracovný postup bol vylepšený, využívajúc niektoré z najnovších funkcií súpravy nástrojov GTK+, vrátane voliteľných hlavičiek a kontextových okien. Spracovanie hesiel bolo vylepšené integráciou PolicyKit, keď je k dispozícii.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja vsebuje pomembne osvežitve vmesnika, hiterejše iskanje, odpravo hroščev. Način dela je izboljšan z uporabo nekaterih zadnjih funkciji GTK+ seta orodji, vključno z naslovnimi pasicami in pojavnimi widgeti. Upravljanje gesel je izboljšano z uporabo PolicyKit (če je na voljo).</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim përfshin një rifreskim të rëndësishëm të ndërfaqes, përmirëson shpejtësinë e kërkimeve, dhe ndreq disa të meta. Rrjedha e punës është përmirësuar, duke përdorur disa nga veçoritë më të reja të grupit të mjeteve GTK+, përfshi shtylla opsionale kreu dhe widget-e flluskë opsionale. Shfrytëzimi i fjalëkalimeve është përmirësuar përmes integrimit të PolicyKit-it, kur kjo është e mundur.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање доноси значајно освежење изгледа сучеља, побољшање брзине претраге и отклон неколико буба. Ток рада је побољшан и користи неке најновије могућности прибора ГТК+-а, укључујући могућности заглавља и искачућих справица. Управљање лозинком је побољшано уз усклађивање са прибором лозинки када је доступан.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna version inkluderar omfattande gränssnittsuppdateringar, förbättrad sökhastighet, och rättar till flera fel. Arbetsflödet har förbättrats, genom att använda några av de senaste funktionerna i GTK+ verktygslådan, inkluderande valfria rubrikrader och popover widgets. Lösenordshantering har förbättrats med integrationen av PolicyKit då detta är tillgängligt.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้มีการปรับปรุงส่วนติดต่อผู้ใช้อย่างมาก มีการปรับปรุงความเร็วในการค้นหา และมีการแก้บั๊กหลายรายการ กระบวนการทำงานได้รับการปรับปรุง โดยใช้ประโยชน์จากความสามารถใหม่ล่าสุดบางประการของทูลคิต GTK+ ซึ่งรวมถึงแถบหัวเรื่องและวิดเจ็ตผุดขึ้น การรองรับรหัสผ่านในรุ่นนี้ได้รับการปรับปรุงโดยเชื่อมรวมกับ PolicyKit เมื่อทำได้</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm önemli arayüz yenilemesi içerir, arama hızını artırır ve türlü hataları düzeltir. İsteğe bağlı başlık çubukları ve popover widget'ları dahil, GTK + araç takımının en yeni özelliklerinden bazılarını kullanarak iş akışı geliştirildi. PasswordKit ile olabildiğince tümleşimle şifre kullanımı geliştirildi.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей реліз включає в себе значне оновлення інтерфейсу, покращує швидкість пошуку, і виправляє ряд помилок. Робочий процес був поліпшений, використовуючи деякі з останніх особливостей GTK + набір інструментів, включаючи додаткові headerbars і popover віджетів. Обробка пароля була покращена з інтеграцією PolicyKit при їх наявності.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">本次更新包括了重大更新的界面，搜索速度的改善，和对诸多错误的修正。利用 GTK+工具包的一些最新功能，包括可选的标题栏和弹出窗口小部件，工作流程得到了改进。 在可用时集成了 PolicyKit， 使密码处理得到了改进。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本包含了顯著的界面更新，改善搜尋速度，並修復許多臭蟲。工作流程已被改善，並利用了一些 GTK+ 元件工具箱的最新功能，包含了可選的標題列與彈出式視窗小工具。密碼處理也因為在可用的時候整合了 PolicyKit 而改善了。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2014-09-21" version="1.2.2">
      <description>
        <p>This release fixes two new bugs and includes updated translations.</p>
        <p lang="ar">يعمل هذا الإصدار على إصلاح اثنين من الأخطاء الجديدة ويتضمن ترجمات محدثة.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску выпраўлены дзве новыя хібы і абноўленыя пераклады.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази версия поправя две нови грешки и включва обновления на преводите.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió corregeix dos errors nous i inclou traduccions actualitzades.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání opravuje dvě nové chyby a zahrnuje aktualizované překlady.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse retter to fejl og inkluderer opdaterede oversættelser.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version behebt zwei neue Fehler und enthält aktualisierte Übersetzungen.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση διορθώνει δύο νέα σφάλματα και περιλαμβάνει ενημερωμένες μεταφράσεις.</p>
        <p lang="en_AU">This release fixes two new bugs and includes updated translations.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión corrige dos errores nuevos e incluye traducciones actualizadas.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek bi akats berri konpontzen ditu eta itzulpen eguneratuak sartzen ditu.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä julkaisu korjaa kaksi uutta bugia ja sisältää päivitetyt käännökset.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version corrige deux nouveaux bogues et comporte des mises à jour de traductions.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión arranxa dous fallos novos e inclúe traducións actualizadas.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו מתקנת שני באגים חדשים וכוללת תרגומים מעודכנים.</p>
        <p lang="hr">Ovo izdanje rješava dvije nove greške i uključuje ažurirane prijevode.</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás két új hibát javít, és frissített fordításokat tartalmaz.</p>
        <p lang="hy_AM">Տարբերակում ուղղուած են երկու սխալ եւ թարմացուած են թարգմանութիւնները  </p>
        <p lang="hye">Տարբերակում ուղղուած են երկու սխալ եւ թարմացուած են թարգմանութիւնները  </p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini memperbaiki dua kutu baru dan menyertakan pemutakhiran terjemahan.</p>
        <p lang="ie">Ti-ci publication correcte du nov errores e include actualisat traductiones.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio corregge due nuovi bug ed include traduzioni aggiornate.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは、2つの新しいバグ修正と翻訳の更新が含まれます。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리즈는 2가지의 새로운 버그를 수정 하고 번역 업데이트를 포함합니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Šioje laidoje ištaisomos dvi naujos klaidos ir yra atnaujinami vertimai.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini membaiki dua pepijat baharu dan sertakan terjemahan yang dikemakinikan.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen fikser to nye feil og oppdatert oversettelse.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze uitgave bevat reparaties voor twee fouten en bijgewerkte vertalingen.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie poprawia dwa nowe błędy i zawiera aktualizację tłumaczeń.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão corrige dois erros novos e inclui traduções atualizadas.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão corrige dois novos bugs e inclui traduções atualizadas.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск исправляет пару новых ошибок и включает обновлённые переводы.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie opravuje dve nové chyby a zahŕňa aktualizované preklady.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdja popravlja dva hrošča in dopolnuje prevod.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim ndreq dy të meta dhe përfshin përditësime të përkthimeve.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање решава две нове бубе и укључује у себи освежене преводе.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna version rättar till två nya fel och innehåller uppdaterade översättningar.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้แก้บั๊กที่ได้รับรายงานใหม่สองรายการ และปรับคำแปล</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm, iki yeni hatayı düzeltir ve güncellenmiş çevirileri içerir.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей реліз виправляє дві нові помилки і включає в себе оновлені переклади.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">本版本修复了两处新的缺陷同时完善了翻译情况</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本修復了兩個新的臭蟲並包含了更新的翻譯。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.2.1" date="2014-08-19">
      <description>
        <p>This release fixes a regression where the application is unable to start on some systems.</p>
        <p lang="ar">يعمل هذا الإصدار على إصلاح الانحدار حيث يتعذر على التطبيق البدء في بعض الأنظمة.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску выпраўлена рэгрэсія, калі праграму немагчыма запусціць у некаторых сістэмах.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази версия отстранява регресия, при която приложението не може да стартира при някои системи.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió corregeix una regressió que impedia que l'aplicació s'iniciés en alguns sistemes.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání opravuje chybu, při které se na některých systémech aplikace nespustila.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse retter en regression hvor programmet ikke er i stand til at starte på nogle systemer.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version behebt einen Rückschritt, bei dem es der Anwendung nicht möglich ist, auf einigen Systemen, zu starten.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση διορθώνει ένα σφάλμα που επανεμφανίστηκε, όπου σε ορισμένα συστήματα η εφαρμογή δεν εκκινούσε.</p>
        <p lang="en_AU">This release fixes a regression where the application is unable to start on some systems.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión corrige una regresión que impedía que la aplicación se iniciara en algunos sistemas.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek sistema batzuetan aplikazioa abiaraztea galarazten duen atzerapen bat konpontzen du.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä julkaisu korjaa regression joka esti sovelluksen käynnistymisen joillain järjestelmillä.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version corrige une régression qui empêchait l’application de démarrer sur certains systèmes.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión arranxa unha regresión na que a aplicación non daba arrancado nalgúns sistemas.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו מתקנת באג רגרסיה בו האפליקציה לא היתה ניתנת להפעלה בכמה מערכות.</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás egy regressziót javít, amely szerint az alkalmazás egyes rendszereken képtelen elindulni.</p>
        <p lang="hy_AM">Տարբերակում ուղղուած է որոշ համակարգերում յաւելուածի միացման խնդիրը։</p>
        <p lang="hye">Տարբերակում ուղղուած է որոշ համակարգերում յաւելուածի միացման խնդիրը։</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini memperbaiki sebuah regresi di mana aplikasi tidak bisa dimulai pada beberapa sistem.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio corregge una regressione per cui l'applicazione non era in grado di avviarsi in alcuni sistemi.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは、一部のシステムでアプリケーションを起動できないリグレッション問題が修正されています。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리즈는 일부 시스템에서 실행 불가능한 문제를 해결했습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Šioje laidoje yra ištaisyta regresija, dėl kurios kai kuriose sistemose buvo neįmanoma paleisti programos.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini membaiki regresi yang mana aplikasi tidak berupaya dimulakan pada beberapa sistem.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen fikser en regresjon som førte til at programmet ikke startet på enkelte systemer.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze versie bevat een reparatie voor een regressiefout waardoor deze toepassing op sommige systemen niet kon starten.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie naprawia regresję, w wyniku której na niektórych systemach program nie był w stanie się uruchomić.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão corrige uma regressão em que a aplicação é incapaz de iniciar em alguns sistemas.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão corrige uma regressão em que o aplicativo não pode ser iniciado em alguns sistemas.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск исправляет регрессию с невозможностью запуска приложения на некоторых системах.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie opravuje pád programu pri spustení na niektorých systémoch.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja odpravlja regresijo, ko se aplikacije na nekaterih sistemih ni mogla pognati.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim ndreq një hap mbrapa, nën të cilin aplikacioni s’është në gjendje të niset në disa sisteme.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање решава губитак старих могућности, где програм није могао да се покрене на неким склоповима.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna version ordnar en regression som gjorde att programmet inte gick att starta på en del system.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้แก้ปัญหาความถดถอยซึ่งทำให้โปรแกรมไม่สามารถเปิดทำงานได้ในบางระบบ</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm, uygulamanın bazı sistemlerde başlatılamadığı gerilemeyi düzeltir.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей реліз виправляє неможливість запуску програми на деяких системах.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此版本修复了本应用在某些系统上无法启动的回归。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本修復了應用程式無法在某些系統上執行的問題。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2014-08-16" version="1.2.0">
      <description>
        <p>This release fixes a regression where multiple search terms were no longer supported. An InfoBar is now displayed when the search database is outdated, and the dialogs used to update the database have been improved.</p>
        <p lang="ar">يعمل هذا الإصدار على إصلاح الانحدار حيث لم تعد مصطلحات البحث المتعددة مدعومة. يتم عرض شريط المعلومات الآن عندما تكون قاعدة بيانات البحث قديمة ، وتم تحسين مربعات الحوار المستخدمة لتحديث قاعدة البيانات.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску выпраўлена рэгрэсія, калі некалькі тэрмінаў пошуку больш не падтрымліваецца. Інфармацыйная панэль зараз адлюстроўваюцца, калі база даных пошуку састарэла, і дыялогавыя вокны, якія выкарыстоўваюцца для абнаўлення базы даных, былі палепшаныя.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази версия отстранява регресия, при която няколко термина за търсене вече не се поддържат. Вече се показва информационна лента, когато базата данни за търсене е остаряла и диалозите, използвани за обновяване на базата данни, са подобрени.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió corregeix una regressió que impedia especificar diversos termes de cerca. Ara es mostra una barra d'informació quan l'índex de cerca és obsolet, també s'han millorat els diàlegs per actualitzar la base de dades.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tato verze opravuje regrese, kdy nebylo podporováno více hledaných výrazů. Informační panel se nyní zobrazí, když je vyhledávací databáze zastaralá, a byly vylepšeny dialogy používané k aktualizaci databáze.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse retter en regression hvor flere søgetermer ikke længere var understøttet. En infolinje vises nu når søgedatabasen er forældet og dialogerne som bruges til at opdatere databasen er blevet forbedret.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version behebt einen Rückschritt, wobei mehrere Suchbegriffe nicht mehr unterstützt wurden. Eine Infoleiste wird jetzt angezeigt, wenn die Suchdatenbank nicht mehr aktuell ist und die Dialoge, die verwendet werden, um die Datenbank zu aktualisieren, wurden verbessert.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση διορθώνει ένα σφάλμα που επανεμφανίστηκε, όπου πολλαπλοί όροι αναζήτησης δεν υποστηρίζονταν. Εμφανίζεται πλέον και μια γραμμή πληροφοριών όταν η βάση δεδομένων αναζήτησης είναι ξεπερασμένη, και έχουν βελτιωθεί τα παράθυρα διαλόγου που χρησιμοποιούνται για την ενημέρωση της βάσης δεδομένων.</p>
        <p lang="en_AU">This release fixes a regression where multiple search terms were no longer supported. An InfoBar is now displayed when the search database is outdated, and the dialogs used to update the database have been improved.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión corrige una regresión que impedía especificar varios términos de búsqueda. Ahora se muestra una barra de información cuando el índice de búsqueda está obsoleto y se han mejorado los diálogos para actualizarlo.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek bilaketa termino ugari erabiltzea baimentzen ez zuen atzerapen bat konpontzen du. Informazio barra bat erakusten da orain datu-basea zaharkituta dagoenean, eta datu-basea eguneratzeko erabiltzen diren leihotxoak hobetu dira.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä julkaisu korjaa regression jossa monen hakusanan käyttöä ei enää tuettu. Tietopalkki näytetään nyt kun hakutietokanta on vanhentunut, ja tietokannan päivitysikkunoita parannettiin.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version corrige une régression dans laquelle plusieurs termes de recherche n’étaient plus pris en charge. Une barre d’informations s’affiche désormais lorsque la base des données de recherche n’est plus à jour. De plus, la boîte de dialogue de mise à jour de la base de données a été améliorée.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión arranxa unha regresión na que non se admitían varios termos de busca. Agora aparece unha barra informativa cando a base de datos de buscas está desfasada e os diálogos empregados para actualizar a base de datos recibiron melloras.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו מתקנת באג רגרסיה בו מונחי חיפוש מרובים לא היו עוד נתמכים. כעת מוצגת שורת מידע כאשר מאגר החיפוש אינו בתוקף, והדו שיח לעדכון המאגר עבר שיפור.</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás egy regressziót javít, amely szerint a több egyidejű keresési kifejezések már nem támogatottak. Egy információs sáv jelenik meg, ha az adatbázis elavult, és az adatbázis frissítéséhez használt párbeszédablak is fejlesztésre került.</p>
        <p lang="hy_AM">Տարբերակում ուղղուած է բազմակի եզրոյթների որոնման հետ կապուած խնդիրը։ InfoBar֊ը ցուցադրուում է, երբ հնանում է որոնման շտեմարանը, մշակուել է նաեւ շտեմարանի թարմացումը։ </p>
        <p lang="hye">Տարբերակում ուղղուած է բազմակի եզրոյթների որոնման հետ կապուած խնդիրը։ InfoBar֊ը ցուցադրուում է, երբ հնանում է որոնման շտեմարանը, մշակուել է նաեւ շտեմարանի թարմացումը։ </p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini memperbaiki sebuah regresi di mana beberapa istilah pencarian tidak lagi didukung. Sebuah Bilah Info kini ditampilkan ketika basis data pencarian telah lama tidak diperbarui, dan dialog yang digunakan untuk memperbarui basis data telah ditingkatkan.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio risolve una regressione per cui termini di ricerca multipli non erano più supportati. Adesso viene mostrato un avviso quando il database di ricerca non è aggiornato, e le finestre di dialogo di aggiornamento database sono state migliorate.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは複数のキーワードでの検索ができなくなっていた問題を解決しました。検索データベースが古くなると情報バーが表示されるようにもなり、データベースのアップデートについてのダイアログも改善されました。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리즈는 다중 검색이 불가능 했던 점이 수정되었습니다. 정보 표시줄에 검색 데이터베이스가 오래된 경우 표시되며, 데이터베이스 업데이트를 하기위한 대화상자가 향상되었습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Šioje laidoje yra ištaisoma regresija, dėl kurios keli paieškos terminai būdavo nebepalaikomi. Dabar, kai paieškos duomenų bazė yra pasenusi, yra rodoma informacinė juosta, o taip pat yra patobulinti duomenų bazės atnaujinimo dialogai.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini membaiki regresi yang mana terma gelintar berbilang tidak lagi disokong. Satu Palang Maklumat kini dipaparkan bila pangkalan data gelintar telah lapuk, dan dialog digunakan untuk mengemaskini telah ditambah baik.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen fikser en regresjons hvor flere søkekrav ikke lenger var støttet. En InfoBar er nå vist når søkedatabasen er for gammel, og dialogen for å oppdatere databasen har blitt forbedret.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze uitgave herstelt een regressiefout waardoor meerdere zoektermen niet langer werden ondersteund. Er wordt nu een InfoBalk getoond wanneer de gegevensbank met zoekgegevens verouderd is, en de dialoogschermpjes die worden gebruikt om de gegevensbank bij te werken, zijn verbeterd.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie naprawia błąd, w wyniku którego nie były obsługiwane wielokrotne warunki wyszukiwania. Wyświetlany jest pasek informacyjny, gdy przeszukiwana baza danych jest przedawniona. Ulepszono także okna dialogowe wykorzystywane do aktualizowania bazy danych.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão corrige uma regressão onde vários termos de pesquisa não eram mais suportados. Uma barra de informações é agora exibida quando a base de dados de pesquisa está desatualizada, e os diálogos utilizados para a atualização da base de dados foram melhorados.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão corrige uma regressão onde vários termos de pesquisa não eram mais suportados. Uma barra de informações é exibida quando a base de dados de pesquisa está desatualizada e os diálogos usados para atualizar a base de dados foram melhorados.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск исправляет регрессию, при которой не поддерживались множественные условия поиска. Теперь отображается InfoBar, когда поисковая база данных устарела; диалоги, используемые для обновления базы данных, также улучшены.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie opravuje regresiu funkcionality, po ktorej už nebolo podporované vyhľadávanie s viacerými výrazmi. Keď je vyhľadávacia databáza zastaraná, zobrazí sa informačný panel, a boli vylepšené dialógové okná používané na aktualizáciu databázy.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja popravlja napako, ko več iskalnih pogojev ni več na voljo. Ko je iskalna baza zastarela, se pojavi informacijska pasica, dialogi za posodabljanje baze pa so bili izboljšani.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim ndreq një hap mbrapa, nën të cilin, nuk mbuloheshin më terma të shumëfishtë kërkimi. Tashmë, kur baza e të dhënave të kërkimeve është e vjetruar, shfaqet një InfoBar, dhe janë përmirësuar dialogët e përdorur gjatë përditësimit të bazës së të dhënave.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање решава губитак старих могућности вишеструких услова претраге. Трака обавештења се сада приказује када складиште података застари, а прозор који се користи за освежавање складишта података је побољшан.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna version ordnar en regression som gjorde att flera söktermer inte längre stöddes. En Inforad visas nu då sökdatabasen är föråldrad, och dialogerna som används för att uppdatera databasen har förbättrats.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้แก้ปัญหาความถดถอยที่ทำให้การรองรับคำค้นมากกว่าหนึ่งคำไม่ทำงาน มีการแสดงแถบแจ้งข้อมูลเมื่อฐานข้อมูลค้นหาล้าสมัย และมีการปรับปรุงกล่องโต้ตอบสำหรับปรับฐานข้อมูล</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm, birden çok arama teriminin artık desteklenmediği bağlanımı düzeltir. Arama veri tabanının modası geçmiş ve artık veri tabanını güncellemek için kullanılan iletişim pencereleri geliştirildiğinde bir BilgiÇubuğu görüntülenmekte.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей реліз виправляє помилки, коли не підтримувався мультипошук термінів. На інформаційній панелі тепер відображається, коли база даних пошуку застаріла, і діалоги, які використовуються для оновлення бази даних були покращені.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此版本修复了不再支持多个搜索字词的回归。 现在，当搜索数据库过期时，将显示InfoBar，并且用于更新数据库的对话框已得到改进。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本修復了多重搜尋字詞不被支援的問題。現在當搜尋資料庫過期時也會顯示資訊列，而用於更新資料庫的對話框也已改善。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.3" date="2014-08-09">
      <description>
        <p>This release fixes two issues where locate would not be properly executed and improves handling of missing symbolic icons.</p>
        <p lang="ar">عمل هذا الإصدار على إصلا مشكلتين و هما عدم القدرة على تنفيذ مسار بشكل صحيح و كذا يحسن التعامل مع  الرومز الرمزية المخفية.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску выпраўлены дзве праблемы: месцазнаходжанне не вызначалася належным чынам, палепшана апрацоўка зніклых сімвалічных значкоў.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази версия отстранява два проблема, при които локализирането не би било правилно изпълнено и подобрява работата с липсващи символни икони.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió corregeix dos problemes que impedien executar l'ordre locate correctament i millora la gestió de la manca d'icones simbòliques.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tato verze opravuje dva problémy, kdy vyhledání nebylo řádně provedeno a zlepšuje manipulaci s chybějícími symbolickými ikonami.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse retter to problemer hvor lokaliser ikke korrekt ville køre og forbedrer handling af manglende symbolske ikoner.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version behebt zwei Probleme, wo »locate« nicht richtig ausgeführt wurde und verbessert die Behandlung von fehlenden symbolischen Symbole.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση διορθώνει δύο ζητήματα, της τοποθεσίας που δεν μπορούσε να εκτελεστεί σωστά και βελτιώνει το χειρισμό των συμβολικών εικονιδίων που λείπουν.</p>
        <p lang="en_AU">This release fixes two issues where locate would not be properly executed and improves handling of missing symbolic icons.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión corrige dos problemas que impedían ejecutar la orden locate correctamente y mejora el manejo de la falta de iconos simbólicos.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek bilaketa ondo burutzen ez zen bi kasu konpontzen ditu eta falta diren ikono sinbolikoen kudeaketa hobetzen du.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä julkaisu korjaa kaksi ongelmaa jossa locate:a ei suoritettu oikein ja parantaa puuttuvien symboolisten kuvakkeiden käsittelyä.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version corrige deux problèmes dans lesquels la localisation ne serait pas exécutée correctement et améliore la gestion des icônes symboliques manquantes.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión arranxa dúas incidencias nos que a busca non se executaba axeitadamente e mellora o manexo das iconas simbólicas que faltan.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו מתקנת שתי בעיות בהן איתור לא היה מבוצע בצורה תקינה ומשפרת טיפול באיקונים סימבוליים חסרים.</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás két problémát old meg: a keresés nem mindig hajtódott végre rendesen, és a hiányzó szimbolikus ikonok kezelése is javítva lett.</p>
        <p lang="hy_AM">Տարբերակում ուղղուած է երկու խնդիր կապուած որոնման գործողութեան ճիշտ գործարկման եւ նշանային պատկերակների բացակայութեան հետ կապուած։</p>
        <p lang="hye">Տարբերակում ուղղուած է երկու խնդիր կապուած որոնման գործողութեան ճիշտ գործարկման եւ նշանային պատկերակների բացակայութեան հետ կապուած։</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini memperbaiki dua permasalahan di mana locate tidak dieksekusi dengan benar dan peningkatan penanganan ikon simbolis yang hilang.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio risolve due problemi per cui la localizzazione non era correttamente eseguita e migliora la gestione delle icone simboliche mancanti.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは、locate が正しく実行されない問題と欠けているシンボリックアイコンの処理を改善する問題が修正されています。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리즈는 locate가 제대로 실행되지 않고 누락 된 기호 아이콘의 처리를 향상시키는 두 가지 문제를 수정합니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Šioje laidoje yra ištaisoma regresija, kuomet nebuvo tinkamai vykdomas vietos nustatymas, o taip pat patobulinamas trūkstamų simbolinių piktogramų apdorojimas.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini membaiki dua isu yang lokasi tidak dilakukan dengan betul dan juga menambahbaik pengendalian ikon simbolik yang hilang.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen fikser to utfordringer hvor de ikke kunne bli korrekt kjørt og forbedrer behandling av mangel på symbolske ikoner.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze uitgave herstelt twee fouten waardoor 'locate' niet juist uitgevoerd werd en verbetert de omgang met ontbrekende symbolische pictogrammen.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie naprawia dwa przypadki, w których nie były poprawnie ustawiane położenia, i ulepsza obsługę brakujących ikon symbolicznych.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão corrige duas problemas em que o localizar não seria executado corretamente e melhora a manipulação da falta de ícones simbólicos.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão corrige duas questões em que localizar não seria executado corretamente e melhora a manipulação da falta ícones simbólicos.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск исправляет две проблемы, при которых не удавалось правильно выполнить locate, и улучшает работу с отсутствующими символическими значками.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie opravuje dva problémy, pri ktorých lokalizácia nebola vykonaná správne, a zlepšuje spracovanie chýbajúcich symbolických ikon.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja dve napaki, ko lociranje ni bilo pravilno izvedeno in ozboljša delo z manjkajočimi simbilnimi ikonami.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Kjo hedhje në qarkullim ndreq dy probleme, me të cilat gjetja e vendit nuk përmbushej si duhet, dhe përmirëson trajtimin e ikonave simbolike kur mungojnë.</p>
        <p lang="sr">Ово издање исправља две појаве у којима се locate не извршава како треба, и побољшава баратање недостајућим знаковним сличицама.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna version ordnar två problem då lokalisering inte gjordes på rätt sätt och förbättrar hantering av saknade symboliska ikoner.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้แก้ปัญหาสองรายการที่ทำให้ locate ไม่สามารถทำงานได้ และมีการปรับปรุงการจัดการไอคอนสัญลักษณ์ที่ขาดหาย</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm, locate'ın düzgün yürütülmeyeceği ve eksik simgesel simgelerin işlenmesini geliştirdiği iki sorunu giderir.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей реліз виправляє дві проблеми, де місцезнаходження не будуть належним чином оформленої і покращує обробку відсутніх значків символів.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此版本修复了定位无法正确执行的两个错误，并改进了对缺少符号图标的处理。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本修復了兩個問題，包含了 locate 可能無法正確執行，以及改善遺失符號圖示的處理。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.2" date="2014-03-09">
      <description>
        <p>This stable release improved the reliability of the password dialog, cleaned up unused code, and fixed potential issues with the list and item selection.</p>
        <p lang="ar">أدى هذا الإصدار المستقر إلى تحسين موثوقية مربع حوار كلمة المرور ، وتنظيف الشفرة غير المستخدمة ، وإصلاح المشكلات المحتملة في القائمة واختيار العنصر.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым стабільным выпуску павышана надзейнасць дыялога паролю, выдалены невыкарыстоўваемы код і выпраўленыя патэнцыйныя праблемы са спісам і выбарам элементаў.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Това стабилно освобождаване подобри надеждността на диалоговия прозорец за парола, изчистен е непотребен код и са фиксираните потенциални проблеми със списъка и избора на елементи.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta versió estable millora la fiabilitat del diàleg de la contrasenya, neteja el codi sense ús i corregeix possibles incidències amb la llista i la selecció d'elements.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Tato stabilní verze zlepšila spolehlivost dialogového okna pro zadávání hesla, byl pročištěn nepoužívaný kód a opraveny potenciální problémy se seznamem a výběrem položky.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne stabile udgivelse forbedrede pålideligheden af adgangskode-dialogen, ryddede op i ubrugt kode og rettede potentielle problemer med listen og valg af punkt.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese stabile Version verbessert die Zuverlässigkeit des Passwortdialoges, bereinigt nicht benutzten Code und behebt mögliche Probleme mit der Liste und Elementauswahl.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η σταθερή έκδοση βελτιώνει την αξιοπιστία στο παράθυρο διαλόγου του κωδικού, καθαρίζει αχρησιμοποίητο κώδικα, και διορθώνει πιθανά ζητήματα με την επιλογή λίστας και στοιχείων.</p>
        <p lang="en_AU">This stable release improved the reliability of the password dialog, cleaned up unused code, and fixed potential issues with the list and item selection.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta versión estable mejora la fiabilidad del diálogo de la contraseña, elimina código no utilizado y corrige posibles problemas con la lista y la selección de elementos.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio egonkor honek pasahitz leihotxoaren fidagarritasuna hobetzen du, erabili gabeko kodea kentzen du eta zerrenda eta elementuen hautaketarekin arazo potentzialak konpontzen ditu.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä vakaa julkaisu parantaa salasanaikkunan luotettavuutta, poistettu käyttämätöntä koodia, ja mahdolliset ongelmat listan ja kohteiden valinnassa korjattu.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version stable a amélioré la fiabilité de la boîte de dialogue du mot de passe, nettoyé le code inutilisé, et corrigé les problèmes potentiels lors de la sélection des listes et des éléments.</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión estábel mellorou a lexibilidade do diálogo do contrasinal, limpou código que non se usaba e arranxou incidencias potenciais coa selección de listas e elementos.</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה יציבה זו שיפרה את האמינות של דו־שיח סיסמאות, ניקתה קוד לא בשימוש, ותיקנה בעיות פוטנציאליות בבחירת רשימות ופריטים.</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a stabil kiadás javította a jelszó párbeszédablak megbízhatóságát, kitisztította a nem használt kódot, és lehetséges problémákat javított a lista- és elemkiválasztásban.</p>
        <p lang="hy_AM">Այս կայուն տարբերակում գաղտնաբառի պատուհանի հուսանելիութիւնն աւելացել է, մաքրուել է չգործարկուող այլագիրը եւ ուղղուել է ցուցակի ու տարրերի ընտրութեան հետ կապուած խնդիրները։</p>
        <p lang="hye">Այս կայուն տարբերակում գաղտնաբառի պատուհանի հուսանելիութիւնն աւելացել է, մաքրուել է չգործարկուող այլագիրը եւ ուղղուել է ցուցակի ու տարրերի ընտրութեան հետ կապուած խնդիրները։</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis stabil ini meningkatkan reliabilitas dialog kata sandi, membersihkan kode yang tidak digunakan, dan memperbaiki permasalahan potensial dengan daftar dan pemilihan item.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio stabile migliora l'affidabilità della finestra di dialogo per la password, elimina codice non usato e risolve potenziali problemi con la selezione di oggetti e liste.</p>
        <p lang="ja">この安定版のリリースでは、パスワードダイアログの信頼性を改善し、未使用のコードを削除し、リスト選択とアイテム選択に関する潜在的な問題を修正しました。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이번 안정적인 릴리즈는 암호 대화상자의 신뢰성을 향상시키고, 사용되지 않는 코드를 청소하였으며, 잠재적인 목록과 요소의 선택 문제를 수정하였습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Ši stabili laida pagerino slaptažodžio dialogo patikimumą, buvo išvalytas nebenaudojamas kodas ir ištaisytos potencialios, su sąrašo ir elemento pasirinkimu susijusios, klaidos.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran stabil ini menambahbaik kebolehpercayaan dialog kata laluan, membuang kod yang tidak diperlukan, dan membaiki isu-isu dengan pemilihan senarai dan item.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne stabile utgivelse forbedrer stabiliteten på passord dialogvinduet, rydder opp i ubrukt kode og fikser potensielle utfordringer med liste og filvalg.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze stabiele uitgave heeft de betrouwbaarheid van het dialoogscherm voor het wachtwoord verbeterd, ongebruikte code opgeruimd, en mogelijke problemen met de selectie van lijst en element verholpen.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To stabilne wydanie poprawiło niezawodność okna dialogowego hasła, wyczyściło nieużywany kod i naprawiło potencjalne problemy z listą i wyborem elementów.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão estável melhorou a fiabilidade da caixa de diálogo da palavra-passe, limpou código não utilizado e corrigiu potenciais problemas com a lista e seleção de itens.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão estável melhorou a confiabilidade do diálogo de senha, limpou código não utilizado, e corrige possíveis problemas com a lista e seleção de itens.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот стабильный выпуск улучшил надёжность диалога паролей, очистил неиспользуемый код и исправил потенциальную проблему с выбором списка и объектов.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto stabilné vydanie vylepšuje spoľahlivosť dialógového okna s heslom. Bol vyčistený nepoužívaný kód a opravené potencionálne chyby s výberom zoznamu a položky.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta stabilna izdaja izboljša zanesljivosti dialog z gesli, očisti neuporabljeno kodo in popravlja možne težave s szenami in izbrianjem predmetov.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Me këtë hedhje e qëndrueshme në qarkullim u përmirësua dialogu i fjalëkalimeve, u pastrua kod i papërdorur, dhe u ndreqën probleme potenciale me përzgjedhje listash dhe objektesh.</p>
        <p lang="sr">У овом стабилном издању је побољшана поузданост прозорчета лозинке, очишћен вишак кода, и исправљене могуће потешкоће са списком и избором ставки.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna stabila version förbättrade lösenordsdialogens tillförlitlighet, rensade upp oanvänd kod, och ordnade eventuella problem med list- och objektmarkering.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นเสถียรรุ่นนี้มีการปรับปรุงความแน่นอนของการทำงานของกล่องโต้ตอบรหัสผ่าน กำจัดโค้ดที่ไม่ใช้แล้ว และแก้ปัญหาที่มีแนวโน้มจะเกิดเกี่ยวกับรายชื่อและการเลือกรายการ</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu kararlı sürüm, şifre iletişim kutusunun güvenilirliğini geliştirdi, kullanılmayan kodları temizledi ayrıca liste ve madde seçimi ile ilgili potansiyel sabit sorunlar düzeltildi.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Це стабільний реліз підвищує надійність діалогу пароля, очищено невикористаний код, і полагоджені потенційні проблеми зі списком і вибору елементів.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">此稳定版本提高了密码对话框的可靠性，清除了未使用的代码，并修复了列表和项目选择的潜在问题。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個穩定版本改善了密碼視窗的可靠性，清理無用的程式碼，並修復了清單與項目選取的潛在問題。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.1" date="2014-02-27">
      <description>
        <p>This release fixed a potential security issue with program startup and fixed a regression with selecting multiple items.</p>
        <p lang="ar">هذا الإصدار عمل على إصلاح مشكلة أمنية محتملة مع بدء تشغيل البرنامج وإصلاح انهياره مع اختيار عناصر متعددة.</p>
        <p lang="be">У гэтым выпуску выпраўленыя патэнцыйная праблема бяспекі пры запуску праграмы і рэгрэсія выбару некалькіх элементаў.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Тази версия отстрани потенциален проблем със сигурността при стартиране на програмата и фиксира регресия с избиране на няколко елемента.</p>
        <p lang="ca">Aquesta actualització soluciona un possible problema de seguretat amb l'inici del programa i corregeix una regressió en seleccionar múltiples elements.</p>
        <p lang="cs">Toto vydání opravuje potenciální bezpečnostní problém se spuštěním programu a opravuje regresi s výběrem více položek.</p>
        <p lang="da">Denne udgivelse rettede et potentielt sikkerhedsproblem med programopstart og rettede en regression med valg af flere punkter.</p>
        <p lang="de">Diese Version behebt eine mögliches Sicherheitsproblem beim Programmstart und einen Rückschritt bei der Auswahl mehrerer Elemente.</p>
        <p lang="el">Αυτή η έκδοση διορθώνει ένα πιθανό ζήτημα ασφάλειας με την εκκίνηση του προγράμματος και διορθώνει ένα σφάλμα που επανεμφανίστηκε σε σχέση με την επιλογή πολλών στοιχείων.</p>
        <p lang="en_AU">This release fixed a potential security issue with program startup and fixed a regression with selecting multiple items.</p>
        <p lang="es">Esta actualización soluciona un posible problema de seguridad con el inicio del programa y corrige una regresión al seleccionar múltiples elementos.</p>
        <p lang="eu">Bertsio honek programa hasieraren segurtasun arrisku handi bat konpontzen du eta baita hainbat elementu hautatzeko atzerapen bat ere.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Tämä julkaisuu korjaa mahdollisen turvaongelman ohjelman käynnistyksessä ja korjaa regression useiden kohteiden valinnassa.</p>
        <p lang="fr">Cette version a corrigé une faille de sécurité potentielle dans le programme de démarrage ainsi qu’une régression avec la sélection multiples d’éléments .</p>
        <p lang="gl">Esta versión arranxou unha incidencia de seguranza potencial no inicio do programa e arranxou unha regresión ao seleccionar varios elementos</p>
        <p lang="he">גרסה זו תיקנה בעית אבטחה פוטנציאלית בהפעלת התוכנה ותיקנה באג רגרסיה בבחירת פריטים מרובים.</p>
        <p lang="hu">Ez a kiadás lehetséges biztonsági problémákt javított a program indításakor, és kijavított egy, több elem kiválasztását érintő, regressziót.</p>
        <p lang="hy_AM">Տարբերակում լուծուած են պաշտպանութեան սխալները, ուղղած է հետադարձը կապը ընտրուած բազմակի տարրերի հետ։</p>
        <p lang="hye">Տարբերակում լուծուած են պաշտպանութեան սխալները, ուղղած է հետադարձը կապը ընտրուած բազմակի տարրերի հետ։</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis ini memperbaiki sebuah permasalahan keamanan potensial ketika memulai program, dan memperbaiki sebuah regresi dengan pemilihan beberapa item.</p>
        <p lang="it">Questo rilascio risolve un potenziale problema di sicurezza all'avvio del programma e risolve una regressione con la selezione di oggetti multipli.</p>
        <p lang="ja">このリリースでは、起動時の潜在的なセキュリティの問題を修正しました。また、複数項目の選択に関する問題についても修正しました。</p>
        <p lang="ko">이 릴리즈는 프로그램이 시작될 때 잠재적인 보안 문제를 해결하였고 여러개를 선택 할 때의 회귀문제를 해결 하였습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Šioje laidoje ištaisyta potenciali saugumo problema, susijusi su programos paleidimu, o taip pat ištaisyta, su kelių elementų pasirinkimu susijusi, regresija.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran ini membaiki isu keselamatan yang mungkin berlaku ketika permulaan program dan juga membaiki regresi ketika memilih item berbilang.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne utgivelsen fikser en potensiell sikkerhetsutfordring med oppstart av programmet og fikser en regresjon ved valg av flere elementer.</p>
        <p lang="nl">Deze uitgave heeft een mogelijk veiligheidsprobleem hersteld inzake programma-opstart en heeft een regressiefout hersteld betreffende het selecteren van meerdere elementen.</p>
        <p lang="pl">To wydanie naprawiło potencjalny problem z bezpieczeństwem podczas uruchamiania programu i naprawiło regresję z wyborem wielu elementów.</p>
        <p lang="pt">Esta versão corrigiu um problema de segurança com a inicialização do programa e fixa uma regressão com a seleção de vários itens.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">Esta versão corrigiu um problema de segurança com a inicialização do programa e corrige uma regressão com a seleção de vários itens.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Этот выпуск исправил потенциальную проблему безопасности при запуске программы и регрессию при выборе нескольких объектов.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Toto vydanie opravuje potencionálnu bezpečnostnú zraniteľnosť pri spúšťaní programu a tiež opravuje pád programu pri výbere viacerých položiek.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Ta izdaja popravlja potencialen varnostni problem s zagonom programa in odpravlja napako pri izbiranju več vrstic.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Me këtë hedhje në qarkullim u ndreq një problem potencial sigurie me nisjen e programit dhe ndreq një hap mbrapa në përzgjedhjen e shumë zërave njëherësh.</p>
        <p lang="sr">У овом издању су исправљене могући безбедносни пропусти са самопокретањем програма и губитак старих могућности избора више ставки.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Denna version ordnade ett möjligt säkerhetsproblem med programstart och ordnade en regression med markering av flera objekt.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นนี้แก้ปัญหาที่มีแนวโน้มจะเกิดเกี่ยวกับระบบรักษาความปลอดภัยขณะโปรแกรมเริ่มทำงาน และแก้ปัญหาความถดถอยเกี่ยวกับการเลือกหลายรายการ</p>
        <p lang="tr">Bu sürüm, programın başlatılmasıyla ilgili olası güvenlik sorununu düzeltti ve çoklu öge seçiminde gerilemeyi düzeltti.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Цей реліз полагодив потенційну проблему безпеки з запуску програми і виправлена регресія з можливістю вибору декількох елементів.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">本次更新修复了程序启动时的潜在安全问题，并修复了选择多个搜索结果的回归。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">這個版本修復程式啟動時的潛在安全性問題，並修復選取多個項目的問題。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2014-02-04">
      <description>
        <p>The first release in the 1.0.x series introduced a refreshed interface and fixed a number of long-standing bugs. Improvements to the default permissions eliminated a number of warnings when packaging for distributions. Accessibility was enhanced as all strings have been made translatable and keyboard accelerators have been improved.</p>
        <p lang="ar">أول إصدار في سلسلة 1.0x قدم واجهة منتعشة وأصلح عددا من الأخطاء منذ فترة طويلة. تحسينات على الأذونات الافتراضية القضاء على عدد من التحذيرات عند التعبئة للتوزيعات. تم تعزيز إمكانية الوصول حيث تم جعل جميع السلاسل قابلة للترجمة وتحسين مسرعات لوحة المفاتيح.</p>
        <p lang="be">У першым выпуск серыі 1.0.x прадстаўлены абноўлены інтэрфейс і выпраўлены шэраг даўніх хібаў. Пераразмеркаванне прадвызначаных дазволаў дапамагло ліквідаваць шэраг папярэджанняў пры стварэнні пакункаў. Былі палепшаныя адмысловыя магчымасці: усе радкі можна перакласці і пераробленыя паскаральнікі клавіятуры.</p>
        <p lang="bg">Първата версия в серията 1.0.x въведе обновения интерфейс и отстрани редица отдавнашни бъгове. Подобренията на правата по подразбиране премахнаха няколко предупреждения при пакетите за дистрибуциите. Достъпността бе подобрена, тъй като всички нишки бяха направени прехвърлими и клавишните ускорители бяха подобрени.</p>
        <p lang="ca">La primera versió de la sèrie 1.0.x introdueix una interfície renovada i corregeix una sèrie d'errors antics. Les millores en els permisos predeterminats han eliminat una sèrie d'advertències en empaquetar per a les distribucions. L'accessibilitat s'ha millorat, ja que totes les cadenes s'han fet traduïbles, i s'han millorat les tecles de drecera.</p>
        <p lang="cs">První vydání v sérii 1.0.x  představilo aktualizované rozhraní a opravenou řadu dlouhodobých chyb. Zlepšení ve výchozím oprávnění odstraňuje mnohá varování při balíčkování pro distribuci. Dostupnost byla rozšířena umožněním přeložit všechny texty a byly vylepšeny klávesové zkratky.</p>
        <p lang="da">Den første udgivelse i 1.0.x-serien introducerede en genopfrisket grænseflade og rettede et antal fejl som har været der i lang tid. Forbedringer til standardtilladelser eliminerer et antal advarsler ved pakning af distributioner. Tilgængelighed blev forbedret eftersom alle strenge nu kan oversættes og tastaturgenveje er blevet forbedret.</p>
        <p lang="de">Bei der ersten Veröffentlichung in der 1.0.x-Serie erscheint mit einer aufgefrischten Oberfläche und behebt eine Reihe von langjährigen Fehlern. Verbesserungen der Standardberechtigungen beseitigt eine Reihe von Warnungen, während der Paketierung für Distributionen. Die Barrierefreiheit wurde verbessert, da alle Seiten übersetzbar gemacht wurden und Tastenkürzel verbessert wurden.</p>
        <p lang="el">Η πρώτη έκδοση της σειράς 1.0.x εισήγαγε μία ανανεωμένη διεπαφή και διόρθωσε πολλά σφάλματα που υπήρχαν πολύ καιρό. Οι βελτιώσεις στα προεπιλεγμένα δικαιώματα εξάλειψαν μια σειρά από προειδοποιήσεις όταν το πρόγραμμα συσκευαζόταν για διανομές. Ενισχύθηκε η προσβασιμότητα καθώς όλα τα κείμενα έχουν γίνει μεταφράσιμα και έχουν βελτιωθεί οι συντομεύσεις πληκτρολογίου.</p>
        <p lang="en_AU">The first release in the 1.0.x series introduced a refreshed interface and fixed a number of long-standing bugs. Improvements to the default permissions eliminated a number of warnings when packaging for distributions. Accessibility was enhanced as all strings have been made translatable and keyboard accelerators have been improved.</p>
        <p lang="es">La primera versión de la serie 1.0.x introduce una interfaz renovada y corrige una serie de errores antiguos. Las mejoras en los permisos por defecto han eliminado una serie de avisos al empaquetar para las distribuciones. La accesibilidad se ha mejorado, ya que todas las cadenas se han hecho traducibles, y se han mejorado las teclas aceleradoras.</p>
        <p lang="eu">1.0.x seriearen lehen bertsioak interfaze berri bat sartzen du eta hainbat arazo zahar konpontzen ditu. Banaketetarako paketatzerakoan abisu ugari kendu dira baimen lehenetsietan egindako hobekuntzekin. Irisgarritasuna areagotu da hitz guztiak itzulgarriak bihurtuz eta teklatu bizkortzaileak hobetu dira.</p>
        <p lang="fi">Ensimmäinen julkaisu 1.0.x-sarjassa toi piristetyn käyttöliittymän ja korjasi monta pitkäaikaista bugia. Parannukset oletuslupiin poistivat monta varoitusta kun sovellusta pakattiin jakeluihin. Helppokäyttöisyys parani koska kaikki merkkijonot ovat käännettävissä ja näppäimistökiihdyttäjät parannettiin.</p>
        <p lang="fr">La première version de la série 1.0.x a introduit une nouvelle interface et a corrigé un certain nombre de bogues de longue date. Les améliorations apportées aux autorisations par défaut ont supprimé un certain nombre d’avertissements lors de l’empaquetage pour les distributions. L’accessibilité a été améliorée, toutes les chaînes ont été rendues traduisibles et les raccourcis clavier ont été améliorés.</p>
        <p lang="gl">A primeira versión da serie 1.0.x presentou unha interface anovada e arranxou moitos fallos antigos. As melloras nos permisos predeterminados eliminaron moitos avisos ao empaquetar para as distribucións. Mellorouse a accesibilidade, xa que todas as cadeas son traducíbeis e os aceleradores de teclado recibiron melloras</p>
        <p lang="he">הגרסה הראשונה בסדרה 1.0.x הכניסה לשימוש ממשק מחודש ותיקנה מספר באגים ישנים. שיפורים בהרשאות ברירת מחדל ביטלו מספר אזהרות בעת אריזה להפצות. נגישות עברה העשרה כאשר כל המחרוזות נהפכו להיות ניתנות לתרגום וקיצורי דרך במקלדת עברו שיפור.</p>
        <p lang="hu">Az első kiadás az 1.0.x sorozatban frissített felülettel érkezik, és számos régóta fennálló hibát javít. Az alapértelmezett jogosultságok fejlesztései számos figyelmeztetést szüntettek meg a disztribúciókba csomagoláskor. Az akadálymentesség javítva lett, mivel minden szöveg fordíthatóvá lett téve, és a gyorsbillentyűk is fejlesztve lettek.</p>
        <p lang="hy_AM">1.0x֊ի առաջին տարբերակում թարմացուել է ծրագրի միջերեսը եւ ուղղուել են որոշ խնդիրներ։ Լռելեայն արտաւնութիւնների փոփոխութիւնների արդիւնքում վերացուել են մի շարք խնդիրներ փաթեթաւորման հետ կապուած։ Տողերի թարգմանելի դառնալու արդիւնքում ընդլայնուել է հասանելիութիւնը, մշակուել են ստեղնաշարի արագացուցիչները։</p>
        <p lang="hye">1.0x֊ի առաջին տարբերակում թարմացուել է ծրագրի միջերեսը եւ ուղղուել են որոշ խնդիրներ։ Լռելեայն արտաւնութիւնների փոփոխութիւնների արդիւնքում վերացուել են մի շարք խնդիրներ փաթեթաւորման հետ կապուած։ Տողերի թարգմանելի դառնալու արդիւնքում ընդլայնուել է հասանելիութիւնը, մշակուել են ստեղնաշարի արագացուցիչները։</p>
        <p lang="id">Rilis pertama pada seri 1.0.x memperkenalkan sebuah antarmuka yang segar dan memperbaiki sejumlah kutu yang sudah lama ada. Peningkatan pada perizinan baku mengurangi sejumlah peringatan ketika memaketkan untuk distribusi. Aksesibilitas telah ditingkatkan dengan semua string dapat diterjemahkan, dan akselerator papan tik telah ditingkatkan.</p>
        <p lang="it">Il primo rilascio della serie 1.0.x introduce un'interfaccia ridisegnata e risolve una serie di vecchi bug. I miglioramenti ai permessi predefiniti eliminano molti avvisi durante il confezionamento per le distribuzioni. Sono state migliorate l'accessibilità, rendendo tutte le stringhe traducibili, e le scorciatoie da tastiera.</p>
        <p lang="ja">1.0.xシリーズの最初のリリースでは、インターフェースを刷新し、長年あったバグを修正しました。デフォルトのパーミッションを改善したことでディストリビューション用のパッケージングの際に出る警告が減りました。アクセシビリティも強化され、すべての文字列が翻訳可能となり、キーボードショートカットも改善されました。</p>
        <p lang="ko">1.0.x 시리즈의 첫 번째 릴리스에서는 새로 고쳐진 인터페이스가 도입되어 오랫동안 계속되는 많은 버그가 수정되었습니다. 기본 사용 권한을 향상 시키면서 배포판에 프로그램을 포함하면서 여러 가지 경고가 제거되었습니다. 모든 문자열을 번역 하였고 키보드 단축키가 향상되어 접근 가능성이 향상되었습니다.</p>
        <p lang="lt">Pirma laida 1.0.x serijoje pristatė atnaujintą sąsają ir daugelį ištaisytų ilgai trukusių problemų. Numatytųjų leidimų patobulinimai pašalino daugybę įspėjimų, atsirandančių pakavimo distribucijoms metu.</p>
        <p lang="ms">Keluaran pertama dalam siri 1.0.x memperkenalkan antaramuka serba baharu dan beberapa pembaikan pepijat lama. Penambahbaikan pada keizinan lalai membuang sebilangan amaran ketika mempakej distribusi. Kebolehcapaian telah dipertingkatkan yang mana semua rentetan boleh diterjemah dan pemecut papan kekunci telah ditambah baik.</p>
        <p lang="nb">Denne første utgivelsen i 1.0.x serien introduserer et oppdatert grensesnitt og fikser en mengde utestående feil. Forbedringer knyttet til de standard rettigheter fjernet en rekke advarsler ved distribusjonsinnpakkingen. Tilgjengelighet ble forbedret når alt ble oversatt og keyboard accelerators har blitt forbedret.</p>
        <p lang="nl">De eerste uitgave in de 1.0.x-reeks introduceerde een opgefriste gebruikersschil en herstelde een aantal oude fouten. Verbeteringen inzake de standaardrechten elimineerde een aantal waarschuwingen bij het verpakken voor distributies. Toegankelijkheid werd vergroot doordat alle tekenreeksen vertaalbaar zijn gemaakt en doordat versnellingstoetsen voor het toetsenbord zijn verbeterd.</p>
        <p lang="pl">Pierwsze wydanie z serii 1.0.x wprowadziło odświeżony interfejs i naprawiło wiele długotrwałych błędów. Ulepszenia domyślnych uprawnień wyeliminowały pewną liczbę ostrzeżeń podczas pakowania do dystrybucji. Ulepszono dostępność, ponieważ wszystkie ciągi znaków mogą teraz być przetłumaczone, a akceleratory klawiatury zostały ulepszone.</p>
        <p lang="pt">O primeiro lançamento da série 1.0.x introduziu uma interface renovada e fixa um número de erros de longa data. Melhorias para as permissões padrão eliminaram uma série de avisos quando construindo pacotes para distribuições. A acessibilidade foi reforçada e todas as sequências de caracteres foram tornadas traduzíveis e os aceleradores de teclado foram melhorados.</p>
        <p lang="pt_BR">O primeiro lançamento da série 1.0.x introduziu uma interface renovada e corrige uma série de bugs de longa data. Melhorias para as permissões padrão eliminou uma série de avisos quando empacotado para as distribuições. A acessibilidade foi reforçada como todas as cordas foram feitas traduzível e aceleradores de teclado foram melhorados.</p>
        <p lang="ru">Первый выпуск в серии 1.0.x представил обновлённый интерфейс и исправил несколько давних ошибок. Улучшения в разрешениях по умолчанию позволили избавиться от некоторого количества предупреждений при сборке пакетов для дистрибутивов. Все строки программы стали доступными для перевода, улучшено использование сочетаний клавиш.</p>
        <p lang="sk">Prvé vydanie zo série 1.0.x zaviedlo aktualizované rozhranie a opravilo množstvo dlhotrvajúcich chýb. Vylepšenia predvolených povolení odstránili množstvo upozornení pri vytváraní balíkov pre distribúcie. Zlepšila sa prístupnosť, pretože sa stali preložiteľnými všetky reťazce, a boli vylepšené klávesové akcelerátory.</p>
        <p lang="sl">Prva v vrsti 1.0.x izdaj prinaša osvežen vmesnik in popravlja šetilne stare hrošče. Izboljšave pri privzetih pravicah, so odpravile številna opozorila pri pakiranju za različne distribucije. Dostopnost je bila izboljšana z možnostjo prevajanja vseh nizov, izboljšana pa je bila tudi pohitritev tipkovnice.</p>
        <p lang="sq">Me hedhjen e parë në qarkullim për seritë 1.0.x sillet një ndërfaqe e rifreskuar dhe ndreqen një numër të metash të pranishme për një kohë të gjatë. Përmirësime te lejet parazgjedhje eliminuan një numër sinjalizimesh gjatë paketimit të programit për shpërndarje të ndryshme. Është thelluar përdorshmëria, pasi krejt vargjet tani janë të përkthyeshëm dhe janë përmirësuar edhe shkurtoret e tastierës.</p>
        <p lang="sr">У овом издању низа 1.0.x је представљено ново сучеље и исправљен одређени број упорних старих грешака. Побољшано је управљање подразумеваним овлашћењима које је отклонило појаву упозорења при прављењу дистрибуција. Приступачност је побољшана, свим нискама је омогућен превод и пречице дугмади су побољшане.</p>
        <p lang="sv">Den första versionen i 1.0.x serien introducerar ett uppdaterat gränssnitt och rättar till ett antal gamla fel. Förbättringar av standardbehörigheterna eliminerade ett antal varningar vid paketering för distributioner. Tillgängligheten förbättrades i och med att alla strängar har gjorts översättningsbara och tangentbordsgenvägar har förbättrats.</p>
        <p lang="th">รุ่นแรกในชุด 1.0.x มีการปรับเปลี่ยนส่วนติดต่อผู้ใช้ใหม่ และแก้บั๊กที่ค้างคามานานหลายรายการ การปรับปรุงการกำหนดสิทธิ์โดยปริยายของแฟ้มได้ขจัดคำเตือนต่างๆ ที่เกิดขึ้นขณะสร้างแพกเกจสำหรับชุดจัดแจก มีการปรับปรุงการเข้าถึงของผู้ใช้ด้วยการทำให้ทุกข้อความสามารถแปลเป็นภาษาท้องถิ่นได้ และปุ่มลัดแป้นพิมพ์ก็มีการปรับปรุงด้วย</p>
        <p lang="tr">1.0.x serisindeki ilk sürüm, yenilenmiş arabirim sundu ve uzun süredir süren kimi hataları düzeltti. Öntanımlı izinlerdeki iyileştirmeler, dağıtımlar için paketlerken kimi uyarıları ortadan kaldırdı. Tüm dizeler çevrilebilir hale getirildiğinden ve klavye hızlandırıcılarının geliştirildiği için erişilebilirlik geliştirildi.</p>
        <p lang="uk">Перший випуск в серії 1.0.x представлено оновлений інтерфейс і виправлений ряд застарілих помилок. Покращення дозволу за замовчуванням, усунені ряд попереджень при пакуванні для розподілів. Доступність була збільшена, всі рядки були зроблені перекладним і скорочені клавіші були покращені.</p>
        <p lang="zh_CN">1.0.x 系列的第一个版本引入了一个全新界面并修复了许多长期存在的错误。对默认权限的改进消除了许多为发行打包时的警告。 由于所有字符串都可以被翻译并且键盘加速器被改善，可访问性得以增强。</p>
        <p lang="zh_TW">1.0.x 系列的第一個版本引入了修正過的界面，並修復了許多長期存在的臭蟲，在散佈版搭包時許多的警告也由更改預設權限而消除了。無障礙程度也因為所有字串都可以翻譯，且鍵盤加速器也被改善而強化。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>