<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <pkgname>xfce.ristretto</pkgname>
  <icon width="64" type="cached" height="64">org.xfce.ristretto.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">org.xfce.ristretto.png</icon>
  <id>org.xfce.ristretto</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="bg">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="da">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="de">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="el">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="es">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="et">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="eu">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="fr">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="gl">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="he">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="id">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="it">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="ja">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="ko">리스트레또</name>
  <name lang="lt">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="ms">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="nb">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="nl">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="pl">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="pt">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="ro">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="ru">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="sk">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="sl">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="sq">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="sr">Ристрето</name>
  <name lang="sv">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="tr">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">Ristretto</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">Ristretto</name>
  <summary>Fast and lightweight image viewer</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Бърза и лека програма за преглед на изображения</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Hurtig og letvægts billedfremviser</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Schneller und leichtgewichtiger Bildbetrachter</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Γρήγορο και ελαφρύ πρόγραμμα αναπαραγωγής εικόνων</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Visor de imágenes rápido y ligero</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Lihtne ja kiire pildinäitaja</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Irudi ikustatzaile azkar eta arina</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Visionneur d’images rapide et léger</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Visor de imaxes rápido e lixeiro</summary>
  <summary lang="he">מציג תמונות מהיר וקל משקל</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Penilik gambar yang cepat dan ringan</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Un visualizzatore di immagini veloce e leggero</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">高速で軽量な画像ビューア</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">빠르고 가벼운 그림 보기 프로그램</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Greita ir supaprastinta paveikslų žiūryklė</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Pelihat imej yang ringan dan pantas</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Raskt og ressursvennlig program for bildevisning</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Snelle lichtgewicht-afbeeldingenkijker</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Szybka i lekka przeglądarka obrazów</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Visualizador de imagens rápido e leve</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Visualizador de imagens rápido e leve</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Быстрая и легковесная программа просмотра изображений</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Rýchly a nenáročný prehliadač obrázkov</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Lahek in hiter pregledovalnik slik</summary>
  <summary lang="sq">Parës figurash i shpejtë dhe i peshës së lehtë</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Брз и лаган прегледник слика</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Snabb och lättviktig bildvisare</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Hızlı ve hafif resim görüntüleyici</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">快速轻量的图像查看器 </summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">快速且輕量的圖片檢視程式</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Ristretto is an image viewer for the Xfce desktop environment.</p>
    <p>The Ristretto Image Viewer is an application that can be used to view and scroll through images, run a slideshow of images, open images with other applications like an image-editor or configure an image as the desktop wallpaper.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>Ristretto هو عارض صور لسطح مكتب إكسفسي.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ast">
    <p>Ristretto ye un visor d'imáxenes pal entornu d'escritoriu Xfce.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Ristretto — хуткая і лёгкаважная праграма для прагляду выяў для працоўнага асяроддзя Xfce.</p>
    <p>Праграма для прагляду выяў Ristretto можа паказваць і прагортваць выявы, ствараць з выяў слайд-шоў, перанакіроўваць выявы ў іншыя праграмы, напрыклад рэдактары і рабіць выявы шпалерамі працоўнага стала.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Ristretto е бърза и лека програма за преглед на изображения за работната среда XFCE</p>
    <p>С програмата за преглед на изображения Ristretto можете да преглеждате Вашите изображенията, да превъртате списъка с изображения, да стартирате слайд шоу, да отваряте изображенията с друга програма, като редактор на изображения, както и да задавате изображение, като фон на работният плот.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Ristretto és un visualitzador d'imatges per a l'entorn d'escriptori Xfce.</p>
    <p>El visualitzador d'imatges Ristretto és una aplicació que es pot utilitzar per a la visualització i per al desplaçament per les imatges, per a l'execució d'una presentació de diapositives, per a l'obriment de les imatges amb altres aplicacions com ara un editor o per a la configuració d'una imatge com a fons de l'escriptori.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Ristretto je prohlížeč obrázků pro pracovní prostředí Xfce.</p>
    <p>Prohlížeč obrázků Ristretto je aplikace pro prohlížení a procházení obrázků, spuštění prezentace obrázků, otevírání obrázků v jiných aplikacích, např. v editoru obrázků, nebo pro nastavení obrázku jako tapety pracovní plochy.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Ristretto er en billedfremviser til Xfce-skrivebordsmiljøet.</p>
    <p>Ristretto Billedfremviseren er et program som kan bruges til at vise og gennemse billeder, køre et diasshow af billeder, åbne billeder med andre programmer såsom et billedredigeringsprogram eller konfigurere et billede som et skrivebordstapet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Ristretto ist ein Bildbetrachter für die Xfce-Arbeitsumgebung.</p>
    <p>Mit dem Ristretto-Bildbetrachter können Bilder angezeigt, durchgeblättert und als Diaschau angezeigt werden. Außerdem können Bilder mit anderen Programmen wie Bildbearbeitungsanwendungen geöffnet oder als Hintergrundbild eingestellt werden.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το ristretto είναι ένας διαχειριστής εικόνων για το γραφικό περιβάλλον xfce.</p>
    <p> Η εφαρμογή Προβολής Εικόνων Ristretto μπορεί να χρησιμοποιηθεί για την προβολή και εναλλαγή εικόνων, την προβολή μιας παρουσίασης εικόνων, το άνοιγμα εικόνων με άλλες εφαρμογές όπως ένας επεξεργαστής εικόνων ή για τον ορισμό μιας εικόνας ως φόντο επιφάνειας εργασίας.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_AU">
    <p>Ristretto is an image viewer for the Xfce desktop environment.</p>
    <p>The Ristretto Image Viewer is an application that can be used to view and scroll through images, run a slideshow of images, open images with other applications like an image-editor or configure an image as the desktop wallpaper.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Ristretto is an image viewer for the Xfce desktop environment.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Ristretto es un visor de imágenes para el entorno de escritorio Xfce.</p>
    <p>El visor de imágenes de Ristretto es una aplicación que puede usarse para ver imágenes y desplazarse entre las imágenes, ejecutar un pase de diapositivas, abrir las imágenes con otras aplicaciones como un editor o configurar una imagen como fondo del escritorio.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Ristretto on pildinäitaja Xfce töölauakeskkonna jaoks.</p>
    <p>Ristretto on rakendus, millega saad vaadata ja sirvida pilte, käivitada esitlust, avada pildifaile muudes rakendustes nagu näiteks pildiredaktor või määrata pilti töölaua taustapildiks.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Ristretto Xfce idazmahai inguruneko irudi-ikustatzaile bat da.</p>
    <p>Ristretto argazki ikustatzailea irudiak ikusi eta haien artean mugitu, diaporama bat ikusi, irudiak editatzeko gai den beste aplikazioekin ireki edo argazki bat mahaigain-irudi gisa ezartzeko erabili daitekeen aplikazio bat da.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Ristretto on kuvakatselin Xfce-työpöytäympäristöön.</p>
    <p>Ristretto-kuvankatselin on sovellus, jota voidaan käyttää kuvien katsomiseen ja selaamiseen, diaesitysten näyttämiseen, kuvien avaamiseen muilla sovelluksilla, kuten kuvankäsittelyohjelmilla tai määrittämään kuva työpöydän taustakuvaksi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Ristretto est un visionneur d’images pour l’environnement de bureau Xfce.</p>
    <p>Le visionneur d’images Ristretto est une application qui peut être utilisée pour visionner et faire défiler des images, les ouvrir dans d’autres applications comme un éditeur d’images, ou les définir comme fond d’écran.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Ristretto é un visor de imaxes para o contorno de escritorio Xfce.</p>
    <p>O Visor de Imaxes Ristretto é un aplicativo que se pode empregar para ver imaxes, reproducir unha presentación de imaxes, abrir imaxes con outras aplicacións, como un editor de imaxes, ou configurar unha imaxe como fondo de pantalla.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>‏Ristretto הוא מציג תמונות עבור סביבת שולחן עבודה Xfce.</p>
    <p>מציג התמונות Ristretto הוא תוכנה הניתנת לשימוש לצפייה וגלילה של תמונות, להרצת מצגת, לפתיחת תמונות עם תוכנות אחרות כמו עורך תמונות או להגדרת תמונה כרקע שולחן העבודה.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Ristretto je preglednik slika za  Xfce radno okruženje.</p>
    <p>Ristretto preglednik slika je aplikacija koja se može koristiti za otvaranje i pregledavanje slika. Slike se mogu pregledavati kao prezentacija, otvariti u uređivaču slika ili postaviti kao pozadina radne površine.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>A Ristretto egy képmegjelenítő az Xfce asztali környezethez.</p>
    <p>A Ristretto képmegjelenítő képek megtekintésére, köztük görgetésére, más alkalmazásokkal történő megnyitására (pl. képszerkesztők), háttérként beállítására vagy diavetítés futtatására szolgáló alkalmazás.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hy_AM">
    <p>Ristretto — պատկերների ցուցադրման ծրագիր է, Xfce-ի աշխատասեղանի միջավայրի համար։</p>
    <p>Ristretto պատկերի ցուցադրիչը ծրագիր է, որը կարող է աւգտագործուել պատկերների դիտման, տեսասահիկի միացման, պատկերներն այլ ծրագրերով բացելու համար, աւրինակ՝ պատկերների խմբագիրչը կամ պատկերի կազմաձեւումը, որպէս աշխատասեղանի պաստառ։</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hye">
    <p>Ristretto — պատկերների ցուցադրման ծրագիր է, Xfce-ի աշխատասեղանի միջավայրի համար։</p>
    <p>Ristretto պատկերի ցուցադրիչը ծրագիր է, որը կարող է աւգտագործուել պատկերների դիտման, տեսասահիկի միացման, պատկերներն այլ ծրագրերով բացելու համար, աւրինակ՝ պատկերների խմբագիրչը կամ պատկերի կազմաձեւումը, որպէս աշխատասեղանի պաստառ։</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Ristretto adalah penilik gambar untuk lingkungan desktop Xfce.</p>
    <p>Penilik Gambar Ristretto adalah aplikasi yang dapat digunakan untuk melihat dan menggulir melalui gambar, menjalankan salindia gambar, membuka gambar dengan aplikasi lain seperti penyunting gambar atau mengkonfigurasi gambar sebagai gambar latar desktop.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ie">
    <p>Ristretto es un visor de images por li ambientie Xfce.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>Ristretto er myndaforrit fyrir Xfce skjáborðsumhverfið.</p>
    <p>Ristretto myndaskoðarinn er forrit sem nota má til að skoða og vafra í gegnum myndir, keyra skyggnusýningu  með myndum, opna myndir í öðrum forritum eins og til dæmis myndvinnsluforritum, nú eða nota það til að setja mynd sem bakgrunn á skjáborð.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Ristretto è un visualizzatore di immagini per l'ambiente grafico Xfce.</p>
    <p>Il visualizzatore di immagini Ristretto è un'applicazione che può essere utilizzata per visualizzare e scorrere tra le immagini, eseguire una presentazione, aprire le immagini con altre applicazioni (quali editor di immagini) o per impostare un'immagine come sfondo della scrivania.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>Ristretto は Xfce デスクトップ環境向けの画像ビューアーです。</p>
    <p>Ristretto は画像ビューアーアプリケーションです。画像の表示やスクロール、スライドショー、グラフィックエディターなど他のアプリケーションで画像を開く、あるいはデスクトップの壁紙の設定などが行えます。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <p>Ristretto - Xfce жұмыс үстел ортасы үшін суреттер көрсетушісі.</p>
    <p>Ristretto суреттерді көрсету қолданбасы суреттерді қарау және шолу, слайдшоу ретінде көрсету, суретті басқа, суреттерді түзету сияқты, қолданбасы көмегімен ашуға немесе суретті жұмыс үстелдің фоны ретінде орнатуға мүмкін етеді.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>리스트레또는 Xfce 데스크톱 환경의 그림 보기 프로그램입니다.</p>
    <p>리스트레또 그림 보기 프로그램에서는 이미지를 스크롤 방식으로도 볼 수 있으며 슬라이드 쇼 방식으로 보여줄 수 있고 다른 이미지 편집기에서 이미지를 열어보거나 데스크톱 바탕 화면 이미지로 설정할 수 있습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Ristretto yra paveikslų žiūryklė, skirta Xfce darbalaukio aplinkai.</p>
    <p>Ristretto paveikslų žiūryklė yra programa, kuri gali būti naudojama paveikslų peržiūrai, skaidrių rodymui, paveikslų atvėrimui per kitas, tokias kaip paveikslų redaktorius, programas arba paveikslų, kaip darbalaukio fono, konfigūravimui.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Mousepad merupakan pelihat imej untuk persekitaran desktop Xfce.</p>
    <p>Pelihat IMej Ristretto ialah aplikasi yang digunakan untuk melihat dan menatal imej, menjalankan paparan slaid imej, membuka imej dengan aplikasi lain seperti image-editor atau konfigur imej sebagai kertas dinding desktop.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Ristretto er en bildefremviser for Xfce-skrivebordsmiljøet</p>
    <p>Ristretto bildeviser er et program som kan brukes til å se og bla igjennom bilder, kjøre bildefremvisning, åpne bilder med andre programmer, for eksempel et bilderedigeringsprogram, eller sette et bilde som skrivebordsbakgrunn.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Ristretto is een afbeeldingkijker voor de Xfce-werkomgeving.</p>
    <p>De afbeeldingkijker Ristretto is een toepassing die kan worden gebruikt om door afbeeldingen te bladeren en ze te bekijken, een diapresentatie van afbeeldingen weer te geven, afbeeldingen te openen met andere toepassingen zoals een fotobewerker of om een afbeelding in te stellen als bureaubladachtergrond.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="oc">
    <p>Ristretto es un visionador d’imatges per l’environament de burèu Xfce.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Przeglądarka obrazów dla środowiska Xfce</p>
    <p>Przeglądarka obrazów Ristretto to program, który może być używany do przeglądania i przewijania kolekcji obrazów, uruchamiania prezentacji slajdów z obrazów, otwierania obrazów przy użyciu innego programu, takiego jak edytor grafiki, oraz do konfigurowania obrazu jako tapety pulpitu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>O Ristretto é um visualizador de imagens para o ambiente de trabalho Xfce.</p>
    <p>O visualizador de imagens Ristretto é uma aplicação que pode ser utilizada para ver e deslocar entre imagens, executar uma apresentação de imagens, abrir imagens com outras aplicações como um editor de imagens ou configurar uma imagem como papel de parede.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>O Ristretto é um visualizador de imagens rápido e leve para o ambiente de trabalho Xfce.</p>
    <p>O Visualizador de Imagens Ristretto é um aplicativo que pode ser usado para visualizar ou navegar por uma coleção de imagens, exibir uma apresentação de slides de imagens, abrir imagens com outros aplicativos como um editor de imagens or definir uma imagem como papel de parede da área de trabalho.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ro">
    <p>Ristretto este un vizualizator de imagini pentru mediul desktop Xfce.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Ristretto — быстрая и легковесная программа просмотра изображений для рабочего окружения Xfce.</p>
    <p>Программа просмотра изображений Ristretto может быть использована для показа и смены изображений, демонстрации слайд-шоу из изображений, открытия изображений в других программах, например, в редакторах, и замены обоев на рабочем столе.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Ristretto je prehliadač obrázkov pre pracovné prostredie Xfce.</p>
    <p>Prehliadač obrázkov Ristretto je aplikácia, ktorú môžete použiť na zobrazenie a prechádzanie obrázkami, spustenie prezentácie obrázkov, otvorenie obrázkov v inej aplikácii, ako napr. editor obrázkov, alebo nastaviť obrázok ako tapetu plochy.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Ristretto je pregledovalnik slik za Xfce namizno okolje.</p>
    <p>Ristretto pregledovalnik slik je program za pregledovanje in prikazovanje slik, prikaz diaprojekcije slik, odpiranje slik z izbrano aplikacijom kot npr. urejevalnikom slik ali določanje ozadja namizja.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sq">
    <p>Ristretto është një parës figurash për mjedisin Xfce desktop.</p>
    <p>Parësi i Figurave Ristretto është një aplikacion që mund të përdoret për të parë dhe lëvizur nëpër figura, për të shfaqur figura si diapozitiva, për të hapur figura me aplikacione të tjerë, fjala vjen, me një përpunues figurash ose për ta formësuar një figurë si sfond desktopi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Ристрето је прегледач слика радног окружења Иксфце-а.</p>
    <p>Прегледник слика Ристрето је програм који може да се користи за преглед и клизање кроз слике, покретање покретног приказа слика, отварање слика осталим програмима, као уредник слика или за подешавање слике да буде позадина радне површи.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Ristretto är en bildvisare för skrivbordsmiljön Xfce</p>
    <p>Bildvisaren Ristretto är ett program som kan användas för att visa och bläddra bland bilder, köra ett bildspel, öppna bilder med andra program som en bildredigerare eller ställa in en bild som skrivbordsbakgrund.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="th">
    <p>Ristretto คือโปรแกรมแสดงรูปภาพสำหรับเดสก์ท็อป Xfce</p>
    <p>โปรแกรมดูรูปภาพ Ristretto เป็นโปรแกรมที่สามารถใช้แสดงและเลื่อนดูรูปภาพต่างๆ, แสดงสไลด์ของรูปภาพ, เปิดรูปภาพด้วยโปรแกรมอื่นเช่นโปรแกรมแก้ไขรูปภาพ หรือกำหนดรูปภาพเป็นภาพพื้นหลัง</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Ristretto, Xfce masaüstü ortamı için resim göstericidir.</p>
    <p>Ristretto Resim Gösterici; resimleri görüntülemek, resimler arasında gezinmek, resimlerle sunum  yapmak, resimleri resim düzenleyici gibi başka uygulamalarla açmak ya da resmi masaüstü arka planı olarak ayarlamak için kullanılabilecek uygulamadır.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ug">
    <p>رىسترېتتو(Ristretto) بولسا Xfce ئۈستەلئۈستى مۇھىتىدىكى سۈرەت كۆرگۈدۇر.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Ristretto - переглядач зображень для робочого середовища Xfce.</p>
    <p>Переглядач малюнків Ristretto - це програма, яку можна використовувати для перегляду малюнків, запуску слайд-шоу з малюнків, відкривання малюнків за допомогою інших програм, таких як редактор малюнків, або налаштовувати малюнок в якості шпалер стільниці.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>Ristretto 是 Xfce 桌面环境下的图片查看器。</p>
    <p>Ristretto 图片查看器是一个应用程序,它可以用来查看和滚动浏览图片,运行图片幻灯片,使用其他程序比如图片编辑器来打开图片或者设置一张图片为桌面背景。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>Ristretto 是個 Xfce 桌面環境的影像檢視器。</p>
    <p>Ristretto 影像檢視器是用來檢視及捲動瀏覽影像、播放影像幻燈片、以其他應用程式（如影像編輯器）開啟、或是將影像設定為桌面的桌布的應用程式。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://docs.xfce.org/_media/apps/ristretto/view-images.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://docs.xfce.org/apps/ristretto/start</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.xfce.org/apps/ristretto/issues</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.xfce.org/apps/ristretto/start</url>
  <url type="donation">https://opencollective.com/xfce/donate</url>
  <url type="translate">https://docs.xfce.org/contribute/translate/start</url>
  <project_group>XFCE</project_group>
  <update_contact>xfce4-dev@xfce.org</update_contact>
  <developer_name>Xfce Developers</developer_name>
  <translation type="gettext">ristretto</translation>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.xfce.ristretto.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-07-09" version="0.12.3" />
    <release date="2022-01-14" version="0.12.2" />
    <release date="2021-11-26" version="0.12.1" />
    <release version="0.12.0" date="2021-10-11" />
  </releases>
  <provides>
    <binary>ristretto</binary>
  </provides>
</component>