<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>xfce.xfce4-panel-profiles</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.xfce.PanelProfiles.desktop</launchable>
  <icon height="64" type="cached" width="64">org.xfce.PanelProfiles.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" height="128" width="128">org.xfce.PanelProfiles.png</icon>
  <id>xfce4-panel-profiles.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-3.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <name>Xfce Panel Profiles</name>
  <summary>Application to manage different panel layouts in Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Праграма для кіравання рознымі канфігурацыямі панэляў Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Приложение за управление на различните подредби на панела на Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Aplicació per gestionar els diferents dissenys de taulers a Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Aplikace pro správu různých rozvržení panelu v Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Program til at håndtere forskellige panellayouts i Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Anwendung zur Verwaltung verschiedener Leisten-Layouts in Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Εφαρμογή για τη διαχείριση διαφορετικών σχεδιαγραμμάτων σε Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="en_AU">Application to manage different panel layouts in Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="en_GB">Application to manage different panel layouts in Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Aplicación para gestionar las distintas disposiciones de paneles en Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Rakendus, mis võimaldab hallata erinevaid Xfce paneelide paigutusi</summary>
  <summary lang="eu">Xfcen panel diseinu ezberdinak kudeatzeko aplikazioa</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Sovellus eri paneeliasettelujen hallintaan Xfce:ssä</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Application permettant de gérer différentes dispositions de tableau de bord dans Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Aplicación para xestionar as diferentes disposicións do panel en Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="he">יישום לניהול סידורי לוח שונים ב-Xfce </summary>
  <summary lang="hi">विभिन्न पैनल अभिन्यास के प्रबंधन हेतु अनुप्रयोग</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Aplikacija za upravljanje različitim izgledima ploče za Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Program a különböző Xfce panelbeállítások kezelésére</summary>
  <summary lang="hy_AM">Յաւելուած Xfce֊ում տարբեր ընտրացանկերի շարակարգերը կառավարելու համար։</summary>
  <summary lang="hye">Յաւելուած Xfce֊ում տարբեր ընտրացանկերի շարակարգերը կառավարելու համար։</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Aplikasi pengelola tata letak panel Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="ie">Un application por crear multiplic separat arangeamentes de paneles in Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Forrit til að sýsla með mismunandi uppsetningar á skjástikum í XFCE</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Applicazione per gestire differenti configurazioni del pannello in Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">Xfceの異なったパネルレイアウトを管理するアプリケーション</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">Xfce ішінде әр түрлі панель конфигурацияларын басқаруға арналған қолданба</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">Xfce 의 다양한 패널 레이아웃 관리 프로그램</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Programa, skirta tvarkyti įvairius Xfce skydelio išdėstymus</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Aplikasi untuk mengurus pelbagai bentangan panel di dalam Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Et program som behandler ulike paneloppsett i Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Toepassing om verschillende werkbalkvormen te beheren in Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Aplikacja do zarządzania różnymi układami paneli w Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Aplicação para gerir diferentes esquemas de painel no Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Aplicação para gerenciar diferentes layoutes no painel do Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Приложения для управления разными расположениями панелей Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Aplikácia na správu rôznych rozložení panelov prostredia Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Program za upravljanje različnih razporedov pulta v namizju Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="sq">Aplikacion për administrim skemash të ndryshme paneli në Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Програм за управљање различитим размештајем полице ИксФЦЕ-а</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Program för att hantera olika panellayouter i Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="th">แอปพลิเคชันสำหรับจัดการผังพาเนลต่างๆ ใน Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Xfce'deki panel yapılandırmalarını yöneten, yedekleyen uygulama</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Програма керуванням різними розкладками панелей в Xfce</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">使用 App 来管理不同的 Xfce 面板布局</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_HK">在Xfce中管理不同面板佈局的應用程序</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">在 Xfce 中管理不同面板的應用程式</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Multitude of panel layouts can be created using Xfce panel. This tool enables managing different layouts with little effort. Xfpanel-switch makes it possible to backup, restore, import and export panel layouts.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Мноства канфігурацый панэляў можна стварыць пры дапамозе панэлі Xfce. Гэты інструмент дае магчымасць кіраваць гэтымі варыянтамі. Пераключальнік Xfpanel дае магчымасць ствараць рэзервовы копіі, аднаўляць, імпартаваць і экспартаваць канфігурацыі панэляў.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Множество подредби на панелите могат да бъдат създадени чрез панела на Xfce. Този инструмент ви позволява да управлявате различни оформления с малко усилия. Превключвателят на Xfpanel позволява архивиране, възстановяване, импортиране и експортиране на панелни подредби.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>Es poden crear multituds de dissenys de taulers mitjançant el tauler de Xfce. Aquesta eina permet gestionar diferents dissenys amb poc esforç. Xfpanel-switch permet realitzar còpies de seguretat, restaurar, importar i exportar els dissenys dels taulers.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Při používání panelu Xfce je možné vytvořit jeho různá rozvržení. Tento nástroj vám umožňuje spravovat různá rozvržení s minimálním úsilím. Xfpanel-switch umožňuje rozvržení panelu zálohovat, obnovovat, importovat a exportovat.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Der kan oprettes mange panellayouts med Xfce-panel. Værktøjer gør det muligt at håndtere forskellige layouts uden besvær. Xfpanel-switch giver mulighed for at sikkerhedskopiere, gendanne, importere og eksportere panellayouts.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Mit der Xfce-Leiste können eine Vielzahl von Leistenlayouts erstellt werden. Dieses Werkzeug ermöglicht die Verwaltung verschiedener Layouts mit geringem Aufwand. Xfpanel-switch ermöglicht das Sichern, Wiederherstellen, Importieren und Exportieren von Leistenlayouts.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Το πλήθος των διατάξεων πίνακα μπορεί να δημιουργηθεί χρησιμοποιώντας τον πίνακα Xfce. Αυτό το εργαλείο επιτρέπει τη διαχείριση διαφορετικών σχεδίων με μικρή προσπάθεια. Ο διακόπτης Xfpanel επιτρέπει την δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας, την επαναφορά, την εισαγωγή και την εξαγωγή των σχεδιαγραμμάτων.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_AU">
    <p>Multitude of panel layouts can be created using Xfce panel. This tool enables managing different layouts with little effort. Xfpanel-switch makes it possible to backup, restore, import and export panel layouts.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>Multitude of panel layouts can be created using Xfce panel. This tool enables managing different layouts with little effort. Xfpanel-switch makes it possible to backup, restore, import and export panel layouts.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Es posible crear muchas disposiciones de paneles con Xfce. Esta herramienta permite gestionar las distintas disposiciones con facilidad. Xfpanel-switch posibilita el resguardo, la restauración, la importación y la exportación de disposiciones de paneles.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Xfce paneelide jaoks saab luua erinevaid paigutusi. Käesolev töövahend võimaldab vähese vaevaga hallata selliseid erinevaid paigutusi. Xfpanel'i lülitaja võimaldab varundada, taastada,importida ja eksportida paneelidei paigutusi.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="eu">
    <p>Xfce panela erabiliz panel diseinu ugari sor daitezke. Tresnak honekin diseinu ezberdinak kudeatu daitezke esfortzu txikia eginez. Xfpanel-switchek panel diseinuen babeskopia egitea, hura berrezartzea, inportatzea eta esportatzea baimentzen du.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Xfce-paneelilla voi luoda useita erilaisia paneeliasetelmia. Tämä työkalu mahdollistaa erilaisten asetelmien hallinnan pienellä vaivalla. Xfpanel-switch mahdollistaa paneeliasetelmien varmuuskopioinnin, palauttamisen, tuomisen ja viemisen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Différentes dispositions de tableau de bord Xfce peuvent êtres créées. Cet outil permet de gérer facilement les différentes dispositions. Xfpanel-switch permet la sauvegarde, la restauration, l’importation et l’exportation de dispositions de tableau de bord.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>Pode crear multitude de disposicións de panel empregando o panel Xfce. Esta ferramenta permite a xestión de diferentes disposicións con pouco esforzo. O Xfpanel-switch permite facer copias de seguranza, restauración, importación e exportación das disposicións de panel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>המון סידורי לוח ניתנים ליצירה בעזרת לוח Xfce. כלי זה מאפשר ניהול סידורים שונים במאמץ מועט. Xfpanel-switch מאפשר לבצע גיבוי, שיחזור, יבוא ויצוא של סידורי לוח.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hi">
    <p>Xfce पैनल से कई पैनल अभिन्यास बनाएँ जा सकते हैं। इस साधन द्वारा थोड़े प्रयास से ही विभिन्न अभिन्यासों का प्रबंधन संभव है। Xfpanel-switch के मदद से पैनल अभिन्यास का बैकअप, पुनर्स्थापना, आयात व निर्यात किया जा सकता है।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Xfce ploča omogućava stvaranje velikog broja različitih izgleda. Ovaj alat omogućava lagano upravljanje različitim konfiguracijama. Pomoću Xfpanel-switch možete napraviti i vratiti sigurnosnu kopiju, uvesti ili izvesti izgled ploče.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>Több olyan panelbeállítást lehet készíteni amit aztán az Xfce panel fog használni. Ez az eszköz a különböző panelbeállítások kezelését teszi lehetővé egyszerűen. Az Xfpanel-switch lehetővé teszi a különböző panelbeállítások biztonsági mentését, visszaállítását, importálását és exportálását.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hy_AM">
    <p>Ընտրացանկի շարակարգերի փոփոխութիւնը կարող է իրագործուել Xfce ընտրացանկի աւգնութեամբ։ Այս գործիքը միացնում է տարբեր շարակարգերի կառավարումը փոքր պահանջով։ Xfpanel-switch ֊ը հնարաւորութիւն է տալիս ընտրացանկի շարակարգերը պահելու, վերականգնելու, ներածելու եւ արտածելու։</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hye">
    <p>Ընտրացանկի շարակարգերի փոփոխութիւնը կարող է իրագործուել Xfce ընտրացանկի աւգնութեամբ։ Այս գործիքը միացնում է տարբեր շարակարգերի կառավարումը փոքր պահանջով։ Xfpanel-switch ֊ը հնարաւորութիւն է տալիս ընտրացանկի շարակարգերը պահելու, վերականգնելու, ներածելու եւ արտածելու։</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Sejumlah besar tata letak panel dapat dibuat menggunakan panel Xfce. Alat ini digunakan untuk mengelola berbagai tata letak dengan mudah. Xfpanel-switch bisa melakukan pencadangan, pemulihan, impor dan ekspor tata letak panel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ie">
    <p>Multiplic arangeamentes de paneles posse esser fat per li panel de Xfce. Ti utensile permisse controlar multiplic arangeamentes con poc pena. Xfpanel-switch permisse archivar, restituer, importar e exportar arangeamentes de paneles.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>Hægt er að útbúa urmul af mismunandi uppsetningum á skjástikum í XFCE. Þetta tól auðveldar að sýsla með mismunandi uppsetningar á skjástikum í XFCE. Xfpanel-switch gefur kost á að taka öryggisafrit, endurheimta, flytja uppsetningar á skjástikum út og inn úr kerfinu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Si possono creare molte configurazioni del pannello in Xfce. Questo strumento permette di gestire i diversi layout con un minimo sforzo. Xfpanel-switch permette di salvare, ripristinare, importare ed esportare le configurazioni del pannello.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>Xfce パネルを使用することによって、多数のパネルレイアウトを作成できます。このツールは、少しの作業で異なるレイアウトを管理できます。 Xfpanel-switchは、パネルレイアウトのバックアップ、復元、インポート、およびエクスポートを可能にします。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <p>Xfce панелі көмегімен көптеген панель жаймаларын жасауға болады. Бұл құрал әр түрлі жаймаларды оңай басқаруға мүмкіндік береді. Xfpanel-switch көмегімен панель жаймаларының қор көшірмесін жасау, қалпына келтіру, импорттау және экспорттауға болады.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>Xfce 패널을 사용하여 여러 패널 레이아웃을 만들 수 있습니다. 이 도구는 적은 노력으로 다양한 레이아웃을 만들 수 있습니다. Xfpanel-switch는 패널 레이아웃을 가져오고 내보내고 복구하고 백업할 수 있습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Naudojant Xfce skydelį gali būti sukurta daugybė skydelio išdėstymų. Šis įrankis leidžia be pastangų tvarkyti įvairius išdėstymus. Xfpanel-switch suteikia galimybę daryti atsargines kopijas, atkurti ir eksportuoti skydelio išdėstymus.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Banyak bentangan panel boleh dihasilkan menggunakan panel Xfce. Alat ini membolehkan pengurusan pelbagai jenis bentangan tanpa perlu bersusah payah. Xfpanel-switch membolehkan bentangan panel disandar, dipulihkan, diimport dan dieksport.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Man kan utforme Xfce-panelet på mange måter. Dette verktøyet kan enkelt behandle de ulike utformingene. Xfpanel-switch gjør det mulig å reservekopiere, gjenopprette, importere og eksportere paneloppsett.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Met behulp van Xfce Werkbalkwisselaar kunnen er meerdere werkbalkvormen worden gemaakt. Dit gereedschap stelt u in staat om verschillende werkbalkvormen te beheren met slechts een kleine inspanning. Xfce Werkbalkwisselaar maakt het mogelijk om reservekopieën te maken van werkbalkvormen, hen terug te zetten, te importeren en te exporteren.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Mnogość układów paneli można tworzyć za pomocą panelu Xfce. To narzędzie umożliwia zarządzanie różnymi układami przy niewielkim wysiłku. Xfpanel-switch umożliwia tworzenie kopii zapasowych, przywracanie, importowanie i eksportowanie układów paneli.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>Podem ser criados múltiplos esquemas de painel usando o painel do Xfce. Esta ferramenta permite gerir sem esforço diferentes esquemas. A ferramenta Xfpanel-switch permite guardar, restaurar, importar e exportar esquemas de painel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Vários layouts de painel podem ser criados usando o painel Xfce. Essa ferramenta permite gerenciar diferentes layouts com pouco esforço. O Xfpanel-switch possibilita fazer backup, restaurar, importar e exportar layouts de painel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Множество расположений панелей может быть создано при помощи панели Xfce. Данный инструмент позволяет управлять разными расположениями с небольшими усилиями. Xfpanel-switch даёт возможность сохранять, восстанавливать, импортировать и экспортировать расположения панелей.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>S pomočjo Xfce panel lahko ustvarimo številne razporeditve pultov. To orodje omogoča enostavno upravljanje različnih razporedov. Xfpanel-switch omogoča shranjevanje in obnavljanje, uvoz ter izvoz razporedov pulta.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sq">
    <p>Duke përdorur panelin Xfce mund të krijohen shumë skema panelesh. Ky mjet lejon administrimin me pak mundim të skemave të ndryshme. Xfpanel-switch bën të mundur të kopjeruhen, rikthehen, importohen dhe eksportohen skema panelesh.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>На полици ИксФЦЕ-а се могу направити многоструки размештаји. Овај прибор омогућава управљање различитим размештајима са мало труда. Прекидач полице омогућава чување, повраћај, увоз и извоз размештаја полице.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Mängder av panellayouter kan skapas med Xfce-panelen. Det här verktyget möjliggör hantering av olika layouter med liten ansträngning. Xfpanel-switch gör det möjligt att säkerhetskopiera, återställa, importera och exportera panellayouter.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="th">
    <p>พาเนลของ Xfce สามารถสร้างผังได้หลากหลายรูปแบบมาก เครื่องมือนี้จะช่วยให้คุณจัดการผังต่างๆ โดยใช้ความพยายามเพียงน้อยนิด  Xfpanel-switch ช่วยให้คุณสามารถสำรอง, กู้คืน, นำเข้า และส่งออกผังพาเนลต่างๆ ได้</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Xfce paneli kullanılarak çok sayıda panel yerleşimi oluşturulabilir. Bu araç, farklı düzenleri küçük çabalarla yönetmeyi sağlar. Xfpanel-switch, panel düzenlerini yedekleme, geri yükleme, içe aktarma ve dışa aktarmayı mümkün kılar.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Можна створити безліч конфігурацій панелей, використовуючи панель Xfce. Це знаряддя дозволяє без зусиль керувати різними конфігураціями панелей. За допомогою Xfpanel-switch можна робити запасні копії, відновлювати, імпортувати і експортувати конфігурації панелей.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>Xfce 面板能创建出多个不同的布局配置。该小工具能使管理这些布局变得更加便捷。Xfpanel-switch 使得备份，还原以及导入导出面板布局皆为可能。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>可以使用 Xfce 面板建立多種佈局。這個工具可以輕鬆管理不同的佈局。Xfpanel-switch 讓它可以備份、還原、匯入與匯出面板佈局。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image height="540" width="960">https://screenshots.bluesabre.org/xfce4-panel-profiles/xfce4-panel-profiles.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <translation type="gettext">xfce4-panel-profiles</translation>
  <url type="homepage">https://git.xfce.org/apps/xfce4-panel-profiles</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugzilla.xfce.org/</url>
  <updatecontact>bluesabre@xfce.org</updatecontact>
  <project_group>XFCE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>xfce4-panel-profiles</binary>
  </provides>
</component>