<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <pkgname>xfce.xfce4-appfinder</pkgname>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">xfce4-appfinder.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="cached" width="64" height="64">org.xfce.appfinder.png</icon>
  <icon type="cached" width="128" height="128">org.xfce.appfinder.png</icon>
  <id>xfce4-appfinder.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-3.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Application Finder</name>
  <name lang="am">ፕሮግራም ፈላጊ</name>
  <name lang="ar">مكتشف التطبيقات</name>
  <name lang="ast">Guetador d'aplicaciones</name>
  <name lang="be">Пошук праграм</name>
  <name lang="bg">Търсене на програма</name>
  <name lang="bn">অ্যাপ্লিকেশন অনুসন্ধানকারী</name>
  <name lang="ca">Cercador d'aplicacions</name>
  <name lang="cs">Vyhledávač aplikací</name>
  <name lang="da">Programfinder</name>
  <name lang="de">Anwendungsfinder</name>
  <name lang="el">Εύρεση Εφαρμογών</name>
  <name lang="en_AU">Application Finder</name>
  <name lang="en_CA">Application Finder</name>
  <name lang="en_GB">Application Finder</name>
  <name lang="es">Buscador de aplicaciones</name>
  <name lang="et">Rakenduste leidja</name>
  <name lang="eu">Aplikazio bilatzailea</name>
  <name lang="fi">Sovellusten hakutyökalu</name>
  <name lang="fr">Liste des applications</name>
  <name lang="gl">Buscador de aplicacións</name>
  <name lang="he">מוצא יישומים</name>
  <name lang="hi">अनुप्रयोग खोज</name>
  <name lang="hr">Nalaznik programa</name>
  <name lang="hu">Alkalmazáskereső</name>
  <name lang="hy_AM">Յաւելուածների Որոնում</name>
  <name lang="hye">Յաւելուածների Որոնում</name>
  <name lang="id">Pencari Aplikasi</name>
  <name lang="ie">Trovator de applicationes</name>
  <name lang="is">Forritaleit</name>
  <name lang="it">Trova applicazioni</name>
  <name lang="ja">アプリケーションファインダー</name>
  <name lang="kk">Қолданбаларды табушы</name>
  <name lang="ko">프로그램 탐색기</name>
  <name lang="lt">Programų paieška</name>
  <name lang="lv">Lietotņu meklētājs</name>
  <name lang="ms">Pencari Aplikasi</name>
  <name lang="nb">Programkatalog</name>
  <name lang="nl">Toepassingenzoeker</name>
  <name lang="nn">Programfinnar</name>
  <name lang="oc">Lista de las aplicacions</name>
  <name lang="pa">ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਫਾਈਡਰ</name>
  <name lang="pl">Wyszukiwarka programów</name>
  <name lang="pt">Localizar aplicações</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Localizador de aplicativos</name>
  <name lang="ro">Pornire de programe</name>
  <name lang="ru">Поиск приложений</name>
  <name lang="si">යෙදුම් සෙවුම</name>
  <name lang="sk">Vyhľadávač aplikácií</name>
  <name lang="sl">Iskalec aplikacije</name>
  <name lang="sq">Gjetës Aplikacionesh</name>
  <name lang="sr">Проналазач програма</name>
  <name lang="sv">Programstartare</name>
  <name lang="te">అనువర్తన శోధకం</name>
  <name lang="th">เครื่องมือค้นหาโปรแกรม</name>
  <name lang="tr">Uygulama Bulucu</name>
  <name lang="ug">پروگرامما ئىزدىگۈ</name>
  <name lang="uk">Пошук встановлених програм</name>
  <name lang="ur">اطلاقیہ تلاش کار</name>
  <name lang="ur_PK">اطلاقیہ تلاش کار</name>
  <name lang="vi">Application Finder</name>
  <name lang="zh_CN">应用程序查找器</name>
  <name lang="zh_HK">應用程式協尋器</name>
  <name lang="zh_TW">應用程式協尋器</name>
  <summary>Application to quickly run applications and commands</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">برنامج لتشغيل التطبيقات واﻷوامر بسرعة</summary>
  <summary lang="be">Праграма для хуткага запуску праграм і загадаў</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">Приложение за бързо стартиране на програми и команди</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Aplicació per executar ràpidament aplicacions i ordres</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Aplikace pro rychlé spouštění aplikací a příkazů</summary>
  <summary lang="da">Program til hurtigt at køre programmer og kommandoer</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Anwendung zur schnellen Ausführung von Anwendungen und Befehlen</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Εφαρμογή για γρήγορη εκτέλεση εφαρμογών και εντολών</summary>
  <summary lang="en_AU">Application to quickly run applications and commands</summary>
  <summary lang="en_CA">Application to quickly run applications and commands</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Aplicación para ejecutar rápidamente aplicaciones y comandos</summary>
  <summary lang="et">Rakendus, mille abil saad kiiretsi käivitada teisi rakendusi ja käske</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">Sovellus sovellusten ja komentojen nopeaan käynnistämiseen</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Application pour lancer rapidement des programmes et des commandes</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">Aplicación para executar rapidamente aplicacións e ordes</summary>
  <summary lang="he">יישום להרצה מהירה של יישומים ופקודות</summary>
  <summary lang="hi">अनुप्रयोग व कमांड शीघ्र निष्पादन हेतु अनुप्रयोग</summary>
  <summary lang="hr">Aplikacija za brzo pokretanje aplikacija i naredbi</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">Alkalmazás az alkalmazások és parancsok gyors futtatásához</summary>
  <summary lang="hy_AM">Յաւելուածը դեպի արագ բեռնուող յաւելուածները եւ հրամանները</summary>
  <summary lang="hye">Յաւելուածը դեպի արագ բեռնուող յաւելուածները եւ հրամանները</summary>
  <summary lang="id">Aplikasi untuk menjalankan berbagai aplikasi dan perintah dengan cepat</summary>
  <summary lang="ie">Un application por lansar rapidmen applicationes e comandes</summary>
  <summary lang="is">Forrit til að flyta fyrir ræsingu annarra forrita og skipana</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Applicazione per eseguire velocemente applicazioni e comandi</summary>
  <summary lang="ja">アプリケーションとコマンドをすばやく実行するためのアプリケーション</summary>
  <summary lang="kk">Қолданбалар және командаларды жылдам жөнелтуге арналған қолданба</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">프로그램과 명령을 빠르게 실행하는 프로그램</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Programa, skirta greitai paleisti programas ir komandas</summary>
  <summary lang="ms">Aplikasi untuk jalankan aplikasi dan perintah dengan pantas</summary>
  <summary lang="nb">Et program som raskt finner og kjører programmer og kommandoer</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Toepassing om snel andere toepassingen en opdrachten uit te voeren</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Program do szybkiego uruchamiania aplikacji i poleceń</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">Aplicação para rapidamente executar aplicações e comandos</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Aplicativo para executar rapidamente aplicativos e comandos</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Приложение для быстрого запуска программ и команд</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">Aplikácia slúžiaca na rýchle spustenie aplikácií a príkazov</summary>
  <summary lang="sl">Aplikacija za hiter zagon aplikacij in ukazov</summary>
  <summary lang="sq">Aplikacion për të xhiruar shpejt e shpejt aplikacione dhe urdhra</summary>
  <summary lang="sr">Програм за брзо покретање програма и наредби</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">Program för att snabbt köra program och kommandon</summary>
  <summary lang="th">เครื่องมือสำหรับเรียกโปรแกรมและคำสั่งอย่างเร็ว</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Uygulamaları ve komutları hızlıca çalıştırmak için uygulama</summary>
  <summary lang="uk">Застосунок для швидкого запуску програм і команд </summary>
  <summary lang="zh_CN">快速运行应用程序和命令的应用程序</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_HK">應用程序以快速運行應用程序和命令</summary>
  <summary lang="zh_TW">快速執行應用程式與指令的應用程式</summary>
  <description>
    <p>The application finder is a tool to find and launch installed applications on your system and quickly execute commands. It can also be used to quickly add launchers to the Xfce Panel by dragging an item from the view and drop it on the panel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>مكتشف التطبيقات أداة لإيجاد وتشغيل التطبيقات المثبتة على نظامك وتنفيذ اﻷوامر بسرعة. يمكن استخدامه أيضاً ﻹضافة مشغلات إلى شريط إكسفس بسرعة عن طريق سحب عنصر من العرض وإفلاته على الشريط.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="be">
    <p>Пошук праграм - інструмент для хуткага пошуку і запуску ўсталяваных у вашай сістэме праграм і выканання загадаў. Таксама яе можна выкарыстоўваць для дадання запускальнікаў на панэль Xfce перацягваннем.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="bg">
    <p>Търсачката на приложения е инструмент за намиране и стартиране на инсталирани приложения на вашата система и бързо изпълнение на команди. Той може да се използва и за бързо добавяне на стартери към панела на Xfce, като издърпате елемент от списъка и го пуснете в панела.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ca">
    <p>El cercador d'aplicacions és una eina per trobar i llançar les aplicacions instal·lades al vostre sistema i per a l'execució ràpida d'ordres. També es pot utilitzar per afegir ràpidament llançadors al tauler de Xfce en arrossegar i deixar anar un ítem des de la vista fins al tauler.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Vyhledávač aplikací je nástroj pro hledání a spouštění aplikací nainstalovaných v systému a rychlé spouštění příkazů. Také jej lze přetažením a puštěním položky na panel použít k rychlému přidání spouštěčů na panel Xfce.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="da">
    <p>Programfinderen er et værktøj til at finde og starte installerede programmer på dit system og hurtigt køre kommandoer. Den kan bruges til hurtigt at tilføje opstartere til Xfce-panelet, ved at trække et element fra visningen og slippe det på panelet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Der Anwendungsfinder ist ein Werkzeug, um im System installierte Anwendungen zu finden und zu starten und schnell Befehle auszuführen. Er kann ebenfalls verwendet werden, um schnell Starter zur Xfce-Leiste hinzuzufügen, durch Ziehen aus der Ansicht und Ablegen in der Leiste.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="el">
    <p>Ο εντοπισμός εφαρμογών είναι ένα εργαλείο για την εύρεση και εκκίνηση εγκατεστημένων εφαρμογών στο σύστημά σας και την εκτέλεση εντολών γρήγορα. Μπορεί επίσης να χρησιμοποιηθεί για να προσθέσετε γρήγορες εκκινήσεις προγραμμάτων στον Πίνακα Xfce σύροντας ένα στοιχείο από την προβολή και να το ρίξετε στον πίνακα.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_AU">
    <p>The application finder is a tool to find and launch installed applications on your system and quickly execute commands. It can also be used to quickly add launchers to the Xfce Panel by dragging an item from the view and drop it on the panel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_CA">
    <p>The application finder is a tool to find and launch installed applications on your system and quickly execute commands. It can also be used to quickly add launchers to the Xfce Panel by dragging an item from the view and drop it on the panel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="en_GB">
    <p>The application finder is a tool to find and launch installed applications on your system and quickly execute commands. It can also be used to quickly add launchers to the Xfce Panel by dragging an item from the view and drop it on the panel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>El buscador de aplicaciones es una herramienta para encontrar y ejecutar aplicaciones instaladas en su sistema y ejecutar órdenes rápidamente. También se puede usar para agregar rápidamente lanzadores al panel de Xfce arrastrando un elemento de la vista y soltándolo en el panel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="et">
    <p>Rakenduste leidja on töövahend, mis võimaldab leida ja käivitada sinu süsteemi paigaldatud rakendusi ning samas ka kiiresti käivitada käske. Lohistades kirjeid rakenduste leidja loendist XFCE paneeli saad sa kiiresti lisada paneelidesse uusi käivitajaid.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fi">
    <p>Sovellusten hakutyökalu on työkalu asennettujen sovellusten hakemiseen ja käynnistämistä sekä komentojen nopeaa ajamista varten. Sitä voidaan myös käyttää sovellusten nopeaan lisäämiseen Xfce:n paneeliin vetämällä kohde näkymästä ja pudottamalle se paneeliin.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>La liste des applications est un outil permettant de rechercher et lancer des applications installées sur votre système, et pour exécuter rapidement des commandes. Elle peut aussi être utilisée pour ajouter rapidement des lanceurs au tableau de bord Xfce par un glisser-déposer.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="gl">
    <p>O buscador de aplicacións é unha ferramenta para atopar e iniciar as aplicacións instaladas no sistema e executar ordes rapidamente. Tamén se pode empregar para engadir iniciadores rapidamente ao panel do Xfce arrastrando un elemento da vista e soltándoo no panel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="he">
    <p>מוצא הישומים הוא כלי למציאה והפעלה של יישומים מותקנים במערכת שלך ומבצע במהירות פקודות. הוא יכול לשמש גם להוספה מהירה של מפעילים ללוח Xfce בעזרת גרירת פריט מהתצוגה ושחרורו על הלוח.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hi">
    <p>सिस्टम पर इंस्टॉल हो रखें अनुप्रयोग खोजने व कमांड के शीघ्र निष्पादन हेतु अनुप्रयोग खोज साधन है। दृश्य से माउस द्वारा वस्तु ड्रैग कर एक्सएफसीई पैनल पर लाने से आप संबंधित वस्तु हेतु आरंभ साधन भी जोड़ सकते हैं।</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hr">
    <p>Nalaznik programa je alat za pronalazak instaliranih programa na sustavu te brzo izvođenje naredbi. Također se može koristiti za dodavanje brzih pokretača na Xfce ploču povlačenjem stavke te ispuštanjem na ploču.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hu">
    <p>Az alkalmazáskereső eszköz a telepített alkalmazások megkeresésére és elindítására, és parancsok gyors végrehajtására szolgál. Arra is használható hogy indítóikonokat tegyen az Xfce panelre az elem a nézetből a panelre történő húzásával.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hy_AM">
    <p>Յաւելուածների որոնիչը գործիք է բեռնուած յաւելուածը գտնելու եւ ձեր համակարգում միացնելու համար,  եւ հրամանները արագ գործարկելու համար։ Նաեւ կարող է արագ աւելացնել թողարկիչներ Xfce Ընտրացանկում քաշելով տարրերը դիտումից եւ գցելով ընտրացանկ։</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="hye">
    <p>Յաւելուածների որոնիչը գործիք է բեռնուած յաւելուածը գտնելու եւ Ձեր համակարգում միացնելու համար,  եւ հրամանները արագ գործարկելու համար։ Նաեւ կարող է արագ աւելացնել թողարկիչներ Xfce Ընտրացանկում քաշելով տարրերը դիտումից եւ գցելով ընտրացանկ։</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="id">
    <p>Pencari aplikasi adalah sebuah alat untuk mencari dan menjalankan aplikasi yang terinstal pada sistem Anda dan mengeksekusi perintah dengan cepat. Ia juga bisa digunakan untuk menambahkan peluncur ke Xfce Panel dengan cepat, dengan menyeret sebuah item dari tampilan dan menjatuhkannya pada panel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ie">
    <p>Un trovator de applicationes es un utensile por trovar e lansar applicationes in vor sistema e rapidmen executer comandes. Anc it posse esser usat por adjunter lansatores al panel Xfce rapidmen, tirante un element ex li vise e fante it cader sur li panel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="is">
    <p>Forritaleit er verkfæri til að finna og ræsa forrit og skipanir sem uppsett eru á kerfinu. Það má einnig nota til að bæta forritaræsum í skyndingu á XFCE-skjástikur, með því að draga atriði úr sýn og sleppa þeim á skjástikuna.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Il trova applicazione è uno strumento per trovare ed avviare le applicazioni installate sul proprio sistema e per eseguire velocemente dei comandi. Può essere usato anche per aggiungere velocemente dei lanciatori al pannello di Xfce, trascinando un elemento dalla visualizzazione sul pannello.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ja">
    <p>アプリケーションファインダーはシステムにインストールされているアプリケーションを検索し起動したり、コマンドを実行するためのツールです。ウィンドウ内のアイテムを Xfce パネルにドラッグアンドドロップすることでランチャーを追加することもできます。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="kk">
    <p>Қолданбаларды табушы - бұл жүйеңізде орнатылған қолданбаларды табу және жөнелту, және де командаларды жылдам орындау үшін арналған сайман. Сонымен бірге, оның көмегімен қолданбалар көрінісінен тартып апару арқылы Xfce панеліне жөнелткіштерді қосуға болады.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ko">
    <p>프로그램 검색기는 시스템에 설치한 프로그램을 찾아 실행시키며, 명령을 빠르게 실행 처리하는 도구입니다. 또한 바로 가기 아이콘을 보기 창에서 Xfce 패널로 끌어다 놓는 방식으로 간편하게 추가할 수 있습니다.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="lt">
    <p>Programų paieška yra įrankis, skirtas rasti ir paleisti jūsų sistemoje įdiegtas programas bei greitai vykdyti komandas. Jį taip pat galima naudoti, norint pridėti leistukus į Xfce skydelį, tempiant elementą iš rodinio ir numetant jį ant skydelio.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ms">
    <p>Pencari aplikasi ini adalah alat untuk cari dan lancar aplikasi terpasang di dalam sistem anda dan lakukan perintah dengan pantas. Ia juga boleh digunakan untuk menambah pelancar secara pantas ke Panel Xfce dengan menyeret item dari paparan dan lepas ia ke atas panel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nb">
    <p>Programkatalogen er et verktøy som finner og kjører installerte programmer på systemet ditt. Det kan også kjøre egendefinerte handlinger og legge til hurtigstartere på Xfce-panelet ved å dra elementet fra utlistingen til panelet.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>De Toepassingenzoeker is een hulpmiddel om geïnstalleerde toepassingen te vinden en te starten, en om snel terminalopdrachten uit te voeren. Hij kan ook worden gebruikt om snel starters toe te voegen aan de Xfce-werkbalk, door een element te verslepen vanuit de weergave naar de werkbalk.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pl">
    <p>Wyszukiwarka programów to narzędzie do odnajdywania i uruchamiania zainstalowanych w systemie programów oraz do szybkiego wykonywania poleceń. Może być także używane do szybkiego dodawania aktywatorów do panelu Xfce poprzez przeniesienie elementu z podglądu i upuszczeniu go na panelu.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt">
    <p>A aplicação de localizar é uma ferramenta para encontrar e lançar aplicações instaladas no seu sistema e rapidamente executar comandos. Pode ser usada para adicionar rapidamente lançadores ao painel Xfce ao arrastar um item e largá-lo no painel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>O localizador de aplicativos é uma ferramenta que encontra e executa aplicativos instalados no seu sistema e rapidamente executa comandos. Também pode ser usado para rapidamente adicionar lançadores no painel do Xfce ao arrastar um item da lista e soltá-lo no painel.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Поиск приложений — инструмент для поиска и запуска установленных в вашей системе приложений и для быстрого выполнения команд. Он также может быть использован для быстрого добавления значков запуска на панель Xfce с помощью перетаскивания.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sk">
    <p>Vyhľadávač aplikácií je nástroj na vyhľadanie a spustenie aplikácií nainštalovaných v systéme a na rýchle spustenie príkazov. Možno ho tiež použiť na rýchle pridanie spúšťačov do panela Xfce pretiahnutím položky a jej upustením nad panelom.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sl">
    <p>Iskalnik aplikacij je orodje za iskanje in zagon aplikacij na vašem sistemu in za hitro izvajanje ukazov. Lahko ga uporabite tudi za hitro dodajanje zaganjalnikov v Xfce pult, tako ta povlečete predmet iz pogleda in ga spustite na pult.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sq">
    <p>Gjetësi i aplikacioneve është një mjet për të gjetur dhe nisur aplikacione të instaluar në sistemin tuaj dhe për të ekzekutuar shpejt urdhra. Mund të përdoret edhe për të shtuar shpejt nisës te Paneli i Xfce-së duke e tërhequr një objekt nga pamja dhe duke e hedhur te paneli.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sr">
    <p>Проналазач програма је прибор за претрагу и покретање уграђених програма на склопу и брзо извршавање наредби. Може се користити и за брзо додавање покретача на полицу ИксФЦЕ-а превлачењем ставке са прегледа и спуштањем на полицу.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Programstartaren är ett verktyg för att hitta och starta installerade program på datorn och snabbt utföra kommandon. Det kan också användas för att snabbt lägga till programstartare på Xfce-panelen genom att dra ett objekt från vyn och släppa det på panelen.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="th">
    <p>เครื่องมือค้นหาโปรแกรมเป็นเครื่องมือสำหรับหาและเรียกทำงานโปรแกรมที่ติดตั้งอยู่ในระบบ และใช้สั่งคำสั่งต่างๆ อย่างเร็ว และยังสามารถใช้เพิ่มปุ่มเรียกโปรแกรมลงในพาเนลของ Xfce ได้ด้วยการลากรายการจากในหน้าต่างไปวางบนพาเนล</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Uygulama bulma aracı, sisteminizde kurulu uygulamaları kolayca bulup çalıştırmak ve komutları işletmek için araçtır. Aynı zamanda bir başlatıcıyı panele sürükleyerek Xfce Paneline hızlıca eklemek için de kullanılabilir.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk">
    <p>Шукач програм є знаряддям для пошуку і запуску встановлених програм у Вашій системі і для швидкого запуску команд. Програму можна також використовувати для швидкого додавання запускачів до панелі Xfce, захоплюючи програми зі списку і переносячи їх на панель.</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_CN">
    <p>应用程序查找器 是一个用来查找和启动已安装程序的工具,它能快速执行命令。您也可以用它快速添加启动器到 Xfce 面板,只需要将对应项目拖放到面板上即可。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_HK">
    <p>應用程序查找器是一種工具，用於查找和啟動系統上已安裝的應用程序并快速執行命令。通過將一個項目從視圖中拖放到Xfce面板上，也可以將其快速添加到Xfce面板中。</p>
  </description>
  <description lang="zh_TW">
    <p>應用程式尋找器是一個尋找並啟動在您的系統上已安裝的應用程式，以及快速執行指令的工具。它也可以用以快速新增啟動器到 Xfce 面板，只要從您看得到的地方拖曳項目並在面板上放開按鍵即可。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://docs.xfce.org/_media/xfce/xfce4-appfinder/xfce4-appfinder-expanded.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.xfce.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.xfce.org/xfce/xfce4-appfinder/</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.xfce.org/xfce/xfce4-appfinder/start</url>
  <project_group>Xfce</project_group>
  <update_contact>xfce4-dev@xfce.org</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">xfce4-appfinder</translation>
  <provides>
    <binary>xfce4-appfinder</binary>
  </provides>
</component>