<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <description>
    <p>
      Zathura is a highly customizable and functional document viewer. It
      provides a minimalistic and space saving interface as well as an easy
      usage that mainly focuses on keyboard interaction. Zathura makes it
      possible to completely view and navigate through documents without using a
      mouse.
    </p>
    <p>
      Zathura can be extended to support multiple document formats using
      plugins. Other features include:
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li>SyncTeX forward and backward synchronization support.</li>
      <li>Quickmarks and bookmarks.</li>
      <li>Automatic document reloading.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="ar">
    <p>Zathura هو عارض وثائق قابل للتخصيص وعملي للغاية. فهو يوفر واجهة بسيطة وموفرة للمساحة بالإضافة إلى استخدام سهل يركز بشكل أساسي على تفاعل لوحة المفاتيح. يتيح Zathura إمكانية عرض المستندات والتنقل خلالها بدون استخدام الماوس.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>SyncTeX دعم المزامنة الأمامية والخلفية.</li>
      <li>سرعة العلامات والإشارات المرجعية.</li>
      <li>إعادة تحميل المستندات تلقائيًا.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="cs">
    <p>Zathura je hodně přizpůsobitelný výborný prohlížeč dokumentů. Vyznačuje se poskytováním minimalistického prostor šetřícího rozhraní a snadným používáním s důrazným zaměřením na používání klávesnice Zathura umožňuje plné zobrazení a pohyb v dokumentech bez použití myšího zařízení "myšítka".</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Podpora pro dopředné a zpětné seřízení SyncTeX.</li>
      <li>Rychlé značky a záložky.</li>
      <li>Automatické znovunahrání dokumentu.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="de">
    <p>Zathura ist ein anpassbarer und funktionaler Dokumentenbetrachter. Er bietet eine minimalistische und platzsparende Oberfläche und Verwendung ist auf Tastaturinteraktionen fokussiert. Zathura ermöglicht es ein Dokument gänzlich ohne der Verwendung einer Maus zu betrachten.</p>
    <p>Zathura kann durch Plug-ins um die Unterstützung von verschiedenen Dokumentformaten erwetert werden. Weitere Funktionen umfassen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Unterstützung für SyncTeX-Synchronisation.</li>
      <li>Markierungen und Lesezeichen.</li>
      <li>Automatisches Neuladen von Dokumenten.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="es">
    <p>Zathura es un visor de documentos altamente personalizable y funcional. Proporciona una interfaz ligera y minimalista, fácil de usar, pensada para ser utilizada con teclado. Zathura posibilita ver y navegar por documentos sin necesidad de utilizar el ratón.</p>
    <p>Zathura puede ampliarse para soportar diferentes formatos de documento utilizando plugins. Otras características incluyen:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Soporte de sincronización hacia delante y atrás SyncTex.</li>
      <li>Marcas rápidas y marcadores.</li>
      <li>Recarga automática de documentos.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="fr">
    <p>Zathura est un visionneur de documents très fonctionnel et personnalisable. Il fournit une interface minimaliste et peu encombrante ainsi qu'une utilisation centrée sur l'utilisation du clavier. Zathura permet de visionner et de parcourir des documents sans jamais utiliser la souris. </p>
    <p>Zathura peut être étendu par des greffons afin de gérer de multiples formats de documents. Ses autres fonctionnalités incluent:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Synchronisation bidirectionnelle avec SyncTeX.</li>
      <li>Raccourcis et favoris.</li>
      <li>Rafraîchissement automatique des documents.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="it">
    <p>Zathura è un visualizzatore di documenti altamente personalizzabile e funzionale. Fornisce un'interfaccia minimalista e salvaspazio e un facile utilizzo che si concentra principalmente sull'interazione della tastiera. Zathura rende possibile visualizzare e navigare completamente tra i documenti senza usare il mouse.</p>
    <p>Zathura può usare le estensioni per allargare il supporto a vari formati di file. Tra le altre funzionalità ci sono:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Supporto SyncTeX per la sincronizzazione in avanti e all'indietro.</li>
      <li>Quickmark e bookmark.</li>
      <li>Ricarica automatica del documento.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="nl">
    <p>Zathura is een zeer aanpasbaar en functioneel documentweergaveprogramma. Zathura heeft een minimalistische, ruimtebesparende vormgeving en is vooral gefocust op eenvoudig navigeren middels het toetsenbord. Dit maakt het mogelijk om volledig zonder muis door documenten te kunnen bladeren.</p>
    <p>Met plug-ins kun je ondersteuning toevoegen voor meerdere bestandsformaten. Andere mogelijkheden zijn:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>SyncTeX vooruit- en achteruitsynchronisatie.</li>
      <li>Verwijzingen en bladwijzers.</li>
      <li>Automatisch documenten herladen.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Zathura é um visualizador de documentos funcional e customizável. Ele oferece uma interface minimalista,  fácil de usar e focada na interação por teclado. Zathura torna possível visualizar e navegar por documentos completamente sem o uso do mouse.</p>
    <p>Zathura pode ser estendido para suportar múltiplos formatos de documentos usando plugins. Outros recursos incluem </p>
  </description>
  <description lang="ru">
    <p>Zathura - это настраиваемая и функциональная программа для просмотра документов. Она обеспечивает минималистичный и компактный интерфейс, а также простое использование, которое в основном сосредоточено на взаимодействии с клавиатурой. Zathura позволяет полностью просматривать и перемещаться по документам без использования мыши.</p>
    <p>Zathura может быть расширена для использования нескольких форматов документов при помощи плагинов.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>SyncTeX поддержка прямой и обратной синхронизации.</li>
      <li>Быстрые заметки и закладки.</li>
      <li>Автоматическая перезагрузка документов.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="sv">
    <p>Zathura är en mycket anpassningsbar och funktionell dokumentvisare. Den tillhandahåller ett minimalistiskt och utrymmessparande gränssnitt så väl som enkel användning som i huvudsak fokuserar på tangentbordsinteraktion. Zathur gör det möjligt att helt visa och navigera genom dokument utan att använda en mus.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Stöd för SyncTeX-framåt- och -bakåtsynkronisering.</li>
      <li>Snabbmärken och bokmärken.</li>
      <li>Läs automatisk om dokument.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="tr">
    <p>Zathura, yüksek düzeyde kişiselleştirilebilir ve işlevsel bir dosya görüntüleyicisidir. Minimal ve boşluktan kurtaran bir arayüzünün yanında, klavye etkileşimine dayanan kolay bir kullanım sağlamaktadır. Zathura, fare kullanmadan dosyaların tümüyle görünümüne ve dosyalar arası etkileşime olanak tanımaktadır.</p>
    <p>Zathura, eklentiler yoluyla çeşitli dosya formatlarını desteklemek amacıyla genişletilebilmektedir. Diğer özellikler:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>SyncTeX ileri ve geri senkronizasyon desteği.</li>
      <li>Quickmark ve sık kullanılanlar.</li>
      <li>Otomatik belge yeniden yükleme.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description lang="uk_UA">
    <p>Zathura - це дуже гнучкий та функціональний переглядач документів. Він забезпечує простий та компактний інтерфейс, а також просте використання, яке в основному фокусується на взаємодії з клавіатурою. Zathura дає можливість повністю переглядати та переміщатися по документах без використання миші.</p>
    <p>Zathura може бути розширений для підтримки декількох форматів документів за допомогою плаґінів. Інші можливості включають:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Підтримка Synctex синхронізації вперед та назад .</li>
      <li>Швидкі закладки та закладки.</li>
      <li>Автоматичне перезавантаження документів.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <pkgname>zathura</pkgname>
  <icon width="64" type="cached" height="64">org.pwmt.zathura.png</icon>
  <icon width="128" height="128" type="cached">org.pwmt.zathura.png</icon>
  <id>org.pwmt.zathura</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>Zlib</project_license>
  <name>Zathura</name>
  <name lang="uk_UA">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="tr">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="ta_IN">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="sv">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="ru">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="pt_BR">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="pl">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="no">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="nl">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="lt">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="it">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="id_ID">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="he">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="fr">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="es_CL">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="es">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="eo">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="el">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="de">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="cs">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="ca">Zathura</name>
  <name lang="ar">Zathura</name>
  <summary>A minimalistic document viewer</summary>
  <summary lang="uk_UA">Простий переглядач документів</summary>
  <summary lang="tr">Minimalist bir belge görüntüleyicisi</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">En minimalistisk dokumentvisare</summary>
  <summary lang="ru">Минималистичный просмотрщик документов</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">Um visualizador de documentos minimalista</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">Minimalistyczna przeglądarka dokumentów</summary>
  <summary lang="no">En minimalistisk dokumentleser</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">Een minimalistisch documentweergaveprogramma</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">Paprasta dokumentų skaitytuvė</summary>
  <summary lang="it">Un visualizzatore di documenti minimalista</summary>
  <summary lang="id_ID">Pembaca dokumen minimalis</summary>
  <summary lang="he">מציג מסמכים מינימליסטי</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">Un visionneur de document minimaliste</summary>
  <summary lang="es_CL">Un visor de documentos minimalista</summary>
  <summary lang="es">Un visor de documentos minimalista</summary>
  <summary lang="eo">Malpeza dokumento spektanto</summary>
  <summary lang="el">Ένας ελαφρύς προβολέας κειμένων</summary>
  <summary lang="de">Ein minimalistischer Dokumenten-Betrachter</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">Jednoduchý prohlížeč dokumentů</summary>
  <summary lang="ca">Un visualitzador de documents minimalista</summary>
  <summary lang="ar">عارض وثائق الحد الأدنى</summary>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.pwmt.zathura.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://pwmt.org/projects/zathura</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.pwmt.org/project/zathura</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://pwmt.org/static/img/zathura-cover.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://pwmt.org/static/img/zathura-completion.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://pwmt.org/static/img/zathura-follow.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://pwmt.org/static/img/zathura-bookmarks.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <update_contact>zathura@lists.pwmt.org</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">zathura</translation>
  <provides>
    <binary>zathura</binary>
  </provides>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0" />
</component>